<?xml version="1.0"?>
<?xml-stylesheet href="/storage/feed-stylesheet.xsl" type="text/xsl"?>

<rss xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
 <channel>
  <title><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></title>
  <link>https://dropwave.io</link>
  <description><![CDATA[FIGHT LAUGH FEAST PRESENTS SHOWS PROCLAIMING THE LORDSHIP OF CHRIST OVER ALL OF LIFE.
]]></description>
  <language>en</language>
  <managingEditor><![CDATA[fightlaughfeast@gmail.com (FLF, LLC)]]></managingEditor>
  <webMaster><![CDATA[support@dropwave.io (DropWave Support)]]></webMaster>
  <pubDate>Sat, 05 Aug 2023 13:25:44 +0000</pubDate>
  <lastBuildDate>Sat, 05 Aug 2023 13:25:44 +0000</lastBuildDate>
  <image>
   <url>https://is4-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Podcasts113/v4/58/56/52/5856525c-2973-cf29-3db9-21faa8595391/mza_1144696925612154085.png/1200x1200bb.jpg</url>
   <link>https://dropwave.io</link>
   <title><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></title>
  </image>
  <itunes:author><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></itunes:author>
  <itunes:image href="https://is4-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Podcasts113/v4/58/56/52/5856525c-2973-cf29-3db9-21faa8595391/mza_1144696925612154085.png/1200x1200bb.jpg"/>
  <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
  <itunes:owner>
   <itunes:name><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></itunes:name>
   <itunes:email>fightlaughfeast@gmail.com</itunes:email>
  </itunes:owner>
  <itunes:category text="News"/>
  <item>
   <title><![CDATA[Psalm 33:4-19 [Up and Ready]]]></title>
   <link/>
   <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
   <author><![CDATA[Mark Dewey]]></author>
   <enclosure url="https://app.dropwave.io/episode/a8b9a529-ea59-4e7f-8e70-2d63d64d4c34/psalm-334-19.mp3" length="342" type="audio/mp3"/>
   <guid isPermaLink="false"><![CDATA[a8b9a529-ea59-4e7f-8e70-2d63d64d4c34]]></guid>
   <pubDate>Sat, 05 Aug 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
   <source url=""><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></source>
   <itunes:author><![CDATA[Mark Dewey]]></itunes:author>
   <itunes:image href="https://assets-cdn2.dropwave.io/60c9e557-5882-401d-abb8-06de47904be4/cover-art/zZ8CYlYBUAUu8KNyZzjE092h2WlBblW8upM7tmFg.png"/>
   <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
   <itunes:duration>342</itunes:duration>
   <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title><![CDATA[19 yr Army Veteran Resigned over Health Mandate (Brad Miller) [CrossPolitic Show]]]></title>
   <link/>
   <description><![CDATA[<p class="p1"><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">19 yr Army Veteran Resigned over Health Mandate (Brad Miller)</span></p>
<p class="p2">&nbsp;</p>
<p class="p1"><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">More from Brad Miller (His Substack)</span></p>
<p class="p3"><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://bradmiller10.substack.com/">https://bradmiller10.substack.com/</a><span class="s1"><span class="Apple-converted-space">&nbsp;</span></span></span></p>
<p class="p2">&nbsp;</p>
<p class="p1"><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Sign up for the FLF Conference at the Ark Encounter! (Oct 11-14)</span></p>
<p class="p3"><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><span class="s2"><a href="https://flfnetwork.com/the-politics-of-six-days-creation-conference/">https://flfnetwork.com/the-politics-of-six-days-creation-conference/</a></span><span class="s1">&nbsp;</span></span></p>
<p class="p2">&nbsp;</p>
<p class="p1"><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Support Us &amp; Sign up for a FLF Pub Membership!<span class="Apple-converted-space">&nbsp;</span></span></p>
<p class="p3"><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><span class="s2"><a href="https://flfnetwork.com/product/fightlaughfestclub/?attribute_member-tier=silver-monthly">https://flfnetwork.com/product/fightlaughfestclub/?attribute_member-tier=silver-monthly</a></span><span class="s1"><span class="Apple-converted-space">&nbsp;</span></span></span></p>]]></description>
   <author><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></author>
   <enclosure url="https://app.dropwave.io/episode/5ca96cbf-0e18-4325-8f99-25f850a4312d/19-yr-army-veteran-discharged-over-health-mandate-brad-miller.mp3" length="2193" type="audio/mp3"/>
   <guid isPermaLink="false"><![CDATA[5ca96cbf-0e18-4325-8f99-25f850a4312d]]></guid>
   <pubDate>Sat, 05 Aug 2023 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
   <source url=""><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></source>
   <itunes:author><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></itunes:author>
   <itunes:image href="https://assets-cdn2.dropwave.io/11635dce-94e7-41b8-9261-5c1fc2cc5ebe/cover-art/wvkjcfd3tfj69XopdryYkSF8m1k4KHuikzJF1KzC.jpg"/>
   <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
   <itunes:duration>2193</itunes:duration>
   <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title><![CDATA[Having Two Legs: A Brief Calvinist FAQ [Pastor Toby’s Blog]]]></title>
   <link/>
   <description><![CDATA[<p>In this episode of Having Two Legs, Pastor Toby addresses common questions and concerns associated with Calvinism.</p>
<p>Blog Post: https://tobyjsumpter.com/a-brief-calvinist-faq/</p>]]></description>
   <author><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></author>
   <enclosure url="https://dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/app.dropwave.io/episode/3115660b-e48c-420d-a398-a9d793deff4d/having-two-legs-a-brief-calvinist-faq.mp3" length="528" type="audio/mp3"/>
   <guid isPermaLink="false"><![CDATA[3115660b-e48c-420d-a398-a9d793deff4d]]></guid>
   <pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2023 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
   <source url=""><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></source>
   <itunes:author><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></itunes:author>
   <itunes:image href="https://assets-cdn2.dropwave.io/20dde981-157e-4504-b38f-dd9d7b0e4c50/cover-art/ZdXVos6595FpTNoyp6qYqu16EQyUrG0zPvsBPzMA.png"/>
   <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
   <itunes:duration>528</itunes:duration>
   <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title><![CDATA[Can the U.S. Constitution be a Sufficient Legal Substitute for God? [God, Law, and Liberty]]]></title>
   <link/>
   <description><![CDATA[<p>Having eliminated all the alternatives for grounding an ethical legal system to that grounded in a &ldquo;transcendent and immanent&rdquo; God, law professor Arthur Leff turns us to the U.S. Constitution as a possible substitute. Both David and Leff find trust in an authoritative Constitution misplaced and unworkable. The evidence is found even in the U.S. Supreme Court&rsquo;s decision reversing Roe v. Wade.</p>]]></description>
   <author><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></author>
   <enclosure url="https://app.dropwave.io/episode/75148a6b-3aa8-45d8-aa1c-203db4d4e4db/can-the-us-constitution-be-a-sufficient-legal-substitute-for-god.mp3" length="1207" type="audio/mp3"/>
   <guid isPermaLink="false"><![CDATA[75148a6b-3aa8-45d8-aa1c-203db4d4e4db]]></guid>
   <pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2023 13:24:00 +0000</pubDate>
   <source url=""><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></source>
   <itunes:author><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></itunes:author>
   <itunes:image href="https://assets-cdn2.dropwave.io/467f99a9-2921-459a-b63d-9710f4355795/cover-art/oLYjcGKDrKYiMn2xKTxnv5V0fVm88eIS01y15GGh.jpg"/>
   <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
   <itunes:duration>1207</itunes:duration>
   <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title><![CDATA[Daily News Brief for Friday, August 4th, 2023 [Daily News Brief]]]></title>
   <link/>
   <description><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">This is Garrison Hardie with your CrossPolitic Daily News Brief for Friday, August 4th, 2023.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Isn&rsquo;t it about time to take action on how you're going to give your children and grandchildren a good music education? Moses, David, and all the Saints of the church have worshiped God with musical might, so let&rsquo;s be confidently found doing the same.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Bohnet Music Academy instructs children and adults in how to be musically literate. That&rsquo;s everything you need to know and do as the musician God made you to be. Lessons are available locally in Moscow, ID and online. What&rsquo;s great is that in addition to getting vocal training, you can also study the piano, guitar, violin, cello, drums, or the trumpet.&nbsp;&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Visit Bohnetma.com/crosspolitic for more information on how to equip your family to serve God&rsquo;s musical commands. B-O-H-N-E-T MA.com/crosspolitic</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&nbsp;</span><a href="http://bohnetma.com/crosspolitic"><span style="font-weight: 400;">http://bohnetma.com/crosspolitic</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;">&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://www.dailywire.com/news/pittsburgh-synagogue-shooter-sentenced-to-death-by-jury"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.dailywire.com/news/pittsburgh-synagogue-shooter-sentenced-to-death-by-jury</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Pittsburgh Synagogue Shooter Sentenced To Death By Jury</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">A jury on Wednesday sentenced the man who gunned down 11 people at the Tree of Life Synagogue in Pittsburgh to death, nearly five years after the attack.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The shooter, whom I will not name, was found guilty in June of all 63 counts he was facing, including 11 counts of obstructing the free exercise of religious beliefs resulting in death and 11 counts of hate crimes resulting in death.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The jury&rsquo;s unanimous decision was announced by U.S. District Judge Robert J. Colville, who presided over the trial, which took place in downtown Pittsburgh. The judge will officially sentence the shooter to death later this week.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The victims were from three Jewish congregations who gathered at the Tree of Life synagogue on October 27, 2018. Two other worshipers and five police officers were also wounded by the gunman, who unloaded a Colt AR-15 semi-automatic rifle and three Glock .357 handguns during his attack.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Victims of the shooting were: Joyce Fienberg, Richard Gottfried, Rose Mallinger, Jerry Rabinowitz, Cecil and David Rosenthal, Bernice and Sylvan Simon, Daniel Stein, Melvin Wax, and Irving Younger.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The shooting is considered by authorities to be the deadliest anti-Semitic attack in U.S. history.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Attorneys representing the shooter asked for a life sentence if he pleaded guilty, but prosecutors, with the support of most of the victims&rsquo; families, refused and took the case to trial to pursue the death penalty. The shooter&rsquo;s lawyers also argued that he was impaired by mental illness and a delusional belief system took over his thinking, dictating that he had to kill Jews to stop a genocide of white people, the Associated Press reported.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&ldquo;He turned this place of worship into an exhibit in his criminal trial,&rdquo; U.S. Attorney Eric Olshan said while arguing for jurors to recommend the death penalty, according to the Pittsburgh Gazette.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">A criminal complaint showed that the man told authorities he intentionally targeted the synagogue because he hoped to kill Jewish people. The shooter&rsquo;s defense attorneys acknowledged that he had done the shooting but asked jurors to &ldquo;scrutinize his intent.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">We now go across the pond for this one!</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://thenationalpulse.com/2023/08/02/uk-tories-enforce-diversity-quotas-for-new-members-of-parliament/"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://thenationalpulse.com/2023/08/02/uk-tories-enforce-diversity-quotas-for-new-members-of-parliament/</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>UK Tories Enforce Diversity Quotas for New Members of Parliament.</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The United Kingdom&rsquo;s &lsquo;Conservative&rsquo; Party has implemented new diversity quotas and guidelines for selecting candidates &ndash; would-be Members of Parliament (MPs). The targets include age as well as ethnicity and gender.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Diversity quotas are in place even before candidates are considered as the party&rsquo;s &ldquo;Sifting Committee,&rdquo; which is responsible for sorting through applicants after applying for the position, must have specific characteristics:</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&nbsp;&ldquo;The Sifting Committee must comprise a minimum of one woman and one young person under the age of 30. The additional Association members of the Committee should reflect the different interests of the constituency, i.e. should have a balance of gender, age and ethnicity.&rdquo;&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">After the initial sift, the Selection Committee must &ldquo;recognise their responsibility&rdquo; to ensure that candidates are chosen in a way that &ldquo;displays diversity and variety and which has a due regard to the local profile of the constituency&rdquo; and guarantees a balance of genders.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The selection rules also state that the process must be &ldquo;inclusive and free from discrimination&rdquo; and &ldquo;fully acknowledge and embrace diversity,&rdquo; except when considering female candidates, in which case &ldquo;some degree of positive discrimination is permitted.&rdquo; The rules add that anything considered &ldquo;indirect discrimination&rdquo; is prohibited; meaning, any requirement that could have a &ldquo;disproportionate impact&rdquo; on one group.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&nbsp;President Donald Trump highlighted the Conservative&rsquo;s shift to the &ldquo;far left&rdquo; in an interview with Nigel Farage earlier this year. More recently, the party expelled a mayor for &lsquo;repenting&lsquo; after attending a Pride event.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2023/aug/02/orlando-magic-nba-team-donated-ron-desantis-super-pac"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2023/aug/02/orlando-magic-nba-team-donated-ron-desantis-super-pac</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Orlando Magic donated $50,000 to Ron DeSantis Super Pac</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The Orlando Magic NBA team has donated $50,000 to a Super Pac supporting the presidential bid of Florida&rsquo;s Republican governor, Ron DeSantis.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">According to Federal Election Commission records, the Never Back Down Super Pac received the donation made by the basketball team on 26 June. Further results showed the team making donations to other political causes in past years, with $500 going to Conservative Results in 2016, $2,000 to Maverick Pac USA in 2014 and another $500 to Linda Chapin for Congress in 2000.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">In an initial statement to Popular Information, a Magic spokesperson said: &ldquo;We don&rsquo;t comment publicly on political contributions.&rdquo; However, in a later follow-up statement, a spokesperson clarified the donation, saying that the check was &ldquo;dated/delivered on May 19&rdquo;, five days before DeSantis declared his presidential bid.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&ldquo;This gift was given before Governor DeSantis entered the presidential race. [It] was given as a Florida business in support of a Florida governor for the continued prosperity of central Florida,&rdquo; the spokesperson said.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">According to Never Back Down&rsquo;s website, the Super Pac describes itself as a &ldquo;grassroots movement to elect Governor Ron DeSantis for president in 2024&rdquo;.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The donation has drawn criticism online, particularly given the Magic&rsquo;s claims of supporting &ldquo;diversity, equity and inclusion all year long&rdquo; and DeSantis&rsquo;s culture wars in which he announced plans to block DEI programs in state colleges among other legislation targeting minority and marginalized groups including LGBTQ+ communities.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The Orlando Magic team is under Amway North America, a multi-level marketing firm co-established by Richard DeVos, the late father-in-law of Trump&rsquo;s education secretary Betsy DeVos.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Over the years, the DeVos family has made multiple donations to conservative organizations. In 2006, the Richard and Helen DeVos Foundation made a $540,000 donation to Focus on the Family, a Colorado-based organization that opposes same-sex marriage and abortions, HuffPost reports. In 2008, Richard DeVos donated $100,000 to Florida4Marriage, a group that campaigned to add a state constitutional ban on same-sex marriages.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&ldquo;That&rsquo;s just a sacred issue of respecting marriage,&rdquo; Richard DeVos said in a 2009 interview in reference to his donation.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Following reports of the donation, the National Basketball Players Association, a union representing NBA players, issued a statement on Wednesday, calling the donation &ldquo;alarming&rdquo;.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&ldquo;A political contribution from the Orlando Magic is alarming given recent comments and policies of its beneficiary. NBA governors, players and personnel have the right to express their personal political views, including through donations and statements.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&ldquo;However, if contributions are made on behalf of an entire team, using money earned through the labor of its employees, it is incumbent upon the team governors to consider the diverse values and perspectives of staff and players.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&ldquo;The Magic&rsquo;s donation does not represent player support for the recipient,&rdquo; the union said.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://www.boundingintosports.com/2023/08/shakeups-continue-at-espn-as-nba-analyst-mark-jackson-is-fired-after-10-years-with-the-network/"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.boundingintosports.com/2023/08/shakeups-continue-at-espn-as-nba-analyst-mark-jackson-is-fired-after-10-years-with-the-network/</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Shakeups Continue at ESPN As NBA Analyst Mark Jackson Is Fired After 10 Years With The Network</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Mark Jackson is a New York native who played his college basketball at St. John&rsquo;s before being chosen by the Knicks in the first round of the 1987 draft. He spent two separate stints with the franchise, and his time in the shadows of The City That Never Sleeps had him ready for the big stage when he wanted to transition to television.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">He would go on to a coaching career by taking the helm in Golden State, just before the eventual arrival of Steve Kerr and a slew of NBA titles. Still, he rebounded nicely, and would later famously team with Mike Breen and Van Gundy to form one of the best broadcasting trios in all of sports. That is &ndash; until this week.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">In response, Mark Jackson released a long statement, saying goodbye:</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&ldquo;This morning, unexpectedly, I was informed that my services were no longer needed at ESPN. Although shocked and dismayed with the suddenness of it all, I would like to thank ESPN and all the staff of the NBA ESPN crew for allowing me to be a part of the organization for the past 15+ years. I would also like to thank the NBA fans watching at home and in the arenas throughout the league for all of your support. To the NBA, a heartfelt thank you for allowing a kid to continue to accomplish his dreams.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&ldquo;It has been an honor to sit beside two LEGENDS in the business, who are like brothers to me, Mike Breen and Jeff Van Gundy, and learn so much from them,&rdquo; the former Knicks standout continued. &ldquo;Lisa Salters is a GOAT and like a sister to me and I&rsquo;m so proud of the work she continues to do. To the best producer in the world, and my friend, Tim Corrigan, I give the utmost gratitude and thanks for always inspiring and supporting me. To all of the staff and crew, that may have never been seen on camera&hellip; please know that you were always seen by me and so greatly appreciated.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Jackson then concluded his sign-off from The Worldwide Leader in Sports gracefully, giving praise to God on his way out the door.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&ldquo;Finally, I wish greater measures of success to the new ESPN team. May they continue to elevate this game that has given me a home and a life. I leave ESPN with nothing but gratitude, all the while knowing that my highest praise goes to God! Through it all, He has always sustained me and His grace allows me to know that there are greater blessings ahead. I look forward to what He has in store next.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Jackson&rsquo;s layoff is the latest in a series of cost-cutting moves by the network, which has experienced a sharp drop in popularity and profitability in recent years.</span></p>]]></description>
   <author><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></author>
   <enclosure url="https://app.dropwave.io/episode/e4d136ab-583f-4fb5-b6be-f7908f507383/daily-news-brief-for-friday-august-4th-2023.mp3" length="664" type="audio/mp3"/>
   <guid isPermaLink="false"><![CDATA[e4d136ab-583f-4fb5-b6be-f7908f507383]]></guid>
   <pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
   <source url=""><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></source>
   <itunes:author><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></itunes:author>
   <itunes:image href="https://assets-cdn2.dropwave.io/2ab40ac0-e99d-4f25-a6d2-541d2c9b290a/cover-art/mUK8zsnHkCK3vep7E1W6UgYb9dTnLenASAMEFha3.jpg"/>
   <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
   <itunes:duration>664</itunes:duration>
   <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title><![CDATA[A Real Conference For Real Men! [The Rebel Podcast]]]></title>
   <link/>
   <description><![CDATA[<p>Yeah, just another conference? &nbsp;Pastors Nate &amp; Chris are here to convince you that this men's conference is a REAL conference for REAL men. &nbsp;What does that mean? &nbsp;Have a listen and find out!</p>]]></description>
   <author><![CDATA[Pastors Nate & Chris]]></author>
   <enclosure url="https://app.dropwave.io/episode/cc2f7e9d-68da-45d4-992e-fa8efc426342/a-real-conference-for-real-men.mp3" length="1106" type="audio/mp3"/>
   <guid isPermaLink="false"><![CDATA[cc2f7e9d-68da-45d4-992e-fa8efc426342]]></guid>
   <pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
   <source url=""><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></source>
   <itunes:author><![CDATA[Pastors Nate & Chris]]></itunes:author>
   <itunes:image href="https://assets-cdn2.dropwave.io/2f5403ee-3fd5-417e-8372-cb8279ee1f07/cover-art/w0UbRn2uM5yV9BWgVTAhrwlpOzSNrn99Jo5z83hu.png"/>
   <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
   <itunes:duration>1106</itunes:duration>
   <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title><![CDATA[Proverbs 20:3 [Up and Ready]]]></title>
   <link/>
   <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
   <author><![CDATA[Mark Dewey]]></author>
   <enclosure url="https://app.dropwave.io/episode/054283eb-352d-459c-ab5a-9c77a2a7f14b/proverbs-203.mp3" length="281" type="audio/mp3"/>
   <guid isPermaLink="false"><![CDATA[054283eb-352d-459c-ab5a-9c77a2a7f14b]]></guid>
   <pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
   <source url=""><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></source>
   <itunes:author><![CDATA[Mark Dewey]]></itunes:author>
   <itunes:image href="https://assets-cdn2.dropwave.io/60c9e557-5882-401d-abb8-06de47904be4/cover-art/zZ8CYlYBUAUu8KNyZzjE092h2WlBblW8upM7tmFg.png"/>
   <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
   <itunes:duration>281</itunes:duration>
   <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title><![CDATA[The Hit Animator that was MeToo’d + His Story of Repentance (Chris Savino) [CrossPolitic Show]]]></title>
   <link/>
   <description><![CDATA[<p class="p1"><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The Hit Animator that was MeToo&rsquo;d + His Story of Repentance (Chris Savino)</span></p>
<p class="p2">&nbsp;</p>
<p class="p1"><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Chris Savino joins CrossPolitic to discuss his rise to a hit TV animator, his fall during the MeToo Movement, and his redemption in finding Christ</span></p>
<p class="p2">&nbsp;</p>
<p class="p1"><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Sign up for the FLF Conference at the Ark Encounter! (Oct 11-14)</span></p>
<p class="p3"><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><span class="s1"><a href="https://flfnetwork.com/the-politics-of-six-days-creation-conference/">https://flfnetwork.com/the-politics-of-six-days-creation-conference/</a></span><span class="s2">&nbsp;</span></span></p>
<p class="p2">&nbsp;</p>
<p class="p1"><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Support Us &amp; Sign up for a FLF Pub Membership!<span class="Apple-converted-space">&nbsp;</span></span></p>
<p class="p3"><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><span class="s1"><a href="https://flfnetwork.com/product/fightlaughfestclub/?attribute_member-tier=silver-monthly">https://flfnetwork.com/product/fightlaughfestclub/?attribute_member-tier=silver-monthly</a></span><span class="s2"><span class="Apple-converted-space">&nbsp;</span></span></span></p>]]></description>
   <author><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></author>
   <enclosure url="https://app.dropwave.io/episode/a57921c6-f37b-447b-943c-1575931ddbd0/the-hit-animator-that-was-metood-his-story-of-repentance-chris-savino.mp3" length="2589" type="audio/mp3"/>
   <guid isPermaLink="false"><![CDATA[a57921c6-f37b-447b-943c-1575931ddbd0]]></guid>
   <pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2023 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
   <source url=""><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></source>
   <itunes:author><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></itunes:author>
   <itunes:image href="https://assets-cdn2.dropwave.io/11635dce-94e7-41b8-9261-5c1fc2cc5ebe/cover-art/wvkjcfd3tfj69XopdryYkSF8m1k4KHuikzJF1KzC.jpg"/>
   <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
   <itunes:duration>2589</itunes:duration>
   <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title><![CDATA[CORRUPT Canadian Leaders and Their Rotten Fruit [Liberty Dispatch]]]></title>
   <link/>
   <description><![CDATA[<p class="p1"><strong>Liberty Dispatch</strong> ~ August 03, 2023<br />On this episode, Matty rejoins Andrew on The Dispatch to talk about the sorry state of political leadership across our nation. If we are going to change anything, we, the people, must have better standards, must be better fruit inspectors, and must, ourselves, get active.<br /><br /><strong style="font-family: '-apple-system', BlinkMacSystemFont, 'Segoe UI', Roboto, Oxygen, Ubuntu, Cantarell, 'Open Sans', 'Helvetica Neue', sans-serif;">[Segment 1] -&nbsp; Evil, corrupt, and lawless leaders:<br /></strong>"Alberta Court Strikes Down Hinshaw's Public Health Orders that Violated Charter Freedoms" | <em>Western Standard</em>: <a href="https://www.westernstandard.news/alberta/alberta-court-strikes-down-hinshaws-public-health-orders-that-violated-charter-freedoms/article_d8d58878-307b-11ee-b984-c7de8ca58c6c.html">https://www.westernstandard.news/alberta/alberta-court-strikes-down-hinshaws-public-health-orders-that-violated-charter-freedoms/article_d8d58878-307b-11ee-b984-c7de8ca58c6c.html</a>;<br />"Decision: Ingram v. Alberta Chief Medical Officer of Health" | <em>Justice Centre for Constitutional Freedoms</em> (PDF): <a href="https://www.jccf.ca/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/2023-07-31-DECISION-Ingram-v-Alberta-Chief-Medical-Officer-of-Health-FILED-July-31-20238.pdf">https://www.jccf.ca/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/2023-07-31-DECISION-Ingram-v-Alberta-Chief-Medical-Officer-of-Health-FILED-July-31-20238.pdf</a>;<br />"Saskatoon City Council Spends $612,000 on Equity, Diversity, Inclusion" | <em>Western Standard</em>: <a href="https://www.westernstandard.news/news/saskatoon-city-council-spends-612-000-on-equity-diversity-inclusion/article_dffa64e4-2fe9-11ee-b793-2b1b86b30dce.html">https://www.westernstandard.news/news/saskatoon-city-council-spends-612-000-on-equity-diversity-inclusion/article_dffa64e4-2fe9-11ee-b793-2b1b86b30dce.html</a>;<br />"Freeland Chauffeured Around While Claiming She Has No Car" | <em>Western Standard</em>: <a href="https://www.westernstandard.news/news/freeland-chauffeured-around-while-claiming-she-has-no-car/article_db3a1e76-2f9a-11ee-b900-f3c338d5ae87.html">https://www.westernstandard.news/news/freeland-chauffeured-around-while-claiming-she-has-no-car/article_db3a1e76-2f9a-11ee-b900-f3c338d5ae87.html</a>;<br />"New Heritage Minister: Big Tech" | <em>TNC News</em>: <a href="https://tnc.news/2023/07/29/new-heritage-minister-big-tech">https://tnc.news/2023/07/29/new-heritage-minister-big-tech</a>;<br />"Trudeau Drops Unpopular COVID-Era Ministers from His Cabinet in Massive Shakeup" | <em>LifeSiteNews</em>: <a href="https://www.lifesitenews.com/news/trudeau-drops-unpopular-covid-era-ministers-from-his-cabinet-in-massive-shakeup">https://www.lifesitenews.com/news/trudeau-drops-unpopular-covid-era-ministers-from-his-cabinet-in-massive-shakeup</a>;<br /><br /><strong>[Segment 2] -&nbsp; Justin Trudeau and wife announce separation:</strong><br />"Breaking: Trudeau Announces Divorce, Will Not Resign Amid Personal Crisis" | <em>The Counter Signal</em>: <a href="https://thecountersignal.com/breaking-trudeau-announces-divorce-will-not-resign-amid-personal-crisis">https://thecountersignal.com/breaking-trudeau-announces-divorce-will-not-resign-amid-personal-crisis</a>;<strong><br /></strong>"Divorce: Justin Trudeau, Sophie Trudeau, Pierre Trudeau, Margaret Trudeau" | <em>National Post</em>: <a href="https://nationalpost.com/news/canada/divorce-justin-trudeau-sophie-trudeau-pierre-trudeau-margaret-trudeau">https://nationalpost.com/news/canada/divorce-justin-trudeau-sophie-trudeau-pierre-trudeau-margaret-trudeau</a><strong>;<br /><br />[Segment 3] -&nbsp; Mailbag Questions:<br /></strong>Have a Question? Want to hear us answer it? Send us a mailbag message @ <a href="mailto:mailbag@libertycoalitioncanada.com">mailbag@libertycoalitioncanada.com</a>;<br /><br /><strong>SUPPORT OUR LEGAL ADVOCACY - Help us defend Canadians' God-given rights and liberties: </strong><a href="https://libertycoalitioncanada.com/donate/">https://libertycoalitioncanada.com/donate/</a>; <a href="https://libertycoalitioncanada.com/liberty-defense-fund/our-legal-strategy/;">https://libertycoalitioncanada.com/liberty-defense-fund/our-legal-strategy/;</a><br /><strong><br /></strong><strong>SHOW SPONSORS:<br /></strong><strong>Join&nbsp;<em>Red Balloon&nbsp;</em>Today!:</strong> <a href="https://www.redballoon.work/lcc;">https://www.redballoon.work/lcc;</a>&nbsp;<br /><strong>Invest with Rocklinc:</strong> <a href="mailto:info@rocklinc.com">info@rocklinc.com</a>&nbsp;or call them at 905-631-546;&nbsp;<br /><strong>Diversify Your Money with Bull Bitcoin:&nbsp;</strong><a href="https://mission.bullbitcoin.com/lcc">https://mission.bullbitcoin.com/lcc</a>;<br /><strong>BarterPay: </strong><a href="https://barterpay.ca/">https://barterpay.ca/</a>;&nbsp; <strong>Barter It: </strong><a href="https://vip.barterit.ca/launch;">https://vip.barterit.ca/launch; </a><strong><br />Carpe Fide - "Seize the Faith": Store: </strong><a href="https://carpe-fide.myshopify.com/">https://carpe-fide.myshopify.com</a><a href="https://carpe-fide.myshopify.com/">/</a>, use Promo Code LCC10 for 10% off (US Store Only), or shop Canadian @ <a href="https://canadacarpefide.myshopify.com/">https://canadacarpefide.myshopify.com/</a> | <strong>Podcast: </strong><a href="https://www.carpefide.com/episodes">https://www.carpefide.com/episodes</a>;<br /><br /><strong>Sick of Mainstream Media Lies? Help Support Independent Media! DONATE TO LCC TODAY!:&nbsp;</strong><strong><a href="https://libertycoalitioncanada.com/donate/">https://libertycoalitioncanada.com/donate/</a>&nbsp;</strong><strong>&nbsp;<br /><br /></strong></p>
<p class="p1">Please Support us in bringing you honest, truthful reporting and analysis from a Christian perspective.<br /><br /><strong>SUBSCRIBE TO OUR SHOWS/CHANNELS:<br /></strong>LIBERTY DISPATCH PODCAST: <a href="https://libertydispatch.podbean.com">https://libertydispatch.podbean.com</a>; <a href="https://rumble.com/c/c-1687093">https://rumble.com/LDshow</a>;&nbsp;<br />OPEN MIKE WITH MICHAEL THIESSEN: <a href="https://openmikewithmichaelthiessen.podbean.com">https://openmikewithmichaelthiessen.podbean.com</a>; <a href="https://rumble.com/c/c-1412501">https://rumble.com/openmike</a>;<br />THE OTHER CLUB: <a href="https://rumble.com/c/c-2541984">https://rumble.com/c/c-2541984</a>;&nbsp;<br />THE LIBERTY LOUNGE WITH TIM TYSOE: <a href="https://rumble.com/LLwTT">https://rumble.com/LLwTT</a>;<br /><br /><strong>CONTACT US:</strong><br />Questions/comments about podcasts/news/analysis: <a href="mailto:mailbag@libertycoalitioncanada.com">mailbag@libertycoalitioncanada.com</a>;<br />Questions/comments about donations: <a href="mailto:give@libertycoalitioncanada.com">give@libertycoalitioncanada.com</a>;<br />Questions/comments that are church-related: <a href="mailto:churches@libertycoalitioncanada.com">churches@libertycoalitioncanada.com</a>;<br />General Inquiries: <a href="mailto:info@libertycoalitioncanada.com">info@libertycoalitioncanada.com</a>.&nbsp;</p>
<p class="p1"><strong>STAY UP-TO-DATE ON ALL THINGS LCC:<br /></strong>Gab: <a href="https://gab.com/libertycoalitioncanada">https://gab.com/libertycoalitioncanada</a>&nbsp;</p>
<p class="p2">Telegram: <a href="https://t.me/libertycoalitioncanadanews">https://t.me/libertycoalitioncanadanews</a>&nbsp;</p>
<p class="p2">Instagram: <a href="https://instagram.com/libertycoalitioncanada">https://instagram.com/libertycoalitioncanada</a>&nbsp;</p>
<p class="p2">Facebook: <a href="https://facebook.com/LibertyCoalitionCanada">https://facebook.com/LibertyCoalitionCanada</a>&nbsp;</p>
<p class="p2">Twitter: @LibertyCCanada - <a href="https://twitter.com/LibertyCCanada">https://twitter.com/LibertyCCanada</a>&nbsp;</p>
<p class="p2">Rumble: <a href="https://rumble.com/user/LibertyCoalitionCanada">https://rumble.com/user/LibertyCoalitionCanada</a>&nbsp;</p>
<p class="p2">YouTube: <a href="https://www.youtube.com/@liberty4canada">https://www.youtube.com/@liberty4canada</a> -&nbsp;<strong>WE GOT CANCELLED AGAIN!!!</strong></p>
<p class="p1"><strong>Please LIKE, SUBSCRIBE, RATE &amp; REVIEW and SHARE it with others!</strong></p>]]></description>
   <author><![CDATA[Matthew Hallick, Andrew DeBartolo, SDG Media]]></author>
   <enclosure url="https://app.dropwave.io/episode/f9f11eb0-0653-4d35-91fb-57e7332f2367/corrupt-canadian-leaders-and-their-rotten-fruit.mp3" length="4745" type="audio/mp3"/>
   <guid isPermaLink="false"><![CDATA[f9f11eb0-0653-4d35-91fb-57e7332f2367]]></guid>
   <pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2023 23:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
   <source url=""><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></source>
   <itunes:author><![CDATA[Matthew Hallick, Andrew DeBartolo, SDG Media]]></itunes:author>
   <itunes:image href="https://prod-assets-spc1.nyc3.digitaloceanspaces.com/69893365-4165-4498-b0ac-e9ddf57a000f/cover-art/E86eLfK3NgjrpuXtk9kW9Qv6KcfzQpkJpToltreR.png"/>
   <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
   <itunes:duration>4745</itunes:duration>
   <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title><![CDATA[Gospel Coalition Actually Admits It (Whites Most Bend to Their Will!) [AD on FLF Network]]]></title>
   <link/>
   <description><![CDATA[<p>"Gospel Centered" nonsense</p>]]></description>
   <author><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></author>
   <enclosure url="https://dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/app.dropwave.io/episode/d57ca570-c6c5-48e3-b309-dbeeb4aaa4ec/gospel-coalition-actually-admits-it-whites-most-bend-to-their-will.mp3" length="1835" type="audio/mp3"/>
   <guid isPermaLink="false"><![CDATA[d57ca570-c6c5-48e3-b309-dbeeb4aaa4ec]]></guid>
   <pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2023 20:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
   <source url=""><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></source>
   <itunes:author><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></itunes:author>
   <itunes:image href="https://assets-cdn2.dropwave.io/e985f24f-d823-4e20-b87a-9e2fa86624f5/cover-art/me0OCTvDSY04mcI5sI97SZ3jsUtDXyHr5ExQtpr2.jpg"/>
   <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
   <itunes:duration>1835</itunes:duration>
   <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title><![CDATA[Having Two Legs: The Gilder Argy-Bargy [Pastor Toby’s Blog]]]></title>
   <link/>
   <description><![CDATA[<p>In this episode of Having Two Legs, Pastor Toby Sumpter addresses the hubbub surrounding the republication of George Gilder's book "Men and Marriage." Blog Post: https://tobyjsumpter.com/the-gilder-argy-bargy/</p>]]></description>
   <author><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></author>
   <enclosure url="https://dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/app.dropwave.io/episode/2c099d17-79ec-4717-9fa0-62881a35dd32/having-two-legs-the-gilder-argy-bargy.mp3" length="1080" type="audio/mp3"/>
   <guid isPermaLink="false"><![CDATA[2c099d17-79ec-4717-9fa0-62881a35dd32]]></guid>
   <pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2023 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
   <source url=""><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></source>
   <itunes:author><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></itunes:author>
   <itunes:image href="https://assets-cdn2.dropwave.io/20dde981-157e-4504-b38f-dd9d7b0e4c50/cover-art/ZdXVos6595FpTNoyp6qYqu16EQyUrG0zPvsBPzMA.png"/>
   <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
   <itunes:duration>1080</itunes:duration>
   <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title><![CDATA[Daily News Brief for Thursday, August 3rd, 2023 [Daily News Brief]]]></title>
   <link/>
   <description><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">This is Garrison Hardie with your CrossPolitic Daily News Brief for Thursday, August 3rd, 2023.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Isn&rsquo;t it about time to take action on how you're going to give your children and grandchildren a good music education? Moses, David, and all the Saints of the church have worshiped God with musical might, so let&rsquo;s be confidently found doing the same.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Bohnet Music Academy instructs children and adults in how to be musically literate. That&rsquo;s everything you need to know and do as the musician God made you to be. Lessons are available locally in Moscow, ID and online. What&rsquo;s great is that in addition to getting vocal training, you can also study the piano, guitar, violin, cello, drums, or the trumpet.&nbsp;&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Visit Bohnetma.com/crosspolitic for more information on how to equip your family to serve God&rsquo;s musical commands. B-O-H-N-E-T MA.com/crosspolitic</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&nbsp;</span><a href="http://bohnetma.com/crosspolitic"><span style="font-weight: 400;">http://bohnetma.com/crosspolitic</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;">&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Listen to this! Some good education news&hellip;&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://www.theblaze.com/news/hs-seniors-con-vs-lib"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.theblaze.com/news/hs-seniors-con-vs-lib</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>High school senior boys nearly twice as likely to be conservative as liberal: Survey</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">A University of Michigan survey found that boys in their senior year of high school are almost two times more likely to identify as conservative than as liberal. However, for twelfth-grade girls, they are even more likely to consider themselves liberal than conservative.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">On the Monitoring the Future survey, which is considered a scholarly endeavor that dates back to the 1970s, according to The Hill, political differences that were once somewhat close have drifted farther apart.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">For high school senior boys, the shares of conservative versus liberal were nearly identical between 2014 and 2016, around 19% for both factions. By 2022, that number had shifted to 23% for conservative, which was actually down three points from 2020.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Since that 2016 marker, boys identifying as liberal in grade twelve have plummeted to 13%.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The 2020-2023 numbers are the highest they've been for conservatives since the early 1990s, although the figures have nearly always hovered around the 20% mark, save for 1998-2002.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Just a reminder that while this is positive, conservatism without Christ is what got us to this point where we are now.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Now an update from Budlight.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://dailycaller.com/2023/07/31/distributors-bud-light-beer-dylan-mulvaney-anheuser-busch/"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://dailycaller.com/2023/07/31/distributors-bud-light-beer-dylan-mulvaney-anheuser-busch/</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Distributors Giving up on Bud Light - No Longer Expect Beer Giant to Recover&nbsp;</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The embarrassment is real for Bud Light.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Several distributors of Anheuser-Busch beer say they have accepted the fact they&rsquo;ve lost money &mdash; and a lot of it &mdash; due to consumers boycotting Bud Light. And not just that, but they&rsquo;ve also given up completely on trying to win back customers who have been negatively affected by the anti-American beer&rsquo;s Dylan Mulvaney campaign, according to the New York Post.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Hiring freezes and layoffs have been going on for four months, while some beer truck drivers have been slammed with hecklers and other harassment while Bud Light&rsquo;s sales have tanked over 25%. As a result, wholesalers of Anheuser-Busch have resigned to the large number of customers they&rsquo;ve lost permanently, and in response, they need to focus on a new set of beer drinkers.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&ldquo;Consumers have made a choice,&rdquo; an unidentified executive from a Texas-based beer distributor told the New York Post. &ldquo;They have left [Bud Light] and that&rsquo;s how it&rsquo;s going to be. I don&rsquo;t envision a big percentage of them coming back.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Other Anheuser-Busch branded beers such as Budweiser, Busch Light and Michelob Ultra have also been tanking in sales since Bud Light decided to disastrously partner with Mulvaney.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The executive went on to say that customers have most likely found out that Bud Light competitors including Miller Lite and Coors Light &ldquo;are a very similar product.&rdquo; Reigning victorious in the beer war all comes down to &ldquo;whoever is best at marketing,&rdquo; the executive told The Post.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://www.theepochtimes.com/world/meta-starts-blocking-canadian-news-content-5437258?utm_source=partner&amp;utm_campaign=BonginoReport"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.theepochtimes.com/world/meta-starts-blocking-canadian-news-content-5437258?utm_source=partner&amp;utm_campaign=BonginoReport</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Meta Starts Blocking Canadian News Content</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Meta has announced it has started blocking news content for Canadian users on its platforms, following months of threats to strike back against the Online News Act, which mandates that major tech companies pay Canadian media outlets for news content linked on their platforms.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Starting Aug. 1, Meta begins the process of ending news availability in Canada, the company said in a statement. Over the next few weeks, all users accessing Facebook and Instagram in Canada will no longer be able to view news links and content posted by Canadian news publishers and broadcasters.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Meta said the news outlets to be affected will be identified based on legislative definitions and guidance from the Online News Act, also known as Bill C-18. The bill received royal assent on June 22.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Tech giant Google also said it would retaliate against the the new law. The company announced on June 29 it would remove links to Canadian news from its Search, News, and Discover products, while users in Canada will no longer be able to operate the Google News Showcase.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">After being appointed the new heritage minister, Pascale St-Onge said her door is "always open" to negotiate with the tech companies, but that her government would not back down. Prime Minister Justin Trudeau has called the issue a "dispute over democracy."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">On July 10, Heritage Canada said it would propose regulations to implement the act, which would include establishing a financial threshold for the contributions of tech companies.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The Epoch Times reached out to Heritage Canada for comment but didn't immediately hear back.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Meta says the new legislation is based on an "incorrect premise," that the company gains unfair benefits from news content shared on its platforms. The company also emphasized that the primary usage of its platforms doesn't revolve around news consumption, arguing instead that news outlets voluntarily share content on Facebook and Instagram to expand their audiences and bolster their financial standing.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">"The Online News Act is fundamentally flawed legislation that ignores the realities of how our platforms work, the preferences of the people who use them, and the value we provide news publishers," Meta said. "As the Minister of Canadian Heritage has said, how we choose to comply with the legislation is a business decision we must make, and we have made our choice."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The company assured users that despite the changes regarding news content availability in Canada, their products and services would remain unaffected. Users will continue to have the ability to connect with friends and family, grow their businesses, and support their local communities as before, Meta says.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Speaking of Canada&hellip;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://www.foxnews.com/world/canadian-prime-minister-justin-trudeau-wife-18-years-announce-separation"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.foxnews.com/world/canadian-prime-minister-justin-trudeau-wife-18-years-announce-separation</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Canadian Prime Minister Justin Trudeau, wife of 18 years announce separation</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Canadian Prime Minister Justin Trudeau on Wednesday announced that he and his wife Sophie are separating after 18 years of marriage.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Trudeau made the announcement in an Instagram post.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">"Sophie and I would like to share the fact that after many meaningful and difficult conversations, we have made the decision to separate," Trudeau wrote.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Sophie Gr&eacute;goire, a former television reporter in Quebec, married Trudeau in 2005. They have three children together.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">In an interview with Maclean's magazine in 2005, Trudeau shared that he and Gr&eacute;goire-Trudeau met as adults two years prior, when they co-hosted the Mercedes-Benz Grand Prix ball. Before, Gr&eacute;goire had been a childhood friend of Trudeau's youngest brother, Michel &mdash; who died in an avalanche in 1998 at the age of 23 &mdash; and had spent time at the Trudeau family's home.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The couple became engaged in October 2004 and married on May 28, 2005, at a ceremony at Montreal's Sainte-Madeleine Church.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Trudeau has spoken glowingly of his wife in public in the years since. In April, the prime minister posted a pair of selfies with his wife on social media on her birthday.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">"From this, to this, and everything in between, there&rsquo;s no one I&rsquo;d rather have by my side," he wrote.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">He also praised her on Mother's Day in May, calling Sophie and his mother "two of the strongest, bravest, and greatest people we know."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The prime minister's office said in a statement that Trudeau, 51, and Sophie, 48, have signed a legal agreement making their separation official.</span></p>
<p><a href="https://www.newsmax.com/world/globaltalk/russia-ukraine-war/2023/08/01/id/1129190/"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.newsmax.com/world/globaltalk/russia-ukraine-war/2023/08/01/id/1129190/</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Russia Accuses Ukraine of Moscow Drone Attack</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Russian authorities accused Kyiv early Tuesday of yet another attack on Moscow and its surroundings with drones, one of which hit the same building in the capital that was damaged by a drone just days ago in a similar attack.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Russian officials have claimed that the intensified attacks on the capital region reflect failures in Ukraine's counteroffensive, while Ukrainian President Volodymyr Zelenskyy said over the weekend that "the war is gradually coming back to Russian territory," but stopped short of taking responsibility for the attacks.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The repeated drone strikes underscore Moscow's vulnerability as Russia's war in Ukraine drags into its 18th month.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The Russian military also said that Ukrainian forces tried to attack two of its warships in the Black Sea overnight, using maritime drones. Three drones targeted two patrol vessels, Sergei Kotov and Vasily Bykov, 340 kilometers (210 miles) southwest of the Russian-controlled city of Sevastopol on the Crimean Peninsula, the Defense Ministry reported. All three drones were destroyed, the report said.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://www.outkick.com/los-angeles-dodgers-host-faith-night-after-sisters-of-perpetual-indulgence-disaster-chris-pratt-clayton-kershaw-attend/"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.outkick.com/los-angeles-dodgers-host-faith-night-after-sisters-of-perpetual-indulgence-disaster-chris-pratt-clayton-kershaw-attend/</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>LOS ANGELES DODGERS HOST FAITH NIGHT AFTER &lsquo;SISTERS OF PERPETUAL INDULGENCE&rsquo; DISASTER; CHRIS PRATT, CLAYTON KERSHAW ATTEND</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">On Sunday, the L.A. Dodgers hosted their first &ldquo;Christian Faith and Family Day&rdquo; at Chavez Ravine since 2019 and nearly two months since LA honored &ldquo;Sisters of Perpetual Indulgence,&rdquo; an LGBT group whose past digs at religion drew criticism.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Following a loss to the Cincinnati Reds, hundreds of Dodgers fans remained seated to partake in the team&rsquo;s &ldquo;Christian Family and Faith&rdquo; event.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Sunday&rsquo;s postgame festivities included testimonies &mdash; emphasizing the importance of faith in God &mdash; from Dodgers ace Clayton Kershaw, third baseman Max Muncy, utility player Chris Taylor and movie star Chris Pratt.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Pratt was in charge of throwing Sunday&rsquo;s ceremonial first pitch.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Dodgers skipper Dave Roberts also made an appearance. Roberts, like much of the Dodgers personnel in attendance for the event, identifies as Christian.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&ldquo;My relationship w/ Christ is the most important thing in my life,&rdquo; Roberts previously shared, when discussing the impact of faith on his life.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Kershaw drew the most attention from the media once the event was announced.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The Dodgers pitcher objected to the celebration of the &ldquo;Sisters&rdquo; when the Pride Night event was first publicized in May.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Clayton Kershaw&rsquo;s critics saw the revival of &ldquo;Christian Faith and Family Night&rdquo; &mdash; originally canceled due to COVID in 2020 &mdash; as a countermeasure to the Pride Night event featuring the &ldquo;Sisters.&rdquo; The ace called it coincidental timing.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">OutKick&rsquo;s Ian Miller attended the event on June 16 and noted that the Dodgers seemingly buried noise around it as 2,000 or so Dodgers fans showed up to protest.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">While June&rsquo;s event was met with backlash due to the &ldquo;Sister&rsquo;s&rdquo; mockery of the Christian and Catholic faith, Sunday&rsquo;s event was met with delight.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The LA team has long been worshipped by the Latino community of Southern California, so naturally the fanbase has a strong Catholic representation.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">As detailed by Los Angeles Times&rsquo; Helene Elliott, fans in attendance for the event adamantly cheered Dave Roberts for his appearance at the faith-based event.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Elliott called it a &ldquo;very forgiving crowd,&rdquo; considering the team had just lost, 9-0, to Elly De La Cruz and the Cincinnati Reds.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">To a degree, the Dodgers fans&rsquo; adoration after a deflating loss was emblematic of the idea of &ldquo;grace&rdquo;.</span></p>
<p><br style="font-weight: 400;" /><br style="font-weight: 400;" /></p>]]></description>
   <author><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></author>
   <enclosure url="https://app.dropwave.io/episode/e91cf399-1882-44dd-83dd-b20dc198d8b2/daily-news-brief-for-thursday-august-3rd-2023.mp3" length="716" type="audio/mp3"/>
   <guid isPermaLink="false"><![CDATA[e91cf399-1882-44dd-83dd-b20dc198d8b2]]></guid>
   <pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
   <source url=""><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></source>
   <itunes:author><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></itunes:author>
   <itunes:image href="https://assets-cdn2.dropwave.io/2ab40ac0-e99d-4f25-a6d2-541d2c9b290a/cover-art/mUK8zsnHkCK3vep7E1W6UgYb9dTnLenASAMEFha3.jpg"/>
   <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
   <itunes:duration>716</itunes:duration>
   <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title><![CDATA[Judges 21:25 [Up and Ready]]]></title>
   <link/>
   <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
   <author><![CDATA[Mark Dewey]]></author>
   <enclosure url="https://app.dropwave.io/episode/90bb6c77-f781-4f24-ab16-2f6134ff0622/judges-2125.mp3" length="256" type="audio/mp3"/>
   <guid isPermaLink="false"><![CDATA[90bb6c77-f781-4f24-ab16-2f6134ff0622]]></guid>
   <pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
   <source url=""><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></source>
   <itunes:author><![CDATA[Mark Dewey]]></itunes:author>
   <itunes:image href="https://assets-cdn2.dropwave.io/60c9e557-5882-401d-abb8-06de47904be4/cover-art/zZ8CYlYBUAUu8KNyZzjE092h2WlBblW8upM7tmFg.png"/>
   <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
   <itunes:duration>256</itunes:duration>
   <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title><![CDATA[The Over Administered Life [The Pugcast]]]></title>
   <link/>
   <description><![CDATA[<p class="p1">Today the Pugs respond to an article by Matthew B. Crawford--the author of Shop Class as Soulcraft--entitled: What is Vitalism? After distinguishing what Crawford is talking about from the vitalism of earlier thinkers, the Pugs sympathetically reflect on his main argument--namely, that the over-management of life by the professional managerial class infantilizes people and makes them weak and incompetent. His solution is a return to the real world and manual and mental competence. Tune in and see if you agree!</p>
<p class="p2">&nbsp;</p>
<p class="p3"><span class="s1">Read the article on Matthew Crawford&rsquo;s Substack: <a href="https://mcrawford.substack.com/p/what-is-vitalism?r=3mqy0&amp;utm_medium=ios&amp;utm_campaign=post&amp;fbclid=IwAR20QRIS_sScRMtVs-r9LfHcbEnA29RONe3obeHunV6pAOKgw3jMrQdexpg">https://mcrawford.substack.com/p/what-is-vitalism?r=3mqy0&amp;utm_medium=ios&amp;utm_campaign=post&amp;fbclid=IwAR20QRIS_sScRMtVs-r9LfHcbEnA29RONe3obeHunV6pAOKgw3jMrQdexpg</a></span></p>
<p class="p2">&nbsp;</p>
<p class="p3"><span class="s1">Support the Pugcast on Patreon: <a href="https://www.patreon.com/thetheologypugcast?fbclid=IwAR17UHhfzjphO52C_kkZfursA_C784t0ldFix0wyB4fd-YOJpmOQ3dyqGf8">https://www.patreon.com/thetheologypugcast?fbclid=IwAR17UHhfzjphO52C_kkZfursA_C784t0ldFix0wyB4fd-YOJpmOQ3dyqGf8</a></span></p>
<p class="p2">&nbsp;</p>
<p class="p1">Order The Making of Evangelical Spirituality by Jason Cherry: <a href="https://a.co/d/2SyDFwb"><span class="s2">https://a.co/d/2SyDFwb</span></a></p>]]></description>
   <author><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></author>
   <enclosure url="https://app.dropwave.io/episode/4d0a0623-3e77-4ce6-a83d-232b90394d86/the-over-administered-life.mp3" length="3903" type="audio/mp3"/>
   <guid isPermaLink="false"><![CDATA[4d0a0623-3e77-4ce6-a83d-232b90394d86]]></guid>
   <pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2023 08:48:00 +0000</pubDate>
   <source url=""><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></source>
   <itunes:author><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></itunes:author>
   <itunes:image href="https://assets-cdn2.dropwave.io/95888944-bdd8-4d76-b4ae-8875769ac332/cover-art/aiNC1kS3NVFxfOfz2ZHCCrTnthpK8XAqpLYOu323.jpg"/>
   <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
   <itunes:duration>3903</itunes:duration>
   <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title><![CDATA[Tim Foley on the Border Crisis w/ Arizona Border Recon [CrossPolitic Show]]]></title>
   <link/>
   <description><![CDATA[<p class="p1"><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Tim Foley on the Border Crisis w/ Arizona Border Recon<span class="Apple-converted-space">&nbsp;</span></span></p>
<p class="p2">&nbsp;</p>
<p class="p1"><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Watch the Incredible Doc feat. Tim Foley (Cartel Land)</span></p>
<p class="p3"><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="http://cartellandmovie.com/">http://cartellandmovie.com/</a><span class="s1"><span class="Apple-converted-space">&nbsp;</span></span></span></p>
<p class="p2">&nbsp;</p>
<p class="p1"><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">More on what Tim Foley does at the border</span></p>
<p class="p3"><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://www.arizonaborderrecon.org/">https://www.arizonaborderrecon.org/</a><span class="s1"><span class="Apple-converted-space">&nbsp;</span></span></span></p>
<p class="p2">&nbsp;</p>
<p class="p1"><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Sign up for the FLF Conference at the Ark Encounter! (Oct 11-14)</span></p>
<p class="p3"><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><span class="s2"><a href="https://flfnetwork.com/the-politics-of-six-days-creation-conference/">https://flfnetwork.com/the-politics-of-six-days-creation-conference/</a></span><span class="s1">&nbsp;</span></span></p>
<p class="p2">&nbsp;</p>
<p class="p1"><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Support Us &amp; Sign up for a FLF Pub Membership!<span class="Apple-converted-space">&nbsp;</span></span></p>
<p class="p3"><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><span class="s2"><a href="https://flfnetwork.com/product/fightlaughfestclub/?attribute_member-tier=silver-monthly">https://flfnetwork.com/product/fightlaughfestclub/?attribute_member-tier=silver-monthly</a></span><span class="s1"><span class="Apple-converted-space">&nbsp;</span></span></span></p>]]></description>
   <author><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></author>
   <enclosure url="https://app.dropwave.io/episode/d959ffcc-c778-4a97-bdba-45d0cde6755c/tim-foley-on-the-border-crisis-w-arizona-border-recon.mp3" length="2086" type="audio/mp3"/>
   <guid isPermaLink="false"><![CDATA[d959ffcc-c778-4a97-bdba-45d0cde6755c]]></guid>
   <pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2023 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
   <source url=""><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></source>
   <itunes:author><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></itunes:author>
   <itunes:image href="https://assets-cdn2.dropwave.io/11635dce-94e7-41b8-9261-5c1fc2cc5ebe/cover-art/wvkjcfd3tfj69XopdryYkSF8m1k4KHuikzJF1KzC.jpg"/>
   <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
   <itunes:duration>2086</itunes:duration>
   <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title><![CDATA[THE OTHER CLUB...On the RAINBOW MAFIA Funded by the Feds, Faith & Freedom [The Other Club]]]></title>
   <link/>
   <description><![CDATA[<p class="p1"><strong>The Other Club</strong> <em>with Mike and Tim </em>~ August 02, 2023<br />On this episode of <em>The Other Club</em>, hosts Dr. Michael Thiessen and Tim Tysoe look into a new RAINBOW MAFIA's religious front, <em>Rainbow Faith and Freedom</em>, and how they are trying to push radical LGBTQIA+ agenda in the church with government support and funding.&nbsp;<br /><br /><strong>Rainbow Faith and Freedom: </strong><a href="https://rainbowfaithandfreedom.org/">https://rainbowfaithandfreedom.org/</a>;&nbsp;<br /><strong>Bill C-4: </strong><a href="https://www.parl.ca/DocumentViewer/en/44-1/bill/C-4/first-reading">https://www.parl.ca/DocumentViewer/en/44-1/bill/C-4/first-reading</a>;</p>
<p class="p1"><strong>JOIN PASTORS, CHURCHES, AND CHRISTIAN COMMUNITIES ACROSS CANADA WITH LCC'S NEWEST INITIATIVE, "<em>TRUE READINGS FROM TRUE ROYALTY."&nbsp; <br /></em></strong><strong>Sign up today:&nbsp;</strong><a href="https://libertycoalitioncanada.com/storyhour/">https://libertycoalitioncanada.com/storyhour/</a>&nbsp;<br /><br /><strong>Support Josh's Stand and Help Us Defend His Liberties! Sign Our Petition Here: <a href="https://libertycoalitioncanada.com/i-stand-with-josh-alexander/">https://libertycoalitioncanada.com/i-stand-with-josh-alexander/</a>;<br /><br /></strong><strong>SHOW SPONSORS:<br /></strong><strong>Join&nbsp;<em>Red Balloon&nbsp;</em>Today!:</strong> <a href="https://www.redballoon.work/lcc;">https://www.redballoon.work/lcc;</a>&nbsp;<br /><strong>Invest with Rocklinc:</strong> <a href="mailto:info@rocklinc.com">info@rocklinc.com</a>&nbsp;or call them at 905-631-546;&nbsp;<br /><strong>Diversify Your Money with Bull Bitcoin:&nbsp;</strong><a href="https://mission.bullbitcoin.com/lcc">https://mission.bullbitcoin.com/lcc</a>;<br /><strong>BarterPay: </strong><a href="https://barterpay.ca/">https://barterpay.ca/</a>;&nbsp; <strong>Barter It: </strong><a href="https://vip.barterit.ca/launch;">https://vip.barterit.ca/launch; </a><strong><br />Carpe Fide - "Seize the Faith": Store: </strong><a href="https://carpe-fide.myshopify.com/">https://carpe-fide.myshopify.com</a><a href="https://carpe-fide.myshopify.com/">/</a>, use Promo Code LCC10 for 10% off (US Store Only), or shop Canadian @ <a href="https://canadacarpefide.myshopify.com/">https://canadacarpefide.myshopify.com/</a> | <strong>Podcast: </strong><a href="https://www.carpefide.com/episodes">https://www.carpefide.com/episodes</a>;<br /><br /><strong>Sick of Mainstream Media Lies? Help Support Independent Media! DONATE TO LCC TODAY!:&nbsp;</strong><strong><a href="https://libertycoalitioncanada.com/donate/">https://libertycoalitioncanada.com/donate/</a>&nbsp;</strong><strong> &nbsp;</strong></p>
<p class="p1">Please Support us in bringing you honest, truthful reporting and analysis from a Christian perspective.<br /><br /><strong>SUBSCRIBE TO OUR SHOWS/CHANNELS:<br /></strong>LIBERTY DISPATCH PODCAST: <a href="https://libertydispatch.podbean.com">https://libertydispatch.podbean.com</a>; <a href="https://rumble.com/c/c-1687093">https://rumble.com/LDshow</a>;&nbsp;<br />OPEN MIKE WITH MICHAEL THIESSEN: <a href="https://openmikewithmichaelthiessen.podbean.com">https://openmikewithmichaelthiessen.podbean.com</a>; <a href="https://rumble.com/c/c-1412501">https://rumble.com/openmike</a>;<br />THE OTHER CLUB: <a href="https://rumble.com/c/c-2541984">https://rumble.com/c/c-2541984</a>;&nbsp;<br />THE LIBERTY LOUNGE WITH TIM TYSOE: <a href="https://rumble.com/LLwTT">https://rumble.com/LLwTT</a>;<br /><br /><strong>CONTACT US:</strong><br />Questions/comments about podcasts/news/analysis: <a href="mailto:mailbag@libertycoalitioncanada.com">mailbag@libertycoalitioncanada.com</a>;<br />Questions/comments about donations: <a href="mailto:give@libertycoalitioncanada.com">give@libertycoalitioncanada.com</a>;<br />Questions/comments that are church-related: <a href="mailto:churches@libertycoalitioncanada.com">churches@libertycoalitioncanada.com</a>;<br />General Inquiries: <a href="mailto:info@libertycoalitioncanada.com">info@libertycoalitioncanada.com</a>.&nbsp;<br /><br /></p>
<p class="p1"><strong>STAY UP-TO-DATE ON ALL THINGS LCC:<br /></strong>Gab: <a href="https://gab.com/libertycoalitioncanada">https://gab.com/libertycoalitioncanada</a>&nbsp;</p>
<p class="p2">Telegram: <a href="https://t.me/libertycoalitioncanadanews">https://t.me/libertycoalitioncanadanews</a>&nbsp;</p>
<p class="p2">Instagram: <a href="https://instagram.com/libertycoalitioncanada">https://instagram.com/libertycoalitioncanada</a>&nbsp;</p>
<p class="p2">Facebook: <a href="https://facebook.com/LibertyCoalitionCanada">https://facebook.com/LibertyCoalitionCanada</a>&nbsp;</p>
<p class="p2">Twitter: @LibertyCCanada - <a href="https://twitter.com/LibertyCCanada">https://twitter.com/LibertyCCanada</a>&nbsp;</p>
<p class="p2">Rumble: <a href="https://rumble.com/user/LibertyCoalitionCanada">https://rumble.com/user/LibertyCoalitionCanada</a>&nbsp;</p>
<p class="p2">YouTube: <a href="https://www.youtube.com/@liberty4canada">https://www.youtube.com/@liberty4canada</a> -&nbsp;<strong>WE GOT CANCELLED AGAIN!!!</strong></p>
<p class="p1"><strong>Please LIKE, SUBSCRIBE, RATE &amp; REVIEW and SHARE it with others!</strong></p>]]></description>
   <author><![CDATA[Dr. Michael Thiessen, Tim Tysoe, SDG MEDIA]]></author>
   <enclosure url="https://app.dropwave.io/episode/af37b52c-c001-45b0-9169-e726d9d280b3/the-other-clubon-the-rainbow-mafia-funded-by-the-feds-faith-freedom.mp3" length="3801" type="audio/mp3"/>
   <guid isPermaLink="false"><![CDATA[af37b52c-c001-45b0-9169-e726d9d280b3]]></guid>
   <pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
   <source url=""><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></source>
   <itunes:author><![CDATA[Dr. Michael Thiessen, Tim Tysoe, SDG MEDIA]]></itunes:author>
   <itunes:image href="https://assets-cdn2.dropwave.io/fa60ae5a-cc30-4d09-a355-177a1f38db7f/cover-art/SJO39Qr6B4iH9RwEjgGma927R9ZeuSi8UCuniLIq.png"/>
   <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
   <itunes:duration>3801</itunes:duration>
   <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title><![CDATA[Daily News Brief for Wednesday, August 2nd, 2023 [Daily News Brief]]]></title>
   <link/>
   <description><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">This is Garrison Hardie with your CrossPolitic Daily News Brief for Wednesday, August 2nd, 2023.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Isn&rsquo;t it about time to take action on how you're going to give your children and grandchildren a good music education? Moses, David, and all the Saints of the church have worshiped God with musical might, so let&rsquo;s be confidently found doing the same.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Bohnet Music Academy instructs children and adults in how to be musically literate. That&rsquo;s everything you need to know and do as the musician God made you to be. Lessons are available locally in Moscow, ID and online. What&rsquo;s great is that in addition to getting vocal training, you can also study the piano, guitar, violin, cello, drums, or the trumpet.&nbsp;&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Visit Bohnetma.com/crosspolitic for more information on how to equip your family to serve God&rsquo;s musical commands. B-O-H-N-E-T MA.com/crosspolitic</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&nbsp;</span><a href="http://bohnetma.com/crosspolitic"><span style="font-weight: 400;">http://bohnetma.com/crosspolitic</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;">&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://www.based-politics.com/2023/07/31/were-paying-billions-in-taxes-for-federal-offices-that-are-sitting-mostly-empty/"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.based-politics.com/2023/07/31/were-paying-billions-in-taxes-for-federal-offices-that-are-sitting-mostly-empty/</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>We&rsquo;re paying billions in taxes for federal offices that are sitting mostly empty</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">From Based Politics.com:</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The pandemic changed how people work, with remote work becoming wildly more prominent. And the federal government was no exception. But now, post-pandemic, taxpayers are on the hook for billions to fund federal offices that are sitting mostly empty, a new report reveals.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Earlier this month the Government Accountability Office published a report examining the utilization of current federal workspaces, as John Kartch explains for Americans for Tax Reform, and its results were remarkable.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">As Kartch notes, the report found that all 24 federal agencies&rsquo; headquarters are &ldquo;vastly underutilized&rdquo; with most headquarters under 25% capacity and several below 10% capacity.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">That&rsquo;s right: Many federal offices are 75% or even 90% empty. These include the Department of Agriculture, Department of Education, Department of Transportation, Small Business Administration, Department of Veterans Affairs, and more cabinet-level agencies.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Why does this matter? Well, as Kartch writes, &ldquo;Taxpayers pay for air conditioning, heating, maintenance, and security for agency buildings at a cost of billions per year, while the same agencies lecture Americans about &lsquo;climate&rsquo; and the type of stove you have in your home.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">This isn&rsquo;t cheap. The GAO report notes that &ldquo;The federal government owns 511 million square feet of office space, costing billions annually to operate and maintain.&rdquo; That&rsquo;s money out of our pockets.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://www.breitbart.com/economy/2023/07/30/report-california-loses-nearly-350-million-to-migration-out-of-state/"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.breitbart.com/economy/2023/07/30/report-california-loses-nearly-350-million-to-migration-out-of-state/</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>California Loses Nearly $350 Million to Migration Out-of-State</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The State of California lost nearly $350 million in tax revenues in 2021 due to migration out of the state &mdash; a worrisome figure as the state contemplates a new deficit of $32 billion this year.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The real estate website MyEListing.com reported:</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">California ranks first among states experiencing the worst net negative tax income migration. With a staggering net loss of $343.2 million, the Golden State is witnessing an outflow of high-income earners.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Despite its numerous attractions, from the booming tech industry and world-class universities to beautiful landscapes and cultural richness, California&rsquo;s high personal income tax rates seem discouraging for many high-wealth individuals. This, coupled with the state&rsquo;s high cost of living, will likely fuel a wealth migration out of California.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">These trends affect the state&rsquo;s economy, especially the real estate and job markets. The departure of high-income earners can decrease demand for luxury real estate and potentially affect the commercial real estate sector. It also impacts job creation, as these high-income individuals often play a significant role in business expansion and entrepreneurial activities.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">New York was second, losing $299.6 million; and Illinois was third, with a net loss of $141.7 million.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Gov. Gavin Newsom (D) has focused on attacking conservative states like Florida, but he is losing residents &mdash; and tax revenues to those states. MyEListing.com notes that Florida and Texas led all other states in &ldquo;positive tax migration.&rdquo; Arizona, currently governed by Democrats, was third.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Newsom enjoyed a budget surplus of nearly $100 billion last year, buoyed in part by federal coronavirus funds that were signed into law by President Joe Biden in 2021.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://thepostmillennial.com/private-school-enrollment-jumps-25-percent-in-washington-as-exodus-from-public-schools-continues?utm_campaign=64487"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://thepostmillennial.com/private-school-enrollment-jumps-25-percent-in-washington-as-exodus-from-public-schools-continues?utm_campaign=64487</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Private school enrollment jumps 25 percent in Washington as exodus from public schools continues</strong></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Washington private schools saw a 25 percent jump in enrollment over the last three years and homeschooling saw a 42 percent increase as public school enrollment continued to fall.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">According to the State Board of Education, in 2019-20, there were 65,270 students enrolled in K-12 private schools in the state. By 2022-23, that number had spiked to 81,434 students.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Additionally, the number of students that are homeschooled also increased from 20,844 in 2019-20 to 29,798 in 2022-23.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">According to Liv Finne at the Washington Policy Center, &ldquo;The numbers show that over 110,000 parents in Washington state have decided that enrolling in controversial public schools is not the best option for their children.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">A nationwide data analysis performed by the National Assessment of Education Progress (NAEP), the nation&rsquo;s &ldquo;report card,&rdquo; showed that only 35 percent of Washington's 4th graders are proficient in math with 74 percent testing at a basic level for the 2022-23 school year.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The numbers got worse the older the students got with only 28 percent of 8th graders showing proficiency in math and 64 percent showing only a basic knowledge of the material.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The analysis also revealed that students in the Evergreen State lost over five months (-0.65 grade equivalents) of learning in math, while in Washington's largest district Seattle Public Schools, students were down four and a half months of learning (-0.50 grade equivalent).</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Democrat Governor Jay Inslee, State Superintendent Chris Reykdal, and teachers&rsquo; unions kept public schools shuttered for in-person learning for more than a year in their response to COVID. Public schools did not welcome back students until the fall of 2021 and were regularly closed for &ldquo;outbreaks.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">By comparison, private schools reopened a year earlier in the fall of 2020.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Rather than deal with the learning loss which was already evident just a few months into online learning, in May 2021, Inslee signed SB 5044 to force Critical Race Theory (CRT),&nbsp; including hyper-sexualized gender theory into the classrooms and universities.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Additionally, many schools have begun removing higher-level learning programs including advanced placement courses for more advanced students.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Adding to the many reasons parents are pulling their children is violence in the schools after districts like Seattle and Bellevue banned police officers from campuses.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Washington public schools are getting more desperate for enrollment, as student counts are tied to federal dollars, and have been running ads in various markets trying to get students to return.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Due to the massive loss of students, some districts including Seattle and Bellevue have already announced that some schools will be closed.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Now for my favorite topic&hellip; sports!</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://www.breitbart.com/sports/2023/07/31/report-canadian-non-binary-rugby-player-accused-of-injuring-women-was-named-hardest-hitter-on-mens-team/"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.breitbart.com/sports/2023/07/31/report-canadian-non-binary-rugby-player-accused-of-injuring-women-was-named-hardest-hitter-on-mens-team/</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Canadian &lsquo;Non-Binary&rsquo; Rugby Player Accused of Injuring Women was Named &lsquo;Hardest Hitter&rsquo; on Men&rsquo;s Team</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">A &ldquo;non-binary&rdquo; rugby player accused of injuring women in a match was previously named &ldquo;hardest hitter&rdquo; when serving on the men&rsquo;s team, new evidence shows.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Last June, the &ldquo;non-binary&rdquo; player was removed from a women&rsquo;s rugby match after he injured three competitors. After the identity of the player remained unknown, it has now been revealed. Per Reduxx:</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The identity of the man involved in the incident has now been confirmed as Ash Davis, who previously played in the men&rsquo;s division of the club and had been awarded the &ldquo;hardest hitter&rdquo; designation during the Senior Awards Banquet just last year.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">According to a source within the rugby club, there has been &lsquo;much opposition&rsquo; to Davis&rsquo; participation in the women&rsquo;s category, but club members are concerned about speaking up out of &ldquo;fear of being labeled transphobic.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The source also explained that &lsquo;many people have known Ash for years, making it more sensitive.&rsquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Marshi Smith, the co-founder of the Independent Council on Women&rsquo;s Sports (ICONS), told Reduxx that the rugby club did not care about the safety of the women players.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&nbsp;&ldquo;Young women are being forced to jeopardize their physical safety to satisfy the desires of a man, Ash Davis, in Canadian rugby,&rdquo; Smith said.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Despite opposition within the rugby club, leaders like club President Jane Kirby are willing to risk the health and safety of young female players, prioritizing men&rsquo;s preferences over ethical concerns and the potential for life-threatening injuries or death. This policy of sacrificing girls&rsquo; and women&rsquo;s well-being for men&rsquo;s eligibility preferences is unethical and perilous,&rdquo; Smith added.</span></p>
<p><br style="font-weight: 400;" /><br style="font-weight: 400;" /></p>]]></description>
   <author><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></author>
   <enclosure url="https://app.dropwave.io/episode/97702613-980b-4342-9a3c-8c99a557c30b/daily-news-brief-for-wednesday-august-2nd-2023.mp3" length="564" type="audio/mp3"/>
   <guid isPermaLink="false"><![CDATA[97702613-980b-4342-9a3c-8c99a557c30b]]></guid>
   <pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
   <source url=""><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></source>
   <itunes:author><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></itunes:author>
   <itunes:image href="https://assets-cdn2.dropwave.io/2ab40ac0-e99d-4f25-a6d2-541d2c9b290a/cover-art/mUK8zsnHkCK3vep7E1W6UgYb9dTnLenASAMEFha3.jpg"/>
   <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
   <itunes:duration>564</itunes:duration>
   <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title><![CDATA[Ephesians 2:4a [Up and Ready]]]></title>
   <link/>
   <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
   <author><![CDATA[Mark Dewey]]></author>
   <enclosure url="https://app.dropwave.io/episode/e5a6258b-4362-4d6d-bd2c-6f372af3a94c/ephesians-24a.mp3" length="283" type="audio/mp3"/>
   <guid isPermaLink="false"><![CDATA[e5a6258b-4362-4d6d-bd2c-6f372af3a94c]]></guid>
   <pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
   <source url=""><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></source>
   <itunes:author><![CDATA[Mark Dewey]]></itunes:author>
   <itunes:image href="https://assets-cdn2.dropwave.io/60c9e557-5882-401d-abb8-06de47904be4/cover-art/zZ8CYlYBUAUu8KNyZzjE092h2WlBblW8upM7tmFg.png"/>
   <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
   <itunes:duration>283</itunes:duration>
   <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title><![CDATA[Live Audience Q&A at Worldview Leadership Academy [The Ezra Institute Podcast for Cultural Reformation]]]></title>
   <link/>
   <description><![CDATA[<main class="main-content col-lg-9" role="main">
<article>
<p>In this episode, faculty answer questions from students at the Worldview Leadership Academy. We deal with the charge of Christianity&rsquo;s closed-mindedness, idolatry, apologetics and evangelism, lying to the Nazis, whether you can lose your salvation, and more. Audio quality improves around the 15-minute mark!</p>
<p><a href="https://ezrapress.ca/products/a-time-to-search-discovering-the-meaning-and-purpose-of-life" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Get Joe Boot&rsquo;s classic work of apologetics, A Time to Search, on sale all month at Ezra Press.</a></p>
</article>
</main>
<aside class="sidebar col-lg-3" role="navigation"><nav id="local-nav" class="local-nav"></nav></aside>]]></description>
   <author><![CDATA[Joe Boot, Ryan Eras, Nate Wright, Michael Thiessen]]></author>
   <enclosure url="https://app.dropwave.io/episode/b8112095-6b4d-4ea1-a956-d74284e84a68/live-audience-qa-at-worldview-leadership-academy.mp3" length="3856" type="audio/mp3"/>
   <guid isPermaLink="false"><![CDATA[b8112095-6b4d-4ea1-a956-d74284e84a68]]></guid>
   <pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
   <source url=""><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></source>
   <itunes:author><![CDATA[Joe Boot, Ryan Eras, Nate Wright, Michael Thiessen]]></itunes:author>
   <itunes:image href="https://assets-cdn2.dropwave.io/1c3a97bd-65b0-4aec-bb35-3a1b6eec5d2c/cover-art/4rDIhLUsGj1xuXpLJYNdtwtbungA78glNHA7dOd9.png"/>
   <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
   <itunes:duration>3856</itunes:duration>
   <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title><![CDATA[PASTOR FINED FOR HOLDING OUTDOOR SERVICE!!!: When Ordinary Canadians Push Back Against State Tyranny [Liberty Dispatch]]]></title>
   <link/>
   <description><![CDATA[<p class="p1"><strong>Liberty Dispatch</strong> ~ August 01, 2023<br />On this episode of the Dispatch, Andrew is joined by faithful Canadians who have fought for their rights and freedoms and those of their loved ones in the face of State tyranny.&nbsp;<br /><br /><strong>MUST WATCH &amp; SHARE: </strong>VIDEO OF ALIN'S RUN-IN WITH THE WINDSOR POLICE:<br /><a href="https://www.facebook.com/jesusthelifegiver/videos/741694931060217">https://www.facebook.com/jesusthelifegiver/videos/741694931060217;</a><br /><br /><strong>SUPPORT KIMBERLY's LEGAL BATTLE: </strong><a href="https://www.givesendgo.com/KimberlyNeudorf-Freedom">https://www.givesendgo.com/KimberlyNeudorf-Freedom</a><strong>;&nbsp;</strong><br /><br /><strong>SUPPORT OUR LEGAL ADVOCACY - Help us defend Canadians' God-given rights and liberties: </strong><a href="https://libertycoalitioncanada.com/donate/">https://libertycoalitioncanada.com/donate/</a>; <a href="https://libertycoalitioncanada.com/liberty-defense-fund/our-legal-strategy/;">https://libertycoalitioncanada.com/liberty-defense-fund/our-legal-strategy/;</a><br /><strong><br /></strong><strong>SHOW SPONSORS:<br /></strong><strong>Join&nbsp;<em>Red Balloon&nbsp;</em>Today!:</strong> <a href="https://www.redballoon.work/lcc;">https://www.redballoon.work/lcc;</a>&nbsp;<br /><strong>Invest with Rocklinc:</strong> <a href="mailto:info@rocklinc.com">info@rocklinc.com</a>&nbsp;or call them at 905-631-546;&nbsp;<br /><strong>Diversify Your Money with Bull Bitcoin:&nbsp;</strong><a href="https://mission.bullbitcoin.com/lcc">https://mission.bullbitcoin.com/lcc</a>;<br /><strong>BarterPay: </strong><a href="https://barterpay.ca/">https://barterpay.ca/</a>;&nbsp; <strong>Barter It: </strong><a href="https://vip.barterit.ca/launch;">https://vip.barterit.ca/launch; </a><strong><br />Carpe Fide - "Seize the Faith": Store: </strong><a href="https://carpe-fide.myshopify.com/">https://carpe-fide.myshopify.com</a><a href="https://carpe-fide.myshopify.com/">/</a>, use Promo Code LCC10 for 10% off (US Store Only), or shop Canadian @ <a href="https://canadacarpefide.myshopify.com/">https://canadacarpefide.myshopify.com/</a> | <strong>Podcast: </strong><a href="https://www.carpefide.com/episodes">https://www.carpefide.com/episodes</a>;<br /><br /><strong>Sick of Mainstream Media Lies? Help Support Independent Media! DONATE TO LCC TODAY!:&nbsp;</strong><strong><a href="https://libertycoalitioncanada.com/donate/">https://libertycoalitioncanada.com/donate/</a>&nbsp;</strong><strong>&nbsp;<br /><br /></strong></p>
<p class="p1">Please Support us in bringing you honest, truthful reporting and analysis from a Christian perspective.<br /><br /><strong>SUBSCRIBE TO OUR SHOWS/CHANNELS:<br /></strong>LIBERTY DISPATCH PODCAST: <a href="https://libertydispatch.podbean.com">https://libertydispatch.podbean.com</a>; <a href="https://rumble.com/c/c-1687093">https://rumble.com/LDshow</a>;&nbsp;<br />OPEN MIKE WITH MICHAEL THIESSEN: <a href="https://openmikewithmichaelthiessen.podbean.com">https://openmikewithmichaelthiessen.podbean.com</a>; <a href="https://rumble.com/c/c-1412501">https://rumble.com/openmike</a>;<br />THE OTHER CLUB: <a href="https://rumble.com/c/c-2541984">https://rumble.com/c/c-2541984</a>;&nbsp;<br />THE LIBERTY LOUNGE WITH TIM TYSOE: <a href="https://rumble.com/LLwTT">https://rumble.com/LLwTT</a>;<br /><br /><strong>CONTACT US:</strong><br />Questions/comments about podcasts/news/analysis: <a href="mailto:mailbag@libertycoalitioncanada.com">mailbag@libertycoalitioncanada.com</a>;<br />Questions/comments about donations: <a href="mailto:give@libertycoalitioncanada.com">give@libertycoalitioncanada.com</a>;<br />Questions/comments that are church-related: <a href="mailto:churches@libertycoalitioncanada.com">churches@libertycoalitioncanada.com</a>;<br />General Inquiries: <a href="mailto:info@libertycoalitioncanada.com">info@libertycoalitioncanada.com</a>.&nbsp;</p>
<p class="p1"><strong>STAY UP-TO-DATE ON ALL THINGS LCC:<br /></strong>Gab: <a href="https://gab.com/libertycoalitioncanada">https://gab.com/libertycoalitioncanada</a>&nbsp;</p>
<p class="p2">Telegram: <a href="https://t.me/libertycoalitioncanadanews">https://t.me/libertycoalitioncanadanews</a>&nbsp;</p>
<p class="p2">Instagram: <a href="https://instagram.com/libertycoalitioncanada">https://instagram.com/libertycoalitioncanada</a>&nbsp;</p>
<p class="p2">Facebook: <a href="https://facebook.com/LibertyCoalitionCanada">https://facebook.com/LibertyCoalitionCanada</a>&nbsp;</p>
<p class="p2">Twitter: @LibertyCCanada - <a href="https://twitter.com/LibertyCCanada">https://twitter.com/LibertyCCanada</a>&nbsp;</p>
<p class="p2">Rumble: <a href="https://rumble.com/user/LibertyCoalitionCanada">https://rumble.com/user/LibertyCoalitionCanada</a>&nbsp;</p>
<p class="p2">YouTube: <a href="https://www.youtube.com/@liberty4canada">https://www.youtube.com/@liberty4canada</a> -&nbsp;<strong>WE GOT CANCELLED AGAIN!!!</strong></p>
<p class="p1"><strong>Please LIKE, SUBSCRIBE, RATE &amp; REVIEW and SHARE it with others!</strong></p>]]></description>
   <author><![CDATA[Matthew Hallick, Andrew DeBartolo, SDG Media]]></author>
   <enclosure url="https://app.dropwave.io/episode/8c2a257f-1e06-4a9c-8cce-e2e02e798605/pastor-fined-for-holding-outdoor-service-when-ordinary-canadians-push-back-against-state-tyranny.mp3" length="4670" type="audio/mp3"/>
   <guid isPermaLink="false"><![CDATA[8c2a257f-1e06-4a9c-8cce-e2e02e798605]]></guid>
   <pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
   <source url=""><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></source>
   <itunes:author><![CDATA[Matthew Hallick, Andrew DeBartolo, SDG Media]]></itunes:author>
   <itunes:image href="https://prod-assets-spc1.nyc3.digitaloceanspaces.com/69893365-4165-4498-b0ac-e9ddf57a000f/cover-art/E86eLfK3NgjrpuXtk9kW9Qv6KcfzQpkJpToltreR.png"/>
   <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
   <itunes:duration>4670</itunes:duration>
   <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title><![CDATA[George Gilder on CrossPolitic! Life After Capitalism/Men & Marriage [CrossPolitic Show]]]></title>
   <link/>
   <description><![CDATA[<p class="p1"><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">George Gilder on CrossPolitic! Life After Capitalism/Men &amp; Marriage</span></p>
<p class="p1"><br /><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Purchase George Gilder&rsquo;s Book</span></p>
<p class="p2"><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://dadsareback.com/">https://dadsareback.com/</a><span class="s1"><span class="Apple-converted-space">&nbsp;</span></span></span></p>
<p class="p3">&nbsp;</p>
<p class="p1"><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Sign up for the FLF Conference at the Ark Encounter! (Oct 11-14)</span></p>
<p class="p2"><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><span class="s2"><a href="https://flfnetwork.com/the-politics-of-six-days-creation-conference/">https://flfnetwork.com/the-politics-of-six-days-creation-conference/</a></span><span class="s1">&nbsp;</span></span></p>
<p class="p3">&nbsp;</p>
<p class="p1"><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Support Us &amp; Sign up for a FLF Club Membership!<span class="Apple-converted-space">&nbsp;</span></span></p>
<p class="p2"><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><span class="s2"><a href="https://flfnetwork.com/product/fightlaughfestclub/?attribute_member-tier=silver-monthly">https://flfnetwork.com/product/fightlaughfestclub/?attribute_member-tier=silver-monthly</a></span><span class="s1"><span class="Apple-converted-space">&nbsp;</span></span></span></p>]]></description>
   <author><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></author>
   <enclosure url="https://app.dropwave.io/episode/5687daee-9a84-444c-b5f0-bd8c71f00b22/george-gilder-on-crosspolitic-life-after-capitalismmen-marriage.mp3" length="2295" type="audio/mp3"/>
   <guid isPermaLink="false"><![CDATA[5687daee-9a84-444c-b5f0-bd8c71f00b22]]></guid>
   <pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
   <source url=""><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></source>
   <itunes:author><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></itunes:author>
   <itunes:image href="https://assets-cdn2.dropwave.io/11635dce-94e7-41b8-9261-5c1fc2cc5ebe/cover-art/wvkjcfd3tfj69XopdryYkSF8m1k4KHuikzJF1KzC.jpg"/>
   <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
   <itunes:duration>2295</itunes:duration>
   <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title><![CDATA[Belphoebe, Amoret, and the Gardens of Adonis [Choc Knox Unplugged]]]></title>
   <link/>
   <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
   <author><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></author>
   <enclosure url="https://app.dropwave.io/episode/231c2439-0a39-4499-9ae6-50e504e4b23e/belphoebe-amoret-and-the-gardens-of-adonis.mp3" length="8410" type="audio/mp3"/>
   <guid isPermaLink="false"><![CDATA[231c2439-0a39-4499-9ae6-50e504e4b23e]]></guid>
   <pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
   <source url=""><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></source>
   <itunes:author><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></itunes:author>
   <itunes:image href="https://assets-cdn2.dropwave.io/6123b54f-ab49-406c-9cba-a39f6730fc76/cover-art/ARuuU8PixHGkhNvgtHIHIGGJjBUPNwgZEkuaGqzL.png"/>
   <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
   <itunes:duration>8410</itunes:duration>
   <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title><![CDATA[Franklin [Resistance and Reformation]]]></title>
   <link/>
   <description><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">More from Dr. George Grant</span></p>
<p><a href="https://georgegrant.net/"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://georgegrant.net/</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;">&nbsp;</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&nbsp;</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Adoring God Foundation&nbsp;</span></p>
<p><a href="https://adoringgod.org/"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://adoringgod.org/</span></a></p>
<p><br /><br /></p>]]></description>
   <author><![CDATA[George Grant]]></author>
   <enclosure url="https://app.dropwave.io/episode/39875971-f4b7-4cdc-af8a-db3629a4ee4b/franklin.mp3" length="596" type="audio/mp3"/>
   <guid isPermaLink="false"><![CDATA[39875971-f4b7-4cdc-af8a-db3629a4ee4b]]></guid>
   <pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
   <source url=""><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></source>
   <itunes:author><![CDATA[George Grant]]></itunes:author>
   <itunes:image href="https://assets-cdn2.dropwave.io/261ebdbb-5a5a-4650-ba2c-8c138886911b/cover-art/fEPh0pqkjOi1hWn2VDTvgRSsw3nOsdOFIBOfEGEP.png"/>
   <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
   <itunes:duration>596</itunes:duration>
   <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title><![CDATA[Chris & Jordan On Hollywood, Disney, Netflix & Media [The Rebel Podcast]]]></title>
   <link/>
   <description><![CDATA[<p>In the absence of Pastor Nate, Chris &amp; Jordan take over the show to further discuss The Sound of Freedom movie, more movies, Hollywood secrets, Netflix, Disney and media in general. &nbsp;Should you cancel your Netflix subscription and put your money in Christian media? &nbsp;Hear what Rebels #2 and #3 have to say!</p>]]></description>
   <author><![CDATA[Pastor Chris & Jordan]]></author>
   <enclosure url="https://app.dropwave.io/episode/c5548e1a-eda2-41eb-a630-5b57ebd15db5/chris-jordan-on-hollywood-disney-netflix-media.mp3" length="2635" type="audio/mp3"/>
   <guid isPermaLink="false"><![CDATA[c5548e1a-eda2-41eb-a630-5b57ebd15db5]]></guid>
   <pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
   <source url=""><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></source>
   <itunes:author><![CDATA[Pastor Chris & Jordan]]></itunes:author>
   <itunes:image href="https://assets-cdn2.dropwave.io/2f5403ee-3fd5-417e-8372-cb8279ee1f07/cover-art/w0UbRn2uM5yV9BWgVTAhrwlpOzSNrn99Jo5z83hu.png"/>
   <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
   <itunes:duration>2635</itunes:duration>
   <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title><![CDATA[Psalm 110:3 [Up and Ready]]]></title>
   <link/>
   <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
   <author><![CDATA[Mark Dewey]]></author>
   <enclosure url="https://app.dropwave.io/episode/1681366d-b66c-4cf3-b920-3d6baad0511e/psalm-1103.mp3" length="304" type="audio/mp3"/>
   <guid isPermaLink="false"><![CDATA[1681366d-b66c-4cf3-b920-3d6baad0511e]]></guid>
   <pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
   <source url=""><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></source>
   <itunes:author><![CDATA[Mark Dewey]]></itunes:author>
   <itunes:image href="https://assets-cdn2.dropwave.io/60c9e557-5882-401d-abb8-06de47904be4/cover-art/zZ8CYlYBUAUu8KNyZzjE092h2WlBblW8upM7tmFg.png"/>
   <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
   <itunes:duration>304</itunes:duration>
   <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title><![CDATA[Come to Think About It [In the Bullpen]]]></title>
   <link/>
   <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
   <author><![CDATA[Mark Dewey]]></author>
   <enclosure url="https://app.dropwave.io/episode/5c6c7ae9-7497-4e18-aa3e-eadfff939cdb/come-to-think-about-it.mp3" length="1357" type="audio/mp3"/>
   <guid isPermaLink="false"><![CDATA[5c6c7ae9-7497-4e18-aa3e-eadfff939cdb]]></guid>
   <pubDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2023 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
   <source url=""><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></source>
   <itunes:author><![CDATA[Mark Dewey]]></itunes:author>
   <itunes:image href="https://assets-cdn2.dropwave.io/48817573-c1d0-44c6-8204-930f4c2d3ce5/cover-art/9b92BsnWm2ufHgEHY2ttEsJ9SYr5RF0LGVrFbfmN.png"/>
   <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
   <itunes:duration>1357</itunes:duration>
   <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title><![CDATA[TCND: Vacay with Comics RECAP (Check the Hallway) [The Comedian Next Door]]]></title>
   <link/>
   <description><![CDATA[<p>Welcome to the CAMP GROUD of the Comedian Next Door. We're gathered around a table with our Vacay Friends, talking about our weekend retreat.&nbsp;<br /><br />It wasn't all smooth sailing, Neighbor.&nbsp; We won't give spoilers in this description. But--we've been through some stuff!&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
<p>Tune in as we share our stories...</p>
<p>Contact the Comedian's family by emailing <a href="mailto:nextdoor@johnbranyan.com">nextdoor@johnbranyan.com</a>.&nbsp;</p>
<p>(Note: there was some corrupted audio on the first post. We think it's fixed now.)</p>]]></description>
   <author><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></author>
   <enclosure url="https://app.dropwave.io/episode/145002ec-bea0-4103-9530-7a96171c112c/tcnd-vacay-with-comics-recap-check-the-hallway.mp3" length="2708" type="audio/mp3"/>
   <guid isPermaLink="false"><![CDATA[145002ec-bea0-4103-9530-7a96171c112c]]></guid>
   <pubDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
   <source url=""><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></source>
   <itunes:author><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></itunes:author>
   <itunes:image href="https://assets-cdn2.dropwave.io/66903a54-b4b6-4a52-a303-eb0bd0b792e3/cover-art/obxsSs7zSTuWr3ZFLRWxryhYbCyvdrWYzXEN2soF.png"/>
   <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
   <itunes:duration>2708</itunes:duration>
   <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title><![CDATA[Galatians 6:11-16 [Up and Ready]]]></title>
   <link/>
   <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
   <author><![CDATA[Mark Dewey]]></author>
   <enclosure url="https://app.dropwave.io/episode/af24d157-a4bf-4265-a12e-c5c5c1fccf2a/galatians-611-16.mp3" length="309" type="audio/mp3"/>
   <guid isPermaLink="false"><![CDATA[af24d157-a4bf-4265-a12e-c5c5c1fccf2a]]></guid>
   <pubDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
   <source url=""><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></source>
   <itunes:author><![CDATA[Mark Dewey]]></itunes:author>
   <itunes:image href="https://assets-cdn2.dropwave.io/60c9e557-5882-401d-abb8-06de47904be4/cover-art/zZ8CYlYBUAUu8KNyZzjE092h2WlBblW8upM7tmFg.png"/>
   <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
   <itunes:duration>309</itunes:duration>
   <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title><![CDATA[SPECIAL LEGAL UPDATE: LCC and Josh Alexander Take Legal Action Against School Superintendent [Open Mike with Michael Thiessen]]]></title>
   <link/>
   <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>OPEN MIKE w/Michael Thiessen [LEGAL SPECIAL] ~ </strong>July 29, 2023<br />This week on OPEN MIKE, Dr. Thiessen is joined by LCC chief litigator James S.M. Kitchen to update listeners on why LCC and Josh Alexander are considering taking legal action against Renfrew County District School Board (RCDSB) superintendent Jacqueline Poirier for her extreme discrimination against Josh Alexander for wearing a red "Save Canada" hat to his younger brother's middle-school graduation.<br /><br /><strong>Episode Resources: </strong><em>Josh Alexander v RCDSB: </em><a href="https://libertycoalitioncanada.com/liberty-defense-fund/josh-alexander-v-rccdsb/">https://libertycoalitioncanada.com/liberty-defense-fund/josh-alexander-v-rccdsb/</a>; Video of Josh being kicked out of his brother's graduation: <a href="https://twitter.com/i/status/1674042224487571458">https://twitter.com/i/status/1674042224487571458</a>; "WATCH: Josh Alexander Blocked from Attending Brother's Graduation Over 'Save Canada' Hat" | <em>Western Standard</em>: <a href="https://www.westernstandard.news/news/watch-josh-alexander-blocked-from-attending-brother-s-graduation-over-save-canada-hat/article_aa36476a-16bc-11ee-a44e-b7cafe2d88fa.html" target="_new">https://www.westernstandard.news/news/watch-josh-alexander-blocked-from-attending-brother-s-graduation-over-save-canada-hat/article_aa36476a-16bc-11ee-a44e-b7cafe2d88fa.html</a>;<br /><br /></p>
<p class="p1"><strong>SUPPORT OUR LEGAL ADVOCACY - Help us defend Canadians' God-given rights and liberties: </strong><a href="https://libertycoalitioncanada.com/donate/">https://libertycoalitioncanada.com/donate/</a>; <a href="https://libertycoalitioncanada.com/liberty-defense-fund/our-legal-strategy/;">https://libertycoalitioncanada.com/liberty-defense-fund/our-legal-strategy/;</a><br /><strong><br /></strong><strong>SHOW SPONSORS:<br /></strong><strong>Join&nbsp;<em>Red Balloon&nbsp;</em>Today!:</strong> <a href="https://www.redballoon.work/lcc;">https://www.redballoon.work/lcc;</a>&nbsp;<br /><strong>Invest with Rocklinc:</strong> <a href="mailto:info@rocklinc.com">info@rocklinc.com</a>&nbsp;or call them at 905-631-546;&nbsp;<br /><strong>Diversify Your Money with Bull Bitcoin:&nbsp;</strong><a href="https://mission.bullbitcoin.com/lcc">https://mission.bullbitcoin.com/lcc</a>;<br /><strong>BarterPay: </strong><a href="https://barterpay.ca/">https://barterpay.ca/</a>;&nbsp; <strong>Barter It: </strong><a href="https://vip.barterit.ca/launch;">https://vip.barterit.ca/launch; </a><strong><br />Carpe Fide - "Seize the Faith": Store: </strong><a href="https://carpe-fide.myshopify.com/">https://carpe-fide.myshopify.com</a><a href="https://carpe-fide.myshopify.com/">/</a>, use Promo Code LCC10 for 10% off (US Store Only), or shop Canadian @ <a href="https://canadacarpefide.myshopify.com/">https://canadacarpefide.myshopify.com/</a> | <strong>Podcast: </strong><a href="https://www.carpefide.com/episodes">https://www.carpefide.com/episodes</a>;<br /><br /><strong>Sick of Mainstream Media Lies? Help Support Independent Media! DONATE TO LCC TODAY!:&nbsp;</strong><strong><a href="https://libertycoalitioncanada.com/donate/">https://libertycoalitioncanada.com/donate/</a>&nbsp;</strong><strong>&nbsp;<br /><br /></strong></p>
<p class="p1">Please Support us in bringing you honest, truthful reporting and analysis from a Christian perspective.<br /><br /><strong>SUBSCRIBE TO OUR SHOWS/CHANNELS:<br /></strong>LIBERTY DISPATCH PODCAST: <a href="https://libertydispatch.podbean.com">https://libertydispatch.podbean.com</a>; <a href="https://rumble.com/c/c-1687093">https://rumble.com/LDshow</a>;&nbsp;<br />OPEN MIKE WITH MICHAEL THIESSEN: <a href="https://openmikewithmichaelthiessen.podbean.com">https://openmikewithmichaelthiessen.podbean.com</a>; <a href="https://rumble.com/c/c-1412501">https://rumble.com/openmike</a>;<br />THE OTHER CLUB: <a href="https://rumble.com/c/c-2541984">https://rumble.com/c/c-2541984</a>;&nbsp;<br />THE LIBERTY LOUNGE WITH TIM TYSOE: <a href="https://rumble.com/LLwTT">https://rumble.com/LLwTT</a>;<br /><br /><strong>CONTACT US:</strong><br />Questions/comments about podcasts/news/analysis: <a href="mailto:mailbag@libertycoalitioncanada.com">mailbag@libertycoalitioncanada.com</a>;<br />Questions/comments about donations: <a href="mailto:give@libertycoalitioncanada.com">give@libertycoalitioncanada.com</a>;<br />Questions/comments that are church-related: <a href="mailto:churches@libertycoalitioncanada.com">churches@libertycoalitioncanada.com</a>;<br />General Inquiries: <a href="mailto:info@libertycoalitioncanada.com">info@libertycoalitioncanada.com</a>.&nbsp;</p>
<p class="p1"><strong>STAY UP-TO-DATE ON ALL THINGS LCC:<br /></strong>Gab: <a href="https://gab.com/libertycoalitioncanada">https://gab.com/libertycoalitioncanada</a>&nbsp;</p>
<p class="p2">Telegram: <a href="https://t.me/libertycoalitioncanadanews">https://t.me/libertycoalitioncanadanews</a>&nbsp;</p>
<p class="p2">Instagram: <a href="https://instagram.com/libertycoalitioncanada">https://instagram.com/libertycoalitioncanada</a>&nbsp;</p>
<p class="p2">Facebook: <a href="https://facebook.com/LibertyCoalitionCanada">https://facebook.com/LibertyCoalitionCanada</a>&nbsp;</p>
<p class="p2">Twitter: @LibertyCCanada - <a href="https://twitter.com/LibertyCCanada">https://twitter.com/LibertyCCanada</a>&nbsp;</p>
<p class="p2">Rumble: <a href="https://rumble.com/user/LibertyCoalitionCanada">https://rumble.com/user/LibertyCoalitionCanada</a>&nbsp;</p>
<p class="p2">YouTube: <a href="https://www.youtube.com/@liberty4canada">https://www.youtube.com/@liberty4canada</a> -&nbsp;<strong>WE GOT CANCELLED AGAIN!!!</strong></p>
<p class="p1"><strong>Please LIKE, SUBSCRIBE, RATE &amp; REVIEW and SHARE it with others!</strong></p>]]></description>
   <author><![CDATA[Dr. Michael Thiessen, James S.M. Kitchen, SDG MEDIA]]></author>
   <enclosure url="https://app.dropwave.io/episode/7149df2d-fadc-46e3-a708-1354406ffeb0/special-legal-update-lcc-and-josh-alexander-take-legal-action-against-school-superintendent-1.mp3" length="2587" type="audio/mp3"/>
   <guid isPermaLink="false"><![CDATA[7149df2d-fadc-46e3-a708-1354406ffeb0]]></guid>
   <pubDate>Sat, 29 Jul 2023 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
   <source url=""><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></source>
   <itunes:author><![CDATA[Dr. Michael Thiessen, James S.M. Kitchen, SDG MEDIA]]></itunes:author>
   <itunes:image href="https://assets-cdn2.dropwave.io/a313a937-1864-4720-a5eb-4fe53c91d48d/cover-art/uUheeW63MRtlJ15cfD2JSiW4qu9YifPAUxqcvBE5.jpg"/>
   <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
   <itunes:duration>2587</itunes:duration>
   <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title><![CDATA[Psalm 27:4 [Up and Ready]]]></title>
   <link/>
   <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
   <author><![CDATA[Mark Dewey]]></author>
   <enclosure url="https://app.dropwave.io/episode/74eefec2-cf4a-41b1-9716-ab7fc3b5c888/psalm-274.mp3" length="272" type="audio/mp3"/>
   <guid isPermaLink="false"><![CDATA[74eefec2-cf4a-41b1-9716-ab7fc3b5c888]]></guid>
   <pubDate>Sat, 29 Jul 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
   <source url=""><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></source>
   <itunes:author><![CDATA[Mark Dewey]]></itunes:author>
   <itunes:image href="https://assets-cdn2.dropwave.io/60c9e557-5882-401d-abb8-06de47904be4/cover-art/zZ8CYlYBUAUu8KNyZzjE092h2WlBblW8upM7tmFg.png"/>
   <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
   <itunes:duration>272</itunes:duration>
   <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title><![CDATA[Thrown in Prison for not Snitching: Injustice & 2000 Mules [CrossPolitic Show]]]></title>
   <link/>
   <description><![CDATA[<p class="p1"><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Thrown in Prison for not Snitching: Injustice &amp; 2000 Mules</span></p>
<p class="p2">&nbsp;</p>
<p class="p2">&nbsp;</p>
<p class="p1"><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">More from Gregg &amp; Catherine:</span></p>
<p class="p3"><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://www.onward.social/home?k=7cb2e51c">https://www.onward.social/home?k=7cb2e51c</a><span class="s1"><span class="Apple-converted-space">&nbsp;</span></span></span></p>
<p class="p2">&nbsp;</p>
<p class="p1"><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Sign up for the FLF Conference at the Ark Encounter! (Oct 11-14)</span></p>
<p class="p3"><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><span class="s2"><a href="https://flfnetwork.com/the-politics-of-six-days-creation-conference/">https://flfnetwork.com/the-politics-of-six-days-creation-conference/</a></span><span class="s1">&nbsp;</span></span></p>
<p class="p2">&nbsp;</p>
<p class="p1"><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Support Us &amp; Sign up for a FLF Club Membership!<span class="Apple-converted-space">&nbsp;</span></span></p>
<p class="p3"><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><span class="s2"><a href="https://flfnetwork.com/product/fightlaughfestclub/?attribute_member-tier=silver-monthly">https://flfnetwork.com/product/fightlaughfestclub/?attribute_member-tier=silver-monthly</a></span><span class="s1"><span class="Apple-converted-space">&nbsp;</span></span></span></p>]]></description>
   <author><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></author>
   <enclosure url="https://app.dropwave.io/episode/410c7562-5919-45f8-942b-27886d48b229/thrown-in-prison-for-not-snitching-injustice-2000-mules.mp3" length="2680" type="audio/mp3"/>
   <guid isPermaLink="false"><![CDATA[410c7562-5919-45f8-942b-27886d48b229]]></guid>
   <pubDate>Sat, 29 Jul 2023 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
   <source url=""><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></source>
   <itunes:author><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></itunes:author>
   <itunes:image href="https://assets-cdn2.dropwave.io/11635dce-94e7-41b8-9261-5c1fc2cc5ebe/cover-art/wvkjcfd3tfj69XopdryYkSF8m1k4KHuikzJF1KzC.jpg"/>
   <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
   <itunes:duration>2680</itunes:duration>
   <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title><![CDATA[Why Intelligent and Educated People Reject Reasoned Policy Arguments [God, Law, and Liberty]]]></title>
   <link/>
   <description><![CDATA[<p>Ever wonder why some policy positions or legal arguments are not simply a matter of logic or reason or common senses. For you they are plain as day. For instance, how could any educated person think a biological boy can become a girl? David will explain what changed over the centuries that led educated people to throw out reasoning based on &ldquo;the facts&rdquo; as basis for law and public policy.</p>]]></description>
   <author><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></author>
   <enclosure url="https://app.dropwave.io/episode/0ff34c24-ee82-4a17-9918-bacfaf3c891c/why-intelligent-and-educated-people-reject-reasoned-policy-arguments.mp3" length="2037" type="audio/mp3"/>
   <guid isPermaLink="false"><![CDATA[0ff34c24-ee82-4a17-9918-bacfaf3c891c]]></guid>
   <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2023 17:09:00 +0000</pubDate>
   <source url=""><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></source>
   <itunes:author><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></itunes:author>
   <itunes:image href="https://assets-cdn2.dropwave.io/467f99a9-2921-459a-b63d-9710f4355795/cover-art/NLqARVgbbJ3LxHc0WOL82z8S6GGdiyJpXTYmZlWm.jpg"/>
   <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
   <itunes:duration>2037</itunes:duration>
   <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title><![CDATA[Daily News Brief for Friday, July 28th, 2023 [Daily News Brief]]]></title>
   <link/>
   <description><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">This is Garrison Hardie with your CrossPolitic Daily News Brief for Friday, July 28th, 2023.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>Story Real Estate:</strong></span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Home. It&rsquo;s where you build your legacy. Where traditions are started, seeds are planted, meals are shared, and stories are told. Home is where you prepare to go out into the world. Finding the home that&rsquo;s perfect for your family is a big job.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">&nbsp;</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Story Real Estate is Moscow&rsquo;s top real estate team. They give people real estate advice all over the country. Family homes, investments, land, new construction, or commercial&mdash; they know real estate.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">&nbsp;</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">If you&rsquo;ve thought about a move to Moscow or anywhere in the country, reach out to get connected with a Story Real Estate agent. Wherever you&rsquo;re going, they can help guide you Home. Visit storyrealestate.com.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://www.breitbart.com/europe/2023/07/26/russia-preparing-to-enforce-blockade-on-ukraine-with-warships-says-uk/"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.breitbart.com/europe/2023/07/26/russia-preparing-to-enforce-blockade-on-ukraine-with-warships-says-uk/</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>Russia Preparing to &lsquo;Enforce Blockade on Ukraine&rsquo; With Warships, Says UK</strong></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Russia has redeployed its warships in the Black Sea and there is a &ldquo;realistic possibility&rdquo; that it will deploy a task force to intercept civilian ships heading to and from Ukraine&rsquo;s ports as part of a blockade, a British intelligence digest says.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The Black Sea Grain Initiative collapsing last week, meaning there is no longer a safe corridor for Ukrainian grain exports by sea, has seen a shift in Russian military posture says the United Kingdom, predicting the coming of a full-on blockade.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Noting the redeployment of a modern Russian corvette to the southern Black Sea, the UK&rsquo;s Ministry of Defence said in an intelligence digest that: &ldquo;Russia&rsquo;s Black Sea Fleet has altered its posture since Russia pulled out of the Black Sea Grain Initiative (BSGI), in preparedness to enforce a blockade on Ukraine&hellip; There is a realistic possibility that it will form part of a task group to intercept commercial vessels Russia believes are heading to Ukraine.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Without the Grain Initiative moderating behaviour in the Black Sea and providing a corridor for exports, there is now &ldquo;the potential for the intensity and scope of violence in the area to increase&rdquo;, the MOD said. Russia has already massively stepped up attacks on Ukraine&rsquo;s port infrastructure, regularly bombing Odessa for over a week.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The consequences of the collapse of the grain deal are potentially considerable, given Ukraine&rsquo;s status as a major exporter in the world food market, and the fact a lot of their exports have traditionally gone to less wealthy countries. As previously reported, a sudden spike in grain prices causes fresh waves of emigration from the developing world, sparking new migrant crises in Europe.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">It is claimed the collapse of the grain deal will see global grain prices spike by up to 15 per cent. While Ukraine has a considerable land border with Europe, simply switching from maritime to overland shipping for grain is extremely difficult given the enormous bulk of the commodity, the typical destinations for the product, and the lack of infrastructure.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Exporting by the Danube is being explored. Ukraine says Russia is deliberately targeting its grain exporting infrastructure, with Ukrainian Agrarian Council Denys Marchuk remarking: &ldquo;Russia understands that Ukrainian grain is one of the key directions of Ukraine&rsquo;s potential export, which gives money, and they really don&rsquo;t want to see Ukrainian grain. In fact today, by blocking the Black Sea, they are artificially raising the price of grain in the world so that later offer their grain to poor countries, and at high prices&rdquo;.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Marchuk said if European countries didn&rsquo;t want to see fresh waves of migration from poor nations, it should give Ukraine more weapons more quickly.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Given the importance of grain exports from Ukraine to the rest of the world, even if just indirectly for developed nations wanting to reduce push-factors for global mass migration, there may be pressure for the West to do more to defend merchant shipping in the Black Sea. This could take the form of more equipment donations to Ukraine, but as has been previously suggested, could be more direct, risking direct conflict between NATO and Russia.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Speaking of the military&hellip;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/news/white-house/biden-diversity-level-of-the-military"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/news/white-house/biden-diversity-level-of-the-military</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>Biden: 'Critical' that diversity is 'reflected at every level' of the military</strong></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">President Joe Biden released a statement Wednesday committing to further advancing diversity at "every level of the Department of Defense, including at the highest levels of leadership."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The president's Wednesday statement commemorated the 75th anniversary of the signing of President Harry Truman's executive order desegregating the armed forces after World War II.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">"This landmark Order, issued more than a decade before the passage of the Civil Rights Act, directed the military to ensure the 'equality of treatment and opportunity for all persons in the armed services without regard to race, color, religion or national origin,'" Biden wrote. "It was a vital step forward for our nation. It recognized the equal bravery and equal sacrifices of generations of service members of color who deserved to be equally honored."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The president highlighted the contributions of black service members throughout U.S. history, including black regiments who fought for the Union in the Civil War, the Harlem Hellfighters, and the Tuskegee Airmen.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">"Today, more than 40 percent of active-duty service members are people of color. Yet, despite this growing diversity, service members of color still face unacceptable barriers," Biden continued. "They are underrepresented in positions of senior leadership, face bias in the military justice system, and are still more likely to be dishonorably discharged. We owe it to them and the entire force to continue working to build a military where equal dignity and equal respect are fully realized."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The president specifically called advancing equity throughout the military a personal "priority," both for him and his "entire administration."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Earlier this week, Biden designated three sites as part of a new Emmett Till national memorial, but the president is also facing growing concerns among black voters, a key demographic, heading into the 2024 election cycle.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">A May poll from Ipsos and the Washington Post showed that just 34% of black Americans believe that Biden's agenda has helped their community. Nearly a majority of black respondents said his policies have had no impact, and 14% say the president's agenda is harming black people.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">And a poll conducted by YouGov and the Economist found that only 46% of black respondents wanted Biden to seek a second term, compared to 56% of all Democrats.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://www.dailywire.com/news/summer-camps-embrace-gender-theory-trans-inclusion-critical-race-theory"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.dailywire.com/news/summer-camps-embrace-gender-theory-trans-inclusion-critical-race-theory</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>Summer Camps Embrace Gender Theory, &lsquo;Trans Inclusion,&rsquo; Critical Race Theory</strong></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">National summer camp organizations have adopted practices and policies based on gender identity theory, &ldquo;trans inclusion,&rdquo; and Critical Race Theory (CRT).</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The American Camp Association (ACA), an organization of 10,000 summer camp professionals, is one of the groups that has embedded leftwing theories on race and gender into their operations. The organization is also responsible for accrediting summer camps across the country.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">ACA&rsquo;s 2023 National conference, which took place in February, included one session, titled &ldquo;Trans Inclusion in Overnight Programs.&rdquo; It focused on &ldquo;best practices for overnight camps striving to be welcoming spaces for trans and gender non-conforming campers and staff.&rdquo; The session was led by Chris Rehs-Dupin, the founder of a group that hosts trainings on &ldquo;LGBTQIA+ inclusive practices&rdquo; called Transplaining for Camps.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">&ldquo;Transplaining for Camps exists to help camps build inclusive practices that will create spaces of belonging for campers and staff of all gender identities and sexualities,&rdquo; the organization&rsquo;s website reads.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Another ACA conference session, which focused on the creation of racially exclusive &ldquo;affinity groups,&rdquo; was titled &ldquo;Creating Belonging Through Affinity Spaces At Camp&rdquo; and led by members of the Aloha Foundation, which runs camp programs in Vermont.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Meanwhile, a different session at the ACA conference, titled &ldquo;Centering Equity and Justice at Summer Camp: The Kids Are Ready&rdquo; argues that there is an evident need &ldquo;to tackle issues of social justice with our young people &hellip; and provide them not only with a safe(r) space to discuss these topics but the tools to become agents of change.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Other ACA sessions included &ldquo;Creating Safe and Affirming Spaces for LGBTQIA2S+ Folks at Camp&rdquo; and &ldquo;Lessons Learned in LGBTQIA+ Inclusive Practices.&rdquo; The ACA also has a &ldquo;checklist for gender inclusive practices at camp&rdquo; and a &ldquo;gender support plan for camp&rdquo; created by Gender Spectrum, an organization that promotes child transgenderism.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">An equity statement from Outward Bound USA claims that the &ldquo;outdoor community was and is a part of the underlying structure of injustice that governs American society,&rdquo; also going on to add &ldquo;we are deeply committed to dismantling inequities and working to write a new chapter.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">There&rsquo;s also Camp Fire, an organization that runs teen leadership events and camps, and seeks to connect young people to the outdoors &ldquo;through playful, inclusive, affordable, and powerful out-of-class experiences.&rdquo; It boasts that it has over 1,300 program sites across the country.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">A&nbsp; report from The Daily Wire revealed that there are also several summer camps across the country that have not only adopted policies based on gender theory or Critical Race Theory, but are specifically intended for children who identify as transgender or LGBT.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The ACA, Outward Bound USA, and Camp Fire did not respond to requests for comment.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">In entertainment news&hellip;&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://www.foxnews.com/entertainment/kevin-spacey-not-guilty-sexual-assault-trial"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.foxnews.com/entertainment/kevin-spacey-not-guilty-sexual-assault-trial</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>Kevin Spacey found not guilty in sexual assault trial</strong></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">A jury found Oscar-winning actor Kevin Spacey not guilty Wednesday in his criminal sexual assault trial in London surrounding allegations that he assaulted four men.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Jurors began deliberating Monday after nearly four weeks of testimony. The jury returned the verdicts at the Southwark Crown Court after three days. Spacey sobbed as he spoke to media outside the courthouse after the verdicts were announced.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=4qKrojl-JKs"><span style="font-weight: 400;" data-rich-links="{&quot;fple-t&quot;:&quot;Kevin Spacey speaks after being acquitted in U.K. sexual assault trial&quot;,&quot;fple-u&quot;:&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=4qKrojl-JKs&quot;,&quot;fple-mt&quot;:null,&quot;type&quot;:&quot;first-party-link&quot;}">Kevin Spacey speaks after being acquitted in U.K. sexual assault trial</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;">- Play Video&nbsp;</span></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Spacey, who also turned 64 on Wednesday, pleaded not guilty to charges of sexual assault, indecent assault and causing a person to engage in penetrative sexual activity without consent. Four men testified about similar encounters that involved Spacey allegedly groping them.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The acts alleged between 2001 and 2013 ranged from unwanted touching to aggressive crotch-grabbing and, in one instance, performing oral sex on an unconscious man.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">In closing arguments, prosecutors had argued Spacey got away with his behavior because of his celebrity status.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Spacey allegedly seized brief moments for an "opportunity grab" and was able to get away with the assaults for years because he was a celebrity who took advantage of his power, prosecutor Christine Agnew said.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Agnew emphasized that the four men's accounts were similar not because they had conspired to bring Spacey down, but because groping was reportedly Spacey's "trademark" move, according to the prosecution.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Spacey's defense lawyer said during closing arguments Friday that three of the men are liars, and he suggested jurors not convict him for making a "clumsy pass" at a fourth man.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Spacey testified himself over a span of two days, during which he denied violently groping one of his accusers and instead painted a picture of their "intimate" and "somewhat sexual" relationship for the jury. "I never thought that (the man) I knew would ... 20 years later stab me in the back," he said.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Elton John also testified remotely in Spacey's defense at one point during the trial, confirming the "American Beauty" star only attended one of the musician's annual gala parties in 2001. One of Spacey's alleged victims claimed the actor assaulted him while the two were driving to John's White Tie &amp; Tiara Ball in 2004 or 2005.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Spacey first faced allegations of sexual misconduct when actor Anthony Rapp came forward in 2017. Rapp accused Spacey of assaulting him at a party in the 1980s. Spacey was found not liable in Rapp's civil lawsuit.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Following Rapp's claim, more men came forward with accusations against Spacey, and he was booted from the Netflix show "House of Cards."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Spacey recently returned to the screen with roles in Italian director Franco Nero&rsquo;s "The Man Who Drew God," the biopic "Once Upon a Time in Croatia" and the film "Peter Five Eight."</span></p>
<p><br /><br /></p>]]></description>
   <author><![CDATA[Garrison Hardie]]></author>
   <enclosure url="https://app.dropwave.io/episode/90d31d80-8f4a-4945-aa68-360995ac3101/daily-news-brief-for-friday-july-28th-2023.mp3" length="816" type="audio/mp3"/>
   <guid isPermaLink="false"><![CDATA[90d31d80-8f4a-4945-aa68-360995ac3101]]></guid>
   <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
   <source url=""><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></source>
   <itunes:author><![CDATA[Garrison Hardie]]></itunes:author>
   <itunes:image href="https://assets-cdn2.dropwave.io/2ab40ac0-e99d-4f25-a6d2-541d2c9b290a/cover-art/mUK8zsnHkCK3vep7E1W6UgYb9dTnLenASAMEFha3.jpg"/>
   <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
   <itunes:duration>816</itunes:duration>
   <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title><![CDATA[Joshua 24:14-15 [Up and Ready]]]></title>
   <link/>
   <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
   <author><![CDATA[Mark Dewey]]></author>
   <enclosure url="https://app.dropwave.io/episode/dd907c97-37eb-43f1-aea0-d12461b2c95b/joshua-2414-15.mp3" length="266" type="audio/mp3"/>
   <guid isPermaLink="false"><![CDATA[dd907c97-37eb-43f1-aea0-d12461b2c95b]]></guid>
   <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
   <source url=""><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></source>
   <itunes:author><![CDATA[Mark Dewey]]></itunes:author>
   <itunes:image href="https://assets-cdn2.dropwave.io/60c9e557-5882-401d-abb8-06de47904be4/cover-art/zZ8CYlYBUAUu8KNyZzjE092h2WlBblW8upM7tmFg.png"/>
   <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
   <itunes:duration>266</itunes:duration>
   <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title><![CDATA[Vanessa (Gothix) & Graeme Wilson: Cancelled on Twitch to Servant of God [CrossPolitic Show]]]></title>
   <link/>
   <description><![CDATA[<p class="p1"><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Vanessa (Gothix) &amp; Graeme Wilson: Cancelled on Twitch to Servant of God</span></p>
<p class="p1">&nbsp;</p>
<p class="p1"><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Support Gothix on Loor TV</span></p>
<p class="p3"><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://www.loor.tv/sign-up?slug=gothix">https://www.loor.tv/sign-up?slug=gothix</a><span class="s1"><span class="Apple-converted-space">&nbsp;</span></span></span></p>
<p class="p2">&nbsp;</p>
<p class="p1"><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Sign up for the FLF Conference at the Ark Encounter! (Oct 11-14)</span></p>
<p class="p3"><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><span class="s2"><a href="https://flfnetwork.com/the-politics-of-six-days-creation-conference/">https://flfnetwork.com/the-politics-of-six-days-creation-conference/</a></span><span class="s1">&nbsp;</span></span></p>
<p class="p2">&nbsp;</p>
<p class="p1"><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Support Us &amp; Sign up for a FLF Club Membership!<span class="Apple-converted-space">&nbsp;</span></span></p>
<p class="p3"><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><span class="s2"><a href="https://flfnetwork.com/product/fightlaughfestclub/?attribute_member-tier=silver-monthly">https://flfnetwork.com/product/fightlaughfestclub/?attribute_member-tier=silver-monthly</a></span><span class="s1"><span class="Apple-converted-space">&nbsp;</span></span></span></p>]]></description>
   <author><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></author>
   <enclosure url="https://app.dropwave.io/episode/96aea020-decd-48eb-8cc0-0a75f411fc95/vanessa-gothix-graeme-wilson-cancelled-on-twitch-to-servant-of-god.mp3" length="1911" type="audio/mp3"/>
   <guid isPermaLink="false"><![CDATA[96aea020-decd-48eb-8cc0-0a75f411fc95]]></guid>
   <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2023 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
   <source url=""><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></source>
   <itunes:author><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></itunes:author>
   <itunes:image href="https://assets-cdn2.dropwave.io/11635dce-94e7-41b8-9261-5c1fc2cc5ebe/cover-art/wvkjcfd3tfj69XopdryYkSF8m1k4KHuikzJF1KzC.jpg"/>
   <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
   <itunes:duration>1911</itunes:duration>
   <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title><![CDATA[HERE COMES THE CLIMATE CULT!: We Are Living in a Woke, Neo-Marxist, Soft-Totalitarian State [Liberty Dispatch]]]></title>
   <link/>
   <description><![CDATA[<p class="p1"><strong>Liberty Dispatch</strong> ~ July 27, 2023<br />On this episode of the Dispatch, Andrew is flying solo, and he is taking a look at the woke, neo-Marxist, soft-totalitarian state that is Canada. As always, he brings receipts to show how this regime continues to move forward full-steam with continued covid madness, climate hysteria, and rainbow indoctrination. Buckle up!<br /><br /><strong style="font-family: '-apple-system', BlinkMacSystemFont, 'Segoe UI', Roboto, Oxygen, Ubuntu, Cantarell, 'Open Sans', 'Helvetica Neue', sans-serif;">[Segment 1] -&nbsp; <span data-doc-id="2726862000000791001" data-doc-type="writer">The State and its fiscal insanity</span>:<br /></strong>"Alberta Taxpayers Paid Millions in Severance to AHS Advisors Last Year: Sunshine List" | <em>Rebel News</em>: <a href="https://www.rebelnews.com/alberta_taxpayers_paid_millions_severance_ahs_advisors_last_year_sunshine_list" target="_new">https://www.rebelnews.com/alberta_taxpayers_paid_millions_severance_ahs_advisors_last_year_sunshine_list</a>;<br />"RCMP Systemically Racist" | <em>TNC News</em>: <a href="https://tnc.news/2023/07/26/rcmp-systemically-racist" target="_new">https://tnc.news/2023/07/26/rcmp-systemically-racist</a>;<br /><br /><strong>[Segment 2] -&nbsp; <span data-doc-id="2726862000000791001" data-doc-type="writer">COVID collateral damage continues</span>:</strong><br />"Serious Doubt Raised About COVID-19 Vaccine Safety After Forced Release of 15,000 Pages of Clinical Trial Data" | <em>The Epoch Times</em>: <a href="https://www.theepochtimes.com/article/serious-doubt-raised-about-covid-19-vaccine-safety-after-forced-release-of-15000-pages-of-clinical-trial-data-5414614?src_src=partner&amp;src_cmp=whatfinger" target="_new">https://www.theepochtimes.com/article/serious-doubt-raised-about-covid-19-vaccine-safety-after-forced-release-of-15000-pages-of-clinical-trial-data-5414614?src_src=partner&amp;src_cmp=whatfinger</a>;<br />"New COVID Vaccine Bombshell Emerges | Facts Matter" | <em>The Epoch Times</em>: <a href="https://www.theepochtimes.com/epochtv/new-covid-vaccine-bombshell-emerges-facts-matter-5422680?est=p2lMm60AxUk4KhT8Tdg435i1Z5If8F9MGXFPu83cvxgWW2F97OB20TlVkrGxtGEV0H8dPjIWTE7DUg%3D%3D" target="_new">https://www.theepochtimes.com/epochtv/new-covid-vaccine-bombshell-emerges-facts-matter-5422680?est=p2lMm60AxUk4KhT8Tdg435i1Z5If8F9MGXFPu83cvxgWW2F97OB20TlVkrGxtGEV0H8dPjIWTE7DUg%3D%3D</a>;<br />"Risk of Clotting and Bleeding Events Associated With the Janssen COVID-19 Vaccine: A Disproportionality Analysis" | <em>Zenodo</em>: <a href="https://zenodo.org/record/8120771" target="_new">https://zenodo.org/record/8120771</a>;<br />"Despite Minimal COVID Deaths, All-Cause Mortality Spiked in Netherlands: Prof. Theo Schetters" | <em>Bright Light News</em>: <a href="https://brightlightnews.com/despite-minimal-covid-deaths-all-cause-mortality-spiked-in-netherlands-prof-theo-schetters" target="_new">https://brightlightnews.com/despite-minimal-covid-deaths-all-cause-mortality-spiked-in-netherlands-prof-theo-schetters</a>;<br />"Funding Vax Passport to 2026" | <em>Blacklock's Reporter</em>: <a href="https://www.blacklocks.ca/funding-vax-passport-to-2026" target="_new">https://www.blacklocks.ca/funding-vax-passport-to-2026</a>;<br /><strong><br />[Segment 3] -&nbsp; <span data-doc-id="2726862000000791001" data-doc-type="writer">Here comes the Climate cult</span>:<br /></strong>"Deadly Heat Wave Kills Dozens in Europe as Continent Braces for More" | <em>The New York Times</em>: <a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2023/07/20/world/europe/heat-elderly.html" target="_new">https://www.nytimes.com/2023/07/20/world/europe/heat-elderly.html</a>;<br />"Globalists Suggest Finance Shock and Climate Controls to Launch Their Great Reset" | <em>ZeroHedge</em>: <a href="https://www.zerohedge.com/geopolitical/globalists-suggest-finance-shock-and-climate-controls-launch-their-great-reset" target="_new">https://www.zerohedge.com/geopolitical/globalists-suggest-finance-shock-and-climate-controls-launch-their-great-reset</a>.<br /><br /><strong>SUPPORT OUR LEGAL ADVOCACY - Help us defend Canadians' God-given rights and liberties: </strong><a href="https://libertycoalitioncanada.com/donate/">https://libertycoalitioncanada.com/donate/</a>; <a href="https://libertycoalitioncanada.com/liberty-defense-fund/our-legal-strategy/;">https://libertycoalitioncanada.com/liberty-defense-fund/our-legal-strategy/;</a><br /><strong><br /></strong><strong>SHOW SPONSORS:<br /></strong><strong>Join&nbsp;<em>Red Balloon&nbsp;</em>Today!:</strong> <a href="https://www.redballoon.work/lcc;">https://www.redballoon.work/lcc;</a>&nbsp;<br /><strong>Invest with Rocklinc:</strong> <a href="mailto:info@rocklinc.com">info@rocklinc.com</a>&nbsp;or call them at 905-631-546;&nbsp;<br /><strong>Diversify Your Money with Bull Bitcoin:&nbsp;</strong><a href="https://mission.bullbitcoin.com/lcc">https://mission.bullbitcoin.com/lcc</a>;<br /><strong>BarterPay: </strong><a href="https://barterpay.ca/">https://barterpay.ca/</a>;&nbsp; <strong>Barter It: </strong><a href="https://vip.barterit.ca/launch;">https://vip.barterit.ca/launch; </a><strong><br />Carpe Fide - "Seize the Faith": Store: </strong><a href="https://carpe-fide.myshopify.com/">https://carpe-fide.myshopify.com</a><a href="https://carpe-fide.myshopify.com/">/</a>, use Promo Code LCC10 for 10% off (US Store Only), or shop Canadian @ <a href="https://canadacarpefide.myshopify.com/">https://canadacarpefide.myshopify.com/</a> | <strong>Podcast: </strong><a href="https://www.carpefide.com/episodes">https://www.carpefide.com/episodes</a>;<br /><br /><strong>Sick of Mainstream Media Lies? Help Support Independent Media! DONATE TO LCC TODAY!:&nbsp;</strong><strong><a href="https://libertycoalitioncanada.com/donate/">https://libertycoalitioncanada.com/donate/</a>&nbsp;</strong><strong>&nbsp;<br /><br /></strong></p>
<p class="p1">Please Support us in bringing you honest, truthful reporting and analysis from a Christian perspective.<br /><br /><strong>SUBSCRIBE TO OUR SHOWS/CHANNELS:<br /></strong>LIBERTY DISPATCH PODCAST: <a href="https://libertydispatch.podbean.com">https://libertydispatch.podbean.com</a>; <a href="https://rumble.com/c/c-1687093">https://rumble.com/LDshow</a>;&nbsp;<br />OPEN MIKE WITH MICHAEL THIESSEN: <a href="https://openmikewithmichaelthiessen.podbean.com">https://openmikewithmichaelthiessen.podbean.com</a>; <a href="https://rumble.com/c/c-1412501">https://rumble.com/openmike</a>;<br />THE OTHER CLUB: <a href="https://rumble.com/c/c-2541984">https://rumble.com/c/c-2541984</a>;&nbsp;<br />THE LIBERTY LOUNGE WITH TIM TYSOE: <a href="https://rumble.com/LLwTT">https://rumble.com/LLwTT</a>;<br /><br /><strong>CONTACT US:</strong><br />Questions/comments about podcasts/news/analysis: <a href="mailto:mailbag@libertycoalitioncanada.com">mailbag@libertycoalitioncanada.com</a>;<br />Questions/comments about donations: <a href="mailto:give@libertycoalitioncanada.com">give@libertycoalitioncanada.com</a>;<br />Questions/comments that are church-related: <a href="mailto:churches@libertycoalitioncanada.com">churches@libertycoalitioncanada.com</a>;<br />General Inquiries: <a href="mailto:info@libertycoalitioncanada.com">info@libertycoalitioncanada.com</a>.&nbsp;</p>
<p class="p1"><strong>STAY UP-TO-DATE ON ALL THINGS LCC:<br /></strong>Gab: <a href="https://gab.com/libertycoalitioncanada">https://gab.com/libertycoalitioncanada</a>&nbsp;</p>
<p class="p2">Telegram: <a href="https://t.me/libertycoalitioncanadanews">https://t.me/libertycoalitioncanadanews</a>&nbsp;</p>
<p class="p2">Instagram: <a href="https://instagram.com/libertycoalitioncanada">https://instagram.com/libertycoalitioncanada</a>&nbsp;</p>
<p class="p2">Facebook: <a href="https://facebook.com/LibertyCoalitionCanada">https://facebook.com/LibertyCoalitionCanada</a>&nbsp;</p>
<p class="p2">Twitter: @LibertyCCanada - <a href="https://twitter.com/LibertyCCanada">https://twitter.com/LibertyCCanada</a>&nbsp;</p>
<p class="p2">Rumble: <a href="https://rumble.com/user/LibertyCoalitionCanada">https://rumble.com/user/LibertyCoalitionCanada</a>&nbsp;</p>
<p class="p2">YouTube: <a href="https://www.youtube.com/@liberty4canada">https://www.youtube.com/@liberty4canada</a> -&nbsp;<strong>WE GOT CANCELLED AGAIN!!!</strong></p>
<p class="p1"><strong>Please LIKE, SUBSCRIBE, RATE &amp; REVIEW and SHARE it with others!</strong></p>]]></description>
   <author><![CDATA[Matthew Hallick, Andrew DeBartolo, SDG Media]]></author>
   <enclosure url="https://app.dropwave.io/episode/2600a508-bff2-4ea3-a3ac-9117d2f1bc09/here-comes-the-climate-cult-we-are-living-in-a-woke-neo-marxist-soft-totalitarian-stateit-sucks.mp3" length="3204" type="audio/mp3"/>
   <guid isPermaLink="false"><![CDATA[2600a508-bff2-4ea3-a3ac-9117d2f1bc09]]></guid>
   <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2023 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
   <source url=""><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></source>
   <itunes:author><![CDATA[Matthew Hallick, Andrew DeBartolo, SDG Media]]></itunes:author>
   <itunes:image href="https://prod-assets-spc1.nyc3.digitaloceanspaces.com/69893365-4165-4498-b0ac-e9ddf57a000f/cover-art/E86eLfK3NgjrpuXtk9kW9Qv6KcfzQpkJpToltreR.png"/>
   <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
   <itunes:duration>3204</itunes:duration>
   <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title><![CDATA[The Case for Church Membership [Leadership Now Podcast]]]></title>
   <link/>
   <description><![CDATA[<p>In this week's episode, Dr. Aaron Rock covers all things church membership: it's importance in the life of the believer, it's purpose, and the authority of the elders over its flock.&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>More Resources:</strong></p>
<p>We are excited to partner with the Fight Laugh Feast Network to reach more listeners. Download the app here:&nbsp;<a href="https://subsplash.com/fightlaughfeastnetwork/app">https://subsplash.com/</a><a href="https://subsplash.com/fightlaughfeastnetwork/app">fightlaughfeastnetwork/app</a></p>
<p>&nbsp;More resources at Dr. Aaron Rock&rsquo;s blog: Pursuit of Glory&nbsp;<a href="https://pursuitofglory.org/">https://pursuitofglory.org/</a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>]]></description>
   <author><![CDATA[Dr. Aaron Rock, Chris Eelman]]></author>
   <enclosure url="https://app.dropwave.io/episode/3ab15788-09eb-4dd9-af0d-514b67264600/the-case-for-church-membership.mp3" length="4315" type="audio/mp3"/>
   <guid isPermaLink="false"><![CDATA[3ab15788-09eb-4dd9-af0d-514b67264600]]></guid>
   <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2023 19:03:00 +0000</pubDate>
   <source url=""><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></source>
   <itunes:author><![CDATA[Dr. Aaron Rock, Chris Eelman]]></itunes:author>
   <itunes:image href="https://assets-cdn2.dropwave.io/3312a6b0-2b88-4186-bfdd-e9c55d3d7e0f/cover-art/DJmJxOQEoRfGbs693sV6kEnKEGWstWUfdEXbQra8.png"/>
   <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
   <itunes:duration>4315</itunes:duration>
   <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title><![CDATA[AD: You Need More Far Right Wing Content [AD on FLF Network]]]></title>
   <link/>
   <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
   <author><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></author>
   <enclosure url="https://dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/app.dropwave.io/episode/e17e5d0e-0036-4b81-bc70-1fc2db5d31d3/ad-you-need-more-far-right-wing-content.mp3" length="1217" type="audio/mp3"/>
   <guid isPermaLink="false"><![CDATA[e17e5d0e-0036-4b81-bc70-1fc2db5d31d3]]></guid>
   <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2023 18:24:00 +0000</pubDate>
   <source url=""><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></source>
   <itunes:author><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></itunes:author>
   <itunes:image href="https://assets-cdn2.dropwave.io/e985f24f-d823-4e20-b87a-9e2fa86624f5/cover-art/me0OCTvDSY04mcI5sI97SZ3jsUtDXyHr5ExQtpr2.jpg"/>
   <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
   <itunes:duration>1217</itunes:duration>
   <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title><![CDATA[CrossPolitic Daily News Brief for Thursday, July 27th, 2023 [Daily News Brief]]]></title>
   <link/>
   <description><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">This is Garrison Hardie with your CrossPolitic Daily News Brief for Thursday, July 27th, 2023.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>Olive Tree Biblical Software:</strong></span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Discover why more than a million people use the free Olive Tree Bible App as their go-to for reading, studying, and listening to the God&rsquo;s Word.&nbsp;&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Start by downloading one of many free Bibles and start taking notes, highlighting verses, and bookmarking your favorite passages. You can read at your own pace, or choose from a large selection of Reading Plans, including the Bible Reading Challenge. When you are ready to go deeper into your studies, Olive Tree is right there with a large selection of study Bibles, commentaries, and other helpful study resources available for purchase. There&rsquo;s also an extensive bookstore allows you to build your digital library one book at a time and Olive Tree&rsquo;s sync technology lets you pick up where you left off on your tablet, pc or phone and get right to studying on another supported device.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">&nbsp;</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Now here's the best part &ndash; You can start with the Olive Tree Essentials Bundle for FREE. Visit www.olivetree.com/FLF and download it today! </span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://apnews.com/article/ufos-uaps-congress-whistleblower-spy-aliens-ba8a8cfba353d7b9de29c3d906a69ba7"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://apnews.com/article/ufos-uaps-congress-whistleblower-spy-aliens-ba8a8cfba353d7b9de29c3d906a69ba7</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>Whistleblower tells Congress the US is concealing &lsquo;multi-decade&rsquo; program that captures UFOs</strong></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The U.S. is concealing a longstanding program that retrieves and reverse engineers unidentified flying objects, a former Air Force intelligence officer testified Wednesday to Congress. The Pentagon has denied his claims.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Retired Maj. David Grusch&rsquo;s highly anticipated testimony before a House Oversight subcommittee was Congress&rsquo; latest foray into the world of UAPs &mdash; or &ldquo;unidentified aerial phenomena,&rdquo; which is the official term the U.S. government uses instead of UFOs. While the study of mysterious aircraft or objects often evokes talk of aliens and &ldquo;little green men,&rdquo; Democrats and Republicans in recent years have pushed for more research as a national security matter due to concerns that sightings observed by pilots may be tied to U.S. adversaries.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Grusch said he was asked in 2019 by the head of a government task force on UAPs to identify all highly classified programs relating to the task force&rsquo;s mission. At the time, Grusch was detailed to the National Reconnaissance Office, the agency that operates U.S. spy satellites.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">&ldquo;I was informed in the course of my official duties of a multi-decade UAP crash retrieval and reverse engineering program to which I was denied access,&rdquo; he said.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Asked whether the U.S. government had information about extraterrestrial life, Grusch said the U.S. likely has been aware of &ldquo;non-human&rdquo; activity since the 1930s.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The Pentagon has denied Grusch&rsquo;s claims of a coverup. In a statement, Defense Department spokeswoman Sue Gough said investigators have not discovered &ldquo;any verifiable information to substantiate claims that any programs regarding the possession or reverse-engineering of extraterrestrial materials have existed in the past or exist currently.&rdquo; The statement did not address UFOs that are not suspected of being extraterrestrial objects.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Grusch says he became a government whistleblower after his discovery and has faced retaliation for coming forward. He declined to be more specific about the retaliatory tactics, citing an ongoing investigation.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://hotair.com/david-strom/2023/07/26/swiss-study-heart-injuries-from-covid-vaccine-3000x-higher-than-thought-n567151"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://hotair.com/david-strom/2023/07/26/swiss-study-heart-injuries-from-covid-vaccine-3000x-higher-than-thought-n567151</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>Swiss study: heart injuries from COVID vaccine 3000x higher than thought</strong></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">It is a small study, but a very disturbing one.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">In fact, in a study with only 777 participants with a median age of 37--all medical professionals getting the COVID vaccine&ndash;the incidence of elevated cardiac enzymes 3 days after injection was pretty substantial, at almost 3%.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The CDC did a study and from that, they claimed the rate was 0.001%, or one out of 100,000.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">2.8% is a lot higher than 0.001%. Another 0.3% had &ldquo;probable myocarditis,&rdquo; putting the total at over 3%. That is 3000 times higher than the US government claimed.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">In this small study, nobody had serious complications, but with a myocarditis complication rate of 3%, you would have to expect that giving out hundreds of millions of doses is a pretty risky proposition.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">I think we all knew that already, but this study seems to put the nail in the coffin of &ldquo;vaccine injuries are super rare&rdquo; from COVID-19 shots.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">One oddity was that the rate of myocarditis among the participants was heavily weighted toward women, not men. That could be an artifact of the sample, or it could indicate that women are more likely to get a complication, but the complications are more likely to be serious among men.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">One reason the researchers posit for the vast difference between their results&ndash;which are based upon blood tests looking for cardiac enzymes in all participants&ndash;and the commonly asserted claim that vaccine-induced myocarditis is rare is that the only cases that are diagnosed without looking specifically for it are severe.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">In other words, most people don&rsquo;t go to the doctor until there is a serious problem, so many people suffer from myocarditis without ever getting diagnosed.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">This suggests that there is a very large group of people who were afflicted but never treated. This in most cases would not be a huge problem, as the inflammation resolves on its own, but in some cases, actual damage to the heart was done without it ever being caught.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">In any case, this study sheds quite a light on just how deceptive the CDC, the FDA, and NIAID have been about vaccine safety. And also how intentionally ignorant they have chosen to be. This was not a complicated study to do. The researchers chose a cohort easy to recruit, tested them both before and after vaccination to create a baseline and comparison, and analyzed the data.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://www.foxnews.com/politics/hunter-biden-plea-deal-appears-fall-apart-first-court-appearance"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.foxnews.com/politics/hunter-biden-plea-deal-appears-fall-apart-first-court-appearance</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>Hunter Biden pleads 'not guilty' as plea deal falls apart during Delaware court appearance</strong></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Hunter Biden's plea deal fell apart during his first court appearance Wednesday morning and pleaded "not guilty" as federal prosecutors confirmed the president's son is still under federal investigation.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The president's son was expected to plead guilty to two misdemeanor tax counts of willful failure to pay federal income tax, as part of plea deal to avoid jail time on a felony gun charge.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">But Judge Maryellen Noreika did not accept the plea agreement, questioning the constitutionality--specifically the diversion clause and the immunity Hunter Biden would receive.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Hunter Biden was also expected to enter into a pretrial diversion agreement regarding a separate felony charge of possession of a firearm by a person who is an unlawful user of or addicted to a controlled substance.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">House Ways &amp; Means Committee Chairman Jason Smith filed an amicus brief to the court, requesting that testimony be considered ahead of accepting the planned plea deal, saying Hunter Biden "appears to have benefited from political interference which calls into question the propriety of the investigation of the U.S. Attorney&rsquo;s Office."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">"In the interest of full transparency and fairness for all citizens, it is critical for the Court to have this relevant information when evaluating the Plea Agreement," Smith wrote in the brief.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Meanwhile, on the eve of the court appearance, the judge threatened to sanction Hunter Biden's legal team after one of his attorneys allegedly lied about who she was while asking to remove IRS whistleblower testimony from the court docket.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The defense, though, denied the allegations and called the incident "an unfortunate and unintentional miscommunication."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/news/new-york-city-crane-falls-engulfed-flames"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/news/new-york-city-crane-falls-engulfed-flames</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>New York City crane collapse: Construction equipment tumbles to ground as it is engulfed in flames</strong></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">A crane fell near the Hell's Kitchen neighborhood of Manhattan on Wednesday after a fire broke out on the construction equipment, but officials say it could have been much worse.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The crane was engulfed in flames before part of it fell to the ground, hitting a nearby building in the process. The New York City Fire Department said that six people, including two firefighters, have injuries. The injuries to the two firefighters are "non-life threatening," while the four civilian injuries are "minor," according to the department.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">"As you see from the debris on the street, this could have been much worse. We are extremely fortunate, No. 1, that [it was] not during the busy time of the day &mdash; as you know, the Port Authority is here. Many of the buses move through here. We were extremely fortunate," New York City Mayor Eric Adams said at a press conference.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The first report of the fire to FDNY came at 7:25 a.m. local time, with officials saying the fire started in the engine compartment of the crane. The top part of the crane and a 16-ton load collapsed as firefighters were arriving at the scene. One of the injuries was described as "chest pains" for one of the firefighters.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">At a news conference Wednesday morning, fire officials said the fire had been mostly extinguished but that operations are still ongoing. Fifty units, totaling 220 fire personnel, responded to the scene of the fire, according to FDNY.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">New York City Department of Buildings Commissioner Jimmy Oddo said the building where the crane fire occurred was an under-construction 54-story mixed-use building, which had all proper permits filed. Oddo said the only previous incident at the site was when construction workers hit a vault during excavation for the building.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">City officials also said the crane operator had attempted to put out the fire when he noticed it, but when he was unable to do so safely, he evacuated from the crane and is OK.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://thenationalpulse.com/2023/07/25/accept-deadly-blackouts-to-fight-climate-change-says-paper/"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://thenationalpulse.com/2023/07/25/accept-deadly-blackouts-to-fight-climate-change-says-paper/</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>Accept Deadly Blackouts to Fight &lsquo;Climate Change&rsquo;, Says Paper</strong></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The Los Angeles Times says that blackouts have to increase in order to combat climate change, while stunningly acknowledging the policy may cost people&rsquo;s lives. The newspaper has asked its dwindling audience to consider &ldquo;a larger conversation&rdquo; in which people become more accustomed to changing their expectations, including the idea of living without electricity for large parts of their lives so as to prevent &ldquo;climate catastrophe.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The piece also insists that &ldquo;fossil-funded lies,&rdquo; apparently spread by Republicans &ndash; such as the overall uselessness of solar farms and wind turbines &ndash; should not be considered within the discussion on how to address climate change. Instead, the conversation must be orientated towards adding &ldquo;solar panels, wind turbines and all kinds of energy storage to the grid as fast as possible.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The newspaper also recognizes the risk of such a policy as it reports that someone dies every time there is a blackout, and includes a quote from the director of reliability assessment and performance analysis at the North American Electric Reliability Corp, John Moura, that &ldquo;it&rsquo;s not really about keeping the lights on. It&rsquo;s about keeping people alive.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Accepting increased blackouts is yet another extreme measure being suggested to tackle climate change. One recent study suggested changing working hours from 9 am to 5 am to 6 am to 2 pm.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Speaking of climate change&hellip;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://www.theblaze.com/news/npr-ridiculed-for-regurgitating-claim-that-the-movement-to-push-bug-food-on-the-masses-is-a-racist-conspiracy-theory"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.theblaze.com/news/npr-ridiculed-for-regurgitating-claim-that-the-movement-to-push-bug-food-on-the-masses-is-a-racist-conspiracy-theory</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>NPR ridiculed for regurgitating claim that the movement to push bug food on the masses is a 'racist' conspiracy theory</strong></span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">NPR's race-obsessed and taxpayer-subsidized show "Code Switch" recently peddled the notion that it is conspiratorial thinking to take proponents of the bug-food movement at their word.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">What's more, host Gene Demby's guest on the July 19 episode, entitled "This right wing conspiracy theory about eating bugs is about as racist as you think," has intimated that criticism both of bug food and of those technocrats who seek to alter consumer behavior may be racist.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">NPR has since been met with ridicule by those aware that the desire to supplement or replace normal food with bugs is not a conspiracy theory but rather a real initiative with substantial momentum, which has been long detailed and defended in academic journals, trusted publications, and even on NPR.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">NPR reporter Huo Jingnan joined "Code Switch" host Gene Demby on last week's episode to regurgitate talking points from his April NPR article, wherein he simultaneously held that the claim that "elites want people to eat bugs" was a right-wing conspiracy theory while also acknowledging the inclusion of bugs in human food was "an emerging, but still marginal, idea among climate scientists and food security experts."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Jingnan hinted both in his article and on Demby's show there must also be a racial component to the growing concerns about the bug-food movement and the motivations driving it.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">While Demby appeared keen to write off the bug-food movement as "not that big a deal," and Jingnan intimated that it might just the MAGA crowd who are paying attention, critics have pointed that NPR's publication history suggests otherwise.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Here are the titles of just a few NPR features in recent months and years:</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">"These Pictures Might Tempt You To Eat Bugs" &mdash; July 18, 2013;</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">"Making Food From Flies (It's Not That Icky)" &mdash; Sept. 19, 2013;</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">"Even Neil DeGrasse Tyson Is Now Munching On Bugs" &mdash; March 23, 2015;</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">"Street Food No More: Bug Snacks Move To Store Shelves In Thailand" &mdash; April 15, 2015;</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">"Are Insects The Future Of Food?" &mdash; Nov. 17, 2016;</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">"At Bug-Eating Festival, Kids Crunch Down On The Food Of The Future" &mdash; Sept. 14, 2017;</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">"Your Ancestors Probably Ate Insects. So What's Bugging You?" &mdash; July 16, 2018;</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">"VIDEO: 4 Ways That Wild Edibles, Including Insects, Will Wow You" &mdash; Dec. 20, 2018; and</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">"Should Hyping Edible Bugs Focus On The Experience Instead Of The Environment?" &mdash; Jan. 10, 2019.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The food of the future indeed&hellip;&nbsp;</span></p>]]></description>
   <author><![CDATA[Garrison Hardie]]></author>
   <enclosure url="https://app.dropwave.io/episode/4b15b356-ce83-4852-969e-37f76652a1fe/crosspolitic-daily-news-brief-for-thursday-july-27th-2023.mp3" length="842" type="audio/mp3"/>
   <guid isPermaLink="false"><![CDATA[4b15b356-ce83-4852-969e-37f76652a1fe]]></guid>
   <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
   <source url=""><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></source>
   <itunes:author><![CDATA[Garrison Hardie]]></itunes:author>
   <itunes:image href="https://assets-cdn2.dropwave.io/2ab40ac0-e99d-4f25-a6d2-541d2c9b290a/cover-art/mUK8zsnHkCK3vep7E1W6UgYb9dTnLenASAMEFha3.jpg"/>
   <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
   <itunes:duration>842</itunes:duration>
   <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title><![CDATA[Fashionable Euthanasia? [The Pugcast]]]></title>
   <link/>
   <description><![CDATA[<p class="p1">An increasing trend has sprung up in the West, the Netherlands and Canada most recently, where assisted suicide and euthanasia have become fashionable options for people not merely suffering interminable diseases during the latter days of their lives but for young and old who are just tired of living for one reason or the other, whether its recurrent depression, an eating disorder, or a bad break-up. Tom introduces this disturbing trend, and the guys engage it from many angles, offering theological and ethical analysis on the one side, but also ministerial and sound counsel on the other.</p>
<p class="p2">&nbsp;</p>
<p class="p3"><span class="s1">Support the Pugcast on Patreon: <a href="https://www.patreon.com/thetheologypugcast?fbclid=IwAR17UHhfzjphO52C_kkZfursA_C784t0ldFix0wyB4fd-YOJpmOQ3dyqGf8">https://www.patreon.com/thetheologypugcast?fbclid=IwAR17UHhfzjphO52C_kkZfursA_C784t0ldFix0wyB4fd-YOJpmOQ3dyqGf8</a></span></p>
<p class="p2">&nbsp;</p>
<p class="p1">Order The Making of Evangelical Spirituality by Jason Cherry: <a href="https://a.co/d/2SyDFwb"><span class="s2">https://a.co/d/2SyDFwb</span></a></p>]]></description>
   <author><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></author>
   <enclosure url="https://app.dropwave.io/episode/5016ee48-9b3f-4347-9a90-76eff953c5c0/fashionable-euthanasia.mp3" length="3801" type="audio/mp3"/>
   <guid isPermaLink="false"><![CDATA[5016ee48-9b3f-4347-9a90-76eff953c5c0]]></guid>
   <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2023 09:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
   <source url=""><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></source>
   <itunes:author><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></itunes:author>
   <itunes:image href="https://assets-cdn2.dropwave.io/95888944-bdd8-4d76-b4ae-8875769ac332/cover-art/aiNC1kS3NVFxfOfz2ZHCCrTnthpK8XAqpLYOu323.jpg"/>
   <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
   <itunes:duration>3801</itunes:duration>
   <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title><![CDATA[Mark 16:6 [Up and Ready]]]></title>
   <link/>
   <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
   <author><![CDATA[Mark Dewey]]></author>
   <enclosure url="https://app.dropwave.io/episode/e1bb9997-9c15-4d49-86bc-a284d7bb1d1b/mark-166.mp3" length="290" type="audio/mp3"/>
   <guid isPermaLink="false"><![CDATA[e1bb9997-9c15-4d49-86bc-a284d7bb1d1b]]></guid>
   <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
   <source url=""><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></source>
   <itunes:author><![CDATA[Mark Dewey]]></itunes:author>
   <itunes:image href="https://assets-cdn2.dropwave.io/60c9e557-5882-401d-abb8-06de47904be4/cover-art/zZ8CYlYBUAUu8KNyZzjE092h2WlBblW8upM7tmFg.png"/>
   <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
   <itunes:duration>290</itunes:duration>
   <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title><![CDATA[Tucker & Tate are Dangerous - The Good & The Bad [CrossPolitic Show]]]></title>
   <link/>
   <description><![CDATA[<p class="p1"><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Tucker &amp; Tate are Dangerous - The Good &amp; The Bad</span></p>
<p class="p2">&nbsp;</p>
<p class="p1"><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Support our lowly producer&rsquo;s podcast (In The Garden)<span class="Apple-converted-space">&nbsp;</span></span></p>
<p class="p3"><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://open.spotify.com/show/1XLwvHSTwYNIM3nlHNlmqy?si=HeOMZFpFTiGAZhuxhKz3qA">https://open.spotify.com/show/1XLwvHSTwYNIM3nlHNlmqy?si=HeOMZFpFTiGAZhuxhKz3qA</a><span class="s1"><span class="Apple-converted-space">&nbsp;</span></span></span></p>
<p class="p2">&nbsp;</p>
<p class="p1"><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Sign up for the FLF Conference at the Ark Encounter! (Oct 11-14)</span></p>
<p class="p3"><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><span class="s2"><a href="https://flfnetwork.com/the-politics-of-six-days-creation-conference/">https://flfnetwork.com/the-politics-of-six-days-creation-conference/</a></span><span class="s1">&nbsp;</span></span></p>
<p class="p2">&nbsp;</p>
<p class="p1"><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Support Us &amp; Sign up for a FLF Club Membership!<span class="Apple-converted-space">&nbsp;</span></span></p>
<p class="p3"><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><span class="s2"><a href="https://flfnetwork.com/product/fightlaughfestclub/?attribute_member-tier=silver-monthly">https://flfnetwork.com/product/fightlaughfestclub/?attribute_member-tier=silver-monthly</a></span><span class="s1"><span class="Apple-converted-space">&nbsp;</span></span></span></p>]]></description>
   <author><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></author>
   <enclosure url="https://app.dropwave.io/episode/dd59766b-c94e-4455-95e3-d6dbfa74604d/tucker-tate-are-dangerous-the-good-the-bad.mp3" length="2399" type="audio/mp3"/>
   <guid isPermaLink="false"><![CDATA[dd59766b-c94e-4455-95e3-d6dbfa74604d]]></guid>
   <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2023 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
   <source url=""><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></source>
   <itunes:author><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></itunes:author>
   <itunes:image href="https://assets-cdn2.dropwave.io/11635dce-94e7-41b8-9261-5c1fc2cc5ebe/cover-art/wvkjcfd3tfj69XopdryYkSF8m1k4KHuikzJF1KzC.jpg"/>
   <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
   <itunes:duration>2399</itunes:duration>
   <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title><![CDATA[Christian Combat w/Michael Thiessen [The Ezra Institute Podcast for Cultural Reformation]]]></title>
   <link/>
   <description><![CDATA[<p>Michael Thiessen of Liberty Coalition Canada joins us to discuss the latest developments in the ongoing saga of the church&rsquo;s relationship to LGBT issues, and the further complication of what happens when the state gets involved. We deal with the proper use of legal process as Christians, news stories, citizenship, charity law, and the prophetic calling of the church.</p>
<p><a href="https://www.ezrainstitute.com/donate/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">We rely on your support to continue with all of our work. Would you donate to the Ezra Institute?</a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<div class="featured-resources mt-5 rp4wp-related-posts rp4wp-related-mere_resource">&nbsp;</div>]]></description>
   <author><![CDATA[Joe Boot, Ryan Eras, Michael Thiessen]]></author>
   <enclosure url="https://app.dropwave.io/episode/23fcfc6b-35b7-4b0d-a979-67916e7bf1c2/christian-combat-wmichael-thiessen.mp3" length="4502" type="audio/mp3"/>
   <guid isPermaLink="false"><![CDATA[23fcfc6b-35b7-4b0d-a979-67916e7bf1c2]]></guid>
   <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jul 2023 19:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
   <source url=""><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></source>
   <itunes:author><![CDATA[Joe Boot, Ryan Eras, Michael Thiessen]]></itunes:author>
   <itunes:image href="https://assets-cdn2.dropwave.io/1c3a97bd-65b0-4aec-bb35-3a1b6eec5d2c/cover-art/4rDIhLUsGj1xuXpLJYNdtwtbungA78glNHA7dOd9.png"/>
   <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
   <itunes:duration>4502</itunes:duration>
   <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title><![CDATA[Daily News Brief for Wednesday, July 26th, 2023 [Daily News Brief]]]></title>
   <link/>
   <description><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">This is Garrison Hardie with your CrossPolitic Daily News Brief for Wednesday, July 26th, 2023.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>PUB MEMBERSHIP PLUG:</strong></span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Summer has been great here at CrossPolitic, and we want you to join us on this ride&hellip; First, we&rsquo;re no longer calling it the Fight Laugh Feast club&hellip; it&rsquo;s now called the Pub! Second, we are launching a new line of content, focused on family entertainment. We will have our new show &ldquo;This America&rdquo; and our exciting new &ldquo;Rowdy Christian Guides&rdquo; highlighting the practical guides to fun and godly life! Additionally, we will have the live streaming of our conferences, and our past conference talks, all bundled within our new polished Fight Laugh Feast App. Sign up today! Head on over to fightlaughfeast.com, and join the Pub! that&rsquo;s fightlaughfeast.com.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://thepostmillennial.com/breaking-biden-admin-launches-permanent-pandemic-preparedness-office?utm_campaign=64487"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://thepostmillennial.com/breaking-biden-admin-launches-permanent-pandemic-preparedness-office?utm_campaign=64487</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>Biden admin launches PERMANENT pandemic preparedness office</strong></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">President Joe Biden has created a permanent office for pandemic response. Called the Office of Pandemic Preparedness and Response Policy, the new office within the executive branch replaces the Covid-19 response team that Biden ushered in during his first days in the White House.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">This new office will ensure that the Biden administration can continue to implement so-called pandemic mitigation strategies for any new communicable disease that comes down the pike.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">"This will be a permanent office in the Executive Office of the President (EOP)," the White House offers in a briefing, "charged with leading, coordinating, and implementing actions related to preparedness for, and response to, known and unknown biological threats or pathogens that could lead to a pandemic or to significant public health-related disruptions in the United States."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">This office replaces those set up for both Covid and the oddly named Mpox, so called because its original name, Monkey Pox, was deemed to be racist by Democrats who believe that in some way "monkey" is racist against black people.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The new team, led by retired Major General Paul Friedrichs, will "continue to coordinate and develop policies and priorities related to pandemic preparedness and response."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">This office will be primarily responsible to the executive branch, and will "drive and coordinate federal science and technology efforts related to pandemic preparedness." What this entails in specific is the overseeing of "efforts to develop, manufacture, and procure the next generation of medical countermeasures, including leveraging emerging technologies and working with HHS on next generation vaccines and treatments for COVID-19 and other public health threats."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The administration also took the opportunity to tout its efforts during the Covid pandemic, which began when a virus created through gain-of-function research leaked from a Wuhan, China lab that was funded in part by the National Institutes of Health.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">It was also during the Biden administration's pandemic response that Americans were encouraged to not leave their homes, to shut down churches and schools while leaving casinos, liquor stores, and Walmarts open, and to mandate the wearing of face coverings that later studies revealed were steeped with bacteria. Under Biden's watch, newly-created vaccines were mandated both for federal employees and the employees of companies that contracted with the federal government.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">This is the kind of pandemic response the new Office of Pandemic Preparedness and Response Policy will be ready to implement as soon as the next potential pandemic comes along.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://www.theguardian.com/environment/2023/jul/24/greta-thunberg-fined-for-disobeying-swedish-police-at-climate-protest"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.theguardian.com/environment/2023/jul/24/greta-thunberg-fined-for-disobeying-swedish-police-at-climate-protest</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>Greta Thunberg fined for disobeying Swedish police at climate protest</strong></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Greta Thunberg has been fined by a Swedish court after she was found guilty of disobeying a police order to leave a climate protest.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The 20-year-old climate activist, who from 2018 became the face of the youth climate movement, had admitted taking part in the protest in Malm&ouml; in June, but pleaded not guilty on the grounds she had acted out of necessity.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">&ldquo;My actions are justifiable,&rdquo; Thunberg told the court in Malm&ouml;, according to local media. &ldquo;I believe that we are in an emergency that threatens life, health and property. Countless people and communities are at risk both in the short term and in the long term.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Five years ago, Thunberg, then 15, began skipping school each Friday and staging solo climate protests outside the Swedish parliament in Stockholm, holding up a sign reading: &ldquo;Skolstrejk f&ouml;r klimatet&rdquo; (school strike for climate).</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Her weekly demonstrations snowballed into a global wave of youth climate protest, as she gained fame for her youth and her blunt speaking on the dire future faced by young people staring down the barrel of the climate crisis.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Although the school strikes movement lost some of its momentum with the outbreak of the coronavirus pandemic, Thunberg has continued to travel the world joining climate protests and speaking at international summits, urging world leaders to act on the climate crisis.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">It is believed that Monday&rsquo;s trial is her first conviction for climate protest.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Thunberg was part of a group of protesters that blocked the road for oil trucks in Malm&ouml; harbour. She was charged for failing to leave when ordered to do so by police.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The fine will be based on Thunberg&rsquo;s reported income and it was not immediately clear how much she would have to pay, Reuters reported.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://newsbusters.org/blogs/nb/tim-graham/2023/07/24/solvency-dies-darkness-washington-post-pace-lose-100-million-year"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://newsbusters.org/blogs/nb/tim-graham/2023/07/24/solvency-dies-darkness-washington-post-pace-lose-100-million-year</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>Washington Post On Pace to Lose $100 Million This Year</strong></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The New York Times buried the lede in a story about Amazon billionaire Jeff Bezos owning The Washington Post. It isn't quite profitable, you learn in the eighth paragraph: "The Post is on a pace to lose about $100 million in 2023, according to two people with knowledge of the company&rsquo;s finances."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The headline doesn't include that eye-grabbing detail. It's just this:</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">A Decade Ago, Jeff Bezos Bought a Newspaper. Now He&rsquo;s Paying Attention to It Again.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The Amazon founder, who purchased The Washington Post for $250 million in 2013, has taken a more active role in the paper&rsquo;s operations this year.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Yes, you can imagine he'd take a "more active role" with this nagging problem. Post employees were delighted a liberal billionaire bought the paper, so they didn't have to be too worried about profits. "Prestige journalism" for the liberals isn't working out right now, even as the paper extends its Trump obsession forward.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://www.newsmax.com/world/globaltalk/russia-lgbtq-transgender-procedures-banned/2023/07/24/id/1128275/"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.newsmax.com/world/globaltalk/russia-lgbtq-transgender-procedures-banned/2023/07/24/id/1128275/</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>Russian President Signs Legislation Marking the Final Step Outlawing Gender-affirming Procedures</strong></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Russian President Vladimir Putin signed new legislation Monday which marked the final step in outlawing gender-affirming procedures, a crippling blow to Russia&rsquo;s already embattled LGBTQ+ community.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The bill, which was approved unanimously by both houses of parliament, bans any &ldquo;medical interventions aimed at changing the sex of a person,&rdquo; as well as changing one&rsquo;s gender in official documents and public records. The only exception will be medical intervention to treat congenital anomalies.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">It also annuls marriages in which one person has &ldquo;changed gender&rdquo; and bars transgender people from becoming foster or adoptive parents.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The ban is said to stem from the Kremlin&rsquo;s crusade to protect what it views as the country&rsquo;s &ldquo;traditional values.&rdquo; Lawmakers say the legislation is to safeguard Russia against &ldquo;Western anti-family ideology,&rdquo; with some describing gender transitioning as &ldquo;pure satanism.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Russia&rsquo;s crackdown on LGBTQ+ people started a decade ago when Putin first proclaimed a focus on &ldquo;traditional family values,&rdquo; supported by the Russian Orthodox Church.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">In 2013, the Kremlin adopted legislation that banned any public endorsement of &ldquo;nontraditional sexual relations&rdquo; among minors. In 2020, Putin pushed through constitutional reform that outlawed same-sex marriage, and last year signed a law banning &ldquo;propaganda of nontraditional sexual relations&rdquo; among adults as well.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://www.breitbart.com/latin-america/2023/07/24/brazil-lula-limits-gun-rights-by-decree-hoping-for-disarmed-country/"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.breitbart.com/latin-america/2023/07/24/brazil-lula-limits-gun-rights-by-decree-hoping-for-disarmed-country/</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>Brazil: Lula Limits Gun Rights by Decree, Hoping for a &lsquo;Disarmed Country&rsquo;</strong></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Brazilian radical leftist President Luiz In&aacute;cio Lula da Silva signed a &ldquo;Responsible Gun Control&rdquo; decree this weekend to further restrict civilian access to firearms, rolling back policies implemented by former President Jair Bolsonaro.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The executive order, signed on Friday at the presidential Planalto Palace, forbids civilians from having access to certain types of firearms, reduces the total legal number of firearms a citizen may own, greatly reduces the annual amount of ammunition that civilians can legally buy, and imposes restrictions on shooting clubs and firearms for hunters, marksmen, and collectors.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The decree also establishes guidelines to transfer authority over the regulation and inspection of civilian firearms from the Brazilian army to the federal police, which will now exercise exclusive power over civilian activities involving weapons and ammunition in cooperation with the nation&rsquo;s Justice and Public Security Ministry.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">In a speech announcing the new regulations, Lula said, &ldquo;we cannot allow there to be arsenals of weapons in the hands of people.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">&ldquo;That is why we will continue to fight for a disarmed country,&rdquo; Lula said. &ldquo;It is the Brazilian police who have to be well armed, it is the Brazilian armed forces who have to be well armed. What we need to lower is the prices of books, and the price of access to cultural things that our children do not have access to.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Brazil&rsquo;s Minister of Justice Fl&aacute;vio Dino said that the new set of rules ends &ldquo;irresponsible armamentism&rdquo; as a result of Bolsonaro&rsquo;s gun rights reforms.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Civilians are now only allowed to purchase up to two firearms for self-defense, down from four, and must comply with a series of requirements to demonstrate proof of self-defense use. The total amount of ammunition that Brazilian citizens can buy per year has been reduced from 200 to 50 bullets.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The decree rolled back reforms Bolsonaro implemented that allowed civilians to purchase 9mm, .40, and .45 Automatic Colt Pistols (ACP), as well as semi-automatic smoothbore firearms. Brazilian citizens can no longer legally obtain these types of firearms.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The decree also reduces the duration of firearm registry permits from ten years to three to five years depending on the firearm&rsquo;s intended use. Active members of Brazil&rsquo;s police and other government security officials, meanwhile, no longer have to abide by any time limit on their permits.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Lula further imposed restrictions on firearms for hunters, marksmen, and collectors, reducing the total number of firearms and ammunition permitted in each category, introducing new required authorization permits for hunters, establishing new sub-categories for sports shooters, and reducing the number of firearms legally allowed for collectors from five of each model down to one weapon of each model, type, brand, variant, caliber, and origin.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">While the decree &ldquo;guarantees&rdquo; legal possession of these types of firearms if previously obtained and properly registered, the Brazilian government announced that it will implement a buyback program for these firearms this year.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The decree also imposes restrictions on sport shooting clubs, prohibiting 24-hour establishments and limiting operating hours from 6 a.m. to 10 p.m. Shooting clubs and instructional businesses must now be located at least one kilometer away from public or private schools, giving existing locations an 18-month grace period to comply with the new ruling.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The new gun control decree is the first part of a broader &ldquo;Security Action Program&rdquo; launched by Lula&rsquo;s administration on Friday. In addition to gun control, the Security Action Program, according to the Brazilian government, seeks to combat school violence, protect the Amazon region, and change regional public fund financing.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The program will also greatly increase penalties for crimes &ldquo;committed against the democratic rule of law,&rdquo; including longer prison sentences for those who organize, finance, or lead &ldquo;anti-democratic movements.&rdquo; It will also reportedly provide for the blocking of bank accounts and seizure of assets of people in whose cases law enforcement finds &ldquo;sufficient evidence of authorship or financing of crimes against the democratic state of law.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Now, to my favorite topic, sports!</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://thepostmillennial.com/breaking-lebron-james-18-year-old-son-suffers-heart-attack-on-basketball-court?utm_campaign=64487"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://thepostmillennial.com/breaking-lebron-james-18-year-old-son-suffers-heart-attack-on-basketball-court?utm_campaign=64487</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>Lebron James' 18-year-old son suffers heart attack on basketball court</strong></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">During a basketball workout at the University of Southern California, basketball legend Lebron James&rsquo; son, Bronny, was rushed to the hospital after suffering cardiac arrest.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">A family spokesperson told TMZ Sports, "Yesterday while practicing Bronny James suffered a cardiac arrest. Medical staff was able to treat Bronny and take him to the hospital. He is now in stable condition and no longer in ICU. We ask for respect and privacy for the James family and we will update media when there is more information."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">"LeBron and Savannah wish to publicly send their deepest thanks and appreciation to the USC medical and athletic staff for their incredible work and dedication to the safety of their athletes," the spokesperson added.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Sources with direct knowledge told the outlet that a 911 call was made at 9:26 am on Monday morning from USC&rsquo;s Galen Center, where the 18-year-old had fallen unconscious. He was taken by ambulance to a nearby hospital.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Sources said that it was a Code 3, in which first responders use lights and sirens during transport, indicating the seriousness of the incident.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Bronny had recently committed to the USC Trojans and is expected to play for the NBA like his father.</span></p>]]></description>
   <author><![CDATA[Garrison Hardie]]></author>
   <enclosure url="https://app.dropwave.io/episode/ae0c9ac6-2363-4677-853c-3b4d38a04c77/daily-news-brief-for-wednesday-july-26th-2023.mp3" length="806" type="audio/mp3"/>
   <guid isPermaLink="false"><![CDATA[ae0c9ac6-2363-4677-853c-3b4d38a04c77]]></guid>
   <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jul 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
   <source url=""><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></source>
   <itunes:author><![CDATA[Garrison Hardie]]></itunes:author>
   <itunes:image href="https://assets-cdn2.dropwave.io/2ab40ac0-e99d-4f25-a6d2-541d2c9b290a/cover-art/mUK8zsnHkCK3vep7E1W6UgYb9dTnLenASAMEFha3.jpg"/>
   <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
   <itunes:duration>806</itunes:duration>
   <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title><![CDATA[John 1:14 [Up and Ready]]]></title>
   <link/>
   <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
   <author><![CDATA[Mark Dewey]]></author>
   <enclosure url="https://app.dropwave.io/episode/9da63c31-505c-4f24-b8a2-2fcaba34cb88/john-114.mp3" length="268" type="audio/mp3"/>
   <guid isPermaLink="false"><![CDATA[9da63c31-505c-4f24-b8a2-2fcaba34cb88]]></guid>
   <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jul 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
   <source url=""><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></source>
   <itunes:author><![CDATA[Mark Dewey]]></itunes:author>
   <itunes:image href="https://assets-cdn2.dropwave.io/60c9e557-5882-401d-abb8-06de47904be4/cover-art/zZ8CYlYBUAUu8KNyZzjE092h2WlBblW8upM7tmFg.png"/>
   <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
   <itunes:duration>268</itunes:duration>
   <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title><![CDATA[The Antitypes to the False Cupid/ Snow White's New Mythos [Choc Knox Unplugged]]]></title>
   <link/>
   <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
   <author><![CDATA[Choc Knox & Jason Farley]]></author>
   <enclosure url="https://app.dropwave.io/episode/92d9f5fe-9d32-46c0-b669-6a4937304c9e/the-antitypes-to-the-false-cupid-snow-whites-new-mythos.mp3" length="7253" type="audio/mp3"/>
   <guid isPermaLink="false"><![CDATA[92d9f5fe-9d32-46c0-b669-6a4937304c9e]]></guid>
   <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jul 2023 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
   <source url=""><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></source>
   <itunes:author><![CDATA[Choc Knox & Jason Farley]]></itunes:author>
   <itunes:image href="https://assets-cdn2.dropwave.io/6123b54f-ab49-406c-9cba-a39f6730fc76/cover-art/ARuuU8PixHGkhNvgtHIHIGGJjBUPNwgZEkuaGqzL.png"/>
   <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
   <itunes:duration>7253</itunes:duration>
   <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title><![CDATA[Q Shaman (Jake Angeli-Chansley) on CrossPolitic [CrossPolitic Show]]]></title>
   <link/>
   <description><![CDATA[<p class="p1"><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Q Shaman (Jake Angeli-Chansley) on CrossPolitic</span></p>
<p class="p2">&nbsp;</p>
<p class="p1"><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Sign up for the FLF Conference at the Ark Encounter! (Oct 11-14)</span></p>
<p class="p3"><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><span class="s1"><a href="https://flfnetwork.com/the-politics-of-six-days-creation-conference/">https://flfnetwork.com/the-politics-of-six-days-creation-conference/</a></span><span class="s2">&nbsp;</span></span></p>
<p class="p2">&nbsp;</p>
<p class="p1"><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Support Us &amp; Sign up for a FLF Club Membership!<span class="Apple-converted-space">&nbsp;</span></span></p>
<p class="p3"><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><span class="s1"><a href="https://flfnetwork.com/product/fightlaughfestclub/?attribute_member-tier=silver-monthly">https://flfnetwork.com/product/fightlaughfestclub/?attribute_member-tier=silver-monthly</a></span><span class="s2"><span class="Apple-converted-space">&nbsp;</span></span></span></p>]]></description>
   <author><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></author>
   <enclosure url="https://app.dropwave.io/episode/b5f7ebc7-43d3-4435-92a3-03f37f3d4fa9/q-shaman-jake-angeli-chansley-on-crosspolitic.mp3" length="2861" type="audio/mp3"/>
   <guid isPermaLink="false"><![CDATA[b5f7ebc7-43d3-4435-92a3-03f37f3d4fa9]]></guid>
   <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jul 2023 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
   <source url=""><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></source>
   <itunes:author><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></itunes:author>
   <itunes:image href="https://assets-cdn2.dropwave.io/11635dce-94e7-41b8-9261-5c1fc2cc5ebe/cover-art/wvkjcfd3tfj69XopdryYkSF8m1k4KHuikzJF1KzC.jpg"/>
   <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
   <itunes:duration>2861</itunes:duration>
   <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title><![CDATA[In the World, Not of the World: Christians Working Worshipfully in the Public Square [Liberty Dispatch]]]></title>
   <link/>
   <description><![CDATA[<p class="p1"><strong>Liberty Dispatch</strong> ~ July 25, 2023<br />On this episode of&nbsp;<em>Liberty Dispatch</em>, host Andrew DeBartolo is joined by faithful Christian men working worshipfully in the public square. First, Andrew talks to Owner &amp; Creative Director at Kurios Creative Media, Thaddeus Maharaj, about creating great art for the glory of God. Next, pastor and bitcoiner Alin Armstrong joins him to speak about fiat money, Bitcoin, his newest projects, his new book and his new initiative. Finally, Ontario President of the Christian Heritage Party, Jim Enos, joins him to talk about glorifying God in the political arena.&nbsp;<br /><br /><strong style="font-family: '-apple-system', BlinkMacSystemFont, 'Segoe UI', Roboto, Oxygen, Ubuntu, Cantarell, 'Open Sans', 'Helvetica Neue', sans-serif;">[Interview 1] ft. Thaddeus Maharaj (08:54-31:44):</strong><br />Kurios Creative Media: <a href="https://kuriosmedia.com/">https://kuriosmedia.com/</a>&nbsp;<br />Theotivity Podcast: <a href="https://www.theotivity.com/">https://www.theotivity.com/</a>;<br /><br /><strong style="font-family: '-apple-system', BlinkMacSystemFont, 'Segoe UI', Roboto, Oxygen, Ubuntu, Cantarell, 'Open Sans', 'Helvetica Neue', sans-serif;">[Interview 2] ft. Alan Armstrong (33:04-53:11):<br /></strong>Bitcoin for Babies: <a href="https://www.lifegiverchurch.net/bitcoin-for-babies/">https://www.lifegiverchurch.net/bitcoin-for-babies/</a>;<br />"The Bible and Bitcoin" by Alin Armstrong: <a href="https://thebibleandbitcoin.lifegiverchurch.net/">https://thebibleandbitcoin.lifegiverchurch.net/</a>;<br /><br /><strong><strong style="font-family: '-apple-system', BlinkMacSystemFont, 'Segoe UI', Roboto, Oxygen, Ubuntu, Cantarell, 'Open Sans', 'Helvetica Neue', sans-serif;">[Interview 3] ft. Jim Enos (5405-01:18:08):</strong></strong><br />Jim's CHP Profile: <a href="https://www.chp.ca/candidates/jim-enos">https://www.chp.ca/candidates/jim-enos</a>;<br />ARPA v. Hamilton: <a href="https://arpacanada.ca/publication/arpa-v-hamilton/">https://arpacanada.ca/publication/arpa-v-hamilton/</a>;&nbsp;<br />ARPA v. Hamilton Reply: <a href="https://arpacanada.ca/publication/arpa-v-hamilton-reply/">https://arpacanada.ca/publication/arpa-v-hamilton-reply/</a>;&nbsp;<br /><br /><strong>SUPPORT OUR LEGAL ADVOCACY - Help us defend Canadians' God-given rights and liberties: </strong><a href="https://libertycoalitioncanada.com/donate/">https://libertycoalitioncanada.com/donate/</a>; <a href="https://libertycoalitioncanada.com/liberty-defense-fund/our-legal-strategy/;">https://libertycoalitioncanada.com/liberty-defense-fund/our-legal-strategy/;</a><br /><strong><br /></strong><strong>SHOW SPONSORS:<br /></strong><strong>Join&nbsp;<em>Red Balloon&nbsp;</em>Today!:</strong> <a href="https://www.redballoon.work/lcc;">https://www.redballoon.work/lcc;</a>&nbsp;<br /><strong>Invest with Rocklinc:</strong> <a href="mailto:info@rocklinc.com">info@rocklinc.com</a>&nbsp;or call them at 905-631-546;&nbsp;<br /><strong>Diversify Your Money with Bull Bitcoin:&nbsp;</strong><a href="https://mission.bullbitcoin.com/lcc">https://mission.bullbitcoin.com/lcc</a>;<br /><strong>BarterPay: </strong><a href="https://barterpay.ca/">https://barterpay.ca/</a>;&nbsp; <strong>Barter It: </strong><a href="https://vip.barterit.ca/launch;">https://vip.barterit.ca/launch; </a><strong><br />Carpe Fide - "Seize the Faith": Store: </strong><a href="https://carpe-fide.myshopify.com/">https://carpe-fide.myshopify.com</a><a href="https://carpe-fide.myshopify.com/">/</a>, use Promo Code LCC10 for 10% off (US Store Only), or shop Canadian @ <a href="https://canadacarpefide.myshopify.com/">https://canadacarpefide.myshopify.com/</a> | <strong>Podcast: </strong><a href="https://www.carpefide.com/episodes">https://www.carpefide.com/episodes</a>;<br /><br /><strong>Sick of Mainstream Media Lies? Help Support Independent Media! DONATE TO LCC TODAY!:&nbsp;</strong><strong><a href="https://libertycoalitioncanada.com/donate/">https://libertycoalitioncanada.com/donate/</a>&nbsp;</strong><strong>&nbsp;<br /><br /></strong></p>
<p class="p1">Please Support us in bringing you honest, truthful reporting and analysis from a Christian perspective.<br /><br /><strong>SUBSCRIBE TO OUR SHOWS/CHANNELS:<br /></strong>LIBERTY DISPATCH PODCAST: <a href="https://libertydispatch.podbean.com">https://libertydispatch.podbean.com</a>; <a href="https://rumble.com/c/c-1687093">https://rumble.com/LDshow</a>;&nbsp;<br />OPEN MIKE WITH MICHAEL THIESSEN: <a href="https://openmikewithmichaelthiessen.podbean.com">https://openmikewithmichaelthiessen.podbean.com</a>; <a href="https://rumble.com/c/c-1412501">https://rumble.com/openmike</a>;<br />THE OTHER CLUB: <a href="https://rumble.com/c/c-2541984">https://rumble.com/c/c-2541984</a>;&nbsp;<br />THE LIBERTY LOUNGE WITH TIM TYSOE: <a href="https://rumble.com/LLwTT">https://rumble.com/LLwTT</a>;<br /><br /><strong>CONTACT US:</strong><br />Questions/comments about podcasts/news/analysis: <a href="mailto:mailbag@libertycoalitioncanada.com">mailbag@libertycoalitioncanada.com</a>;<br />Questions/comments about donations: <a href="mailto:give@libertycoalitioncanada.com">give@libertycoalitioncanada.com</a>;<br />Questions/comments that are church-related: <a href="mailto:churches@libertycoalitioncanada.com">churches@libertycoalitioncanada.com</a>;<br />General Inquiries: <a href="mailto:info@libertycoalitioncanada.com">info@libertycoalitioncanada.com</a>.&nbsp;</p>
<p class="p1"><strong>STAY UP-TO-DATE ON ALL THINGS LCC:<br /></strong>Gab: <a href="https://gab.com/libertycoalitioncanada">https://gab.com/libertycoalitioncanada</a>&nbsp;</p>
<p class="p2">Telegram: <a href="https://t.me/libertycoalitioncanadanews">https://t.me/libertycoalitioncanadanews</a>&nbsp;</p>
<p class="p2">Instagram: <a href="https://instagram.com/libertycoalitioncanada">https://instagram.com/libertycoalitioncanada</a>&nbsp;</p>
<p class="p2">Facebook: <a href="https://facebook.com/LibertyCoalitionCanada">https://facebook.com/LibertyCoalitionCanada</a>&nbsp;</p>
<p class="p2">Twitter: @LibertyCCanada - <a href="https://twitter.com/LibertyCCanada">https://twitter.com/LibertyCCanada</a>&nbsp;</p>
<p class="p2">Rumble: <a href="https://rumble.com/user/LibertyCoalitionCanada">https://rumble.com/user/LibertyCoalitionCanada</a>&nbsp;</p>
<p class="p2">YouTube: <a href="https://www.youtube.com/@liberty4canada">https://www.youtube.com/@liberty4canada</a> -&nbsp;<strong>WE GOT CANCELLED AGAIN!!!</strong></p>
<p class="p1"><strong>Please LIKE, SUBSCRIBE, RATE &amp; REVIEW and SHARE it with others!</strong></p>]]></description>
   <author><![CDATA[Matthew Hallick, Andrew DeBartolo, SDG Media, Alin Armstrong, Thaddeaus Maharaj]]></author>
   <enclosure url="https://app.dropwave.io/episode/4e7948c2-a731-438f-ad89-11480368c1d9/in-the-world-not-of-the-world-christians-working-worshipfully-in-the-public-square.mp3" length="4928" type="audio/mp3"/>
   <guid isPermaLink="false"><![CDATA[4e7948c2-a731-438f-ad89-11480368c1d9]]></guid>
   <pubDate>Tue, 25 Jul 2023 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
   <source url=""><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></source>
   <itunes:author><![CDATA[Matthew Hallick, Andrew DeBartolo, SDG Media, Alin Armstrong, Thaddeaus Maharaj]]></itunes:author>
   <itunes:image href="https://prod-assets-spc1.nyc3.digitaloceanspaces.com/69893365-4165-4498-b0ac-e9ddf57a000f/cover-art/E86eLfK3NgjrpuXtk9kW9Qv6KcfzQpkJpToltreR.png"/>
   <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
   <itunes:duration>4928</itunes:duration>
   <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title><![CDATA[Athanasius [Resistance and Reformation]]]></title>
   <link/>
   <description><![CDATA[<p>More from Dr. George Grant</p>
<p><a href="https://georgegrant.net/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" data-callout-id="edit_links_in_description">https://georgegrant.net/</a>&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Adoring God Foundation&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://adoringgod.org/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" data-callout-id="edit_links_in_description">https://adoringgod.org/</a></p>]]></description>
   <author><![CDATA[George Grant]]></author>
   <enclosure url="https://app.dropwave.io/episode/b59ea499-2bf1-4c00-94e4-78390c3ba1ac/athanasius.mp3" length="499" type="audio/mp3"/>
   <guid isPermaLink="false"><![CDATA[b59ea499-2bf1-4c00-94e4-78390c3ba1ac]]></guid>
   <pubDate>Tue, 25 Jul 2023 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
   <source url=""><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></source>
   <itunes:author><![CDATA[George Grant]]></itunes:author>
   <itunes:image href="https://assets-cdn2.dropwave.io/261ebdbb-5a5a-4650-ba2c-8c138886911b/cover-art/fEPh0pqkjOi1hWn2VDTvgRSsw3nOsdOFIBOfEGEP.png"/>
   <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
   <itunes:duration>499</itunes:duration>
   <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title><![CDATA[Daily News Brief for Tuesday, July 25th, 2023 [Daily News Brief]]]></title>
   <link/>
   <description><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">This is Garrison Hardie with your CrossPolitic Daily News Brief for Tuesday, July 25th, 2023.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>Fight Laugh Feast Conference - Ark Encounter</strong></span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">This year, our Fight Laugh Feast Conference is at the Ark Encounter in Kentucky on The Politics of Six Day Creation. The politics of six day creation is the difference between a fixed standard of justice and a careening standard of justice, the difference between the corrosive relativism that creates mobs and anarchy and the freedom of objectivity, truth, and due process. The politics of six day creation establishes the authority and sufficiency of God&rsquo;s Word for all of life: from what is a man or a woman, when does human life begin, and how is human society best organized?</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Come hear Ken Ham, Pastor Doug Wilson, Dr. Ben Merkle, Dr. Gordon Wilson, me and more, and of course a live CrossPolitic show! Mark your calendars for October 11th-14th, as we fight, laugh, and feast, with beer &amp; psalms, our amazing lineup of speakers, our Rowdy Christian Merch, and a Sabbath Feast to wrap up the occasion. Maybe an infant baptism while we&rsquo;re at it! Visit fightlaughfeast.com for more information!</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">We start today at the southern border&hellip;&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://justthenews.com/government/security/biden-has-border-terrorism-problem-encounters-flagged-aliens-explode-nine-fold"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://justthenews.com/government/security/biden-has-border-terrorism-problem-encounters-flagged-aliens-explode-nine-fold</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>Biden has a border terrorism problem as encounters with flagged aliens explode ninefold</strong></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The number of foreigners on the U.S. terrorist screening list who have tried illegally crossing into the United States has exploded ninefold since President Joe Biden took office, an alarming increase that experts say puts national security at risk.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">So far in fiscal 2023, 140 people on the terror list have been apprehended between ports of entry, already crushing last year&rsquo;s record of 98.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">There were only three such crossings in the last year of Donald Trump&rsquo;s presidency, and 16 in Biden&rsquo;s first year.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The rapid growth in crossings by illegal aliens with terror ties is a warning sign that countries with bad intent may be trying to sneak potential terror cells into the United States, experts told Just the News.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Added Mark Morgan, the former acting commissioner of the Customs Border Protection agency: &ldquo;We literally could have the next terrorist sleeper cell in United States planning a terrorist attack, and we would have no idea.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The pattern also has alarmed Congress, which began an investigation earlier this summer. Lawmakers said they are particularly concerned that there have been 1.5 million gotaways who have never been encountered illegally crossing the border, raising the possibility there are many more potential terrorists already in the country.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">&ldquo;These &lsquo;known gotaways&rsquo; do not provide biometric or biographic information to USBP agents and continue their journey into the interior of the country without background checks against law enforcement databases,&rdquo; Reps. Jim Jordan, James Comer and Mark Green wrote in a recent letter to Homeland Security Secretary Alejandro Mayorkas.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Jordan, Comer and Green chair three of the most powerful committees in Congress: Judiciary, Oversight and Homeland Security.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">&nbsp;</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The lawmakers also cited a recent change in language by the Homeland Security Department, raising concerns that some illegal aliens with terror ties may not have been deported.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Concerns have been exacerbated by the recent revelation the Biden released an illegal alien with known terrorism ties, and it took two weeks to apprehend him.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://justthenews.com/politics-policy/coronavirus/china-publishes-then-deletes-official-covid-data-indicating-over-1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://justthenews.com/politics-policy/coronavirus/china-publishes-then-deletes-official-covid-data-indicating-over-1</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>China publishes then deletes official COVID data indicating over 1 million more deaths than reported</strong></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">While Beijing has claimed about 83,700 people have died in China since the start of the COVID-19 pandemic, the Zhejiang provincial government published and quickly deleted official data indicating the true death toll is significantly higher.&nbsp;&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The Zhejiang government deleted the data last week just days after it was published, but epidemiologists who reviewed the information said it was the latest indication that China's official death toll is vastly undercounted, according to The New York Times.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Provincial data shows that the number of cremations rose to 171,000 in the first quarter of 2023, which is 72,000 more cremations than the same period last year when China's stringent COVID mandates were still in place.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">China has only acknowledged about 83,700 deaths in total.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">An analysis earlier this year from the New York paper estimated that China's most recent wave of COVID, which started late last year, may have resulted in between one million and 1.5 million deaths.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Experts say the data from Zhejiang, which has a population of 65.8 million people, when extrapolated to China's population of 1.4 billion, is consistent with earlier mortality estimates.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">"I&rsquo;m not sure the impact would have been exactly the same in every province, but I think it would be useful for a rough extrapolation," University of Hong Kong epidemiologist Ben Cowling said. "It&rsquo;s consistent with the estimates of around 1.5 million."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Over to Portland we go&hellip;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://thepostmillennial.com/former-kmart-in-portland-that-became-a-homeless-squat-burns-down-in-huge-fire?utm_campaign=64487"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://thepostmillennial.com/former-kmart-in-portland-that-became-a-homeless-squat-burns-down-in-huge-fire?utm_campaign=64487</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>Former Kmart in Portland that became a homeless squat burns down in huge fire</strong></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">An abandoned Kmart store that homeless vagrants have been using as their temporary home in Portland, Oregon was riddled by a massive fire on Wednesday, authorities say.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Portland Fire Bureau spokesperson Rick Graves told The Oregonian that it was only a matter of time before the site was set ablaze.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">"We know this structure," Graves asserted. "We've known this has been vacant for some time &hellip; [with] people gaining occupancy and using it as their home."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Several complaints from nearby residents have recently been made towards the city over the building's accessibility and draw for homeless individuals, trash, and debris. The most recent complaint, filed on July 6, prompted a city inspection, which is currently ongoing.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">It is unknown at this moment if anyone was trapped inside the structure when the fire broke out on Wednesday morning. No known injuries exist, authorities say.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Firefighters were able to gain control of the blaze on Wednesday morning, with Graves explaining that the "major challenge" in controlling the fire was a lack of water supply due to a lack of water hydrants in the area, according to the outlet.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">A nearby resident, 67-year-old Laurel McAfee, told reporters that huge bunches of ash were scattered throughout the yard of her home.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">McAfee said the initial "boom" was so loud she had "thought maybe a car had hit a building or something."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The cause of Wednesday&rsquo;s fire has not yet been identified.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">So while Portland is continuing it&rsquo;s decent into Mordor status, Disney does the same!</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://notthebee.com/article/disneys-new-snow-white-its-not-1937-shes-not-gonna-be-saved-by-the-prince-and-shes-not-going-to-be-dreaming-about-true-love-shes-dreaming-about-becoming-the-leader-she-knows-she-can-be?fbclid=IwAR1-Lnh2oHRUkC7B62wlOx4v6tQukl3sn81zXp26vGDGzM5Ct6Uazpd4UJg"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://notthebee.com/article/disneys-new-snow-white-its-not-1937-shes-not-gonna-be-saved-by-the-prince-and-shes-not-going-to-be-dreaming-about-true-love-shes-dreaming-about-becoming-the-leader-she-knows-she-can-be?fbclid=IwAR1-Lnh2oHRUkC7B62wlOx4v6tQukl3sn81zXp26vGDGzM5Ct6Uazpd4UJg</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>Disney's new Snow White: "It's not 1937. She&rsquo;s not gonna be saved by the prince and she&rsquo;s not going to be dreaming about true love. She&rsquo;s dreaming about becoming the leader she knows she can be."</strong></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Another remake that's here to smash the patriarchy.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://twitter.com/i/status/1683121280390660097"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://twitter.com/i/status/1683121280390660097</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> - Play Video&nbsp;</span></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">How many billions will this Snow White remake cost Disney?</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Good luck with that Disney! In other entertainment news&hellip;&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://www.breitbart.com/entertainment/2023/07/20/nolte-sound-of-freedom-crosses-100-million-mark/"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.breitbart.com/entertainment/2023/07/20/nolte-sound-of-freedom-crosses-100-million-mark/</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>&lsquo;Sound of Freedom&rsquo; Crosses $100 Million Mark</strong></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Thanks to a Wednesday haul of another $4.5 million, Angel Studios&rsquo; Sound of Freedom has crossed the magic $100 million mark at the domestic box office.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">&ldquo;Angel Studios, the platform empowering filmmakers with full creative control to crowdfund and create, has reached a new theatrical milestone,&rdquo; the studio said in a statement released Thursday. &ldquo;Its independent summer hit, SOUND of FREEDOM. has now sold over 8.9 million tickets, and the film has now passed $100M in box office revenue.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">&ldquo;Since the films&rsquo; July 4 release, SOUND of FREEDOM has never left the top 3 positions on the charts[.]&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">On Wednesday, after 16 days of release, Sound of Freedom also managed to nearly top Mission: Impossible &mdash; Dead Reckoning Part One once again, which is only in its eighth day of release &mdash; $4.37 million for Dead Reckoning&rsquo;s Wednesday haul compared to Sound of Freedom&rsquo;s $4.5 million.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">As Breitbart News reported Tuesday, Tom Cruise&rsquo;s seventh outing as Ethan Hunt enjoys the advantage of playing in 1,000+ more screens&mdash;4,327 to 3,265. So, as far as packing in the crowds on a per-screen average, Jim Caviezel&rsquo;s $14.5 million movie is beating Tom Cruise&rsquo;s $250 to $300 million blockbuster, and doing so after being in wide release a week longer.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Currently, Sound of Freedom is the second most popular movie in the country and there are no signs it will slow down. Barbie and Oppenheimer open this weekend, but just as we saw with Dead Reckoning the previous weekend, Sound of Freedom is operating in a lane all of its own. The anti-child trafficking movie (a topic the pro-grooming left finds offensive and controversial) is bringing normal people back to movie theaters. all kinds of people who long ago divorced mainstream Hollywood and have or intend to see Sound of Freedom. Top Gun: Maverick did the same last year.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Normal people are craving normal entertainment. No gay sex. No smug lectures about the patriarchy. No deconstructing our heroes. No Mary Sues. Normal people want good stories created around interesting and complicated characters. Hollywood did this without breaking a sweat for a hundred years. Now a normal movie is an exception in an ocean of woketardery, shaming, and the normalization of destructive perversions.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">By all accounts, Sound of Freedom is a quality movie about an important subject that&rsquo;s making a fortune and driving the left-wing establishment crazy.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">It doesn&rsquo;t get any better than that.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">I suspect Disney will soon produce a remake where the sex traffickers are the heroes rescuing children from their traditional parents. Yes, the liberation of gay sex to unshackle the suffocating tenets of the Christian Faith. Coming soon to an empty theater near you.</span></p>]]></description>
   <author><![CDATA[Garrison Hardie]]></author>
   <enclosure url="https://app.dropwave.io/episode/f11f99ea-3d1c-4fc3-856e-9b547a683666/daily-news-brief-for-tuesday-july-25th-2023.mp3" length="699" type="audio/mp3"/>
   <guid isPermaLink="false"><![CDATA[f11f99ea-3d1c-4fc3-856e-9b547a683666]]></guid>
   <pubDate>Tue, 25 Jul 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
   <source url=""><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></source>
   <itunes:author><![CDATA[Garrison Hardie]]></itunes:author>
   <itunes:image href="https://assets-cdn2.dropwave.io/2ab40ac0-e99d-4f25-a6d2-541d2c9b290a/cover-art/mUK8zsnHkCK3vep7E1W6UgYb9dTnLenASAMEFha3.jpg"/>
   <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
   <itunes:duration>699</itunes:duration>
   <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
  </item>
 </channel>
</rss>
