<?xml version="1.0"?>
<?xml-stylesheet href="/storage/feed-stylesheet.xsl" type="text/xsl"?>

<rss xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
 <channel>
  <title><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></title>
  <link>https://dropwave.io</link>
  <description><![CDATA[FIGHT LAUGH FEAST PRESENTS SHOWS PROCLAIMING THE LORDSHIP OF CHRIST OVER ALL OF LIFE.
]]></description>
  <language>en</language>
  <managingEditor><![CDATA[fightlaughfeast@gmail.com (FLF, LLC)]]></managingEditor>
  <webMaster><![CDATA[support@dropwave.io (DropWave Support)]]></webMaster>
  <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2023 01:25:46 +0000</pubDate>
  <lastBuildDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2023 01:25:46 +0000</lastBuildDate>
  <image>
   <url>https://is4-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Podcasts113/v4/58/56/52/5856525c-2973-cf29-3db9-21faa8595391/mza_1144696925612154085.png/1200x1200bb.jpg</url>
   <link>https://dropwave.io</link>
   <title><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></title>
  </image>
  <itunes:author><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></itunes:author>
  <itunes:image href="https://is4-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Podcasts113/v4/58/56/52/5856525c-2973-cf29-3db9-21faa8595391/mza_1144696925612154085.png/1200x1200bb.jpg"/>
  <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
  <itunes:owner>
   <itunes:name><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></itunes:name>
   <itunes:email>fightlaughfeast@gmail.com</itunes:email>
  </itunes:owner>
  <itunes:category text="News"/>
  <item>
   <title><![CDATA[Daily News Brief for Wednesday, June 28th, 2023 [Daily News Brief]]]></title>
   <link>https://app.dropwave.io/episode/5eb0c00b-37ea-416b-b9ca-eef94a81271e/daily-news-brief-for-wednesday-june-28th-2023.mp3</link>
   <description><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">This is Garrison Hardie with your CrossPolitic Daily News Brief for Wednesday, June 28th, 2023.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>Armored Republic</strong></span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The Mission of Armored Republic is to Honor Christ by equipping Free Men with Tools of Liberty necessary to preserve God-given rights. In the Armored Republic there is no King but Christ. We are Free Craftsmen. Body Armor is a Tool of Liberty. We create Tools of Liberty. Free men must remain ever vigilant against tyranny wherever it appears. God has given us the tools of liberty needed to defend the rights He bestowed to us. Armored Republic is honored to offer you those Tools. Visit them, at ar500armor.com</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Before we get to the news, how about a little on this day in history?&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">On this day in history June 28th:</span></p>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">1776 Final draft of Declaration of Independence submitted to Continental Congress</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">1778 Battle of Monmouth, New Jersey (General Washington beats Clinton)</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">1820 Tomato is proven to be non-poisonous by Colonel Robert Gibbon eating a tomato on steps of courthouse in Salem, New Jersey</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">1838 Coronation of Queen Victoria in Westminster Abbey, London</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">1870 U.S. Congress creates federal holidays (New Year's Day, Independence Day, Thanksgiving Day, and Christmas Day), initially applicable only to federal employees</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">1894 Labor Day established as a holiday for US federal employees</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">1902 Germany, Italy, and the Austro-Hungarian Empire renew their Triple Alliance for six more years</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">1910 1st airship with passengers makes its maiden voyage; the Zeppelin LZ7-Deutscheland and gets stuck in some trees in Mount Limberg, Lower Saxony, injuring one crew member</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">1919 Treaty of Versailles, ending WWI and establishing the League of Nations, is signed in France</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">1965 1st US ground combat forces in Vietnam authorized by President Lyndon B. Johnson</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">1996 Remake of "The Nutty Professor" starring Eddie Murphy opens in theaters in the USA</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">2000 NBA Draft: Cincinnati power forward Kenyon Martin first pick by New Jersey Nets</span></li>
</ul>
<p><br /><br /></p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://dailycaller.com/2023/06/27/nyc-shelters-homeless-people-migrants/"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://dailycaller.com/2023/06/27/nyc-shelters-homeless-people-migrants/</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>NYC Is Housing More Illegal Migrants Than Homeless People</strong></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The number of migrants in New York City&rsquo;s care has outpaced the homeless population in local shelters, according to NBC4 New York.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">As of Sunday, the city had 50,000 migrants in its care, including in local hotels and temporary shelters, and 49,700 local homeless residents, NBC4 reported. The influx of migrants crossing the southern border illegally has led to more migrants arriving in the Big Apple, some of whom have been bused in by Republican Texas Gov. Greg Abbott.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The city has turned the historic Roosevelt Hotel, which closed three years ago, into a migrant shelter.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">&ldquo;My heart breaks a little bit, and I have these conflicting feelings,&rdquo; Deputy Mayor Anne Williams-Isom said during a tour of the hotel, according to NBC4.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Democratic New York City Mayor Eric Adams has floated asking his residents to help shelter migrants in their homes, he said in early June.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">&ldquo;It is my vision to take the next step to this, to go to the faith-based locales and then move to private residents, there are residents who are suffering right now because of economic challenges,&rdquo; Adams said at the time.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">&ldquo;They have spare rooms, they have locales and if we can find a way to get over the 30-day rule and other rules that government has in its place, we can take that $4.2 billion, $4.3 maybe now, that we potentially will have to spend, and we can put it back in the pockets of everyday New Yorkers, everyday houses of worship, instead of putting it in the pockets of corporations,&rdquo; Adams added.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Adams has also taken matters into his own hands by busing some of the arriving migrants to New York suburbs, including an area near the northern border, where the Daily Caller News Foundation previously observed some of them crossing into Canada illegally. Adams has also transported dozens of migrants to Republican-run states, like Florida and Texas, South America and one to China, Politico reported Friday.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Adams&rsquo; office didn&rsquo;t immediately respond to a request for comment.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://dailycaller.com/2023/06/26/fox-news-fires-remaining-tucker-staffers/"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://dailycaller.com/2023/06/26/fox-news-fires-remaining-tucker-staffers/</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>Fox News Fires Remaining Tucker Staffers In Show&rsquo;s Final Stroke</strong></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Fox News has fired the remaining staffers from Tucker Carlson&rsquo;s show as the network announces a new primetime lineup, Daily Caller confirmed Monday.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The network let go of at least nine remaining staffers, including long-standing producers, in a move described as &ldquo;shockingly callous&rdquo; by one former Fox News producer who spoke to the Daily Caller.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">&ldquo;Some of the producers fired have been at Fox for well over a decade,&rdquo; the producer told the Daily Caller.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Another former Fox producer told the Daily Caller that staffers on Carlson&rsquo;s team were repeatedly told following his departure that their jobs were safe, including as recently as last week when two of Carlson&rsquo;s producers left the network.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The remaining staffers were told they could apply for any jobs throughout the company, the former producer told the Daily Caller, noting that employees who once staffed Bill O&rsquo;Reilly and Dan Bongino&rsquo;s show were simply reassigned on other shows after both hosts left the network.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Staffers told the former producer the terminations were clearly an &ldquo;anti-Tucker move to purge any of his remaining stamp he had on the network as Fox begins this new lineup change.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The news comes after Fox News announced that Jesse Watters will replace Carlson in the 8:00 p.m. time slot.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Watters, who originally started his career at the 8:00 p.m. time slot hosting a Man on the Street segment during Bill O&rsquo;Reilly&rsquo;s program, is slated to take over the hour, Fox News said in a press release.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Laura Ingraham will take over Watters&rsquo; 7:00 p.m. time slot while Greg Gutfeld will move his show to the 10:00 p.m. time slot. Sean Hannity will remain in his 9:00 p.m. slot.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Fox announced in late April it was parting ways with Carlson just days after the network announced it was also parting ways with Dan Bongino. Carlson has since started hosting his own show on Twitter, prompting a public legal battle between Fox News and the Daily Caller co-founder.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Fox News issued a &ldquo;cease and desist&rdquo; to Carlson in mid-June after accusing him of breaching his contract by violating its non-compete clause when he posted the first episode of his show on Twitter.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://www.npr.org/2023/06/27/1149982782/julian-sands-dead-a-room-with-a-view"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.npr.org/2023/06/27/1149982782/julian-sands-dead-a-room-with-a-view</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>Actor Julian Sands found dead in California after going missing on hike</strong></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The San Bernardino County Sheriff's office has confirmed the death of Julian Sands after human remains were found on Southern California's Mount Baldy. He was 65 years old.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">He was hiking Mount Baldy when his family reported him missing on January 13, 2023.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Sands had a wide and varied career but was best known for his role in the 1985 movie A Room with a View, starring opposite Helena Bonham Carter.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Sands learned acting at the Central School of Speech and Drama in London. In A Room with a View, he played George Emerson, a love interest to the young upper-class Lucy Honeychurch, played by Carter. In 1986, he told NPR in an interview that he was well aware of the class dynamics at play in the movie. "Nobody's actually seen to do anything other than live some leisurely life which allows them to pursue their own indulgences," he said.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Sands' acting career brought him an eclectic array of roles. His film credits include Arachnophobia, Leaving Las Vegas, and the Jackie Chan movie The Medallion. On TV, he appeared in small roles on shows such as Castle, Smallville and Dexter. In Season 5 of the action drama 24, he played the main villain Vladimir Bierko, a terrorist in possession of a deadly nerve gas.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">He loved the outdoors. In a 2020 interview with The Guardian, he was asked when he was happiest. His answer was: "Close to a mountain summit on a glorious cold morning."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Now in entertainment news&hellip;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://boundingintocomics.com/2023/06/26/the-flash-collapses-in-its-second-weekend-at-the-box-office-with-massive-72-drop-analyst-predicts-film-will-lose-at-least-150-million/"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://boundingintocomics.com/2023/06/26/the-flash-collapses-in-its-second-weekend-at-the-box-office-with-massive-72-drop-analyst-predicts-film-will-lose-at-least-150-million/</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>&lsquo;The Flash&rsquo; Collapses In Its Second Weekend At The Box Office With Massive 72% Drop, Analyst Predicts Film Will Lose At Least $150 Million</strong></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Ezra Miller&rsquo;s The Flash completely collapsed at the box office with an enormous 72% drop from its opening weekend.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The Flash had a long row to hoe after it&rsquo;s extremely poor opening weekend of $55 million at the domestic box office. And it does not look like it&rsquo;s going to be reaping anything but losses following its second weekend collapse of 72%.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The-Numbers reports the film only grossed $15.2 million in its second weekend despite adding another 22 more theaters compared to its first weekend. The per theater gross declined from $13,000 in its opening weekend to $3,587 in its second weekend.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The film&rsquo;s second weekend much like its first underperformed predictions. Box office tracking website Box Office Pro predicted the film would have a 69% drop and bring in $17.3 million.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The-Numbers predicted the film would only have a 59% decline and would bring in $22.5 million.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Comparing the film to other DCEU films, The Flash is one of the worst performing films as it stands right now. The only films it&rsquo;s outperformed at the worldwide box office are Birds of Prey, The Suicide Squad, Wonder Woman 1984, and Shazam! Fury of the Gods.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Following this second weekend, box office analyst OMB Reviews predicts The Flash will only bring in a total gross between $300 million to $400 million worldwide in its entire theatrical run.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">However, he goes on to note, &ldquo;roughly between $300 and $350 million dollars if the film performs as a typical bad movie.&rdquo; That means it will likely stay in the same position it is on the DCEU list given Shazam! grossed $363.5 million and Black Adam brought in $391.2 million.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">OMB Reviews then points to the reported cost of the film being between $200 million and $220 million. He notes this means the film will likely lose around $150 million due to his estimated predictions that the film&rsquo;s total cost with marketing is approximately $330 million. Factoring in the film&rsquo;s split with theaters, he predicts the film&rsquo;s break even point is $550 million.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Thus if the film performs at the top of his estimates at $400 million, it would lose $150 million.</span></p>]]></description>
   <author><![CDATA[Garrison Hardie]]></author>
   <enclosure url="https://app.dropwave.io/episode/5eb0c00b-37ea-416b-b9ca-eef94a81271e/daily-news-brief-for-wednesday-june-28th-2023.mp3" length="728" type="audio/mp3"/>
   <guid isPermaLink="false"><![CDATA[5eb0c00b-37ea-416b-b9ca-eef94a81271e]]></guid>
   <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
   <source url=""><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></source>
   <itunes:author><![CDATA[Garrison Hardie]]></itunes:author>
   <itunes:image href="https://assets-cdn2.dropwave.io/2ab40ac0-e99d-4f25-a6d2-541d2c9b290a/cover-art/hUZu1H9lrRY0wXg66WHC8eLwYBA3hbRNTAHQmHt2.png"/>
   <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
   <itunes:duration>728</itunes:duration>
   <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title><![CDATA[Psalm 73:1,25-28 [Up and Ready]]]></title>
   <link>https://app.dropwave.io/episode/83ae5073-3f04-4a4c-9561-9b23d1a23c8a/psalm-73125-28.mp3</link>
   <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
   <author><![CDATA[Mark Dewey]]></author>
   <enclosure url="https://app.dropwave.io/episode/83ae5073-3f04-4a4c-9561-9b23d1a23c8a/psalm-73125-28.mp3" length="252" type="audio/mp3"/>
   <guid isPermaLink="false"><![CDATA[83ae5073-3f04-4a4c-9561-9b23d1a23c8a]]></guid>
   <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
   <source url=""><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></source>
   <itunes:author><![CDATA[Mark Dewey]]></itunes:author>
   <itunes:image href="https://assets-cdn2.dropwave.io/60c9e557-5882-401d-abb8-06de47904be4/cover-art/zZ8CYlYBUAUu8KNyZzjE092h2WlBblW8upM7tmFg.png"/>
   <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
   <itunes:duration>252</itunes:duration>
   <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title><![CDATA[Wrapping up Q&A on the Ten Commandments [The Ezra Institute Podcast for Cultural Reformation]]]></title>
   <link>https://app.dropwave.io/episode/d6361114-42ae-482a-9919-012430cf7325/wrapping-up-qa-on-the-ten-commandments.mp3</link>
   <description><![CDATA[<p>Joe Boot and Nate Wright are back again to answer a few lingering questions resulting from the Ten Commandments podcast series. In this episode we consider how the earliest humans married and reproduced, compared with later Mosaic incest laws. We also tackle questions on how the church and the individual ought to think and act with regard to charitable status, tax exemption, and the administration of tithes and offerings.</p>
<p><a href="https://www.ezrainstitute.com/training-programs/worldview-leadership-academy/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">This is the final week to apply for a scholarship to the Worldview Leadership</a></p>]]></description>
   <author><![CDATA[Joe Boot, Ryan Eras, Nate Wright]]></author>
   <enclosure url="https://app.dropwave.io/episode/d6361114-42ae-482a-9919-012430cf7325/wrapping-up-qa-on-the-ten-commandments.mp3" length="3159" type="audio/mp3"/>
   <guid isPermaLink="false"><![CDATA[d6361114-42ae-482a-9919-012430cf7325]]></guid>
   <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2023 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
   <source url=""><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></source>
   <itunes:author><![CDATA[Joe Boot, Ryan Eras, Nate Wright]]></itunes:author>
   <itunes:image href="https://assets-cdn2.dropwave.io/1c3a97bd-65b0-4aec-bb35-3a1b6eec5d2c/cover-art/4rDIhLUsGj1xuXpLJYNdtwtbungA78glNHA7dOd9.png"/>
   <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
   <itunes:duration>3159</itunes:duration>
   <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title><![CDATA[Comedian, Actor, Protestor, Christian - Arrested for Making a Stand [CrossPolitic Show]]]></title>
   <link>https://app.dropwave.io/episode/8d3f6e6d-8b9c-4bd8-9596-1b3e35967254/comedian-actor-protestor-christian-arrested-for-making-a-stand.mp3</link>
   <description><![CDATA[<p class="p1"><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Comedian, Actor, Protestor, Christian - Arrested for Making a Stand</span></p>
<p class="p2">&nbsp;</p>
<p class="p1"><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">J. Emilio Martinez honed his comedy craft as a performer in the LA improv scene, working with the likes of Bob Odenkirk, Andy Dick, Kathy Griffin and Jennifer Coolidge.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p class="p1"><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Enter Cancel Culture&hellip;Emilio now works to battle against mainstream news and the narratives they push to stoke the woke mob.</span></p>
<p class="p2">&nbsp;</p>
<p class="p1"><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Loor TV (Support Emilio&rsquo;s Projects!)</span></p>
<p class="p3"><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><span class="s1"><a href="https://www.loor.tv/">https://www.loor.tv/</a></span><span class="s2">&nbsp;</span></span></p>
<p class="p2">&nbsp;</p>
<p class="p1"><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Sign up for the FLF Conference at the Ark Encounter! (Oct 11-14)</span></p>
<p class="p3"><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><span class="s1"><a href="https://flfnetwork.com/the-politics-of-six-days-creation-conference/">https://flfnetwork.com/the-politics-of-six-days-creation-conference/</a></span><span class="s2">&nbsp;</span></span></p>
<p class="p3">&nbsp;</p>]]></description>
   <author><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></author>
   <enclosure url="https://app.dropwave.io/episode/8d3f6e6d-8b9c-4bd8-9596-1b3e35967254/comedian-actor-protestor-christian-arrested-for-making-a-stand.mp3" length="2734" type="audio/mp3"/>
   <guid isPermaLink="false"><![CDATA[8d3f6e6d-8b9c-4bd8-9596-1b3e35967254]]></guid>
   <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2023 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
   <source url=""><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></source>
   <itunes:author><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></itunes:author>
   <itunes:image href="https://assets-cdn2.dropwave.io/11635dce-94e7-41b8-9261-5c1fc2cc5ebe/cover-art/wvkjcfd3tfj69XopdryYkSF8m1k4KHuikzJF1KzC.jpg"/>
   <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
   <itunes:duration>2734</itunes:duration>
   <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title><![CDATA[Adults EXPOSE Themselves to Children at State-funded and State-sanctioned 2SLGBTQ+ Pride Festivals: Canadaâ€™s NEW Established Sex-cult Religion [Liberty Dispatch]]]></title>
   <link>https://app.dropwave.io/episode/96a06207-7dd6-4d55-830d-7e1f6cea06df/adults-expose-themselves-to-children-at-state-funded-and-state-sanctioned-2slgbtq-pride-festivals-canadas-new-established-sex-cult-religion.mp3</link>
   <description><![CDATA[<p class="p1"><strong>Liberty Dispatch</strong> ~ June 27, 2023<br />On this episode of the Dispatch, hosts Andrew and Matty EXPOSE Canada's newly established sex-cult religion -The 2SLGBTQIA+ Rainbow Mafia- which, as it turns out, likes to EXPOSE itself in public around children with the full approval of law-enforce and the State. Think it's time to push back? Us too!<br /><br /><strong style="font-family: '-apple-system', BlinkMacSystemFont, 'Segoe UI', Roboto, Oxygen, Ubuntu, Cantarell, 'Open Sans', 'Helvetica Neue', sans-serif;">[Segment 1] - The NEW Established State Religion - 2SLGBTQ+ PRIDE (07:20 - 27:25):<br /></strong>"Trudeau attends Pride event despite COVID-19 restrictions" | TNC News: <a href="https://tnc.news/2023/06/13/trudeau-pride-covid">https://tnc.news/2023/06/13/trudeau-pride-covid</a>;<br />"Ottawa commits $25 million to Canada's first LGBTQ entrepreneurship program" | Financial Post: <a href="https://tnc.news/2023/06/13/trudeau-pride-covid">https://tnc.news/2023/06/13/trudeau-pride-covid</a>;<br />"The state has a duty to protect trans students" | The Globe and Mail: <a href="https://www.theglobeandmail.com/opinion/editorials/article-the-state-has-a-duty-to-protect-trans-students">https://www.theglobeandmail.com/opinion/editorials/article-the-state-has-a-duty-to-protect-trans-students</a>;<br />"Trudeau Liberals celebrate Toronto Pride sponsored by Bud Light as fetishists expose themselves to children" | The Post Millennial: <a href="https://thepostmillennial.com/breaking-trudeau-liberals-celebrate-toronto-pride-sponsored-by-bud-light-as-fetishists-expose-themselves-to-children">https://thepostmillennial.com/breaking-trudeau-liberals-celebrate-toronto-pride-sponsored-by-bud-light-as-fetishists-expose-themselves-to-children</a>;<br />"Adults Expose Themselves to Children at Toronto Pride" | The Post Millennial: <a href="https://thepostmillennial.com/adults-expose-themselves-to-children-at-toronto-pride-parade">https://thepostmillennial.com/adults-expose-themselves-to-children-at-toronto-pride-parade</a>;&nbsp;<br /><br /><strong>[Segment 2] - Interview ft. Concerned Parent and Child who witnessed men exposing themselves to minors at the Toronto Pride Festival (27:26 - 40:54)</strong><br /><br /><strong>[Segment 3] - The Woke Indoctrination System (41:47 - 55:37):</strong><br />"Sexually explicit books at TVDSB" | CPAL (Substack publication): <a href="https://cpal.substack.com/p/sexually-explicit-books-at-tvdsb?publication_id=1585338&amp;post_id=127872526&amp;isFreemail=true">https://cpal.substack.com/p/sexually-explicit-books-at-tvdsb?publication_id=1585338&amp;post_id=127872526&amp;isFreemail=true</a>;<br />"Gender identity and gender expression procedures" | Hamilton-Wentworth District School Board (HWDSB) Blog: <a href="https://www.hwdsb.on.ca/blog/gender-identity-and-gender-expression-procedures">https://www.hwdsb.on.ca/blog/gender-identity-and-gender-expression-procedures</a>;<br />"Pupil-teacher 'despicable' for identifying as a cat, transgender" | The Telegraph: <a href="https://www.hwdsb.on.ca/blog/gender-identity-and-gender-expression-procedures">https://www.hwdsb.on.ca/blog/gender-identity-and-gender-expression-procedures</a>;<br />Tweet by TPoint UK: <a href="https://twitter.com/tpointuk/status/1670145753669410816">https://twitter.com/tpointuk/status/1670145753669410816</a>;<br />"Help a teacher fight back after being fired for sharing an article about students skipping Pride Day" | Rebel News: <a href="https://www.rebelnews.com/help_a_teacher_fight_back_after_being_fired_for_sharing_an_article_about_students_skipping_pride_day">https://www.rebelnews.com/help_a_teacher_fight_back_after_being_fired_for_sharing_an_article_about_students_skipping_pride_day</a>;<br /><strong><br />[Segment 4] - Interview ft. Jacob Reaume (55:37 - 01:16:28)<br /><br />[Segment 5] - Conclusion (01:16:29 - END)</strong><br /><strong><br />JOIN PASTORS, CHURCHES, AND CHRISTIAN COMMUNITIES ACROSS CANADA WITH LCC'S NEWEST INITIATIVE, "<em>TRUE READINGS FROM TRUE ROYALTY."&nbsp; <br /></em></strong><strong>Sign up today:&nbsp;</strong><a href="https://libertycoalitioncanada.com/storyhour/">https://libertycoalitioncanada.com/storyhour/</a>&nbsp;<br /><br /><strong>Support Josh's Stand and Help Us Defend His Liberties! Sign Our Petition Here: <a href="https://libertycoalitioncanada.com/i-stand-with-josh-alexander/">https://libertycoalitioncanada.com/i-stand-with-josh-alexander/</a>;<br /><br /></strong><strong>SHOW SPONSORS:<br /></strong><strong>Join&nbsp;<em>Red Balloon&nbsp;</em>Today!:</strong> <a href="https://www.redballoon.work/lcc;">https://www.redballoon.work/lcc;</a>&nbsp;<br /><strong>Invest with Rocklinc:</strong> <a href="mailto:info@rocklinc.com">info@rocklinc.com</a>&nbsp;or call them at 905-631-546;&nbsp;<br /><strong>Diversify Your Money with Bull Bitcoin:&nbsp;</strong><a href="https://mission.bullbitcoin.com/lcc">https://mission.bullbitcoin.com/lcc</a>;<br /><strong>BarterPay: </strong><a href="https://barterpay.ca/">https://barterpay.ca/</a>;&nbsp; <strong>Barter It: </strong><a href="https://vip.barterit.ca/launch;">https://vip.barterit.ca/launch; </a><strong><br />Carpe Fide - "Seize the Faith": Store: </strong><a href="https://carpe-fide.myshopify.com/">https://carpe-fide.myshopify.com</a><a href="https://carpe-fide.myshopify.com/">/</a>, use Promo Code LCC10 for 10% off (US Store Only), or shop Canadian @ <a href="https://canadacarpefide.myshopify.com/">https://canadacarpefide.myshopify.com/</a> | <strong>Podcast: </strong><a href="https://www.carpefide.com/episodes">https://www.carpefide.com/episodes</a>;<br /><br /><strong>Sick of Mainstream Media Lies? Help Support Independent Media! DONATE TO LCC TODAY!:&nbsp;</strong><strong><a href="https://libertycoalitioncanada.com/donate/">https://libertycoalitioncanada.com/donate/</a>&nbsp;</strong><strong>&nbsp;<br /><br /></strong></p>
<p class="p1">Please Support us in bringing you honest, truthful reporting and analysis from a Christian perspective.<br /><br /><strong>SUBSCRIBE TO OUR SHOWS/CHANNELS:<br /></strong>LIBERTY DISPATCH PODCAST: <a href="https://libertydispatch.podbean.com">https://libertydispatch.podbean.com</a>; <a href="https://rumble.com/c/c-1687093">https://rumble.com/LDshow</a>;&nbsp;<br />OPEN MIKE WITH MICHAEL THIESSEN: <a href="https://openmikewithmichaelthiessen.podbean.com">https://openmikewithmichaelthiessen.podbean.com</a>; <a href="https://rumble.com/c/c-1412501">https://rumble.com/openmike</a>;<br />THE OTHER CLUB: <a href="https://rumble.com/c/c-2541984">https://rumble.com/c/c-2541984</a>;&nbsp;<br />THE LIBERTY LOUNGE WITH TIM TYSOE: <a href="https://rumble.com/LLwTT">https://rumble.com/LLwTT</a>;<br /><br /><strong>CONTACT US:</strong><br />Questions/comments about podcasts/news/analysis: <a href="mailto:mailbag@libertycoalitioncanada.com">mailbag@libertycoalitioncanada.com</a>;<br />Questions/comments about donations: <a href="mailto:give@libertycoalitioncanada.com">give@libertycoalitioncanada.com</a>;<br />Questions/comments that are church-related: <a href="mailto:churches@libertycoalitioncanada.com">churches@libertycoalitioncanada.com</a>;<br />General Inquiries: <a href="mailto:info@libertycoalitioncanada.com">info@libertycoalitioncanada.com</a>.&nbsp;<br /><br /></p>
<p class="p1"><strong>STAY UP-TO-DATE ON ALL THINGS LCC:<br /></strong>Gab: <a href="https://gab.com/libertycoalitioncanada">https://gab.com/libertycoalitioncanada</a>&nbsp;</p>
<p class="p2">Telegram: <a href="https://t.me/libertycoalitioncanadanews">https://t.me/libertycoalitioncanadanews</a>&nbsp;</p>
<p class="p2">Instagram: <a href="https://instagram.com/libertycoalitioncanada">https://instagram.com/libertycoalitioncanada</a>&nbsp;</p>
<p class="p2">Facebook: <a href="https://facebook.com/LibertyCoalitionCanada">https://facebook.com/LibertyCoalitionCanada</a>&nbsp;</p>
<p class="p2">Twitter: @LibertyCCanada - <a href="https://twitter.com/LibertyCCanada">https://twitter.com/LibertyCCanada</a>&nbsp;</p>
<p class="p2">Rumble: <a href="https://rumble.com/user/LibertyCoalitionCanada">https://rumble.com/user/LibertyCoalitionCanada</a>&nbsp;</p>
<p class="p2">YouTube: <a href="https://www.youtube.com/@liberty4canada">https://www.youtube.com/@liberty4canada</a> -&nbsp;<strong>WE GOT CANCELLED AGAIN!!!</strong></p>
<p class="p1"><strong>Please LIKE, SUBSCRIBE, RATE &amp; REVIEW and SHARE it with others!</strong></p>]]></description>
   <author><![CDATA[Matthew Hallick, Andrew DeBartolo, Jacob Reaume, SDG Media]]></author>
   <enclosure url="https://app.dropwave.io/episode/96a06207-7dd6-4d55-830d-7e1f6cea06df/adults-expose-themselves-to-children-at-state-funded-and-state-sanctioned-2slgbtq-pride-festivals-canadas-new-established-sex-cult-religion.mp3" length="4790" type="audio/mp3"/>
   <guid isPermaLink="false"><![CDATA[96a06207-7dd6-4d55-830d-7e1f6cea06df]]></guid>
   <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2023 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
   <source url=""><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></source>
   <itunes:author><![CDATA[Matthew Hallick, Andrew DeBartolo, Jacob Reaume, SDG Media]]></itunes:author>
   <itunes:image href="https://prod-assets-spc1.nyc3.digitaloceanspaces.com/69893365-4165-4498-b0ac-e9ddf57a000f/cover-art/E86eLfK3NgjrpuXtk9kW9Qv6KcfzQpkJpToltreR.png"/>
   <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
   <itunes:duration>4790</itunes:duration>
   <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title><![CDATA[1492 [Resistance and Reformation]]]></title>
   <link>https://app.dropwave.io/episode/e8a9a8c6-bb3a-4b0f-a5dc-409a824e77df/1492.mp3</link>
   <description><![CDATA[<p>More from Dr. George Grant</p>
<p><a href="https://georgegrant.net/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" data-callout-id="edit_links_in_description">https://georgegrant.net/</a>&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Adoring God Foundation&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://adoringgod.org/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" data-callout-id="edit_links_in_description">https://adoringgod.org/</a></p>]]></description>
   <author><![CDATA[George Grant]]></author>
   <enclosure url="https://app.dropwave.io/episode/e8a9a8c6-bb3a-4b0f-a5dc-409a824e77df/1492.mp3" length="0" type="audio/mp3"/>
   <guid isPermaLink="false"><![CDATA[e8a9a8c6-bb3a-4b0f-a5dc-409a824e77df]]></guid>
   <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2023 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
   <source url=""><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></source>
   <itunes:author><![CDATA[George Grant]]></itunes:author>
   <itunes:image href="https://assets-cdn2.dropwave.io/261ebdbb-5a5a-4650-ba2c-8c138886911b/cover-art/fEPh0pqkjOi1hWn2VDTvgRSsw3nOsdOFIBOfEGEP.png"/>
   <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
   <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title><![CDATA[The False Cupid [Choc Knox Unplugged]]]></title>
   <link>https://app.dropwave.io/episode/be370bea-79f0-4b2a-9031-390a8abf03e8/the-false-cupid.mp3</link>
   <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
   <author><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></author>
   <enclosure url="https://app.dropwave.io/episode/be370bea-79f0-4b2a-9031-390a8abf03e8/the-false-cupid.mp3" length="7110" type="audio/mp3"/>
   <guid isPermaLink="false"><![CDATA[be370bea-79f0-4b2a-9031-390a8abf03e8]]></guid>
   <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2023 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
   <source url=""><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></source>
   <itunes:author><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></itunes:author>
   <itunes:image href="https://assets-cdn2.dropwave.io/6123b54f-ab49-406c-9cba-a39f6730fc76/cover-art/ARuuU8PixHGkhNvgtHIHIGGJjBUPNwgZEkuaGqzL.png"/>
   <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
   <itunes:duration>7110</itunes:duration>
   <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title><![CDATA[Daily News Brief for Tuesday, June 27th, 2023 [Daily News Brief]]]></title>
   <link>https://app.dropwave.io/episode/2faff94a-7c68-473d-af8b-ef65a4f34a7b/daily-news-brief-for-tuesday-june-27th-2023.mp3</link>
   <description><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">This is Garrison Hardie with your CrossPolitic Daily News Brief for Tuesday, June 27th, 2023.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>Fight Laugh Feast Conference - Ark Encounter</strong></span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">This year, our Fight Laugh Feast Conference is at the Ark Encounter in Kentucky on The Politics of Six Day Creation. The politics of six day creation is the difference between a fixed standard of justice and a careening standard of justice, the difference between the corrosive relativism that creates mobs and anarchy and the freedom of objectivity, truth, and due process. The politics of six day creation establishes the authority and sufficiency of God&rsquo;s Word for all of life: from what is a man or a woman, when does human life begin, and how is human society best organized?</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Come hear Ken Ham, Pastor Doug Wilson, Dr. Ben Merkle, Dr. Gordon Wilson, me and more, and of course a live CrossPolitic show! Mark your calendars for October 11th-14th, as we fight, laugh, and feast, with beer &amp; psalms, our amazing lineup of speakers, our Rowdy Christian Merch, and a Sabbath Feast to wrap up the occasion. Maybe an infant baptism while we&rsquo;re at it! Visit fightlaughfeast.com for more information!</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://justthenews.com/politics-policy/anniversary-roe-v-wade-being-overturned-gop-rep-promotes-bill-help-expectant"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://justthenews.com/politics-policy/anniversary-roe-v-wade-being-overturned-gop-rep-promotes-bill-help-expectant</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>On anniversary of Roe v. Wade being overturned, GOP Rep. promotes bill to help expectant mothers</strong></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">On the anniversary of Roe v. Wade being overturned, Minnesota Republican Congresswoman Michelle Fischbach promoted a proposed bill titled "The HOPE Act" that promotes helping expectant mothers.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">"It is crucial that women are supported when facing an unexpected pregnancy, which is why I have introduced The Health, Opportunity, Protecting Life, Education (HOPE) Act, which improves access to prenatal telehealth care, supports positive alternatives to abortion, and improves access to information for expectant mothers, providing tangible ways to help women feel confident during and beyond their pregnancy," Fischbach wrote in an opinion piece published by The Hill.&nbsp;&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">On June 24, 2022, the Supreme Court of the United States ruled to overturn Roe v. Wade, ending the constitutional right to abortion and allowing individual states to decide for themselves on whether to restrict or allow abortions.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The HOPE Act would provide funding for grants and other activities related to maternal care. It would also establish informed consent and parental notification requirements for abortion providers.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">"The HOPE Act creates a pilot grant program to provide support and equipment like blood pressure monitors, scales, and portable fetal heart rate monitors to community health providers," Fischbach wrote. "Increasing telehealth options gives expectant mothers the flexibility they need to receive the care they deserve."&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">It would also prohibit any government funding going to Planned Parenthood.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://www.foxnews.com/media/bud-light-sponsors-toronto-pride-parade-naked-men-children"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.foxnews.com/media/bud-light-sponsors-toronto-pride-parade-naked-men-children</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>Bud Light sponsors Toronto Pride parade attended by naked men, children</strong></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Bud Light is serving as an official sponsor of the Toronto Pride parade, where video footage shows naked men standing around and riding bicycles in clear view of children attending the event.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The footage, captured by Beth Baisch of the Post Millennial, shows dozens of attendees riding past a large cheering crowd. The fully naked bikers, some covered in paint or tattoos, wave back at the crowd. One naked man high-fives an onlooker while another peddles a recumbent bike with a gold blow-up swan adorned around his neck.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">A second video shows a group of naked men with hats standing in a circle amidst the crowd. Several children walk past the group of men with their families.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Another clip shows a person wearing a giant penis costume that covers his entire head. The camera captures a young girl sitting in a stroller and staring toward the phallic-costumed individual.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Other videos show a group of naked men playing and rinsing themselves off alongside a fountain surrounded by kids. Meanwhile, a stage, clearly adorned with Bud Light branding, featured scantily clad dancers wearing fishnets, nipple stickers and strange sock-like masks.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The company's website notes that this year's sponsorship is representative of a longstanding partnership with the Pride event.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">"Bud Light Canada has been a proud partner of Pride Toronto for the last 10 years. This year, we're commemorating this milestone with Pride Toronto by featuring them on our can design, as well as continuing as the official beer sponsor of the festival," the beer brand's website states.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">According to the website, Bud Light Canada also provides $100,000 to various organizations that support the LGBTQUA2S+ community across Canada and has created a range of commemorative Pride beer cans to celebrate the collaboration.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The partnership comes nearly three months after Bud Light received massive backlash for partnering with trans activist Dylan Mulvaney. The decision angered consumers and the brand saw a significant decrease in sales, resulting in billions of dollars in lost market value.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">In early April, Anheuser-Busch CEO Brendan Whitworth attempted to douse the flames with a lengthy statement to customers.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">"We never intended to be part of a discussion that divides people. We are in the business of bringing people together over a beer," he said in part. "My time serving this country taught me the importance of accountability and the values upon which America was founded: freedom, hard work and respect for one another. As CEO of Anheuser-Busch, I am focused on building and protecting our remarkable history and heritage."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Despite losing business, Bud Light continued to anger customers for co-sponsoring an "all-ages Pride event" in Flagstaff, Arizona, on June 17.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The party, called "Pride in the Pines," included drag queens and other performers, and listed Bud Light as one of the companies sponsoring the June 17 event. (Bud Light was initially mentioned prominently in one of the posters.) The event is listed as a "family festival event" and a family-friendly, "safe space" for all visitors.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://www.foxnews.com/us/colorado-springs-club-q-nonbinary-shooting-suspect-pleads-guilty-murder-charges"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.foxnews.com/us/colorado-springs-club-q-nonbinary-shooting-suspect-pleads-guilty-murder-charges</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>Colorado Club Q 'nonbinary' shooter sentenced to life in prison after pleading guilty to murder</strong></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Club Q shooting suspect Anderson Lee Aldrich was sentenced to life in prison after pleading guilty to murder and attempted murder charges during an arraignment hearing Monday morning, avoiding the prospect of a public trail just seven months after the deadly Colorado attack.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Aldrich, who public defenders have said identifies as nonbinary and prefers to be described using they/them pronouns, is accused of fatally shooting five people and wounding 17 others at the LGBTQ+ nightclub Club Q in Colorado Springs, Colorado, on Nov. 19, 2022.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The suspect, whom the judge referred to as "Mx. Aldrich" during Monday&rsquo;s arraignment hearing, accepted a plea agreement for a life sentence without the possibility of parole in exchange for pleading guilty to five counts of first-degree murder. Aldrich also pleaded guilty Monday to 46 counts of attempted murder in the first degree.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The suspect pleaded no contest to felony and misdemeanor charges of bias-motivated crimes. "Because of the evidence presented I believe there is a high probability of being convicted at trial to those counts, and so I am pleading no contest or nolo contendere," Aldrich told the court Monday, explaining the no contest plea.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">In an interview from jail, Aldrich reportedly admitted to The Associated Press to being on a "very large plethora of drugs" and abusing steroids at the time, expressing regret for the attack and adding that suggesting the shooting was motivated by hate was "completely off base."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">In court hearings earlier this year, law enforcement testified that Aldrich ran a neo-Nazi website and used gay and racial slurs while gaming online, while the defense countered that Aldrich's sometimes abusive mother forced the suspect to frequent LGBTQ+ clubs.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Two veterans out at Club Q reportedly helped thwart the attack by disarming Aldrich, who was beaten by patrons and displayed a bruised and bloodied face in his initial mugshot and court appearance. Aldrich was facing more than 300 state counts, including murder and hate crimes. The Justice Department is also considering pursuing federal hate crime charges, according to a senior law enforcement official who spoke to the AP.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">However, the charges against Aldrich were thrown out in July 2022 after Aldrich's mother and grandparents, the victims in the case, refused to cooperate with prosecutors, evading efforts to serve them with subpoenas to testify, according to court documents unsealed after the shooting. Other relatives told a judge they feared Aldrich would hurt the grandparents if released, painting a picture of an isolated, violent person who did not have a job and was given $30,000 that was spent largely on the purchase of 3D printers to make guns, the records showed.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Aldrich was released from jail then and authorities kept two guns -- a ghost gun pistol and an MM15 rifle &ndash; seized in the arrest. But there was nothing to stop Aldrich from legally purchasing more firearms, raising questions immediately after the shooting about whether authorities should have sought a red flag order to prevent such purchases.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/news/nearly-half-bee-colonies-died-2023"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/news/nearly-half-bee-colonies-died-2023</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>Nearly half of honey bee colonies died in 2023 after three tumultuous years</strong></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">From April of last year to April of this year, 48% of honey bee colonies prematurely died off.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">University of Maryland and Auburn University have collaborated with nonprofit Bee Informed to track and report on managed bee colonies every year since 2007. Last year saw losses of 48%, the previous year&rsquo;s loss was 39%, and the year before that, it was 50.8%. The average loss over the last 12 years is 39.6%.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The cause of these losses is a mix of the parasitic mite, varroa destructor, which helps spread viruses between bees, increased use of pesticides, which inhibit the bee's ability to stave off diseases, and dramatic changes in the environment. When it becomes warmer than usual during the winter, bees will leave their colonies to begin pollinating many of the crops we eat, as well as other plants, but when the weather chills again, the bees die off.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Still, the most commonly reported cause of death during the winter was the varroa. During the rest of the year, the most common report revolved around issues with the queen bee.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">"High levels of losses do not necessarily result in a decrease in the total number of colonies managed in the United States because beekeepers can replace lost colonies throughout the year," the report read.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">This report comes from a self-reported survey of 3,006 beekeepers from across the United States who collectively manage 314,360 colonies, the majority of which are commercially operated. This is only 12% of the estimated 2.70 million managed honey-producing colonies in the country in 2022, per the report.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The collaboration, known as "the Bee Informed Partnership," is a non-profit organization dedicated to improving honey bee colony health in particular.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://www.conservativereview.com/unable-to-rely-on-wind-and-solar-sweden-ditches-100-renewable-target-and-bets-big-on-nuclear-power-2661896744.html"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.conservativereview.com/unable-to-rely-on-wind-and-solar-sweden-ditches-100-renewable-target-and-bets-big-on-nuclear-power-2661896744.html</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>Unable to rely on wind and solar, Sweden ditches 100% renewable target and bets big on nuclear power</strong></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The Swedish parliament determined last week that in order to ensure the country has a "stable energy system," it will have to abandon its goal of "100 per cent renewable electricity production by 2040."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">To satisfy electricity demand, which is set to double to around 300 TwH by 2040, Sweden's right-of-center government announced June 20 that it would instead lean more heavily on nuclear energy and subsidize the construction of new nuclear plants &mdash; plants green-lit in 2016 but sidelined for fear they would be too expensive, reported Reuters.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The country, home to just over 10.5 million people, presently has three nuclear plants with six nuclear reactors in commercial operation. The state-owned Vattenfall aims to bring the tally up to eight reactors and refurbish extant facilities.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">While Sweden's heightened nuclear focus is consistent with the country's commitment to shifting entirely off fossil fuels in a way that doesn't altogether cripple the nation, this bullishness on carbon-free nuclear power represents a significant about-face on atomic energy, which the country decided in a 1980 referendum to phase out.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Swedish support for nuclear energy is presently at a record high of 56%, up from 42% in 2022, reported Bloomberg. The jump in support has been attributed in part to the energy crisis that overwhelmed Europe in concert with the invasion of Ukraine and the revelation that renewable energies are not tenable as alternatives.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">A 2021 study published in the journal Nature Communications indicated, "If future net-zero emissions energy systems rely heavily on solar and wind resources, spatial and temporal mismatches between resource availability and electricity demand may challenge system reliability."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The researchers indicated that "the most reliable renewable electricity systems are wind-heavy and satisfy countries' electricity demand in 72-91% of hours ... Yet even in systems which meet &gt;90% o demand, hundreds of hours of unmet demand may occur annually."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">These lost hours could prove too dear in a country where temperatures routinely drop below freezing several months out of every year.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Even the former energy minister for the defeated leftist Social Democratic Party, was cognizant of the country's strained energy situation, warning last August of "strains on the power system this winter," both in terms of outages and high prices.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The U.S. Department of Energy indicated that nuclear energy is the most reliable energy source on this side of the Atlantic Ocean. Each nuclear reactor typically produces the same amount of power as 431 utility-scale wind turbines or 3.1 million solar panels.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">According to the Swedish government, roughly 75% of its electricity comes from hydroelectric (43%) and nuclear (31%) power. 16% of the electricity comes from wind power. Approximately 9% comes from combined heat and power plants, largely powered by biofuels. Solar energy has yet to crack 1% of total supply.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Finance Minister Elisabeth Svan-tesson of the Moderate Party said, "We need more electricity production, we need clean electricity and we need a stable energy system."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Since wind and solar won't cut it, "This creates the conditions for nuclear power," said Svantesson.</span></p>]]></description>
   <author><![CDATA[Garrison Hardie]]></author>
   <enclosure url="https://app.dropwave.io/episode/2faff94a-7c68-473d-af8b-ef65a4f34a7b/daily-news-brief-for-tuesday-june-27th-2023.mp3" length="890" type="audio/mp3"/>
   <guid isPermaLink="false"><![CDATA[2faff94a-7c68-473d-af8b-ef65a4f34a7b]]></guid>
   <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
   <source url=""><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></source>
   <itunes:author><![CDATA[Garrison Hardie]]></itunes:author>
   <itunes:image href="https://assets-cdn2.dropwave.io/2ab40ac0-e99d-4f25-a6d2-541d2c9b290a/cover-art/hUZu1H9lrRY0wXg66WHC8eLwYBA3hbRNTAHQmHt2.png"/>
   <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
   <itunes:duration>890</itunes:duration>
   <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title><![CDATA[Biblical Cosmology Episode 2: Return of the old gods [The Rebel Podcast]]]></title>
   <link>https://app.dropwave.io/episode/210175bf-7568-42d5-a596-1d679222b941/biblical-cosmology-episode-2-return-of-the-old-gods.mp3</link>
   <description><![CDATA[<div>What is this universe that we live in? Its full of rocks and dust, hummingbirds and anteaters, black holes and microbials. But is it just stuff? What about the things we cannot see? The things that go bump in the night?</div>
<div dir="ltr">&nbsp;</div>
<div>The bible is full of information about the unseen realm of this universe and it also has a lot to say about the conflict taking place in this war torn cosmos.</div>
<div>&nbsp;</div>
<div>This is the second episode in this new series, so make sure that if you missed the previous episode you go back to hear the groundwork that has been laid.</div>
<div dir="ltr">&nbsp;</div>
<div>In episode two we diacuss the old gods of the Old Testament and what it looks to see them.potentially return as the crumbling ruins of Christendom no longer provides the protection it once did.</div>
<p>If you have questions while we work our way through, please send them to us through any social media messaging or by emailing&nbsp;<a href="mailto:rebelpodcastflf@gmail.com">rebelpodcastflf@gmail.com</a></p>]]></description>
   <author><![CDATA[Pastors Nate & Chris & Jordan, The Rebels]]></author>
   <enclosure url="https://app.dropwave.io/episode/210175bf-7568-42d5-a596-1d679222b941/biblical-cosmology-episode-2-return-of-the-old-gods.mp3" length="2817" type="audio/mp3"/>
   <guid isPermaLink="false"><![CDATA[210175bf-7568-42d5-a596-1d679222b941]]></guid>
   <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
   <source url=""><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></source>
   <itunes:author><![CDATA[Pastors Nate & Chris & Jordan, The Rebels]]></itunes:author>
   <itunes:image href="https://assets-cdn2.dropwave.io/2f5403ee-3fd5-417e-8372-cb8279ee1f07/cover-art/w0UbRn2uM5yV9BWgVTAhrwlpOzSNrn99Jo5z83hu.png"/>
   <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
   <itunes:duration>2817</itunes:duration>
   <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title><![CDATA[Hebrews 10:23-25 [Up and Ready]]]></title>
   <link>https://app.dropwave.io/episode/2e7206be-cb32-4cc6-a8f1-3cfc574f5b08/hebrews-1023-25.mp3</link>
   <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
   <author><![CDATA[Mark Dewey]]></author>
   <enclosure url="https://app.dropwave.io/episode/2e7206be-cb32-4cc6-a8f1-3cfc574f5b08/hebrews-1023-25.mp3" length="271" type="audio/mp3"/>
   <guid isPermaLink="false"><![CDATA[2e7206be-cb32-4cc6-a8f1-3cfc574f5b08]]></guid>
   <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
   <source url=""><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></source>
   <itunes:author><![CDATA[Mark Dewey]]></itunes:author>
   <itunes:image href="https://assets-cdn2.dropwave.io/60c9e557-5882-401d-abb8-06de47904be4/cover-art/zZ8CYlYBUAUu8KNyZzjE092h2WlBblW8upM7tmFg.png"/>
   <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
   <itunes:duration>271</itunes:duration>
   <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title><![CDATA[What Are You Watching? [In the Bullpen]]]></title>
   <link>https://app.dropwave.io/episode/9ba076e0-2903-4ada-bdd4-226995511be0/what-are-you-watching.mp3</link>
   <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
   <author><![CDATA[Mark Dewey]]></author>
   <enclosure url="https://app.dropwave.io/episode/9ba076e0-2903-4ada-bdd4-226995511be0/what-are-you-watching.mp3" length="1812" type="audio/mp3"/>
   <guid isPermaLink="false"><![CDATA[9ba076e0-2903-4ada-bdd4-226995511be0]]></guid>
   <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jun 2023 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
   <source url=""><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></source>
   <itunes:author><![CDATA[Mark Dewey]]></itunes:author>
   <itunes:image href="https://assets-cdn2.dropwave.io/48817573-c1d0-44c6-8204-930f4c2d3ce5/cover-art/9b92BsnWm2ufHgEHY2ttEsJ9SYr5RF0LGVrFbfmN.png"/>
   <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
   <itunes:duration>1812</itunes:duration>
   <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title><![CDATA[TCND:  Submersibles and Role-Playing Evil (Nerves!) [The Comedian Next Door]]]></title>
   <link>https://app.dropwave.io/episode/29a17239-87e2-42b7-a0b8-0dc937204f4f/tcnd-submersibles-and-role-playing-evil-nerves.mp3</link>
   <description><![CDATA[<p>John is desperately injured... Sports, sore hips, and charlie horses.&nbsp;</p>
<p>But it could be worse!&nbsp; We could be crushed by the ocean while riding in a tin can!</p>
<p>There was a time when men were respected for their courage and willingness to take perilous risks for the sake of potentially great reward. But, in our current society, most people try to mitigate and avoid risk as much as possible. Someone who fails spectacularly isn't encouraged for at least TRYING... he's ridiculed for doing something "stupid" which "could have been avoided."</p>
<p>You've got Christopher Columbus, the Apollo Missions, and Whats-her-name in that strapless gown. What do all of them have in common???</p>
<p>What would cause a person to attempt to go over Niagara Falls in a barrel? Or tighrope walk between skyscrapers?</p>
<p>Later:&nbsp; If you want a good example of concentrated evil, ask The Internet how it feels about Billionaires who lost their lives in a horrific accident. How can people justify SAYING these ugly, despicable things?&nbsp;</p>
<p>Here's our theory about The Role-Play Game Phenomenon.&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
<p>People are creating Altar Egos on the internet, and then those Altars are taking over...</p>
<p>To contact The Comedian, John Branyan, just email him at <a href="mailto:nextdoor@johnbranyan.com">nextdoor@johnbranyan.com.</a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>]]></description>
   <author><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></author>
   <enclosure url="https://app.dropwave.io/episode/29a17239-87e2-42b7-a0b8-0dc937204f4f/tcnd-submersibles-and-role-playing-evil-nerves.mp3" length="2940" type="audio/mp3"/>
   <guid isPermaLink="false"><![CDATA[29a17239-87e2-42b7-a0b8-0dc937204f4f]]></guid>
   <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jun 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
   <source url=""><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></source>
   <itunes:author><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></itunes:author>
   <itunes:image href="https://assets-cdn2.dropwave.io/66903a54-b4b6-4a52-a303-eb0bd0b792e3/cover-art/obxsSs7zSTuWr3ZFLRWxryhYbCyvdrWYzXEN2soF.png"/>
   <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
   <itunes:duration>2940</itunes:duration>
   <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title><![CDATA[John 13:34-35 [Up and Ready]]]></title>
   <link>https://app.dropwave.io/episode/94bee591-02a3-45b2-81aa-a9167db8482f/john-1334-35.mp3</link>
   <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
   <author><![CDATA[Mark Dewey]]></author>
   <enclosure url="https://app.dropwave.io/episode/94bee591-02a3-45b2-81aa-a9167db8482f/john-1334-35.mp3" length="237" type="audio/mp3"/>
   <guid isPermaLink="false"><![CDATA[94bee591-02a3-45b2-81aa-a9167db8482f]]></guid>
   <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jun 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
   <source url=""><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></source>
   <itunes:author><![CDATA[Mark Dewey]]></itunes:author>
   <itunes:image href="https://assets-cdn2.dropwave.io/60c9e557-5882-401d-abb8-06de47904be4/cover-art/zZ8CYlYBUAUu8KNyZzjE092h2WlBblW8upM7tmFg.png"/>
   <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
   <itunes:duration>237</itunes:duration>
   <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title><![CDATA[Dr. Gregory Chan: A Cause for Concern - A Canadian Physician Tracks the Alarming Side-Effects of the COVID Jab [Open Mike with Michael Thiessen]]]></title>
   <link>https://app.dropwave.io/episode/c5d889ba-8591-4c8e-a55a-b5ff8e057d76/dr-gregory-chan-a-cause-for-concern-a-canadian-physician-tracks-the-alarming-side-effects-of-the-covid-jab.mp3</link>
   <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>OPEN MIKE w/Michael Thiessen ~ </strong>June 24, 2023<br />On this episode of Open Mike, Dr. Thiessen is joined by Dr. Gregory Chan, a Canadian Family Physician, to discuss the dangers of the COVID jab and unscientific groupthink in the medical profession.&nbsp;<span class="css-901oao css-16my406 r-poiln3 r-bcqeeo r-qvutc0"><br /></span></p>
<p><strong>Episode Resource:</strong> <span class="css-901oao css-16my406 r-poiln3 r-bcqeeo r-qvutc0">Dr. Chan's Testimony @&nbsp;<em>National Citizen's Inquiry</em>: <a href="https://rumble.com/v2kwt5s-dr.-chans-experience-of-healthcare-during-covid-19-vaccine-rollout-day-1-re.html">https://rumble.com/v2kwt5s-dr.-chans-experience-of-healthcare-during-covid-19-vaccine-rollout-day-1-re.html</a><a href="https://harvestwindsor.ca/;">;</a>&nbsp;<em>National Citizen's Inquiry </em>Channel: <a href="https://rumble.com/user/NationalCitizensInquiryCA">https://rumble.com/user/NationalCitizensInquiryCA</a>;<br /></span><span class="css-901oao css-16my406 r-poiln3 r-bcqeeo r-qvutc0"><br /></span><strong>JOIN PASTORS, CHURCHES, AND CHRISTIAN COMMUNITIES ACROSS CANADA WITH LCC'S NEWEST INITIATIVE, "<em>TRUE READINGS FROM TRUE ROYALTY."&nbsp; <br /></em></strong><strong>Sign up today:&nbsp;</strong><a href="https://libertycoalitioncanada.com/storyhour/">https://libertycoalitioncanada.com/storyhour/</a>&nbsp;<br /><br /><strong>Support Josh's Stand and Help Us Defend His Liberties! Sign Our Petition Here: <a href="https://libertycoalitioncanada.com/i-stand-with-josh-alexander/">https://libertycoalitioncanada.com/i-stand-with-josh-alexander/</a>;<br /><br /></strong><strong>SHOW SPONSORS:<br /></strong><strong>Join&nbsp;<em>Red Balloon&nbsp;</em>Today!:</strong> <a href="https://www.redballoon.work/lcc;">https://www.redballoon.work/lcc;</a>&nbsp;<br /><strong>Invest with Rocklinc:</strong> <a href="mailto:info@rocklinc.com">info@rocklinc.com</a>&nbsp;or call them at 905-631-546;&nbsp;<br /><strong>Diversify Your Money with Bull Bitcoin:&nbsp;</strong><a href="https://mission.bullbitcoin.com/lcc">https://mission.bullbitcoin.com/lcc</a>;<br /><strong>BarterPay: </strong><a href="https://barterpay.ca/">https://barterpay.ca/</a>;&nbsp; <strong>Barter It: </strong><a href="https://vip.barterit.ca/launch;">https://vip.barterit.ca/launch; </a><strong><br />Carpe Fide - "Seize the Faith": Store: </strong><a href="https://carpe-fide.myshopify.com/">https://carpe-fide.myshopify.com</a><a href="https://carpe-fide.myshopify.com/">/</a>, use Promo Code LCC10 for 10% off (US Store Only), or shop Canadian @ <a href="https://canadacarpefide.myshopify.com/">https://canadacarpefide.myshopify.com/</a> | <strong>Podcast: </strong><a href="https://www.carpefide.com/episodes">https://www.carpefide.com/episodes</a>;<br /><br /><strong>Sick of Mainstream Media Lies? Help Support Independent Media! DONATE TO LCC TODAY!:&nbsp;</strong><strong><a href="https://libertycoalitioncanada.com/donate/">https://libertycoalitioncanada.com/donate/</a>&nbsp;</strong><strong> &nbsp;</strong></p>
<p class="p1">Please Support us in bringing you honest, truthful reporting and analysis from a Christian perspective.<br /><br /><strong>SUBSCRIBE TO OUR SHOWS/CHANNELS:<br /></strong>LIBERTY DISPATCH PODCAST: <a href="https://libertydispatch.podbean.com">https://libertydispatch.podbean.com</a>; <a href="https://rumble.com/c/c-1687093">https://rumble.com/LDshow</a>;&nbsp;<br />OPEN MIKE WITH MICHAEL THIESSEN: <a href="https://openmikewithmichaelthiessen.podbean.com">https://openmikewithmichaelthiessen.podbean.com</a>; <a href="https://rumble.com/c/c-1412501">https://rumble.com/openmike</a>;<br />THE OTHER CLUB: <a href="https://rumble.com/c/c-2541984">https://rumble.com/c/c-2541984</a>;&nbsp;<br />THE LIBERTY LOUNGE WITH TIM TYSOE: <a href="https://rumble.com/LLwTT">https://rumble.com/LLwTT</a>;<br /><br /><strong>CONTACT US:</strong><br />Questions/comments about podcasts/news/analysis: <a href="mailto:mailbag@libertycoalitioncanada.com">mailbag@libertycoalitioncanada.com</a>;<br />Questions/comments about donations: <a href="mailto:give@libertycoalitioncanada.com">give@libertycoalitioncanada.com</a>;<br />Questions/comments that are church-related: <a href="mailto:churches@libertycoalitioncanada.com">churches@libertycoalitioncanada.com</a>;<br />General Inquiries: <a href="mailto:info@libertycoalitioncanada.com">info@libertycoalitioncanada.com</a>.&nbsp;<br /><br /></p>
<p class="p1"><strong>STAY UP-TO-DATE ON ALL THINGS LCC:<br /></strong>Gab: <a href="https://gab.com/libertycoalitioncanada">https://gab.com/libertycoalitioncanada</a>&nbsp;</p>
<p class="p2">Telegram: <a href="https://t.me/libertycoalitioncanadanews">https://t.me/libertycoalitioncanadanews</a>&nbsp;</p>
<p class="p2">Instagram: <a href="https://instagram.com/libertycoalitioncanada">https://instagram.com/libertycoalitioncanada</a>&nbsp;</p>
<p class="p2">Facebook: <a href="https://facebook.com/LibertyCoalitionCanada">https://facebook.com/LibertyCoalitionCanada</a>&nbsp;</p>
<p class="p2">Twitter: @LibertyCCanada - <a href="https://twitter.com/LibertyCCanada">https://twitter.com/LibertyCCanada</a>&nbsp;</p>
<p class="p2">Rumble: <a href="https://rumble.com/user/LibertyCoalitionCanada">https://rumble.com/user/LibertyCoalitionCanada</a>&nbsp;</p>
<p class="p2">YouTube: <a href="https://www.youtube.com/@liberty4canada">https://www.youtube.com/@liberty4canada</a> -&nbsp;<strong>WE GOT CANCELLED AGAIN!!!</strong></p>
<p class="p1"><strong>Please LIKE, SUBSCRIBE, RATE &amp; REVIEW and SHARE it with others!</strong></p>]]></description>
   <author><![CDATA[Dr. Michael Thiessen, Dr. Gregory Chan, SDG MEDIA]]></author>
   <enclosure url="https://app.dropwave.io/episode/c5d889ba-8591-4c8e-a55a-b5ff8e057d76/dr-gregory-chan-a-cause-for-concern-a-canadian-physician-tracks-the-alarming-side-effects-of-the-covid-jab.mp3" length="4193" type="audio/mp3"/>
   <guid isPermaLink="false"><![CDATA[c5d889ba-8591-4c8e-a55a-b5ff8e057d76]]></guid>
   <pubDate>Sat, 24 Jun 2023 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
   <source url=""><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></source>
   <itunes:author><![CDATA[Dr. Michael Thiessen, Dr. Gregory Chan, SDG MEDIA]]></itunes:author>
   <itunes:image href="https://assets-cdn2.dropwave.io/a313a937-1864-4720-a5eb-4fe53c91d48d/cover-art/uUheeW63MRtlJ15cfD2JSiW4qu9YifPAUxqcvBE5.jpg"/>
   <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
   <itunes:duration>4193</itunes:duration>
   <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title><![CDATA[Psalm 139:7-12 [Up and Ready]]]></title>
   <link>https://app.dropwave.io/episode/6965c679-aeb7-4b49-899c-f1b500168ecb/psalm-1397-12.mp3</link>
   <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
   <author><![CDATA[Mark Dewey]]></author>
   <enclosure url="https://app.dropwave.io/episode/6965c679-aeb7-4b49-899c-f1b500168ecb/psalm-1397-12.mp3" length="269" type="audio/mp3"/>
   <guid isPermaLink="false"><![CDATA[6965c679-aeb7-4b49-899c-f1b500168ecb]]></guid>
   <pubDate>Sat, 24 Jun 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
   <source url=""><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></source>
   <itunes:author><![CDATA[Mark Dewey]]></itunes:author>
   <itunes:image href="https://assets-cdn2.dropwave.io/60c9e557-5882-401d-abb8-06de47904be4/cover-art/zZ8CYlYBUAUu8KNyZzjE092h2WlBblW8upM7tmFg.png"/>
   <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
   <itunes:duration>269</itunes:duration>
   <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title><![CDATA[What Kind of Cosmos Puts Juneteenth on its Public Calendar? [God, Law, and Liberty]]]></title>
   <link>https://app.dropwave.io/episode/9b1f980d-bf69-40b9-9c5c-315972d3883f/what-kind-of-cosmos-puts-juneteenth-on-its-public-calendar.mp3</link>
   <description><![CDATA[<p>At the Choc Knox Live event we hosted in Franklin last month, panelist Dr. George Grant said, &ldquo;If you want to change a culture, you have to change the calendar.&rdquo; On today&rsquo;s episode, panelists Jason Farley and George Grant will explain why that is so, and what changed&nbsp;that has turned Christmas into a holiday season and June into Pride Month?</p>]]></description>
   <author><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></author>
   <enclosure url="https://app.dropwave.io/episode/9b1f980d-bf69-40b9-9c5c-315972d3883f/what-kind-of-cosmos-puts-juneteenth-on-its-public-calendar.mp3" length="1634" type="audio/mp3"/>
   <guid isPermaLink="false"><![CDATA[9b1f980d-bf69-40b9-9c5c-315972d3883f]]></guid>
   <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jun 2023 20:50:00 +0000</pubDate>
   <source url=""><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></source>
   <itunes:author><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></itunes:author>
   <itunes:image href="https://assets-cdn2.dropwave.io/467f99a9-2921-459a-b63d-9710f4355795/cover-art/Gv4eZkacrb8eKMXhgDmp8MRYvk63c5eCXFm5oezz.jpg"/>
   <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
   <itunes:duration>1634</itunes:duration>
   <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title><![CDATA[Daily News Brief for Friday, June 23rd, 2023 [Daily News Brief]]]></title>
   <link>https://app.dropwave.io/episode/7bf225dd-f6dd-42dd-b556-11e3ea899ac4/daily-news-brief-for-friday-june-23rd-2023.mp3</link>
   <description><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">This is Garrison Hardie with your CrossPolitic Daily News Brief for Friday, June 23rd, 2023.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Dime Payments</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Dime Payments is a Christian owned processing payment business. Every business needs a payment process system, so please go to https://dimepayments.com/flf and sign your business up. Working with them supports us. They wont cancel you, like Stripe canceled President Trump. They wont cancel you, like Mailchimp canceled the Babylon Bee. Check them out. At least have a phone call and tell them that CrossPolitic sent you. Go to https://dimepayments.com/flf.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://thepostmillennial.com/breaking-us-coast-guard-states-all-5-aboard-lost-titan-submersible-are-dead?utm_campaign=64487"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://thepostmillennial.com/breaking-us-coast-guard-states-all-5-aboard-lost-titan-submersible-are-dead?utm_campaign=64487</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>US Coast Guard states all 5 aboard lost Titan submersible are dead</strong></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The US Coast Guard confirmed on Thursday that those who were aboard the Titan submersible are now dead. A spokesperson said that the debris that was found shows that the Titan passengers could not have survived the destruction of the pressure chamber.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">A Remote Operating Vehicle discovered the debris on Thursday morning. In consultation with experts from within the unified command, the debris is consistent with the catastrophic loss of the pressure chamber." The Coast Guard immediately reached out to the families, and offered their condolences.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://twitter.com/i/status/1671957337308033024"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://twitter.com/i/status/1671957337308033024</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> - Play Video</span></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Authorities do not believe that bodies will be recovered, and stated that as to the cause of the destruction, an expert said that the Titanic, or a crash with the Titanic, was not at fault. Instead, they believe it was "an implosion in the water column." This was a "catastrophic implosion."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The timing of the implosion as regards the length of time Titan was underwater before the implosion is not yet known.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">A statement released by OceanGate, the company behind the Titan submersible that went missing Sunday after descending to the depths to view the wreckage of the famed, ill-fated luxury liner Titanic, stating that all of those aboard are dead.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://dailycaller.com/2023/06/22/bidens-plan-to-cancel-student-loan-debt-stands-after-house-fails-to-overturn-veto/"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://dailycaller.com/2023/06/22/bidens-plan-to-cancel-student-loan-debt-stands-after-house-fails-to-overturn-veto/</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>Biden&rsquo;s Plan To Cancel Student Loan Debt Stands After House Fails To Overturn Veto</strong></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">President Joe Biden&rsquo;s veto of a bill intended to block his plan to cancel up to $20,000 in student loan debt for some borrowers remains standing after House Republicans failed to garner the two-thirds majority needed to override.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">After the Government Accountability Office (GAO) determined that Biden&rsquo;s plan was subject to the Congressional Review Act (CRA), House Republicans moved to block the president&rsquo;s proposal, The Hill reported.&nbsp; Republicans have argued that student loan forgiveness would cost the American taxpayer $400 billion and is unfair to those who repaid their student loans or didn&rsquo;t attend college.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The subsequent resolution passed both the House and the Democrat-majority Senate after gaining support from Democrats Joe Manchin of West Virginia and Jon Tester of Montana, as well as Independent Arizona Sen. Kyrsten Sinema. Earlier in June, however, Biden vetoed the resolution, arguing that student loan relief would help offset the financial strains felt by borrowers during and after the Covid-19 pandemic.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Despite having enough support to pass the initial resolution, House Republicans failed to garner enough support Wednesday to overcome Biden&rsquo;s veto. The resulting 221-206 vote in the House was among party lines. Although Congress was unable to overturn Biden&rsquo;s veto, the Supreme Court still must rule on the measure. Republican attorney generals and conservative groups have argued that Biden&rsquo;s plan is &ldquo;an illegal abuse of executive power.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://www.bbc.com/news/business-65981876"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.bbc.com/news/business-65981876</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>Elon Musk and Mark Zuckerberg agree to hold cage fight</strong></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Two of the world's most high-profile technology billionaires - Elon Musk and Mark Zuckerberg - have agreed to fight each other in a cage match.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Mr Musk posted a message on his social media platform Twitter that he was "up for a cage fight" with Mr Zuckerberg.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Mr Zuckerberg, the boss of Facebook and Instagram parent company Meta, then posted a screenshot of Mr Musk's tweet with the caption "send me location".</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">"The story speaks for itself," a Meta spokesperson said.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Mr Musk then replied to Mr Zuckerberg's response with: "Vegas Octagon."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The Octagon is the competition mat and fenced-in area used for Ultimate Fighting Championship (UFC) bouts. The UFC is based in Las Vegas, Nevada.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Mr Musk, who turns 52 later this month, also tweeted: "I have this great move that I call 'The Walrus', where I just lie on top of my opponent &amp; do nothing."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">He later tweeted short videos of walruses, perhaps suggesting his challenge to Mr Zuckerberg may not entirely be serious.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://www.boundingintosports.com/2023/06/dodgers-strange-struggles-continue-in-the-fallout-of-recent-pride-month-controversy/"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.boundingintosports.com/2023/06/dodgers-strange-struggles-continue-in-the-fallout-of-recent-pride-month-controversy/</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>Dodgers&rsquo; Strange Struggles Continue In The Fallout Of Recent &lsquo;Pride&rsquo; Month Controversy</strong></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The Los Angeles Dodgers&rsquo; 2023 season has been one of the strangest ones that Tinsel Town has ever seen. Between a front office that has struggled to explain the team&rsquo;s social stances and a team that has been playing well below its potential, both manager Dave Roberts and team president Andrew Friedman have been left searching for answers.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The Dodgers are by no means out of the race, sitting in third place in the NL West. They entered play on Wednesday with a 40-33 record, 3.5 games behind the Arizona Diamondbacks. In between Los Angeles and The Snakes stand the second-place Giants, with the Dodgers currently one game behind their rival. In their last 10 games, the Boys in Blue have gone an underwhelming 4-6 and are currently marred by mediocre momentum and morale.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">So, there&rsquo;s still a strong possibility that Roberts leads the squad to another playoff berth, and the year is certainly not a lost cause. There&rsquo;s also no reason to believe that the players suddenly forgot how to hit, catch, and throw, just because of the storm that swirled around the organization recently.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Still, it&rsquo;s not a stretch to wonder if all the off-the-field distractions haven&rsquo;t affected the club&rsquo;s psyche. The media scrutiny surrounding the team has been at a fever pitch surrounding their inclusion of the LGBTQ group, The Sisters of Perpetual Indulgence, at last week&rsquo;s Pride Night event. The organization, often labeled an anti-Catholic hate group, was even awarded during the team&rsquo;s recognition of the LGBTQ community.</span></p>]]></description>
   <author><![CDATA[Garrison Hardie]]></author>
   <enclosure url="https://app.dropwave.io/episode/7bf225dd-f6dd-42dd-b556-11e3ea899ac4/daily-news-brief-for-friday-june-23rd-2023.mp3" length="484" type="audio/mp3"/>
   <guid isPermaLink="false"><![CDATA[7bf225dd-f6dd-42dd-b556-11e3ea899ac4]]></guid>
   <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jun 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
   <source url=""><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></source>
   <itunes:author><![CDATA[Garrison Hardie]]></itunes:author>
   <itunes:image href="https://assets-cdn2.dropwave.io/2ab40ac0-e99d-4f25-a6d2-541d2c9b290a/cover-art/hUZu1H9lrRY0wXg66WHC8eLwYBA3hbRNTAHQmHt2.png"/>
   <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
   <itunes:duration>484</itunes:duration>
   <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title><![CDATA[1 Kings 18:17-21 [Up and Ready]]]></title>
   <link>https://app.dropwave.io/episode/10c37f4b-0067-4a81-a4bb-670f84f4dd03/1-kings-1817-21.mp3</link>
   <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
   <author><![CDATA[Mark Dewey]]></author>
   <enclosure url="https://app.dropwave.io/episode/10c37f4b-0067-4a81-a4bb-670f84f4dd03/1-kings-1817-21.mp3" length="330" type="audio/mp3"/>
   <guid isPermaLink="false"><![CDATA[10c37f4b-0067-4a81-a4bb-670f84f4dd03]]></guid>
   <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jun 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
   <source url=""><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></source>
   <itunes:author><![CDATA[Mark Dewey]]></itunes:author>
   <itunes:image href="https://assets-cdn2.dropwave.io/60c9e557-5882-401d-abb8-06de47904be4/cover-art/zZ8CYlYBUAUu8KNyZzjE092h2WlBblW8upM7tmFg.png"/>
   <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
   <itunes:duration>330</itunes:duration>
   <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title><![CDATA[Bryson Gray: Reclaiming the Rainbow on CrossPoliticÂ  [CrossPolitic Show]]]></title>
   <link>https://app.dropwave.io/episode/56fa0b60-6035-4841-9c38-3a8d8c3bedf9/bryson-gray-reclaiming-the-rainbow-on-crosspolitic.mp3</link>
   <description><![CDATA[<p class="p1"><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Bryson Gray: Reclaiming the Rainbow on CrossPolitic<span class="Apple-converted-space">&nbsp;</span></span></p>
<p class="p2">&nbsp;</p>
<p class="p1"><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">More from Bryson Gray:</span></p>
<p class="p3"><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://www.brysoncreates2.com/">https://www.brysoncreates2.com/</a><span class="s1"><span class="Apple-converted-space">&nbsp;</span></span></span></p>
<p class="p2">&nbsp;</p>
<p class="p1"><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Sign up for the FLF Conference at the Ark Encounter! (Oct 11-14)</span></p>
<p class="p3"><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><span class="s2"><a href="https://flfnetwork.com/the-politics-of-six-days-creation-conference/">https://flfnetwork.com/the-politics-of-six-days-creation-conference/</a></span><span class="s1"><span class="Apple-converted-space">&nbsp;</span></span></span></p>
<p class="p1">&nbsp;</p>
<p class="p1"><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The Article in CNN:</span></p>
<p class="p3"><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://www.cnn.com/2023/06/22/entertainment/james-cameron-titanic-sub/index.html">https://www.cnn.com/2023/06/22/entertainment/james-cameron-titanic-sub/index.html</a><span class="s1"><span class="Apple-converted-space">&nbsp;</span></span></span></p>]]></description>
   <author><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></author>
   <enclosure url="https://app.dropwave.io/episode/56fa0b60-6035-4841-9c38-3a8d8c3bedf9/bryson-gray-reclaiming-the-rainbow-on-crosspolitic.mp3" length="2106" type="audio/mp3"/>
   <guid isPermaLink="false"><![CDATA[56fa0b60-6035-4841-9c38-3a8d8c3bedf9]]></guid>
   <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jun 2023 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
   <source url=""><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></source>
   <itunes:author><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></itunes:author>
   <itunes:image href="https://assets-cdn2.dropwave.io/11635dce-94e7-41b8-9261-5c1fc2cc5ebe/cover-art/wvkjcfd3tfj69XopdryYkSF8m1k4KHuikzJF1KzC.jpg"/>
   <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
   <itunes:duration>2106</itunes:duration>
   <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title><![CDATA[The Unholy Globalist Trinity and Their Tyrannical Future â€Utopiaâ€ ft. Bull Bitcoinâ€™s Francis Pouliot [Liberty Dispatch]]]></title>
   <link>https://app.dropwave.io/episode/f7e689bb-2459-42ea-b7f2-e69fb4b18a6e/the-unholy-globalist-trinity-and-their-tyrannical-future-utopia-ft-bull-bitcoins-francis-pouliot.mp3</link>
   <description><![CDATA[<p class="p1"><strong>Liberty Dispatch</strong> ~ June 22, 2023<br />On this episode of the Dispatch, hosts Andrew and Matty look deep-dive into the continued machinations of the globalist tyrants in the UN, WEF, and WHO. As it turns out, Canada is eager to implement all of their dystopian ideas. You're not going to want to miss this one.<br /><br /><strong>WATCH - UN SDGs: The Roadmap to a Tyrannical Future: </strong><a href="https://rumble.com/v2q1dei-uns-17-sustainable-development-goals-sdgs-a-roadmap-to-a-tyrannical-utopia.html">https://rumble.com/v2q1dei-uns-17-sustainable-development-goals-sdgs-a-roadmap-to-a-tyrannical-utopia.html</a>;<br /><br /><strong style="font-family: '-apple-system', BlinkMacSystemFont, 'Segoe UI', Roboto, Oxygen, Ubuntu, Cantarell, 'Open Sans', 'Helvetica Neue', sans-serif;">[Segment 1] - Globalism Abroad:<br /></strong><a href="http://lifesitenews.com/news/wef-document-calls-for-limiting-private-car-use-drastic-reduction-in-the-number-of-cars-by-2050">http://lifesitenews.com/news/wef-document-calls-for-limiting-private-car-use-drastic-reduction-in-the-number-of-cars-by-2050</a>;<br /><a href="https://slaynews.com/news/wef-ai-rewrite-bible-create-religions-actually-correct">https://slaynews.com/news/wef-ai-rewrite-bible-create-religions-actually-correct</a>;<br /><a href="https://expose-news.com/2023/04/26/who-is-forging-ahead-with-plans-to-implement">https://expose-news.com/2023/04/26/who-is-forging-ahead-with-plans-to-implement</a>;<br /><a href="https://europeanconservative.com/articles/news/dystopia-eu-and-who-sign-global-vaccine-passport-deal">https://europeanconservative.com/articles/news/dystopia-eu-and-who-sign-global-vaccine-passport-deal</a>;<br /><span style="font-family: '-apple-system', BlinkMacSystemFont, 'Segoe UI', Roboto, Oxygen, Ubuntu, Cantarell, 'Open Sans', 'Helvetica Neue', sans-serif;"><a href="https://www.un.org/sites/un2.un.org/files/our-common-agenda-policy-brief-information-integrity-en.pdf">https://www.un.org/sites/un2.un.org/files/our-common-agenda-policy-brief-information-integrity-en.pdf</a>;<br /></span><br /><strong>[Segment 2] - Globalism at Home ft. Interview with Kelly Hale:<br /></strong><a href="https://www.canada.ca/en/government/system/laws/developing-improving-federal-regulations/modernizing-regulations/agile-nations.html">https://www.canada.ca/en/government/system/laws/developing-improving-federal-regulations/modernizing-regulations/agile-nations.html</a><br /><a href="https://www.parl.ca/DocumentViewer/en/44-1/bill/C-47/first-reading">https://www.parl.ca/DocumentViewer/en/44-1/bill/C-47/first-reading</a><br /><a href="https://www.infrastructure.gc.ca/sc-vi/map-applications.php">https://www.infrastructure.gc.ca/sc-vi/map-applications.php</a><br /><a href="https://www.infrastructure.gc.ca/cities-villes/index-eng.html">https://www.infrastructure.gc.ca/cities-villes/index-eng.html</a><br /><a href="https://globalnews.ca/news/9681894/bank-of-canada-public-consultations-digital-currency">https://globalnews.ca/news/9681894/bank-of-canada-public-consultations-digital-currency</a><br /><a href="https://www.bankofcanada.ca/digitaldollar">https://www.bankofcanada.ca/digitaldollar</a><br /><strong><br />[Segment 3] - Interview ft. Bull Bitcoin's Francis Pouliot</strong><br /><strong><br />JOIN PASTORS, CHURCHES, AND CHRISTIAN COMMUNITIES ACROSS CANADA WITH LCC'S NEWEST INITIATIVE, "<em>TRUE READINGS FROM TRUE ROYALTY."&nbsp; <br /></em></strong><strong>Sign up today:&nbsp;</strong><a href="https://libertycoalitioncanada.com/storyhour/">https://libertycoalitioncanada.com/storyhour/</a>&nbsp;<br /><br /><strong>Support Josh's Stand and Help Us Defend His Liberties! Sign Our Petition Here: <a href="https://libertycoalitioncanada.com/i-stand-with-josh-alexander/">https://libertycoalitioncanada.com/i-stand-with-josh-alexander/</a>;<br /><br /></strong><strong>SHOW SPONSORS:<br /></strong><strong>Join&nbsp;<em>Red Balloon&nbsp;</em>Today!:</strong> <a href="https://www.redballoon.work/lcc;">https://www.redballoon.work/lcc;</a>&nbsp;<br /><strong>Invest with Rocklinc:</strong> <a href="mailto:info@rocklinc.com">info@rocklinc.com</a>&nbsp;or call them at 905-631-546;&nbsp;<br /><strong>Diversify Your Money with Bull Bitcoin:&nbsp;</strong><a href="https://mission.bullbitcoin.com/lcc">https://mission.bullbitcoin.com/lcc</a>;<br /><strong>BarterPay: </strong><a href="https://barterpay.ca/">https://barterpay.ca/</a>;&nbsp; <strong>Barter It: </strong><a href="https://vip.barterit.ca/launch;">https://vip.barterit.ca/launch; </a><strong><br />Carpe Fide - "Seize the Faith": Store: </strong><a href="https://carpe-fide.myshopify.com/">https://carpe-fide.myshopify.com</a><a href="https://carpe-fide.myshopify.com/">/</a>, use Promo Code LCC10 for 10% off (US Store Only), or shop Canadian @ <a href="https://canadacarpefide.myshopify.com/">https://canadacarpefide.myshopify.com/</a> | <strong>Podcast: </strong><a href="https://www.carpefide.com/episodes">https://www.carpefide.com/episodes</a>;<br /><br /><strong>Sick of Mainstream Media Lies? Help Support Independent Media! DONATE TO LCC TODAY!:&nbsp;</strong><strong><a href="https://libertycoalitioncanada.com/donate/">https://libertycoalitioncanada.com/donate/</a>&nbsp;</strong><strong> &nbsp;</strong></p>
<p class="p1">&nbsp;</p>
<p class="p1">Please Support us in bringing you honest, truthful reporting and analysis from a Christian perspective.<br /><br /><strong>SUBSCRIBE TO OUR SHOWS/CHANNELS:<br /></strong>LIBERTY DISPATCH PODCAST: <a href="https://libertydispatch.podbean.com">https://libertydispatch.podbean.com</a>; <a href="https://rumble.com/c/c-1687093">https://rumble.com/LDshow</a>;&nbsp;<br />OPEN MIKE WITH MICHAEL THIESSEN: <a href="https://openmikewithmichaelthiessen.podbean.com">https://openmikewithmichaelthiessen.podbean.com</a>; <a href="https://rumble.com/c/c-1412501">https://rumble.com/openmike</a>;<br />THE OTHER CLUB: <a href="https://rumble.com/c/c-2541984">https://rumble.com/c/c-2541984</a>;&nbsp;<br />THE LIBERTY LOUNGE WITH TIM TYSOE: <a href="https://rumble.com/LLwTT">https://rumble.com/LLwTT</a>;<br /><br /><strong>CONTACT US:</strong><br />Questions/comments about podcasts/news/analysis: <a href="mailto:mailbag@libertycoalitioncanada.com">mailbag@libertycoalitioncanada.com</a>;<br />Questions/comments about donations: <a href="mailto:give@libertycoalitioncanada.com">give@libertycoalitioncanada.com</a>;<br />Questions/comments that are church-related: <a href="mailto:churches@libertycoalitioncanada.com">churches@libertycoalitioncanada.com</a>;<br />General Inquiries: <a href="mailto:info@libertycoalitioncanada.com">info@libertycoalitioncanada.com</a>.&nbsp;<br /><br /></p>
<p class="p1"><strong>STAY UP-TO-DATE ON ALL THINGS LCC:<br /></strong>Gab: <a href="https://gab.com/libertycoalitioncanada">https://gab.com/libertycoalitioncanada</a>&nbsp;</p>
<p class="p2">Telegram: <a href="https://t.me/libertycoalitioncanadanews">https://t.me/libertycoalitioncanadanews</a>&nbsp;</p>
<p class="p2">Instagram: <a href="https://instagram.com/libertycoalitioncanada">https://instagram.com/libertycoalitioncanada</a>&nbsp;</p>
<p class="p2">Facebook: <a href="https://facebook.com/LibertyCoalitionCanada">https://facebook.com/LibertyCoalitionCanada</a>&nbsp;</p>
<p class="p2">Twitter: @LibertyCCanada - <a href="https://twitter.com/LibertyCCanada">https://twitter.com/LibertyCCanada</a>&nbsp;</p>
<p class="p2">Rumble: <a href="https://rumble.com/user/LibertyCoalitionCanada">https://rumble.com/user/LibertyCoalitionCanada</a>&nbsp;</p>
<p class="p2">YouTube: <a href="https://www.youtube.com/@liberty4canada">https://www.youtube.com/@liberty4canada</a> -&nbsp;<strong>WE GOT CANCELLED AGAIN!!!</strong></p>
<p class="p1"><strong>Please LIKE, SUBSCRIBE, RATE &amp; REVIEW and SHARE it with others!</strong></p>]]></description>
   <author><![CDATA[Matthew Hallick, Andrew DeBartolo, SDG Media]]></author>
   <enclosure url="https://app.dropwave.io/episode/f7e689bb-2459-42ea-b7f2-e69fb4b18a6e/the-unholy-globalist-trinity-and-their-tyrannical-future-utopia-ft-bull-bitcoins-francis-pouliot.mp3" length="6210" type="audio/mp3"/>
   <guid isPermaLink="false"><![CDATA[f7e689bb-2459-42ea-b7f2-e69fb4b18a6e]]></guid>
   <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
   <source url=""><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></source>
   <itunes:author><![CDATA[Matthew Hallick, Andrew DeBartolo, SDG Media]]></itunes:author>
   <itunes:image href="https://prod-assets-spc1.nyc3.digitaloceanspaces.com/69893365-4165-4498-b0ac-e9ddf57a000f/cover-art/E86eLfK3NgjrpuXtk9kW9Qv6KcfzQpkJpToltreR.png"/>
   <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
   <itunes:duration>6210</itunes:duration>
   <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title><![CDATA[The Deadly Sin of Gluttony [Leadership Now Podcast]]]></title>
   <link>https://app.dropwave.io/episode/e8919974-6899-48a6-9fc1-08ef03ce01c3/the-deadly-sin-of-gluttony.mp3</link>
   <description><![CDATA[<p>It's not popular to talk about, but gluttony is a deadly and rampant sin. In this episode, Dr. Aaron Rock explains exactly what the sin of gluttony is and how we can overcome it.</p>]]></description>
   <author><![CDATA[Aaron Rock, Chris Eelman]]></author>
   <enclosure url="https://app.dropwave.io/episode/e8919974-6899-48a6-9fc1-08ef03ce01c3/the-deadly-sin-of-gluttony.mp3" length="3199" type="audio/mp3"/>
   <guid isPermaLink="false"><![CDATA[e8919974-6899-48a6-9fc1-08ef03ce01c3]]></guid>
   <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jun 2023 18:31:00 +0000</pubDate>
   <source url=""><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></source>
   <itunes:author><![CDATA[Aaron Rock, Chris Eelman]]></itunes:author>
   <itunes:image href="https://assets-cdn2.dropwave.io/3312a6b0-2b88-4186-bfdd-e9c55d3d7e0f/cover-art/DJmJxOQEoRfGbs693sV6kEnKEGWstWUfdEXbQra8.png"/>
   <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
   <itunes:duration>3199</itunes:duration>
   <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title><![CDATA[Daily News Brief forThursday, June 22nd, 2023 [Daily News Brief]]]></title>
   <link>https://app.dropwave.io/episode/bad7d79d-46cf-4de8-8e54-6a5acf142f67/daily-news-brief-forthursday-june-22nd-2023.mp3</link>
   <description><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">This is Garrison Hardie with your CrossPolitic Daily News Brief forThursday, June 22nd, 2023.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>Gravity Jack:</strong></span></p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Gravity Jack is a full service digital agency specializing in the development of Virtual &amp; Augmented Reality experiences, mobile apps, blockchain and Web3 projects. Founded in 2009 as the first American agency to offer augmented reality, they even patented it; Gravity Jack's digital experiences have been a source of innovation for small business, Fortune 500 Companies, and the US Military. Get your vision in motion at </span><a href="http://www.gravityjack.com/"><span style="font-weight: 400;">gravityjack.com</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/americas/submarine-titantic-missing-submersible-tourists-latest-b2360568.html"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/americas/submarine-titantic-missing-submersible-tourists-latest-b2360568.html</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>Rescue hopes for missing Titanic submarine hinge on new &lsquo;banging&rsquo; sounds as 12 hours left&ndash; live</strong></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">There are now 12 hours of oxygen left in the missing Titan submersible as rescue efforts continue for the five passengers.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">A Canadian aircraft searching for the sub in the Atlantic Ocean detected intermittent &ldquo;banging&rdquo; noises from the vicinity of its last known location, the US Coast Guard said.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Crew searching for the missing sub heard banging sounds every 30 minutes on Tuesday and again four hours later on Wednesday after additional sonar devices were deployed.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">However, the US Coast Guard clarified that they &ldquo;don&rsquo;t know the source of the noise&rdquo;.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Aboard the Titan is CEO and founder of OceanGate Expeditions Stockton Rush, British billionaire explorer Hamish Harding, renowned French diver Paul-Henri Nargeolet and Pakistani businessman Shahzada Dawood and his 19-year-old son Suleman Dawood.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Mr Dawood&rsquo;s sister, Sabrina Dawood told Sky News that the Dawood family is solely focused on the rescue of her brother and nephew and hope for their safe return.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The watercraft submerged on Sunday morning from its support vessel to travel to the Titanic wreckage which sits at a depth of 12,500ft. About an hour and 45 minutes later, the Titan lost contact with its surface ship, the Polar Prince.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The Titan is equipped with a four-day emergency oxygen supply.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://notthebee.com/article/texas-christian-university-offers-queer-art-of-drag-class"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://notthebee.com/article/texas-christian-university-offers-queer-art-of-drag-class</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>Someone wanna tell me why Texas "Christian" University offers a "Queer Art of Drag" class?</strong></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Hey TCU, I think it's time for a name change.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Texas Christian University's Women and Gender Studies department offered a "Queer Art of Drag" class during the Spring 2023 semester. The course required students to give a performance as their own "drag persona."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">"Drag is an art form with a rich history of challenging dominant norms and systems of oppression; building queer community; and cultivating experiences of queer joy in a hostile world," the course website rads. "Critical drag explores drag performance as an outlet for social critique, and queer world making."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The syllabus also says students must create a "drag vision board," give an "in-class lip-sync performance," and make a "storyboard" for a final performance.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">A "My Drag Worksheet" assignment required students to create a name, a "drag greeting," a "lip-sync portfolio," and "strike a pose" for their drag persona.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Students were required to give their final presentation using their drag persona voice and submit a video performance for TCU's "Annual Night of Drag."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Why do I suggest TCU change its name? Hmm, let's see&hellip;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">"A woman shall not wear a man's garment, nor shall a man put on a woman's cloak, for whoever does these things is an abomination to the LORD your God," Deuteronomy 22:5 (ESV).</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://notthebee.com/article/huh-math-and-reading-scores-for-13-year-old-americans-are-the-lowest-theyve-been-in-decades-and-tanked-during-the-pandemic"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://notthebee.com/article/huh-math-and-reading-scores-for-13-year-old-americans-are-the-lowest-theyve-been-in-decades-and-tanked-during-the-pandemic</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>Math and reading scores for 13-year-old Americans are the lowest they've been in decades and tanked during the pandemic</strong></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Remember how we shut down all the schools for a virus that didn't put most children in danger?</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The math and reading performance of 13-year-olds in the United States has hit the lowest level in decades, according to test scores released today from the National Assessment of Educational Progress, the gold-standard federal exam.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The last time math performance was this low for 13-year-olds was in 1990. In reading, 2004.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Maybe we should have been listening to the experts who predicted "brain drain" and developmental consequences that would set America, and the world at large, back decades in education by shutting down schools for two years.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">A large body of research shows that most American children experienced academic struggles during the pandemic. It has also been clear that low-income students of color were most heavily affected by school closures and remote learning, which in some districts lasted more than a year.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">I heard many experts discussing this from 2020-2022, but most people probably didn't, because the Experts&trade; censored their peers from warning us. And yet the truth remains that some people did actually warn us that closing schools wasn't merely a 2-year setback, but a decision that would affect multiple generations to come.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The 13-year-olds who took this version of the NAEP exam last fall were 10 years old &mdash; and in fourth or fifth grade &mdash; when the pandemic began. Many were old enough to participate in remote learning without minute-to-minute adult assistance, as younger children often needed.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">But the ages of 10 to 13 are also a crucial period for mastering foundational skills, from multiplication to recognizing a character's feelings in a short narrative passage.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">"The bottom line &mdash; these results show that there are troubling gaps in the basic skills of these students," said Peggy Carr, commissioner of the National Center for Education Statistics, which gives the NAEP exam. "This is a huge-scale challenge that faces the nation."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">But it's okay, because proficiency is racist anyway. Civilization might not work without competent, educated people, but we'll feel nice when we're all equal in squalor. We can be the "quit" in equity!</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The percentage of 13-year-olds who reported reading for fun has also declined. Last fall, 31 percent said they "never or hardly ever" read for fun, compared to 22 percent in 2012.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Have you looked at the woke books they give these kids? No wonder it's not fun!</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Anyway, we might not have to wait long for the end to come, because while we talk about race and gender instead of teaching math, other countries like China are preparing their kids for engineering and war&hellip;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://www.theepochtimes.com/proposed-hate-speech-law-in-michigan-threatens-first-amendment-rights-conservatives-warn_5329978.html?utm_source=partner&amp;utm_campaign=travis_in_flint&amp;src_src=partner&amp;src_cmp=travis_in_flint"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.theepochtimes.com/proposed-hate-speech-law-in-michigan-threatens-first-amendment-rights-conservatives-warn_5329978.html?utm_source=partner&amp;utm_campaign=travis_in_flint&amp;src_src=partner&amp;src_cmp=travis_in_flint</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>Proposed &lsquo;Hate Speech&rsquo; Law in Michigan Threatens First Amendment Rights, Conservatives Warn</strong></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">A bill moving through the Democrat-controlled Michigan State Legislature would make it easier for prosecutors to bring felonious &ldquo;hate crime&rdquo; charges against dissident speech.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The possible implications for preachers, school administrators, teachers, parents, politicians, and citizen activists have alarmed conservatives concerned about the effect the bill may have on free speech.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The proposed legislation, HB 4474, would amend the state&rsquo;s Ethnic Intimidation Act of 1988 in order to consider it a hate crime if a person is accused of causing &ldquo;severe mental anguish&rdquo; to another individual by means of perceived verbal intimidation or harassment.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The amendment defines the words intimidate or harass as a &ldquo;willful course of conduct, involving repeated or continuing harassment of another individual that would cause a reasonable individual to feel terrorized, frightened, intimidated, threatened, harassed, or molested&hellip;&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">&ldquo;Words are malleable,&rdquo; Attorney David Kallman of the Great Lakes Justice Center (GLJC), a non-profit legal organization dedicated to preserving liberty in America, told The Epoch Times. &ldquo;They can be redefined by whoever is in power.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">&ldquo;Under the proposed statute, &lsquo;intimidate and harass&rsquo; can mean whatever the victim, or the authorities, want them to mean. The focus is on how the victim feels rather than on a clearly defined criminal act. This is a ridiculously vague and subjective standard,&rdquo; he said.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">&ldquo;The absence of intent makes no difference under this law. You are still guilty of the crime because the victim felt uncomfortable.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">&ldquo;The bill will lead to the prosecution of conservatives, pastors, and parents attending a school board meeting for simply expressing their opposition to the liberal agenda,&rdquo; Kallman said.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">A convicted violator could receive a fine of up to $10,000, up to five years in prison, or both.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The bill does provide the court with the option of an alternative sentence.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The text reads in part, &ldquo;An alternative sentence may include an order requiring the offender to complete a period of community service intended to enhance the offender&rsquo;s understanding of the impact of the offense upon the victim and wider community.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Michigan Attorney General Dana Nessel, a Democrat, testified that Michigan has the fifth-highest number of hate crimes committed per capita in the United States, with many more incidents not reported.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">She stated that HB 4474, and similar early judicial intervention measures, can help prevent initial non-violent hate crimes from escalating into murder.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">&ldquo;You can literally save lives,&rdquo; Nessel, a lesbian, told the committee.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Wayne County Prosecuting Attorney Kim Worthy, a Democrat, called the existing Ethnic Intimidation Law &ldquo;woefully inadequate.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">She testified that HB 4474 was a &ldquo;useful tool&rdquo; that would make it &ldquo;easier to prosecute real hate crimes&rdquo; and send a message that they are &ldquo;absolutely intolerable in this state.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">&ldquo;We have to protect our victims of hate crimes,&rdquo; Worthy said.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://www.dailywire.com/news/top-disney-diversity-equity-and-inclusion-officer-leaving-the-company?utm_source=facebook&amp;utm_medium=social&amp;utm_campaign=dwbrand"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.dailywire.com/news/top-disney-diversity-equity-and-inclusion-officer-leaving-the-company?utm_source=facebook&amp;utm_medium=social&amp;utm_campaign=dwbrand</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>Top Disney Diversity, Equity, And Inclusion Officer Leaving The Company</strong></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Disney&rsquo;s top Diversity, Equity, and Inclusion (DEI) officer will be leaving the entertainment giant to &ldquo;pursue other endeavors&rdquo; as the company continues to face headwinds from conservative customers over its promotion of LGBT themes and battles with Florida Republicans, according to a memo obtained by Variety.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">An internal memo sent to employees this week announced that Latondra Newton, the company&rsquo;s chief DEI officer and senior vice president, would be moving on from the company, Variety reported Tuesday. Newton will reportedly be moving to a board at a different corporation after six years at Disney.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">&ldquo;I&rsquo;m writing to share the news that Latondra Newton has decided to leave The Walt Disney Company to pursue other endeavors,&rdquo; the internal memo obtained by Variety read. &ldquo;Working alongside all of you and so many others, she has inspired countless cast members and employees to bring about lasting change and to help create a world where we can all feel safe and we all belong.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Julie Merges, currently a human resources executive at the company, will be the interim top DEI officer while a hiring search is conducted.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">At Disney, Newton worked &ldquo;with various business segments and leaders across the enterprise to build on Disney&rsquo;s commitment to produce entertainment that reflects a global audience and sustains a welcoming and inclusive workplace for everyone,&rdquo; according to the company.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Newton signed on to a letter from top Disney executives taking aim at &ldquo;racial disparities&rdquo; following the death of George Floyd in Minneapolis resolving to pursue &ldquo;real change.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Under Newton, Disney also began its &ldquo;Reimagine Tomorrow&rdquo; program which focused on &ldquo;representation&rdquo; for a host of different groups including increasing &ldquo;gender diversity,&rdquo; &ldquo;Black Representation,&rdquo; &ldquo;Female empowerment,&rdquo; &ldquo;Diverse Families,&rdquo; &ldquo;LGBTQIA+ Representation,&rdquo; and &ldquo;Middle Eastern Representation.&rdquo;&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">In recent years, Disney has come under fire from some customers over its insertion of LGBT themes into children&rsquo;s content, including the inclusion of a gay kiss into the 2022 &ldquo;Lightyear&rdquo; film which flopped at the box office. The company also voiced opposition to a Florida law intended to shield kids from being taught gender ideology and sexual topics in the classroom.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The company has also faced backlash online after video emerged of a man in a dress welcoming small children into a Disneyland boutique full of princess costumes.</span></p>]]></description>
   <author><![CDATA[Garrison Hardie]]></author>
   <enclosure url="https://app.dropwave.io/episode/bad7d79d-46cf-4de8-8e54-6a5acf142f67/daily-news-brief-forthursday-june-22nd-2023.mp3" length="713" type="audio/mp3"/>
   <guid isPermaLink="false"><![CDATA[bad7d79d-46cf-4de8-8e54-6a5acf142f67]]></guid>
   <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jun 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
   <source url=""><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></source>
   <itunes:author><![CDATA[Garrison Hardie]]></itunes:author>
   <itunes:image href="https://assets-cdn2.dropwave.io/2ab40ac0-e99d-4f25-a6d2-541d2c9b290a/cover-art/hUZu1H9lrRY0wXg66WHC8eLwYBA3hbRNTAHQmHt2.png"/>
   <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
   <itunes:duration>713</itunes:duration>
   <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title><![CDATA[Proverbs 28:13 [Up and Ready]]]></title>
   <link>https://app.dropwave.io/episode/c3c11615-af13-4619-be0d-ef0541dd9fda/proverbs-2813.mp3</link>
   <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
   <author><![CDATA[Mark Dewey]]></author>
   <enclosure url="https://app.dropwave.io/episode/c3c11615-af13-4619-be0d-ef0541dd9fda/proverbs-2813.mp3" length="255" type="audio/mp3"/>
   <guid isPermaLink="false"><![CDATA[c3c11615-af13-4619-be0d-ef0541dd9fda]]></guid>
   <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jun 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
   <source url=""><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></source>
   <itunes:author><![CDATA[Mark Dewey]]></itunes:author>
   <itunes:image href="https://assets-cdn2.dropwave.io/60c9e557-5882-401d-abb8-06de47904be4/cover-art/zZ8CYlYBUAUu8KNyZzjE092h2WlBblW8upM7tmFg.png"/>
   <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
   <itunes:duration>255</itunes:duration>
   <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title><![CDATA[Jonathan Edwards on Preaching, Praying, and Publishing [The Pugcast]]]></title>
   <link>https://app.dropwave.io/episode/b0daee41-c64e-4596-9329-26e6b845b34b/jonathan-edwards-on-preaching-praying-and-publishing.mp3</link>
   <description><![CDATA[<p class="p1">The Pugs are down one member today--Glenn couldn't make it. But don't panic, they are joined by another historian, Christian Cuthbert, authority on Jonathan Edwards and all around good guy. Jonathan shares the content of a paper he is presenting at the Jonathan Edwards conference in Belgium in July of 2023. Chris and Tom have fun interacting with Christian as the show is recorded in person at the beautiful Blake Center for Faith and Freedom of Hillsdale College, located in Somers, CT. It's a short show this week, but a rich one. Enjoy!</p>
<p class="p2">&nbsp;</p>
<p class="p3"><span class="s1">The Wartime Sermons of Jonathan Edwards: <a href="https://wipfandstock.com/9781725287877/the-wartime-sermons-of-jonathan-edwards/">https://wipfandstock.com/9781725287877/the-wartime-sermons-of-jonathan-edwards/</a></span></p>
<p class="p2">&nbsp;</p>
<p class="p3"><span class="s1">Learn about the Blake Center: <a href="https://blakecenter.hillsdale.edu/">https://blakecenter.hillsdale.edu/</a></span></p>
<p class="p2">&nbsp;</p>
<p class="p3"><span class="s1">Support the Pugcast on Patreon: <a href="https://www.patreon.com/thetheologypugcast?fbclid=IwAR17UHhfzjphO52C_kkZfursA_C784t0ldFix0wyB4fd-YOJpmOQ3dyqGf8">https://www.patreon.com/thetheologypugcast?fbclid=IwAR17UHhfzjphO52C_kkZfursA_C784t0ldFix0wyB4fd-YOJpmOQ3dyqGf8</a></span></p>
<p class="p2">&nbsp;</p>
<p class="p1">Check out The Good Life Podcast with Matt Carpenter: <a href="https://mattcarpenter.podbean.com/"><span class="s2">https://mattcarpenter.podbean.com/</span></a></p>]]></description>
   <author><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></author>
   <enclosure url="https://app.dropwave.io/episode/b0daee41-c64e-4596-9329-26e6b845b34b/jonathan-edwards-on-preaching-praying-and-publishing.mp3" length="2704" type="audio/mp3"/>
   <guid isPermaLink="false"><![CDATA[b0daee41-c64e-4596-9329-26e6b845b34b]]></guid>
   <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jun 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
   <source url=""><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></source>
   <itunes:author><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></itunes:author>
   <itunes:image href="https://assets-cdn2.dropwave.io/95888944-bdd8-4d76-b4ae-8875769ac332/cover-art/aiNC1kS3NVFxfOfz2ZHCCrTnthpK8XAqpLYOu323.jpg"/>
   <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
   <itunes:duration>2704</itunes:duration>
   <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title><![CDATA[Premium Coffee & Cigars: Building the Church - Glorying GodÂ  [CrossPolitic Show]]]></title>
   <link>https://app.dropwave.io/episode/bf9e0dcc-16f8-45c6-97a3-b5494f853463/premium-coffee-cigars-building-the-church-glorying-god.mp3</link>
   <description><![CDATA[<p class="p1"><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Premium Coffee &amp; Cigars: Building the Church - Glorying God<span class="Apple-converted-space">&nbsp;</span></span></p>
<p class="p2">&nbsp;</p>
<p class="p1"><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Cultivate435</span></p>
<p class="p3"><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://www.cultivate435.com/">https://www.cultivate435.com/</a><span class="s1"><span class="Apple-converted-space">&nbsp;</span></span></span></p>
<p class="p2">&nbsp;</p>
<p class="p1"><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Sign up for the FLF Conference at the Ark Encounter! (Oct 11-14)</span></p>
<p class="p3"><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><span class="s2"><a href="https://flfnetwork.com/the-politics-of-six-days-creation-conference/">https://flfnetwork.com/the-politics-of-six-days-creation-conference/</a></span><span class="s1"><span class="Apple-converted-space">&nbsp;</span></span></span></p>
<p class="p2">&nbsp;</p>
<p class="p3"><span class="s1" style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The Article in CNN: <a href="https://www.cnn.com/2023/06/17/europe/poland-lgbtq-march-government-intl/index.html">https://www.cnn.com/2023/06/18/americas/colombia-amazon-rainforest-rescue-indigenous-children-intl/index.html</a></span></p>]]></description>
   <author><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></author>
   <enclosure url="https://app.dropwave.io/episode/bf9e0dcc-16f8-45c6-97a3-b5494f853463/premium-coffee-cigars-building-the-church-glorying-god.mp3" length="2037" type="audio/mp3"/>
   <guid isPermaLink="false"><![CDATA[bf9e0dcc-16f8-45c6-97a3-b5494f853463]]></guid>
   <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jun 2023 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
   <source url=""><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></source>
   <itunes:author><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></itunes:author>
   <itunes:image href="https://assets-cdn2.dropwave.io/11635dce-94e7-41b8-9261-5c1fc2cc5ebe/cover-art/wvkjcfd3tfj69XopdryYkSF8m1k4KHuikzJF1KzC.jpg"/>
   <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
   <itunes:duration>2037</itunes:duration>
   <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title><![CDATA[THE OTHER CLUB on Pandemic Amnesty [The Other Club]]]></title>
   <link>https://app.dropwave.io/episode/eba8f384-119d-45f5-ad0f-63a7cc96a409/the-other-club-on-pandemic-amnesty.mp3</link>
   <description><![CDATA[<p class="p1"><strong>The Other Club</strong> <em>with Mike and Tim </em>~ June 21, 2023<br />On this episode of The Other Club, hosts Dr. Michael Thiessen and Tim Tysoe talk about pandemic amnesty and how to apply biblical principles of forgiveness to the COVID-19 situation in response to <em>Christianity Today</em>'s calls for pandemic amnesty: <a href="https://www.christianitytoday.com/ct/2023/may-web-only/covid-19-pandemic-amnesty-masks-vaccine-lockdown-church.html">https://www.christianitytoday.com/ct/2023/may-web-only/covid-19-pandemic-amnesty-masks-vaccine-lockdown-church.html</a>.<br /><br /><strong>Music:</strong> Sloan - Money City Maniacs. <br />Directed by Sloan and Mark Cutler From the album Navy Blues &copy; 1998 Two Minutes For Music Ltd.<br /><br /><strong>Episode Resources:<br /></strong>LET&rsquo;S DECLARE A PANDEMIC AMNESTY |&nbsp;<em>The Atlantic</em>: <a href="https://www.theatlantic.com/ideas/archive/2022/10/covid-response-forgiveness/671879/">https://www.theatlantic.com/ideas/archive/2022/10/covid-response-forgiveness/671879/</a>;<br />Trudeau Government knew about COVID jab side effects | <em>Life Site News</em>: <a href="https://www.lifesitenews.com/news/secret-memo-shows-trudeau-govt-knew-about-covid-vaccine-injuries-and-strategized-to-allay-fears">https://www.lifesitenews.com/news/secret-memo-shows-trudeau-govt-knew-about-covid-vaccine-injuries-and-strategized-to-allay-fears</a>;<br />More than 100 children suffered COVID jab seizures | <em>The</em> <em>Epoch Times</em>:&nbsp;<a href="https://www.theepochtimes.com/more-than-100-young-children-suffered-seizures-after-covid-vaccination-study_5321835.html">https://www.theepochtimes.com/more-than-100-young-children-suffered-seizures-after-covid-vaccination-study_5321835.html</a>;<br />Green monkey DNA found in COVID shots | <em>The</em> <em>Epoch Times</em>: <a href="https://www.theepochtimes.com/health/green-monkey-dna-found-in-covid-19-shots_5317587.html?src_src=partner&amp;src_cmp=goddeketal">https://www.theepochtimes.com/health/green-monkey-dna-found-in-covid-19-shots_5317587.html?src_src=partner&amp;src_cmp=goddeketal</a>;<br />JAMA reported myocarditis incidents after COVID shots |&nbsp;<em>JAMA Network</em>:&nbsp;<a href="https://jamanetwork.com/journals/jama/fullarticle/2788346">https://jamanetwork.com/journals/jama/fullarticle/2788346</a>;<br />COVID jabs causing largest blood clots ever |&nbsp;<em>Good Neighbour Group</em>: <a href="https://goodneighbourgroup.substack.com/p/covid-injections-causing-largest?publication_id=1164913&amp;post_id=127886137&amp;isFreemail=true">https://goodneighbourgroup.substack.com/p/covid-injections-causing-largest?publication_id=1164913&amp;post_id=127886137&amp;isFreemail=true</a>;<br />Pfizer funnelled $12 million to Anderson Cooper to promote jabs | <em>The Peoples Voice</em>: <a href="https://thepeoplesvoice.tv/pfizer-caught-funnelling-12-million-to-anderson-cooper-to-promote-mrna-jabs-to-americans">https://thepeoplesvoice.tv/pfizer-caught-funnelling-12-million-to-anderson-cooper-to-promote-mrna-jabs-to-americans</a>;<br />Zuckerberg admits they censored true information: <a href="https://twitter.com/kanekoathegreat/status/1667011470406860803">https://twitter.com/kanekoathegreat/status/1667011470406860803</a>;&nbsp;<br />Nurse about to be fired for not having a COVID jab | <em>LFPress</em>: <a href="https://lfpress.com/news/local-news/pregnant-london-nurse-whos-about-to-be-fired-why-is-covid-vaccine-still-mandatory">https://lfpress.com/news/local-news/pregnant-london-nurse-whos-about-to-be-fired-why-is-covid-vaccine-still-mandatory</a>;</p>
<p class="p1"><strong>JOIN PASTORS, CHURCHES, AND CHRISTIAN COMMUNITIES ACROSS CANADA WITH LCC'S NEWEST INITIATIVE, "<em>TRUE READINGS FROM TRUE ROYALTY."&nbsp; <br /></em></strong><strong>Sign up today:&nbsp;</strong><a href="https://libertycoalitioncanada.com/storyhour/">https://libertycoalitioncanada.com/storyhour/</a>&nbsp;<br /><br /><strong>Support Josh's Stand and Help Us Defend His Liberties! Sign Our Petition Here: <a href="https://libertycoalitioncanada.com/i-stand-with-josh-alexander/">https://libertycoalitioncanada.com/i-stand-with-josh-alexander/</a>;<br /><br /></strong><strong>SHOW SPONSORS:<br /></strong><strong>Join&nbsp;<em>Red Balloon&nbsp;</em>Today!:</strong> <a href="https://www.redballoon.work/lcc;">https://www.redballoon.work/lcc;</a>&nbsp;<br /><strong>Invest with Rocklinc:</strong> <a href="mailto:info@rocklinc.com">info@rocklinc.com</a>&nbsp;or call them at 905-631-546;&nbsp;<br /><strong>Diversify Your Money with Bull Bitcoin:&nbsp;</strong><a href="https://mission.bullbitcoin.com/lcc">https://mission.bullbitcoin.com/lcc</a>;<br /><strong>BarterPay: </strong><a href="https://barterpay.ca/">https://barterpay.ca/</a>;&nbsp; <strong>Barter It: </strong><a href="https://vip.barterit.ca/launch;">https://vip.barterit.ca/launch; </a><strong><br />Carpe Fide - "Seize the Faith": Store: </strong><a href="https://carpe-fide.myshopify.com/">https://carpe-fide.myshopify.com</a><a href="https://carpe-fide.myshopify.com/">/</a>, use Promo Code LCC10 for 10% off (US Store Only), or shop Canadian @ <a href="https://canadacarpefide.myshopify.com/">https://canadacarpefide.myshopify.com/</a> | <strong>Podcast: </strong><a href="https://www.carpefide.com/episodes">https://www.carpefide.com/episodes</a>;<br /><br /><strong>Sick of Mainstream Media Lies? Help Support Independent Media! DONATE TO LCC TODAY!:&nbsp;</strong><strong><a href="https://libertycoalitioncanada.com/donate/">https://libertycoalitioncanada.com/donate/</a>&nbsp;</strong><strong> &nbsp;</strong></p>
<p class="p1">Please Support us in bringing you honest, truthful reporting and analysis from a Christian perspective.<br /><br /><strong>SUBSCRIBE TO OUR SHOWS/CHANNELS:<br /></strong>LIBERTY DISPATCH PODCAST: <a href="https://libertydispatch.podbean.com">https://libertydispatch.podbean.com</a>; <a href="https://rumble.com/c/c-1687093">https://rumble.com/LDshow</a>;&nbsp;<br />OPEN MIKE WITH MICHAEL THIESSEN: <a href="https://openmikewithmichaelthiessen.podbean.com">https://openmikewithmichaelthiessen.podbean.com</a>; <a href="https://rumble.com/c/c-1412501">https://rumble.com/openmike</a>;<br />THE OTHER CLUB: <a href="https://rumble.com/c/c-2541984">https://rumble.com/c/c-2541984</a>;&nbsp;<br />THE LIBERTY LOUNGE WITH TIM TYSOE: <a href="https://rumble.com/LLwTT">https://rumble.com/LLwTT</a>;<br /><br /><strong>CONTACT US:</strong><br />Questions/comments about podcasts/news/analysis: <a href="mailto:mailbag@libertycoalitioncanada.com">mailbag@libertycoalitioncanada.com</a>;<br />Questions/comments about donations: <a href="mailto:give@libertycoalitioncanada.com">give@libertycoalitioncanada.com</a>;<br />Questions/comments that are church-related: <a href="mailto:churches@libertycoalitioncanada.com">churches@libertycoalitioncanada.com</a>;<br />General Inquiries: <a href="mailto:info@libertycoalitioncanada.com">info@libertycoalitioncanada.com</a>.&nbsp;<br /><br /></p>
<p class="p1"><strong>STAY UP-TO-DATE ON ALL THINGS LCC:<br /></strong>Gab: <a href="https://gab.com/libertycoalitioncanada">https://gab.com/libertycoalitioncanada</a>&nbsp;</p>
<p class="p2">Telegram: <a href="https://t.me/libertycoalitioncanadanews">https://t.me/libertycoalitioncanadanews</a>&nbsp;</p>
<p class="p2">Instagram: <a href="https://instagram.com/libertycoalitioncanada">https://instagram.com/libertycoalitioncanada</a>&nbsp;</p>
<p class="p2">Facebook: <a href="https://facebook.com/LibertyCoalitionCanada">https://facebook.com/LibertyCoalitionCanada</a>&nbsp;</p>
<p class="p2">Twitter: @LibertyCCanada - <a href="https://twitter.com/LibertyCCanada">https://twitter.com/LibertyCCanada</a>&nbsp;</p>
<p class="p2">Rumble: <a href="https://rumble.com/user/LibertyCoalitionCanada">https://rumble.com/user/LibertyCoalitionCanada</a>&nbsp;</p>
<p class="p2">YouTube: <a href="https://www.youtube.com/@liberty4canada">https://www.youtube.com/@liberty4canada</a> -&nbsp;<strong>WE GOT CANCELLED AGAIN!!!</strong></p>
<p class="p1"><strong>Please LIKE, SUBSCRIBE, RATE &amp; REVIEW and SHARE it with others!</strong></p>]]></description>
   <author><![CDATA[Dr. Michael Thiessen, Tim Tysoe, SDG MEDIA]]></author>
   <enclosure url="https://app.dropwave.io/episode/eba8f384-119d-45f5-ad0f-63a7cc96a409/the-other-club-on-pandemic-amnesty.mp3" length="3532" type="audio/mp3"/>
   <guid isPermaLink="false"><![CDATA[eba8f384-119d-45f5-ad0f-63a7cc96a409]]></guid>
   <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2023 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
   <source url=""><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></source>
   <itunes:author><![CDATA[Dr. Michael Thiessen, Tim Tysoe, SDG MEDIA]]></itunes:author>
   <itunes:image href="https://assets-cdn2.dropwave.io/fa60ae5a-cc30-4d09-a355-177a1f38db7f/cover-art/SJO39Qr6B4iH9RwEjgGma927R9ZeuSi8UCuniLIq.png"/>
   <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
   <itunes:duration>3532</itunes:duration>
   <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title><![CDATA[Daily News Brief for Wednesday, June 21st, 2023 [Daily News Brief]]]></title>
   <link>https://app.dropwave.io/episode/2c616940-0edd-4263-bd01-7cbdd4a78025/daily-news-brief-for-wednesday-june-21st-2023.mp3</link>
   <description><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">This is Garrison Hardie with your CrossPolitic Daily News Brief for Wednesday, June 21st, 2023.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>Story Real Estate:</strong></span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Home. It&rsquo;s where you build your legacy. Where traditions are started, seeds are planted, meals are shared, and stories are told. Home is where you prepare to go out into the world. Finding the home that&rsquo;s perfect for your family is a big job.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">&nbsp;</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Story Real Estate is Moscow&rsquo;s top real estate team. They give people real estate advice all over the country. Family homes, investments, land, new construction, or commercial&mdash; they know real estate.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">&nbsp;</span></p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">If you&rsquo;ve thought about a move to Moscow or anywhere in the country, reach out to get connected with a Story Real Estate agent. Wherever you&rsquo;re going, they can help guide you Home. Visit</span><a href="http://storyrealestate.com/"><span style="font-weight: 400;"> </span><span style="font-weight: 400;">storyrealestate.com</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;">.&nbsp;</span></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2023/06/20/its-official-student-loan-payments-will-restart-in-october.html"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.cnbc.com/2023/06/20/its-official-student-loan-payments-will-restart-in-october.html</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>It&rsquo;s official: Student loan payments will restart in October, Education Department says</strong></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Over the three-year-long pause on student loan payments, the U.S. Department of Education has repeatedly told borrowers their bills were set to resume, only to take it back and provide them more time.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">This time, however, the agency really means it.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The Education Department posted on its website that &ldquo;payments will be due starting in October,&rdquo; and a recent law passed by Congress will make changing that plan difficult.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">It will likely be a big adjustment for borrowers when the pandemic-era policy expires. Around 40 million Americans have debt from their education. The typical monthly bill is roughly $350.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">&ldquo;For many borrowers, the payment pause has been life altering &mdash; saving many from financial ruin and allowing others to finally get ahead financially,&rdquo; said Persis Yu, deputy executive director at the Student Borrower Protection Center.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">President Donald Trump first announced the stay on federal student loan bills and the accrual of interest in March 2020, when the coronavirus pandemic hit the U.S. and crippled the economy.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The pause has since been extended eight times.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Nearly all people eligible for the relief have taken advantage of it, with less than 1% of qualifying borrowers continuing to make payments on their education debt, according to an analysis by higher education expert Mark Kantrowitz.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">As a result of the policy, the average borrower likely saved around $15,000 in student loan payments, Kantrowitz said.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The Education Department notes on its financial aid website that &ldquo;Congress recently passed a law preventing further extensions of the payment pause.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">It is referring to the agreement reached between Republicans and Democrats to raise the nation&rsquo;s debt ceiling, which President Joe Biden signed into law in early June.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">In exchange for voting to increase the borrowing limit, Republicans demanded large cuts to federal spending. They sought to repeal Biden&rsquo;s executive action granting student loan forgiveness, but the Biden administration refused to agree to that.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">However, included in the deal was a provision that officially terminates the pause at the end of August.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Even before that agreement, the Biden administration had been preparing borrowers for their payments to resume by September.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The Education Department says borrowers will be expected to make their first post-pause payment in October. Meanwhile, interest will start accumulating on borrowers&rsquo; debt again on Sept. 1, the department says.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">As the Biden administration tries to ready millions of Americans to restart their student loan payments, there&rsquo;s one big open question that may make that preparation difficult: Most borrowers don&rsquo;t know what they&rsquo;ll owe in the fall.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">That&rsquo;s because the Supreme Court has yet to issue a verdict on the validity of Biden&rsquo;s plan to cancel up to $20,000 in student debt for borrowers. A decision is expected this month.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Around 37 million people would be eligible for some loan cancellation, Kantrowitz estimated.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Roughly a third of those with federal student loans, or 14 million people, would have their balances entirely forgiven by the president&rsquo;s program, according to an estimate by Kantrowitz. As a result, these borrowers won&rsquo;t owe anything come October.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">For those who still have a balance after the relief, the Education Department has said it plans to &ldquo;re-amortize&rdquo; borrowers&rsquo; lower debts. That&rsquo;s a wonky term that means it will recalculate people&rsquo;s monthly payment based on their lower tab and the number of months they have left on their repayment timeline.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Kantrowitz provided an example: Let&rsquo;s say a person currently owes $30,000 in student loans at a 5% interest rate.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Before the pandemic, they would have paid around $320 a month on a 10-year repayment term. If forgiveness goes through and that person gets $10,000 in relief, their total balance would be reduced by a third, and their monthly payment will drop by a third, to roughly $210 a month.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Education Department Undersecretary James Kvaal recently warned that if the administration is unable to deliver on Biden&rsquo;s loan forgiveness, delinquency and default rates could skyrocket.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The borrowers most in jeopardy of defaulting are those for whom Biden&rsquo;s policy would have wiped out their balance entirely, Kvaal said.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://townhall.com/tipsheet/madelineleesman/2023/06/19/ny-post-teacher-called-a-student-despicable-after-questioning-her-classmate-who-identifies-as-a-cat-n2624666"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://townhall.com/tipsheet/madelineleesman/2023/06/19/ny-post-teacher-called-a-student-despicable-after-questioning-her-classmate-who-identifies-as-a-cat-n2624666</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>Teacher Reportedly Calls Student &lsquo;Despicable&rsquo; for Challenging Peer Who &lsquo;Identifies As a Cat&rsquo;</strong></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">A 13-year-old girl and her friend were reportedly called &ldquo;despicable&rdquo; by one of their schoolteachers last week after one of them challenged their classmates about &ldquo;how she identifies as a cat" after a lesson about gender ideology.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The 13-year-old girl and her friend are reportedly students at Rye College in the United Kingdom. The school is affiliated with the Church of England, according to the New York Post. The students were in their end-of-year lesson on &ldquo;life education&rdquo; where they were told they can&rdquo;be who you want to be and how you identify is up to you.&rdquo;&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">After the lesson, one of the students asked her classmate: &ldquo;How can you identify as a cat when you&rsquo;re a girl?&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">As a result, the schoolteacher reprimanded the student and her friend and said that they were being reported to school officials. And, the teacher reportedly said that they would no longer be welcome at the school if they &ldquo;continued to express the view that only boys and girls exist&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The girls informed the teacher that their parents would agree with their views on gender ideology, that someone's gender is not different than their biological sex.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">&ldquo;Well that&rsquo;s very sad as well then,&rdquo; the teacher reportedly said in response, adding that &ldquo;if you don&rsquo;t like it you need to go to a different school.&rdquo;&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">A parent of another student at the school told The Telegraph that &ldquo;what bothers me is the shutting down of debate in such a threatening and aggressive manner, which I don&rsquo;t believe is appropriate in an educational setting.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">&ldquo;Regardless of the subject, education should serve to build awareness of differing points of view to widen the understanding of a subject. It shouldn&rsquo;t be a case of indoctrination,&rdquo; the parent added.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://thepostmillennial.com/crime-so-out-of-control-in-san-francisco-stores-are-locking-up-candy?utm_campaign=64487"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://thepostmillennial.com/crime-so-out-of-control-in-san-francisco-stores-are-locking-up-candy?utm_campaign=64487</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>Crime so out of control in San Francisco, stores are locking up candy</strong></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=78gt7pfjlCU"><strong>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=78gt7pfjlCU</strong></a><strong> - Play Video - 1:26-1:4</strong></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">San Francisco residents that are looking to satisy a sweet tooth will have to go through a series of extra steps as candy is now being locked up in stores amid rising crime in the not so 'golden' city.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">While Butterfingers, Reese's Peanut Butter Cups, Starbursts, and M&amp;M's are locked up behind bars, illegal drugs are readily available for consumers as they flow rampant down the city's streets that are plagued by urine, human feces, and homeless vagrants looking for their next hit.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">In order to fend off thieves, San Francisco store owners have taken extra measures to combat rampant retail theft and are locking up merchandise up and down store aisles, which now includes candy.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">A photo taken by the Daily Mail at a Walgreens store shows a mixture of America's favorite chocolate and gummy candies confined behind a sheer box with a lock on it. If consumers want to purchase a KitKat or a Hershey's Kiss, they will have to ring an alarm for a store associate to come and assist them in grabbing the item off of the shelf.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">&nbsp;</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">A security guard at the Walgreens on Powell Street which is home to San Francisco's famous cable cars told Daily Mail that, "Theft is constant."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">He told the outlet that a homeless man who stole from the store earlier in the day appeared a few hours later only to commit another theft.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Major businesses and retailers have recently announced that they are shuttering their locations in the once-booming downtown corridor, with all citing similar reasons for the departures: rampant retail theft, loss of foot traffic, homeless vagrants attacking employees, and other safety concerns.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">These businesses include Nordstroms, Whole Foods, T-Mobile, Walgreens, Old Navy, and now the entire Westfield shopping center.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">While the San Francisco City Council has weaponized the local criminal justice system, turning it into a revolving door for repeat offenders and enacting laws that prevent police making arrests for petty theft, a Muslim immigrant and business owner, whose store was recently ransacked by a pack of thieves, said that crime in the city is now worse than it is in both Afghanistan and Iraq.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://freebeacon.com/latest-news/biden-admin-gave-university-over-2m-for-monitoring-microaggressions/"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://freebeacon.com/latest-news/biden-admin-gave-university-over-2m-for-monitoring-microaggressions/</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>Biden Admin Gave University Over $2M For &lsquo;Monitoring Microaggressions&rsquo;</strong></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The National Institutes of Health has, since September 2021, been funding a $2.2 million program at the University of Miami examining how "microaggressions" affect "Black cisgender queer women" who have HIV.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">According to a grant listing from the Department of Health and Human Services, the program, known as Monitoring Microaggressions and Adversities to Generate Interventions for Change, seeks to discover how "comments, jokes, and behaviors that are demeaning to a marginalized group" affect health outcomes.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Queer black women with HIV "live at the intersection of multiple marginalized identities and within social structures that take a daily toll," the grant description states. However, the impact of microaggressions on this group has "largely been ignored."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The program is supervised by Sannisha Dale, an associate professor of psychology, who chairs the department&rsquo;s Diversity and Equity Committee.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Dale's first contact with the project was in 2019, according to the University&rsquo;s website. Through text messages and regular visits, the grant team monitored 151 women to understand how microaggressions affected their daily levels of distress and consumption of medication.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">"[Microagressions] can be someone saying, &lsquo;She doesn&rsquo;t look like she&rsquo;s positive,&rsquo; as if HIV has a face," Dale said. "Or &lsquo;I&rsquo;m HIV negative, I&rsquo;m clean,&rsquo; as if someone else is dirty."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The Biden administration has shown a willingness to shell out cash for LGBT initiatives. Biden&rsquo;s most recent budget proposal included a $400 million State Department program to help LGBTQ Africans access the internet. In January, the National Endowment for the Humanities awarded a grant to translate a gay dictionary into Spanish.</span></p>]]></description>
   <author><![CDATA[Garrison Hardie]]></author>
   <enclosure url="https://app.dropwave.io/episode/2c616940-0edd-4263-bd01-7cbdd4a78025/daily-news-brief-for-wednesday-june-21st-2023.mp3" length="685" type="audio/mp3"/>
   <guid isPermaLink="false"><![CDATA[2c616940-0edd-4263-bd01-7cbdd4a78025]]></guid>
   <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
   <source url=""><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></source>
   <itunes:author><![CDATA[Garrison Hardie]]></itunes:author>
   <itunes:image href="https://assets-cdn2.dropwave.io/2ab40ac0-e99d-4f25-a6d2-541d2c9b290a/cover-art/hUZu1H9lrRY0wXg66WHC8eLwYBA3hbRNTAHQmHt2.png"/>
   <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
   <itunes:duration>685</itunes:duration>
   <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title><![CDATA[Psalm 145:17-21 [Up and Ready]]]></title>
   <link>https://app.dropwave.io/episode/4aa59a3d-42de-4d23-a94d-99482b1a94d5/psalm-14517-21.mp3</link>
   <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
   <author><![CDATA[Mark Dewey]]></author>
   <enclosure url="https://app.dropwave.io/episode/4aa59a3d-42de-4d23-a94d-99482b1a94d5/psalm-14517-21.mp3" length="242" type="audio/mp3"/>
   <guid isPermaLink="false"><![CDATA[4aa59a3d-42de-4d23-a94d-99482b1a94d5]]></guid>
   <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
   <source url=""><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></source>
   <itunes:author><![CDATA[Mark Dewey]]></itunes:author>
   <itunes:image href="https://assets-cdn2.dropwave.io/60c9e557-5882-401d-abb8-06de47904be4/cover-art/zZ8CYlYBUAUu8KNyZzjE092h2WlBblW8upM7tmFg.png"/>
   <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
   <itunes:duration>242</itunes:duration>
   <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title><![CDATA[Death and Taxes: More Q&A on the Ten Commandments [The Ezra Institute Podcast for Cultural Reformation]]]></title>
   <link>https://app.dropwave.io/episode/8d8784b8-f53b-4f56-8756-4e2615033925/death-and-taxes-more-qa-on-the-ten-commandments.mp3</link>
   <description><![CDATA[<p>We answer some more questions that emerged out of the Ten Commandments series, dealing with issues of what happens to believers after they die, and responding to the claim that the state only stepped in to provide welfare benefits because the church failed in this job.</p>
<p>Plus, <a href="https://www.ezrainstitute.com/training-programs/worldview-leadership-academy/">scholarships are available for the Worldview Leadership Academy</a>, and a staffing announcement that we're pumped for.</p>]]></description>
   <author><![CDATA[Joe Boot, Ryan Eras, Nate Wright]]></author>
   <enclosure url="https://app.dropwave.io/episode/8d8784b8-f53b-4f56-8756-4e2615033925/death-and-taxes-more-qa-on-the-ten-commandments.mp3" length="4230" type="audio/mp3"/>
   <guid isPermaLink="false"><![CDATA[8d8784b8-f53b-4f56-8756-4e2615033925]]></guid>
   <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2023 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
   <source url=""><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></source>
   <itunes:author><![CDATA[Joe Boot, Ryan Eras, Nate Wright]]></itunes:author>
   <itunes:image href="https://assets-cdn2.dropwave.io/1c3a97bd-65b0-4aec-bb35-3a1b6eec5d2c/cover-art/4rDIhLUsGj1xuXpLJYNdtwtbungA78glNHA7dOd9.png"/>
   <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
   <itunes:duration>4230</itunes:duration>
   <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title><![CDATA[Conservatives Gone Gay: Dodgers & TPUSA w/ Jon Root [CrossPolitic Show]]]></title>
   <link>https://app.dropwave.io/episode/8e5699d6-21b3-46ad-a155-5adc79c2b4c3/conservatives-gone-gay-dodgers-tpusa-w-jon-root.mp3</link>
   <description><![CDATA[<p class="p1"><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Conservatives Gone Gay: Dodgers &amp; TPUSA w/ Jon Root</span></p>
<p class="p2">&nbsp;</p>
<p class="p1"><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Support Us &amp; Sign up for a FLF Club Membership!<span class="Apple-converted-space">&nbsp;</span></span></p>
<p class="p3"><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><span class="s1"><a href="https://flfnetwork.com/product/fightlaughfestclub/?attribute_member-tier=silver-monthly">https://flfnetwork.com/product/fightlaughfestclub/?attribute_member-tier=silver-monthly</a></span><span class="s2"><span class="Apple-converted-space">&nbsp;</span></span></span></p>
<p class="p1">&nbsp;</p>
<p class="p1"><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Sign up for the FLF Conference at the Ark Encounter! (Oct 11-14)</span></p>
<p class="p3"><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><span class="s1"><a href="https://flfnetwork.com/the-politics-of-six-days-creation-conference/">https://flfnetwork.com/the-politics-of-six-days-creation-conference/</a></span><span class="s2"><span class="Apple-converted-space">&nbsp;</span></span></span></p>
<p class="p2">&nbsp;</p>
<p class="p3"><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><span class="s2">The Article in CNN: <a href="https://www.cnn.com/2023/06/17/europe/poland-lgbtq-march-government-intl/index.html">https://www.cnn.com/2023/06/17/europe/poland-lgbtq-march-government-intl/index.html</a></span><span class="Apple-converted-space">&nbsp;</span></span></p>]]></description>
   <author><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></author>
   <enclosure url="https://app.dropwave.io/episode/8e5699d6-21b3-46ad-a155-5adc79c2b4c3/conservatives-gone-gay-dodgers-tpusa-w-jon-root.mp3" length="2328" type="audio/mp3"/>
   <guid isPermaLink="false"><![CDATA[8e5699d6-21b3-46ad-a155-5adc79c2b4c3]]></guid>
   <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2023 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
   <source url=""><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></source>
   <itunes:author><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></itunes:author>
   <itunes:image href="https://assets-cdn2.dropwave.io/11635dce-94e7-41b8-9261-5c1fc2cc5ebe/cover-art/wvkjcfd3tfj69XopdryYkSF8m1k4KHuikzJF1KzC.jpg"/>
   <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
   <itunes:duration>2328</itunes:duration>
   <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title><![CDATA[Where Thereâ€™s Smoke, Thereâ€™s Fire: Trudeauâ€™s Canada is on Fire, Literally and Figuratively [Liberty Dispatch]]]></title>
   <link>https://app.dropwave.io/episode/5235749c-200a-4938-8f8f-57589a3db81b/heres-smoke-theres-fire-trudeaus-canada-is-on-fire-literally-and-figuratively.mp3</link>
   <description><![CDATA[<p class="p1"><strong>Liberty Dispatch</strong> ~ June 20, 2023<br />On this episode of the Dispatch, hosts Andrew and Matty look at the recent massive forest fires in Canada and examine the dumpster fire that is our Prime Tyrant, Justin Trudeau.&nbsp;<br /><br /><strong style="font-family: '-apple-system', BlinkMacSystemFont, 'Segoe UI', Roboto, Oxygen, Ubuntu, Cantarell, 'Open Sans', 'Helvetica Neue', sans-serif;">[Segment 1] - Raging Wildfires in Canada: Who's to Blame? - Climate Change, Arson, or Foolish Green Policies <strong>(08:05-21:17)</strong>:<br /></strong>Satellite Footage of Quebec Wildfires Raises Red Flags | <em>Life Site News</em>: <a href="https://www.lifesitenews.com/news/satellite-footage-raises-possibility-that-arson-not-climate-change-theory-to-blame-for-quebec-fires">https://www.lifesitenews.com/news/satellite-footage-raises-possibility-that-arson-not-climate-change-theory-to-blame-for-quebec-fires</a>;<br />Media Blames Canadian Wildfires on Climate Change Despite Evidence to the Contrary | <em>Life Site News</em>: <a href="https://www.lifesitenews.com/news/media-blames-climate-change-for-canadian-wildfires-despite-arrest-of-multiple-arsonists">www.lifesitenews.com/news/media-blames-climate-change-for-canadian-wildfires-despite-arrest-of-multiple-arsonists</a>;<br />U.S. Forest Fires Aren't Even Close to Historic Highs | <em>FEE</em>: <a href="https://fee.org/articles/forest-fires-aren-t-at-historic-highs-in-the-united-states-not-even-close/">https://fee.org/articles/forest-fires-aren-t-at-historic-highs-in-the-united-states-not-even-close/</a>;&nbsp;<br />Canada&rsquo;s burning because of bad forest policy, not climate change <span style="font-family: '-apple-system', BlinkMacSystemFont, 'Segoe UI', Roboto, Oxygen, Ubuntu, Cantarell, 'Open Sans', 'Helvetica Neue', sans-serif;">| </span><em style="font-family: '-apple-system', BlinkMacSystemFont, 'Segoe UI', Roboto, Oxygen, Ubuntu, Cantarell, 'Open Sans', 'Helvetica Neue', sans-serif;">Fraser Institute</em><span style="font-family: '-apple-system', BlinkMacSystemFont, 'Segoe UI', Roboto, Oxygen, Ubuntu, Cantarell, 'Open Sans', 'Helvetica Neue', sans-serif;">: </span><a style="font-family: '-apple-system', BlinkMacSystemFont, 'Segoe UI', Roboto, Oxygen, Ubuntu, Cantarell, 'Open Sans', 'Helvetica Neue', sans-serif;" href="https://www.fraserinstitute.org/article/canadas-burning-because-of-bad-forest-policy-not-climate-change">https://www.fraserinstitute.org/article/canadas-burning-because-of-bad-forest-policy-not-climate-change</a><span style="font-family: '-apple-system', BlinkMacSystemFont, 'Segoe UI', Roboto, Oxygen, Ubuntu, Cantarell, 'Open Sans', 'Helvetica Neue', sans-serif;">;&nbsp;<br /></span>Blackouts and Fires Caused by California&rsquo;s Ineffective Green Policies <span style="font-family: '-apple-system', BlinkMacSystemFont, 'Segoe UI', Roboto, Oxygen, Ubuntu, Cantarell, 'Open Sans', 'Helvetica Neue', sans-serif;">| </span><em style="font-family: '-apple-system', BlinkMacSystemFont, 'Segoe UI', Roboto, Oxygen, Ubuntu, Cantarell, 'Open Sans', 'Helvetica Neue', sans-serif;">Daily Signal</em><span style="font-family: '-apple-system', BlinkMacSystemFont, 'Segoe UI', Roboto, Oxygen, Ubuntu, Cantarell, 'Open Sans', 'Helvetica Neue', sans-serif;">: </span><a style="font-family: '-apple-system', BlinkMacSystemFont, 'Segoe UI', Roboto, Oxygen, Ubuntu, Cantarell, 'Open Sans', 'Helvetica Neue', sans-serif;" href="https://www.dailysignal.com/2020/08/28/blackouts-and-fires-caused-by-californias-ineffective-green-policies">https://www.dailysignal.com/2020/08/28/blackouts-and-fires-caused-by-californias-ineffective-green-policies</a><span style="font-family: '-apple-system', BlinkMacSystemFont, 'Segoe UI', Roboto, Oxygen, Ubuntu, Cantarell, 'Open Sans', 'Helvetica Neue', sans-serif;">;<br /></span>Glendon woman charged with 32 counts of arson <span style="font-family: '-apple-system', BlinkMacSystemFont, 'Segoe UI', Roboto, Oxygen, Ubuntu, Cantarell, 'Open Sans', 'Helvetica Neue', sans-serif;">| </span><em style="font-family: '-apple-system', BlinkMacSystemFont, 'Segoe UI', Roboto, Oxygen, Ubuntu, Cantarell, 'Open Sans', 'Helvetica Neue', sans-serif;">Lakeland Today</em><span style="font-family: '-apple-system', BlinkMacSystemFont, 'Segoe UI', Roboto, Oxygen, Ubuntu, Cantarell, 'Open Sans', 'Helvetica Neue', sans-serif;">: </span><a style="font-family: '-apple-system', BlinkMacSystemFont, 'Segoe UI', Roboto, Oxygen, Ubuntu, Cantarell, 'Open Sans', 'Helvetica Neue', sans-serif;" href="https://www.lakelandtoday.ca/local-news/glendon-woman-charged-with-32-counts-of-arson-3844982">https://www.lakelandtoday.ca/local-news/glendon-woman-charged-with-32-counts-of-arson-3844982</a><span style="font-family: '-apple-system', BlinkMacSystemFont, 'Segoe UI', Roboto, Oxygen, Ubuntu, Cantarell, 'Open Sans', 'Helvetica Neue', sans-serif;">;<br /><br /></span><strong>OPEN MIKE - Bob Murphy: The Economic INSANITY of the Green Agenda:</strong> <a href="https://rumble.com/v10zwgi-episode-7-bob-murphy-the-economic-insanity-of-the-green-agenda.html">https://rumble.com/v10zwgi-episode-7-bob-murphy-the-economic-insanity-of-the-green-agenda.html</a>;<br /><br /><strong>[Segment 2] - The Smoke of Scandal Exposes the Political Fires of Trudeau's Corruption (22:10-42:29):<br /></strong>First Report - The Right Honourable David Johnston, Independent Special Rapporteur on Foreign Interference | <em>Government of Canada</em>: <a href="https://www.canada.ca/en/democratic-institutions/services/reports/first-report-david-johnston-independent-special-rapporteur-foreign-interference.html">https://www.canada.ca/en/democratic-institutions/services/reports/first-report-david-johnston-independent-special-rapporteur-foreign-interference.html</a>;<br />Erin O'Toole's Response to report | <em>The</em> <em>Globe and Mail</em>: <a href="https://www.theglobeandmail.com/opinion/article-i-met-with-david-johnston-for-his-report-heres-what-happened/">https://www.theglobeandmail.com/opinion/article-i-met-with-david-johnston-for-his-report-heres-what-happened/;</a><br />Special rapporteur, Johnston rejects call to 'step aside' after majority of MPs vote for him to resign | <em>CTV NEWS:</em> <a href="https://www.ctvnews.ca/politics/special-rapporteur-johnston-rejects-call-to-step-aside-after-majority-of-mps-vote-for-him-to-resign-1.6421300">https://www.ctvnews.ca/politics/special-rapporteur-johnston-rejects-call-to-step-aside-after-majority-of-mps-vote-for-him-to-resign-1.6421300</a>;&nbsp;<br />Johnston's resignation leaves Trudeau with few options but a full public inquiry into foreign interference <span style="font-family: '-apple-system', BlinkMacSystemFont, 'Segoe UI', Roboto, Oxygen, Ubuntu, Cantarell, 'Open Sans', 'Helvetica Neue', sans-serif;">| </span><em style="font-family: '-apple-system', BlinkMacSystemFont, 'Segoe UI', Roboto, Oxygen, Ubuntu, Cantarell, 'Open Sans', 'Helvetica Neue', sans-serif;">National Post</em><span style="font-family: '-apple-system', BlinkMacSystemFont, 'Segoe UI', Roboto, Oxygen, Ubuntu, Cantarell, 'Open Sans', 'Helvetica Neue', sans-serif;">: <a href="https://nationalpost.com/news/politics/johnstons-resignation-leaves-trudeau-with-few-options-but-a-full-public-inquiry-into-foreign-interference">https://nationalpost.com/news/politics/johnstons-resignation-leaves-trudeau-with-few-options-but-a-full-public-inquiry-into-foreign-interference</a>;<br /></span>Trudeau Greeted in Ukraine by Nazi Anti-Semite: <a href="https://twitter.com/RealAndyLeeShow/status/1667513139452342272">https://twitter.com/RealAndyLeeShow/status/1667513139452342272</a>;<br />CSE and its Canadian Centre for Cyber Security release advisory on People's Republic of China state-sponsored cyber threat | <em>Government of Canada</em>: <a href="https://www.cyber.gc.ca/en/news-events/advisory-peoples-republic-china-state-sponsored-cyber-threat?s=04&amp;mibextid=Zxz2cZ">https://www.cyber.gc.ca/en/news-events/advisory-peoples-republic-china-state-sponsored-cyber-threat?s=04&amp;mibextid=Zxz2cZ</a>;<br />Trudeau Foundation Has Investments in Chinese Companies Flagged for Security Risks, Says Former Board Member | <em>The Epoch Times</em>: <a href="https://www.theepochtimes.com/trudeau-foundation-has-investments-in-chinese-companies-flagged-for-security-risks-says-former-board-member_5314045.html">https://www.theepochtimes.com/trudeau-foundation-has-investments-in-chinese-companies-flagged-for-security-risks-says-former-board-member_5314045.html</a>;&nbsp;<br /><strong><br />[Segment 3] - Mailbag Segment &amp; Conclusion (43:25-END)</strong><br /><strong><br />JOIN PASTORS, CHURCHES, AND CHRISTIAN COMMUNITIES ACROSS CANADA WITH LCC'S NEWEST INITIATIVE, "<em>TRUE READINGS FROM TRUE ROYALTY."&nbsp; <br /></em></strong><strong>Sign up today:&nbsp;</strong><a href="https://libertycoalitioncanada.com/storyhour/">https://libertycoalitioncanada.com/storyhour/</a>&nbsp;<br /><br /><strong>Support Josh's Stand and Help Us Defend His Liberties! Sign Our Petition Here: <a href="https://libertycoalitioncanada.com/i-stand-with-josh-alexander/">https://libertycoalitioncanada.com/i-stand-with-josh-alexander/</a>;<br /><br /></strong><strong>SHOW SPONSORS:<br /></strong><strong>Join&nbsp;<em>Red Balloon&nbsp;</em>Today!:</strong> <a href="https://www.redballoon.work/lcc;">https://www.redballoon.work/lcc;</a>&nbsp;<br /><strong>Invest with Rocklinc:</strong> <a href="mailto:info@rocklinc.com">info@rocklinc.com</a>&nbsp;or call them at 905-631-546;&nbsp;<br /><strong>Diversify Your Money with Bull Bitcoin:&nbsp;</strong><a href="https://mission.bullbitcoin.com/lcc">https://mission.bullbitcoin.com/lcc</a>;<br /><strong>BarterPay: </strong><a href="https://barterpay.ca/">https://barterpay.ca/</a>;&nbsp; <strong>Barter It: </strong><a href="https://vip.barterit.ca/launch;">https://vip.barterit.ca/launch; </a><strong><br />Carpe Fide - "Seize the Faith": Store: </strong><a href="https://carpe-fide.myshopify.com/">https://carpe-fide.myshopify.com</a><a href="https://carpe-fide.myshopify.com/">/</a>, use Promo Code LCC10 for 10% off (US Store Only), or shop Canadian @ <a href="https://canadacarpefide.myshopify.com/">https://canadacarpefide.myshopify.com/</a> | <strong>Podcast: </strong><a href="https://www.carpefide.com/episodes">https://www.carpefide.com/episodes</a>;<br /><br /><strong>Sick of Mainstream Media Lies? Help Support Independent Media! DONATE TO LCC TODAY!:&nbsp;</strong><strong><a href="https://libertycoalitioncanada.com/donate/">https://libertycoalitioncanada.com/donate/</a>&nbsp;</strong><strong> &nbsp;</strong></p>
<p class="p1">&nbsp;</p>
<p class="p1">Please Support us in bringing you honest, truthful reporting and analysis from a Christian perspective.<br /><br /><strong>SUBSCRIBE TO OUR SHOWS/CHANNELS:<br /></strong>LIBERTY DISPATCH PODCAST: <a href="https://libertydispatch.podbean.com">https://libertydispatch.podbean.com</a>; <a href="https://rumble.com/c/c-1687093">https://rumble.com/LDshow</a>;&nbsp;<br />OPEN MIKE WITH MICHAEL THIESSEN: <a href="https://openmikewithmichaelthiessen.podbean.com">https://openmikewithmichaelthiessen.podbean.com</a>; <a href="https://rumble.com/c/c-1412501">https://rumble.com/openmike</a>;<br />THE OTHER CLUB: <a href="https://rumble.com/c/c-2541984">https://rumble.com/c/c-2541984</a>;&nbsp;<br />THE LIBERTY LOUNGE WITH TIM TYSOE: <a href="https://rumble.com/LLwTT">https://rumble.com/LLwTT</a>;<br /><br /><strong>CONTACT US:</strong><br />Questions/comments about podcasts/news/analysis: <a href="mailto:mailbag@libertycoalitioncanada.com">mailbag@libertycoalitioncanada.com</a>;<br />Questions/comments about donations: <a href="mailto:give@libertycoalitioncanada.com">give@libertycoalitioncanada.com</a>;<br />Questions/comments that are church-related: <a href="mailto:churches@libertycoalitioncanada.com">churches@libertycoalitioncanada.com</a>;<br />General Inquiries: <a href="mailto:info@libertycoalitioncanada.com">info@libertycoalitioncanada.com</a>.&nbsp;<br /><br /></p>
<p class="p1"><strong>STAY UP-TO-DATE ON ALL THINGS LCC:<br /></strong>Gab: <a href="https://gab.com/libertycoalitioncanada">https://gab.com/libertycoalitioncanada</a>&nbsp;</p>
<p class="p2">Telegram: <a href="https://t.me/libertycoalitioncanadanews">https://t.me/libertycoalitioncanadanews</a>&nbsp;</p>
<p class="p2">Instagram: <a href="https://instagram.com/libertycoalitioncanada">https://instagram.com/libertycoalitioncanada</a>&nbsp;</p>
<p class="p2">Facebook: <a href="https://facebook.com/LibertyCoalitionCanada">https://facebook.com/LibertyCoalitionCanada</a>&nbsp;</p>
<p class="p2">Twitter: @LibertyCCanada - <a href="https://twitter.com/LibertyCCanada">https://twitter.com/LibertyCCanada</a>&nbsp;</p>
<p class="p2">Rumble: <a href="https://rumble.com/user/LibertyCoalitionCanada">https://rumble.com/user/LibertyCoalitionCanada</a>&nbsp;</p>
<p class="p2">YouTube: <a href="https://www.youtube.com/@liberty4canada">https://www.youtube.com/@liberty4canada</a> -&nbsp;<strong>WE GOT CANCELLED AGAIN!!!</strong></p>
<p class="p1"><strong>Please LIKE, SUBSCRIBE, RATE &amp; REVIEW and SHARE it with others!</strong></p>]]></description>
   <author><![CDATA[Matthew Hallick, Andrew DeBartolo, SDG Media]]></author>
   <enclosure url="https://app.dropwave.io/episode/5235749c-200a-4938-8f8f-57589a3db81b/heres-smoke-theres-fire-trudeaus-canada-is-on-fire-literally-and-figuratively.mp3" length="3618" type="audio/mp3"/>
   <guid isPermaLink="false"><![CDATA[5235749c-200a-4938-8f8f-57589a3db81b]]></guid>
   <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jun 2023 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
   <source url=""><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></source>
   <itunes:author><![CDATA[Matthew Hallick, Andrew DeBartolo, SDG Media]]></itunes:author>
   <itunes:image href="https://prod-assets-spc1.nyc3.digitaloceanspaces.com/69893365-4165-4498-b0ac-e9ddf57a000f/cover-art/E86eLfK3NgjrpuXtk9kW9Qv6KcfzQpkJpToltreR.png"/>
   <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
   <itunes:duration>3618</itunes:duration>
   <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title><![CDATA[Nostalgia [Resistance and Reformation]]]></title>
   <link>https://app.dropwave.io/episode/3a39a05d-841d-4517-b527-83845e741f97/nostalgia.mp3</link>
   <description><![CDATA[<p>More from Dr. George Grant</p>
<p><a href="https://georgegrant.net/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" data-callout-id="edit_links_in_description">https://georgegrant.net/</a>&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Adoring God Foundation&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://adoringgod.org/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" data-callout-id="edit_links_in_description">https://adoringgod.org/</a></p>]]></description>
   <author><![CDATA[George Grant]]></author>
   <enclosure url="https://app.dropwave.io/episode/3a39a05d-841d-4517-b527-83845e741f97/nostalgia.mp3" length="533" type="audio/mp3"/>
   <guid isPermaLink="false"><![CDATA[3a39a05d-841d-4517-b527-83845e741f97]]></guid>
   <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jun 2023 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
   <source url=""><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></source>
   <itunes:author><![CDATA[George Grant]]></itunes:author>
   <itunes:image href="https://assets-cdn2.dropwave.io/261ebdbb-5a5a-4650-ba2c-8c138886911b/cover-art/fEPh0pqkjOi1hWn2VDTvgRSsw3nOsdOFIBOfEGEP.png"/>
   <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
   <itunes:duration>533</itunes:duration>
   <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title><![CDATA[Introduction to Edmund Spenser's 'The Faerie Queene' and Transformers Spoilers [Choc Knox Unplugged]]]></title>
   <link>https://app.dropwave.io/episode/c2989840-1356-4d5b-bc33-833c4eb967e1/introduction-to-edmund-spencers-the-faerie-queene-and-transformers-spoilers.mp3</link>
   <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
   <author><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></author>
   <enclosure url="https://app.dropwave.io/episode/c2989840-1356-4d5b-bc33-833c4eb967e1/introduction-to-edmund-spencers-the-faerie-queene-and-transformers-spoilers.mp3" length="8494" type="audio/mp3"/>
   <guid isPermaLink="false"><![CDATA[c2989840-1356-4d5b-bc33-833c4eb967e1]]></guid>
   <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jun 2023 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
   <source url=""><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></source>
   <itunes:author><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></itunes:author>
   <itunes:image href="https://assets-cdn2.dropwave.io/6123b54f-ab49-406c-9cba-a39f6730fc76/cover-art/ARuuU8PixHGkhNvgtHIHIGGJjBUPNwgZEkuaGqzL.png"/>
   <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
   <itunes:duration>8494</itunes:duration>
   <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title><![CDATA[Daily News Brief for Tuesday, June 20th, 2023 [Daily News Brief]]]></title>
   <link>https://app.dropwave.io/episode/da5651c0-c9b1-42a3-87c6-4abfb80a3f51/daily-news-brief-for-tuesday-june-20th-2023.mp3</link>
   <description><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">This is Garrison Hardie with your CrossPolitic Daily News Brief for Tuesday, June 20th, 2023.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>CrossPolination Ad</strong></span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Did you guys know that you can sign up for a club membership, a magazine subscription, AND tickets to the Ark Encounter all in one place?! That&rsquo;s some crosspollination right there! Fightlaughfeast.com is your one-stop-shop for everything CrossPolitic. Here&rsquo;s what you should do. You should sign up for a club membership, then sign up for the Ark Encounter for a $100 discount off of your purchase, and then sign up for a magazine subscription. We&rsquo;ve even got our own social media platform built into our website now for our club members&hellip; once you&rsquo;re a club member, you&rsquo;ll get access to exclusive content like a Bible Study series with Pastor Toby, a special series with New Saint Andrews President, Dr. ben Merkle, all of our back-stage content, and all of our conference talks, with more to come!</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">There really hasn&rsquo;t been a better time to be a CrossPolitic Club Member. Sign up today, at fightlaughfeast.com. That&rsquo;s fightlaughfeast.com.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://www.breitbart.com/2nd-amendment/2023/06/18/at-least-21-shot-at-juneteenth-celebration-in-gun-controlled-illinois/"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.breitbart.com/2nd-amendment/2023/06/18/at-least-21-shot-at-juneteenth-celebration-in-gun-controlled-illinois/</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>At Least 21 Shot at Juneteenth Celebration in Gun-Controlled Illinois</strong></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">At least 21 people were shot, one of them fatally, at a Juneteenth celebration in gun-controlled Illinois on Sunday morning around 12:30 a.m.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">CNN reported the shooting occurred &ldquo;in a parking lot in Willowbrook, about 21 miles west of Chicago.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">FOX 32 pointed out&nbsp; two of the wounded remain in critical condition.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">FOX News noted DuPage County Sheriff&rsquo;s Deputy Chief Eric Swanson indicated that deputies patrolling the area near the parking lot heard the gunshots and responded.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Swanson said, &ldquo;The motive behind this incident is unclear and this is still an active investigation.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">No information has been released on the number of shooters involved in the incident.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Illinois has a red flag law, an &ldquo;assault weapons&rdquo; ban, a &ldquo;high capacity&rdquo; magazine ban, a 72-hour waiting period, and a gun owner licensing requirement via the Firearm Owners Identification (FOID) card system, among other controls.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://www.theepochtimes.com/judge-orders-trump-lawyers-not-to-share-evidence-ahead-of-trial_5341862.html?utm_source=partner&amp;utm_campaign=BonginoReport"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.theepochtimes.com/judge-orders-trump-lawyers-not-to-share-evidence-ahead-of-trial_5341862.html?utm_source=partner&amp;utm_campaign=BonginoReport</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>Judge Orders Trump, Lawyers Not to Share Evidence Ahead of Trial</strong></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">President Donald Trump and his lawyers were ordered on June 19 not to share evidence in Trump&rsquo;s criminal case with any people not involved in the case.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Trump, co-defendant Waltine Nauta, and their attorneys must not disclose the discovery materials to the public or news media, or post it on any &ldquo;news or social media platform,&rdquo; without the consent of the U.S, government or approval of the court, U.S. Magistrate Judge Bruce Reinhart said in the order.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Following Trump and Nauta being charged with multiple crimes, including concealing documents, government officials are preparing to hand over discovery materials to the defendants and their representatives.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The materials will include depositions of testimony given by witnesses to the grand jury that approved the charges, as well as other evidence prosecutors plan to present at the trial in the case.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The order from Reinhart, who was appointed by other judges and has criticized Trump on social media, comes in response to a request for such an order from prosecutors.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The government said it was ready to provide unclassified materials to the defense, but that the disclosure of information could compromise ongoing investigations and make public the identity of people who have not been charged.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">&ldquo;As a result, the government proposes protections against the dissemination of discovery materials and the sensitive information that they contain,&rdquo; special counsel Jack Smith said in the request.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Lawyers for Trump and Nauta did not oppose the motion, according to Smith. The lawyers did not respond to requests for comment.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">While Reinhart said that he may authorize the disclosure of information to certain people, lawyers for the defendants must take steps before disclosing the information.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Once a person is authorized to receive the information, the lawyers must give the person a copy of Monday&rsquo;s order and the person must sign an agreement to not disseminate the materials he or she receives, Reinhart said.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The lawyers must keep a copy of each signed agreement.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">&ldquo;No disclosure is permitted to any individual or entity that has not signed such Agreement, except by further order of the Court. Potential witnesses and counsel for potential witnesses may be shown copies of the Discovery Materials as necessary to prepare the defense, but they may not retain copies without prior permission of the Court,&rdquo; Reinhart wrote, adding that defendants must also not copy or reproduce the materials unless necessary to prepare for the trial.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Reinhart also ordered the defendants not to retain copies of the materials, and said they cannot review the materials unless they&rsquo;re &ldquo;under the direct supervision of defense counsel or a member of defense counsel&rsquo;s staff.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The defendants can take notes while reviewing the materials but even the notes have to be stored by lawyers, not the defendants themselves.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Violations of the order may result in being held in contempt of court or other sanctions, the judge said.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Trump was charged with 31 counts of violating the Espionage Act for keeping sensitive records as well as six other counts for crimes such as obstruction and making false statements.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Prosecutors allege Trump illegally failed to turn over records to the government after he left office on Jan. 20, 2021, and that he tried obstructing the investigation into the failure. Trump returned some records but not all of them, authorities say. Trump is also accused of showing the documents to people who lacked security clearance, including a writer and publisher.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Nauta, a top Trump aide, assisted the effort by moving boxes and at one point falsely told FBI agents that he did not know where the boxes had been stored, according to an indictment.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Trump has said he is innocent. A lawyer for Nauta previously declined to comment on the charges.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Trump is also facing felony charges in New York. In that case, the judge also ordered that Trump and his lawyers not disclose discovery materials before trial.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Trump cannot provide such information to any third party or to &ldquo;any news or social media platforms &hellip; without prior approval from the court,&rdquo; the order from acting New York Supreme Court Justice Juan Merchan stated.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">That order was granted after a request from Alvin Bragg, the Manhattan District Attorney.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Bragg&rsquo;s office had argued in a court filing that Trump &ldquo;has a longstanding and perhaps singular history of attacking witnesses, investigators, prosecutors, trial jurors, grand jurors, judges, and others involved in legal proceedings against him, putting those individuals and their families at considerable safety risk.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://www.dailywire.com/news/pixars-elemental-with-non-binary-character-flops-at-box-office-with-2nd-worst-opening-in-studio-history?utm_campaign=news&amp;utm_medium=social&amp;utm_source=twitter&amp;utm_content=dailywire_feed_6/19/2023-13:44:19_na"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.dailywire.com/news/pixars-elemental-with-non-binary-character-flops-at-box-office-with-2nd-worst-opening-in-studio-history?utm_campaign=news&amp;utm_medium=social&amp;utm_source=twitter&amp;utm_content=dailywire_feed_6/19/2023-13:44:19_na</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>Pixar&rsquo;s &lsquo;Elemental,&rsquo; With &lsquo;Non-Binary&rsquo; Character, Flops At Box Office</strong></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Pixar&rsquo;s new animated kid&rsquo;s film &ldquo;Elemental&rdquo; had one of the worst openings in studio history, bringing in just $29.5 million in domestic ticket sales at the weekend box office.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The movie is Pixar&rsquo;s first non-franchise theatrical release since the COVID pandemic that wasn&rsquo;t released directly to streaming, per The New York Times.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">To put those numbers into context, Pixar&rsquo;s worst-performing movie ever was the first movie it ever did, &ldquo;Toy Story,&rdquo; which brought in $29.1 million for the then-unheard-of studio in 1995.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Pixar&rsquo;s top performers include &ldquo;The Incredibles 2,&rdquo; which earned $182.7 million during its opening weekend, &ldquo;Toy Story 4&rdquo; ($120.9 million), &ldquo;Finding Nemo&rdquo; ($70.3 million), and &ldquo;Up&rdquo; ($68.1 million), per Forbes.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">&ldquo;Elemental&rdquo; features the four elements &mdash; earth, water, fire, and air.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">According to the IMDb description, &ldquo;the film journeys alongside an unlikely pair, Ember and Wade, in a city where fire-, water-, land- and air-residents live together. The fiery young woman and the go-with-the-flow guy are about to discover something elemental: how much they actually have in common.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The film is directed by Peter Sohn, best known for &ldquo;The Good Dinosaur&rdquo; (2015).</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The new movie includes the studio&rsquo;s first &ldquo;non-binary&rdquo; character, Lake, who is voiced by the &ldquo;non-binary&rdquo; star Kai Ava Hauser.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">&ldquo;BIG ANNOUNCEMENT I got to play Pixar&rsquo;s first non-binary character. Meet Lake,&rdquo; Hauser posted on Twitter.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The Times noted that the movie cost $200 million to make. &ldquo;Hard to sugarcoat this,&rdquo; David A. Gross, a film consultant who publishes a newsletter on box office numbers, said of the lackluster results.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">NYT writer Brooks Barnes also mentioned that industry insiders have been questioning the future of Pixar since the &ldquo;Toy Story&rdquo; spinoff, &ldquo;Lightyear,&rdquo; underperformed expectations last year. That film also included a highly publicized same-sex kiss. One of the studio&rsquo;s worst performers was &ldquo;Onward,&rdquo; another animated children&rsquo;s film prominently featuring a gay character. &ldquo;Onward&rdquo; earned $39.1 million on opening weekend in 2020.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Now in world news&hellip;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://youtu.be/QDb4QtH66qs"><span style="font-weight: 400;" data-rich-links="{&quot;fple-t&quot;:&quot;WATCH: Blinken in China Says, &lsquo;We Do Not Support Taiwan Independence&rsquo;&quot;,&quot;fple-u&quot;:&quot;https://youtu.be/QDb4QtH66qs&quot;,&quot;fple-mt&quot;:null,&quot;type&quot;:&quot;first-party-link&quot;}">WATCH: Blinken in China Says, &lsquo;We Do Not Support Taiwan Independence&rsquo;</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;">-PLay Video</span></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://freebeacon.com/latest-news/watch-blinken-in-china-says-we-do-not-support-taiwan-independence/"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://freebeacon.com/latest-news/watch-blinken-in-china-says-we-do-not-support-taiwan-independence/</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>Blinken in China Says &lsquo;We Do Not Support Taiwan Independence&rsquo;</strong></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Secretary of State Antony Blinken said the United States does not "support Taiwan independence" during his trip to Beijing this week, clarifying U.S. policy toward Taiwan that President Joe Biden himself has been unclear on.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Biden has made conflicting statements on U.S. policy toward Taiwan. He said in September 2022 that the United States would come to Taiwan's defense in the case of a Chinese invasion, drawing anger from China. He made a similar comment in 2021&mdash;in both cases the White House walked back the remarks.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The comments on Blinken's trip come as tensions between the two countries continue to escalate. Dozens of war games carried out by the Pentagon have indicated the United States is unprepared for a "horrifically bloody" war with China. Meanwhile, the U.S. military has reported close encounters with Chinese ships and planes.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Republican House speaker Kevin McCarthy (Calif.) met with Taiwanese president Tsai Ing-wen in April, refusing to bow to China's pressure to cancel the meeting in California.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">China said in the week before McCarthy and Tsai's meeting that it "firmly opposes and strongly condemns" Tsai&rsquo;s visit, which it sees as an affront to its claims of control over the island nation. It promised "resolute and forceful measures to defend national sovereignty and territorial integrity." Another statement from China's foreign ministry called the meeting "U.S.-Taiwan collusion."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">After then-House speaker Nancy Pelosi (D., Calif.) visited Taiwan last August, China conducted its largest live-fire drills in decades and shot a missile over Taiwan.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://www.bbc.com/news/world-us-canada-65953872"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.bbc.com/news/world-us-canada-65953872</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>Titanic tourist submersible goes missing with search under way</strong></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">A submersible craft used to take people to see the wreck of the Titanic has been missing in the Atlantic Ocean with its crew on board since Sunday, sparking a major search and rescue.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Contact with the submersible was lost about one hour and 45 minutes into the vessel's dive, the US coast guard said.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Tour firm OceanGate said it was exploring all options to get the crew back safely.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Government agencies and deep sea firms are helping the rescue operation.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">OceanGate charges $250,000 (&pound;195,612) a seat for expeditions to the Titanic, which lies some 3,800m (12,500ft) beneath the waves about 435 miles (700km) south of St John's, Newfoundland.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The missing craft is believed to be OceanGate's Titan submersible, a truck-sized sub that holds five people and usually dives with a four-day emergency supply of oxygen.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">On Monday, Rear Adm John Mauger of the US Coast Guard told a news conference: "We anticipate there is somewhere between 70 and the full 96 hours available at this point."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">He also said that two aircrafts, a submarine and sonar buoys were involved in the search for the vessel but noted the area in which the search is taking place was "remote", making operations difficult.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Rear Adm Mauger said the rescue teams were "taking this personally" and were doing everything they could to bring those on board "home safe".</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Hamish Harding, a 58-year-old British billionaire businessman and explorer, is among those on the missing submarine, his family said.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">On social media at the weekend, Mr Harding said he was "proud to finally announce" that he would be aboard the mission to the wreck of the Titanic - but added that due to the "worst winter in Newfoundland in 40 years, this mission is likely to be the first and only manned mission to the Titanic in 2023".</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">He later wrote: "A weather window has just opened up and we are going to attempt a dive tomorrow."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">OceanGate said in a statement that its "entire focus is on the crewmembers in the submersible and their families".</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">"We are deeply thankful for the extensive assistance we have received from several government agencies and deep sea companies in our efforts to re-establish contact with the submersible," it added.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The company bills the eight-day trip on its carbon-fibre submersible as a "chance to step outside of everyday life and discover something truly extraordinary".</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">According to its website, one expedition is ongoing and two more have been planned for June 2024.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://dailycaller.com/2023/06/18/bob-huggins-college-west-virginia-university-basketball-coach-resigns-dui-arrest/"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://dailycaller.com/2023/06/18/bob-huggins-college-west-virginia-university-basketball-coach-resigns-dui-arrest/</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>Legendary West Virginia University Men&rsquo;s Basketball Coach Bob Huggins Resigns After DUI Arrest</strong></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">West Virginia men&rsquo;s basketball coach Bob Huggins resigned Saturday from his coaching position after a DUI arrest Friday.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The West Virginia University head basketball coach said in a statement he will walk away from his post &ldquo;effective immediately.&rdquo; &ldquo;I have let all of you &ndash; and myself &ndash; down. I am solely responsible for my conduct and sincerely apologize to the University community,&rdquo; Huggins said.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Huggins reportedly initially broke the news to his players during a team meeting Saturday, according to an ESPN report.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The famous coach was arrested in Pittsburgh at approximately 8:30 p.m. Friday night after police came across a black SUV holding up traffic. The SUV was damaged with a &ldquo;flat and shredded tire&rdquo; and the driver&rsquo;s side door was ajar, according to police, the outlet reported.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Officers told Huggins to pull the vehicle to the side of the road, which was a challenge for the coach, alleged police. Police then grew suspicious the driver was intoxicated, prompting a sobriety test &mdash; which Huggins did not pass, according to ESPN.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Huggins submitted to a breath test which allegedly determined his blood alcohol content was 0.21%, twice the legal limit in Pennsylvania, according to the outlet.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Just six weeks ago Huggins found himself in hot water over an &ldquo;anti-gay slur&rdquo; during an interview for a Cincinnati radio station. This controversy caused the coach to get slapped with a $1,000,000 salary reduction as well as a three-game suspension, according to ESPN.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Huggins is an alumni of West Virginia University, having once played on the team he coached since 2007. Last fall, he was inducted into the Naismith Memorial Basketball Hall of Fame, the outlet reported.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">During his tenure as head coach, Huggins led the Mountaineers to 11 NCAA tournament appearances as well as making it to the Final Four back in 2010, ESPN added.</span></p>]]></description>
   <author><![CDATA[Garrison Hardie]]></author>
   <enclosure url="https://app.dropwave.io/episode/da5651c0-c9b1-42a3-87c6-4abfb80a3f51/daily-news-brief-for-tuesday-june-20th-2023.mp3" length="952" type="audio/mp3"/>
   <guid isPermaLink="false"><![CDATA[da5651c0-c9b1-42a3-87c6-4abfb80a3f51]]></guid>
   <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jun 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
   <source url=""><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></source>
   <itunes:author><![CDATA[Garrison Hardie]]></itunes:author>
   <itunes:image href="https://assets-cdn2.dropwave.io/2ab40ac0-e99d-4f25-a6d2-541d2c9b290a/cover-art/hUZu1H9lrRY0wXg66WHC8eLwYBA3hbRNTAHQmHt2.png"/>
   <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
   <itunes:duration>952</itunes:duration>
   <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title><![CDATA[Biblical Cosmology Episode 1: Principalities and Powers of Darkness [The Rebel Podcast]]]></title>
   <link>https://app.dropwave.io/episode/8b6c292e-972f-4d43-b286-d6c5c3dafe98/biblical-cosmology-episode-1-principalities-and-powers-of-darkness.mp3</link>
   <description><![CDATA[<div dir="auto">What is this universe that we live in? Its full of rocks and dust, hummingbirds and anteaters, black holes and microbials. But is it just stuff? What about the things we cannot see? The things that go bump in the night?&nbsp;</div>
<div dir="auto">&nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp;The bible is full of information about the unseen realm of this universe and it also has a lot to say about the conflict taking place in this war torn cosmos.</div>
<div dir="auto">&nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp;This week the Rebels welcome back Air Jordan to launch a new mini series on biblical cosmology. &nbsp;This introductory episode will set the ground work for a series exploring these unseen realities. If you have questions while we work our way through, please send them to us through any social media messaging or by emailing <a href="mailto:rebelpodcastflf@gmail.com">rebelpodcastflf@gmail.com</a></div>]]></description>
   <author><![CDATA[Pastors Nate & Chris & Jordan, The Rebels]]></author>
   <enclosure url="https://app.dropwave.io/episode/8b6c292e-972f-4d43-b286-d6c5c3dafe98/biblical-cosmology-episode-1-principalities-and-powers-of-darkness.mp3" length="2972" type="audio/mp3"/>
   <guid isPermaLink="false"><![CDATA[8b6c292e-972f-4d43-b286-d6c5c3dafe98]]></guid>
   <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jun 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
   <source url=""><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></source>
   <itunes:author><![CDATA[Pastors Nate & Chris & Jordan, The Rebels]]></itunes:author>
   <itunes:image href="https://assets-cdn2.dropwave.io/2f5403ee-3fd5-417e-8372-cb8279ee1f07/cover-art/w0UbRn2uM5yV9BWgVTAhrwlpOzSNrn99Jo5z83hu.png"/>
   <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
   <itunes:duration>2972</itunes:duration>
   <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title><![CDATA[Colossians 1:16-20 [Up and Ready]]]></title>
   <link>https://app.dropwave.io/episode/ca692038-8801-4d72-a391-892204c7861f/colossians-116-20.mp3</link>
   <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
   <author><![CDATA[Mark Dewey]]></author>
   <enclosure url="https://app.dropwave.io/episode/ca692038-8801-4d72-a391-892204c7861f/colossians-116-20.mp3" length="290" type="audio/mp3"/>
   <guid isPermaLink="false"><![CDATA[ca692038-8801-4d72-a391-892204c7861f]]></guid>
   <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jun 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
   <source url=""><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></source>
   <itunes:author><![CDATA[Mark Dewey]]></itunes:author>
   <itunes:image href="https://assets-cdn2.dropwave.io/60c9e557-5882-401d-abb8-06de47904be4/cover-art/zZ8CYlYBUAUu8KNyZzjE092h2WlBblW8upM7tmFg.png"/>
   <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
   <itunes:duration>290</itunes:duration>
   <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title><![CDATA[Pastors for Trump? Pastor Craig Hagin on CrossPolitic (The Church & Politics) [CrossPolitic Show]]]></title>
   <link>https://app.dropwave.io/episode/3d9a060f-cacd-4e9b-a92e-ebf043258161/pastors-for-trump-pastor-craig-hagin-on-crosspolitic-the-church-politics.mp3</link>
   <description><![CDATA[<p class="p1"><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Pastors for Trump? Pastor Craig Hagin on CrossPolitic<span class="Apple-converted-space">&nbsp;</span></span></p>
<p class="p2">&nbsp;</p>
<p class="p1"><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">More from Pastor Hagin:</span></p>
<p class="p3"><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://www.pastors4trump.com/">https://www.pastors4trump.com/</a><span class="s1"> <span class="Apple-converted-space">&nbsp;</span></span></span></p>
<p class="p2">&nbsp;</p>
<p class="p1"><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Support Us &amp; Sign up for a FLF Club Membership!<span class="Apple-converted-space">&nbsp;</span></span></p>
<p class="p3"><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><span class="s2"><a href="https://flfnetwork.com/product/fightlaughfestclub/?attribute_member-tier=silver-monthly">https://flfnetwork.com/product/fightlaughfestclub/?attribute_member-tier=silver-monthly</a></span><span class="s1"><span class="Apple-converted-space">&nbsp;</span></span></span></p>
<p class="p1">&nbsp;</p>
<p class="p1"><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Sign up for the FLF Conference at the Ark Encounter! (Oct 11-14)</span></p>
<p class="p3"><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><span class="s2"><a href="https://flfnetwork.com/the-politics-of-six-days-creation-conference/">https://flfnetwork.com/the-politics-of-six-days-creation-conference/</a></span><span class="s1"><span class="Apple-converted-space">&nbsp;</span></span></span></p>
<p class="p2">&nbsp;</p>
<p class="p3"><span class="s1" style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The Article in CNN: <a href="https://www.cnn.com/2023/01/20/politics/donald-trump-march-for-life-abortion/index.html">https://www.cnn.com/2023/01/20/politics/donald-trump-march-for-life-abortion/index.html</a><span class="Apple-converted-space">&nbsp;</span></span></p>]]></description>
   <author><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></author>
   <enclosure url="https://app.dropwave.io/episode/3d9a060f-cacd-4e9b-a92e-ebf043258161/pastors-for-trump-pastor-craig-hagin-on-crosspolitic-the-church-politics.mp3" length="1932" type="audio/mp3"/>
   <guid isPermaLink="false"><![CDATA[3d9a060f-cacd-4e9b-a92e-ebf043258161]]></guid>
   <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jun 2023 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
   <source url=""><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></source>
   <itunes:author><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></itunes:author>
   <itunes:image href="https://assets-cdn2.dropwave.io/11635dce-94e7-41b8-9261-5c1fc2cc5ebe/cover-art/wvkjcfd3tfj69XopdryYkSF8m1k4KHuikzJF1KzC.jpg"/>
   <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
   <itunes:duration>1932</itunes:duration>
   <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title><![CDATA[What Is Happening? [In the Bullpen]]]></title>
   <link>https://app.dropwave.io/episode/75da442d-e1d6-4889-957d-2cb4d69f2b26/what-is-happening.mp3</link>
   <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
   <author><![CDATA[Mark Dewey]]></author>
   <enclosure url="https://app.dropwave.io/episode/75da442d-e1d6-4889-957d-2cb4d69f2b26/what-is-happening.mp3" length="1641" type="audio/mp3"/>
   <guid isPermaLink="false"><![CDATA[75da442d-e1d6-4889-957d-2cb4d69f2b26]]></guid>
   <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2023 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
   <source url=""><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></source>
   <itunes:author><![CDATA[Mark Dewey]]></itunes:author>
   <itunes:image href="https://assets-cdn2.dropwave.io/48817573-c1d0-44c6-8204-930f4c2d3ce5/cover-art/9b92BsnWm2ufHgEHY2ttEsJ9SYr5RF0LGVrFbfmN.png"/>
   <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
   <itunes:duration>1641</itunes:duration>
   <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title><![CDATA[TCND: Cults are Winning (Flush Like the Romans) [The Comedian Next Door]]]></title>
   <link>https://app.dropwave.io/episode/d3ff75e1-e6e6-41b9-a4fe-18ed4e006846/tcnd-cults-are-winning-flush-like-the-romans.mp3</link>
   <description><![CDATA[<p>Please hold while we shuffle the headphones...<br /><br />Okay! Now Luke has a story no one has heard before! Something uncomfortable happened in bathroom at the race track.<br /><br />We're sorry to those who think toilet humor is lowbrow. It's not always like this!&nbsp; But, since we've dragged you down already, go ahead and make suggestions for how Luke can clean up this story enough to tell on stage...</p>
<p>Later: How can we prevent all natural disasters in the future? John has a suggestion. We're not really sure why the LGBT community was so offended by Pat Robertson's predictions, when they haven't properly tested his theory.</p>
<p>Finally: Most of us know what's WRONG with "cults," like Bill Gothard's Anti-Rock-and-Roll community. But what's the positive side of growing up in a Bible Cult?&nbsp; We haven't watched Shiny, Happy People. But the interviews with Jinger Duggar have not been the "shocking, secret-revealing" expose that everyone was promised.</p>
<p>Reach out to the Comedian's family by emailing <a href="mailto:nextdoor@johnbranyan.com">nextdoor@johnbranyan.com</a>.&nbsp;</p>]]></description>
   <author><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></author>
   <enclosure url="https://app.dropwave.io/episode/d3ff75e1-e6e6-41b9-a4fe-18ed4e006846/tcnd-cults-are-winning-flush-like-the-romans.mp3" length="2849" type="audio/mp3"/>
   <guid isPermaLink="false"><![CDATA[d3ff75e1-e6e6-41b9-a4fe-18ed4e006846]]></guid>
   <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
   <source url=""><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></source>
   <itunes:author><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></itunes:author>
   <itunes:image href="https://assets-cdn2.dropwave.io/66903a54-b4b6-4a52-a303-eb0bd0b792e3/cover-art/obxsSs7zSTuWr3ZFLRWxryhYbCyvdrWYzXEN2soF.png"/>
   <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
   <itunes:duration>2849</itunes:duration>
   <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title><![CDATA[Luke 24:50-53 [Up and Ready]]]></title>
   <link>https://app.dropwave.io/episode/ef1bd529-2e4b-4f95-b76d-a30c48aae2b0/luke-2450-53.mp3</link>
   <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
   <author><![CDATA[Mark Dewey]]></author>
   <enclosure url="https://app.dropwave.io/episode/ef1bd529-2e4b-4f95-b76d-a30c48aae2b0/luke-2450-53.mp3" length="294" type="audio/mp3"/>
   <guid isPermaLink="false"><![CDATA[ef1bd529-2e4b-4f95-b76d-a30c48aae2b0]]></guid>
   <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
   <source url=""><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></source>
   <itunes:author><![CDATA[Mark Dewey]]></itunes:author>
   <itunes:image href="https://assets-cdn2.dropwave.io/60c9e557-5882-401d-abb8-06de47904be4/cover-art/zZ8CYlYBUAUu8KNyZzjE092h2WlBblW8upM7tmFg.png"/>
   <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
   <itunes:duration>294</itunes:duration>
   <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title><![CDATA[SPECIAL LEGAL UPDATE: Canada's Corrupt Legal System Comes for Convictional Christians  ft. James S.M. Kitchen [Open Mike with Michael Thiessen]]]></title>
   <link>https://app.dropwave.io/episode/19960760-d428-47d4-978e-5c33cad06a81/special-legal-update-canadas-corrupt-legal-system-comes-for-convictional-christians-ft-james-sm-kitchen.mp3</link>
   <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>OPEN MIKE w/Michael Thiessen [LEGAL SPECIAL] ~ </strong>June 17, 2023</p>
<p>This week on OPEN MIKE, Dr. Thiessen is joined by LCC chief litigator James S.M. Kitchen to update listeners on LCC's latest legal battles.</p>
<p><strong>Episode Resource:</strong> <em>CCOA v. Dr. Curtis Wall</em>: <a href="https://libertycoalitioncanada.com/liberty-defense-fund/college-of-chiropractors-of-alberta-v-dr-curtis-wall/">https://libertycoalitioncanada.com/liberty-defense-fund/college-of-chiropractors-of-alberta-v-dr-curtis-wall/</a>;<br /><em><span class="ct-span">Wanh Porter v. North York General Hospital</span></em>: <a href="https://libertycoalitioncanada.com/liberty-defense-fund/wahn-porter-v-north-york-general-hospital/">https://libertycoalitioncanada.com/liberty-defense-fund/wahn-porter-v-north-york-general-hospital/</a>;<br /><br /></p>
<p class="p1"><strong>JOIN PASTORS, CHURCHES, AND CHRISTIAN COMMUNITIES ACROSS CANADA WITH LCC'S NEWEST INITIATIVE, "<em>TRUE READINGS FROM TRUE ROYALTY."&nbsp; <br /></em></strong><strong>Sign up today:&nbsp;</strong><a href="https://libertycoalitioncanada.com/storyhour/">https://libertycoalitioncanada.com/storyhour/</a>&nbsp;<br /><br /><strong>Support Josh's Stand and Help Us Defend His Liberties! Sign Our Petition Here: <a href="https://libertycoalitioncanada.com/i-stand-with-josh-alexander/">https://libertycoalitioncanada.com/i-stand-with-josh-alexander/</a>;<br /><br /></strong><strong>SHOW SPONSORS:<br /></strong><strong>Join&nbsp;<em>Red Balloon&nbsp;</em>Today!:</strong> <a href="https://www.redballoon.work/lcc;">https://www.redballoon.work/lcc;</a>&nbsp;<br /><strong>Invest with Rocklinc:</strong> <a href="mailto:info@rocklinc.com">info@rocklinc.com</a>&nbsp;or call them at 905-631-546;&nbsp;<br /><strong>Diversify Your Money with Bull Bitcoin:&nbsp;</strong><a href="https://mission.bullbitcoin.com/lcc">https://mission.bullbitcoin.com/lcc</a>;<br /><strong>BarterPay: </strong><a href="https://barterpay.ca/">https://barterpay.ca/</a>;&nbsp; <strong>Barter It: </strong><a href="https://vip.barterit.ca/launch;">https://vip.barterit.ca/launch; </a><strong><br />Carpe Fide - "Seize the Faith": Store: </strong><a href="https://carpe-fide.myshopify.com/">https://carpe-fide.myshopify.com</a><a href="https://carpe-fide.myshopify.com/">/</a>, use Promo Code LCC10 for 10% off (US Store Only), or shop Canadian @ <a href="https://canadacarpefide.myshopify.com/">https://canadacarpefide.myshopify.com/</a> | <strong>Podcast: </strong><a href="https://www.carpefide.com/episodes">https://www.carpefide.com/episodes</a>;<br /><br /><strong>Sick of Mainstream Media Lies? Help Support Independent Media! DONATE TO LCC TODAY!:&nbsp;</strong><strong><a href="https://libertycoalitioncanada.com/donate/">https://libertycoalitioncanada.com/donate/</a>&nbsp;</strong><strong> &nbsp;</strong></p>
<p class="p1">Please Support us in bringing you honest, truthful reporting and analysis from a Christian perspective.<br /><br /><strong>SUBSCRIBE TO OUR SHOWS/CHANNELS:<br /></strong>LIBERTY DISPATCH PODCAST: <a href="https://libertydispatch.podbean.com">https://libertydispatch.podbean.com</a>; <a href="https://rumble.com/c/c-1687093">https://rumble.com/LDshow</a>;&nbsp;<br />OPEN MIKE WITH MICHAEL THIESSEN: <a href="https://openmikewithmichaelthiessen.podbean.com">https://openmikewithmichaelthiessen.podbean.com</a>; <a href="https://rumble.com/c/c-1412501">https://rumble.com/openmike</a>;<br />THE OTHER CLUB: <a href="https://rumble.com/c/c-2541984">https://rumble.com/c/c-2541984</a>;&nbsp;<br />THE LIBERTY LOUNGE WITH TIM TYSOE: <a href="https://rumble.com/LLwTT">https://rumble.com/LLwTT</a>;<br /><br /><strong>CONTACT US:</strong><br />Questions/comments about podcasts/news/analysis: <a href="mailto:mailbag@libertycoalitioncanada.com">mailbag@libertycoalitioncanada.com</a>;<br />Questions/comments about donations: <a href="mailto:give@libertycoalitioncanada.com">give@libertycoalitioncanada.com</a>;<br />Questions/comments that are church-related: <a href="mailto:churches@libertycoalitioncanada.com">churches@libertycoalitioncanada.com</a>;<br />General Inquiries: <a href="mailto:info@libertycoalitioncanada.com">info@libertycoalitioncanada.com</a>.&nbsp;<br /><br /></p>
<p class="p1"><strong>STAY UP-TO-DATE ON ALL THINGS LCC:<br /></strong>Gab: <a href="https://gab.com/libertycoalitioncanada">https://gab.com/libertycoalitioncanada</a>&nbsp;</p>
<p class="p2">Telegram: <a href="https://t.me/libertycoalitioncanadanews">https://t.me/libertycoalitioncanadanews</a>&nbsp;</p>
<p class="p2">Instagram: <a href="https://instagram.com/libertycoalitioncanada">https://instagram.com/libertycoalitioncanada</a>&nbsp;</p>
<p class="p2">Facebook: <a href="https://facebook.com/LibertyCoalitionCanada">https://facebook.com/LibertyCoalitionCanada</a>&nbsp;</p>
<p class="p2">Twitter: @LibertyCCanada - <a href="https://twitter.com/LibertyCCanada">https://twitter.com/LibertyCCanada</a>&nbsp;</p>
<p class="p2">Rumble: <a href="https://rumble.com/user/LibertyCoalitionCanada">https://rumble.com/user/LibertyCoalitionCanada</a>&nbsp;</p>
<p class="p2">YouTube: <a href="https://www.youtube.com/@liberty4canada">https://www.youtube.com/@liberty4canada</a> -&nbsp;<strong>WE GOT CANCELLED AGAIN!!!</strong></p>
<p class="p1"><strong>Please LIKE, SUBSCRIBE, RATE &amp; REVIEW and SHARE it with others!</strong></p>]]></description>
   <author><![CDATA[Dr. Michael Thiessen, James Kitchen,]]></author>
   <enclosure url="https://app.dropwave.io/episode/19960760-d428-47d4-978e-5c33cad06a81/special-legal-update-canadas-corrupt-legal-system-comes-for-convictional-christians-ft-james-sm-kitchen.mp3" length="5618" type="audio/mp3"/>
   <guid isPermaLink="false"><![CDATA[19960760-d428-47d4-978e-5c33cad06a81]]></guid>
   <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jun 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
   <source url=""><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></source>
   <itunes:author><![CDATA[Dr. Michael Thiessen, James Kitchen,]]></itunes:author>
   <itunes:image href="https://assets-cdn2.dropwave.io/a313a937-1864-4720-a5eb-4fe53c91d48d/cover-art/uUheeW63MRtlJ15cfD2JSiW4qu9YifPAUxqcvBE5.jpg"/>
   <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
   <itunes:duration>5618</itunes:duration>
   <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title><![CDATA[Psalm 23 [Up and Ready]]]></title>
   <link>https://app.dropwave.io/episode/fd1ba13c-1977-4db7-a9ea-ba625c711bcf/psalm-23.mp3</link>
   <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
   <author><![CDATA[Mark Dewey]]></author>
   <enclosure url="https://app.dropwave.io/episode/fd1ba13c-1977-4db7-a9ea-ba625c711bcf/psalm-23.mp3" length="251" type="audio/mp3"/>
   <guid isPermaLink="false"><![CDATA[fd1ba13c-1977-4db7-a9ea-ba625c711bcf]]></guid>
   <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jun 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
   <source url=""><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></source>
   <itunes:author><![CDATA[Mark Dewey]]></itunes:author>
   <itunes:image href="https://assets-cdn2.dropwave.io/60c9e557-5882-401d-abb8-06de47904be4/cover-art/zZ8CYlYBUAUu8KNyZzjE092h2WlBblW8upM7tmFg.png"/>
   <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
   <itunes:duration>251</itunes:duration>
   <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title><![CDATA[Billboard Chris: Protecting Children NO MATTER the Cost [Liberty Dispatch]]]></title>
   <link>https://app.dropwave.io/episode/fa691fba-8af6-427e-aba0-8ce851a73af3/billboard-chris-protecting-children-no-matter-the-cost.mp3</link>
   <description><![CDATA[<p class="p1"><strong>Liberty Dispatch [INTERVIEWS]</strong> ~ June 16, 2023<br />On this episode of the Dispatch, hosts Andrew DeBartolo and Matthew Hallick are joined by Canadian father "Billboard" Chris Elston to talk about his international movement to raise awareness of the "biggest child abuse medical scandal in modern medicine history."<br /><br /><strong>Episode Resources: </strong>Billboard Chris Website: <a href="https://www.billboardchris.com/">https://www.billboardchris.com/</a>; Billboard Chris Twitter: <a href="https://twitter.com/BillboardChris">https://twitter.com/BillboardChris</a>;<br /><br /></p>
<p class="p1"><strong>JOIN PASTORS, CHURCHES, AND CHRISTIAN COMMUNITIES ACROSS CANADA WITH LCC'S NEWEST INITIATIVE, "<em>TRUE READINGS FROM TRUE ROYALTY."&nbsp; <br /></em></strong><strong>Sign up today:&nbsp;</strong><a href="https://libertycoalitioncanada.com/storyhour/">https://libertycoalitioncanada.com/storyhour/</a>&nbsp;<br /><br /><strong>Support Josh's Stand and Help Us Defend His Liberties! Sign Our Petition Here: <a href="https://libertycoalitioncanada.com/i-stand-with-josh-alexander/">https://libertycoalitioncanada.com/i-stand-with-josh-alexander/</a>;<br /><br /></strong><strong>SHOW SPONSORS:<br /></strong><strong>Join&nbsp;<em>Red Balloon&nbsp;</em>Today!:</strong> <a href="https://www.redballoon.work/lcc;">https://www.redballoon.work/lcc;</a>&nbsp;<br /><strong>Invest with Rocklinc:</strong> <a href="mailto:info@rocklinc.com">info@rocklinc.com</a>&nbsp;or call them at 905-631-546;&nbsp;<br /><strong>Diversify Your Money with Bull Bitcoin:&nbsp;</strong><a href="https://mission.bullbitcoin.com/lcc">https://mission.bullbitcoin.com/lcc</a>;<br /><strong>BarterPay: </strong><a href="https://barterpay.ca/">https://barterpay.ca/</a>;&nbsp; <strong>Barter It: </strong><a href="https://vip.barterit.ca/launch;">https://vip.barterit.ca/launch; </a><strong><br />Carpe Fide - "Seize the Faith": Store: </strong><a href="https://carpe-fide.myshopify.com/">https://carpe-fide.myshopify.com</a><a href="https://carpe-fide.myshopify.com/">/</a>, use Promo Code LCC10 for 10% off (US Store Only), or shop Canadian @ <a href="https://canadacarpefide.myshopify.com/">https://canadacarpefide.myshopify.com/</a> | <strong>Podcast: </strong><a href="https://www.carpefide.com/episodes">https://www.carpefide.com/episodes</a>;<br /><br /><strong>Sick of Mainstream Media Lies? Help Support Independent Media! DONATE TO LCC TODAY!:&nbsp;</strong><strong><a href="https://libertycoalitioncanada.com/donate/">https://libertycoalitioncanada.com/donate/</a>&nbsp;</strong><strong> &nbsp;</strong></p>
<p class="p1">Please Support us in bringing you honest, truthful reporting and analysis from a Christian perspective.<br /><br /><strong>SUBSCRIBE TO OUR SHOWS/CHANNELS:<br /></strong>LIBERTY DISPATCH PODCAST: <a href="https://libertydispatch.podbean.com">https://libertydispatch.podbean.com</a>; <a href="https://rumble.com/c/c-1687093">https://rumble.com/LDshow</a>;&nbsp;<br />OPEN MIKE WITH MICHAEL THIESSEN: <a href="https://openmikewithmichaelthiessen.podbean.com">https://openmikewithmichaelthiessen.podbean.com</a>; <a href="https://rumble.com/c/c-1412501">https://rumble.com/openmike</a>;<br />THE OTHER CLUB: <a href="https://rumble.com/c/c-2541984">https://rumble.com/c/c-2541984</a>;&nbsp;<br />THE LIBERTY LOUNGE WITH TIM TYSOE: <a href="https://rumble.com/LLwTT">https://rumble.com/LLwTT</a>;<br /><br /><strong>CONTACT US:</strong><br />Questions/comments about podcasts/news/analysis: <a href="mailto:mailbag@libertycoalitioncanada.com">mailbag@libertycoalitioncanada.com</a>;<br />Questions/comments about donations: <a href="mailto:give@libertycoalitioncanada.com">give@libertycoalitioncanada.com</a>;<br />Questions/comments that are church-related: <a href="mailto:churches@libertycoalitioncanada.com">churches@libertycoalitioncanada.com</a>;<br />General Inquiries: <a href="mailto:info@libertycoalitioncanada.com">info@libertycoalitioncanada.com</a>.&nbsp;<br /><br /></p>
<p class="p1"><strong>STAY UP-TO-DATE ON ALL THINGS LCC:<br /></strong>Gab: <a href="https://gab.com/libertycoalitioncanada">https://gab.com/libertycoalitioncanada</a>&nbsp;</p>
<p class="p2">Telegram: <a href="https://t.me/libertycoalitioncanadanews">https://t.me/libertycoalitioncanadanews</a>&nbsp;</p>
<p class="p2">Instagram: <a href="https://instagram.com/libertycoalitioncanada">https://instagram.com/libertycoalitioncanada</a>&nbsp;</p>
<p class="p2">Facebook: <a href="https://facebook.com/LibertyCoalitionCanada">https://facebook.com/LibertyCoalitionCanada</a>&nbsp;</p>
<p class="p2">Twitter: @LibertyCCanada - <a href="https://twitter.com/LibertyCCanada">https://twitter.com/LibertyCCanada</a>&nbsp;</p>
<p class="p2">Rumble: <a href="https://rumble.com/user/LibertyCoalitionCanada">https://rumble.com/user/LibertyCoalitionCanada</a>&nbsp;</p>
<p class="p2">YouTube: <a href="https://www.youtube.com/@liberty4canada">https://www.youtube.com/@liberty4canada</a> -&nbsp;<strong>WE GOT CANCELLED AGAIN!!!</strong></p>
<p class="p1"><strong>Please LIKE, SUBSCRIBE, RATE &amp; REVIEW and SHARE it with others!</strong></p>]]></description>
   <author><![CDATA[Matthew Hallick, Andrew DeBartolo, Billboard Chris, SDG Media]]></author>
   <enclosure url="https://app.dropwave.io/episode/fa691fba-8af6-427e-aba0-8ce851a73af3/billboard-chris-protecting-children-no-matter-the-cost.mp3" length="4900" type="audio/mp3"/>
   <guid isPermaLink="false"><![CDATA[fa691fba-8af6-427e-aba0-8ce851a73af3]]></guid>
   <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
   <source url=""><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></source>
   <itunes:author><![CDATA[Matthew Hallick, Andrew DeBartolo, Billboard Chris, SDG Media]]></itunes:author>
   <itunes:image href="https://prod-assets-spc1.nyc3.digitaloceanspaces.com/69893365-4165-4498-b0ac-e9ddf57a000f/cover-art/E86eLfK3NgjrpuXtk9kW9Qv6KcfzQpkJpToltreR.png"/>
   <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
   <itunes:duration>4900</itunes:duration>
   <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title><![CDATA[What We Can Learn from Woke Marxists [Leadership Now Podcast]]]></title>
   <link>https://app.dropwave.io/episode/1a2e0dbd-0761-47f5-930c-f54028b1e4b6/what-we-can-learn-from-woke-marxists.mp3</link>
   <description><![CDATA[<p>Are we being outsmarted by our opponents? Listen in as Dr. Aaron Rock unpacks strategies the woke cultural Marxists use to advance their agenda and the lessons we can learn from them.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>More Resources:</p>
<p>We are excited to partner with the Fight Laugh Feast Network to reach more listeners. Download the app here:&nbsp;<a href="https://subsplash.com/fightlaughfeastnetwork/app" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" data-callout-id="edit_links_in_description">https://subsplash.com/</a><a href="https://subsplash.com/fightlaughfeastnetwork/app" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">fightlaughfeastnetwork/app</a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>More resources at Dr. Aaron Rock&rsquo;s blog: Pursuit of Glory&nbsp;<a href="https://pursuitofglory.org/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" data-callout-id="edit_links_in_description">https://pursuitofglory.org/</a></p>]]></description>
   <author><![CDATA[Aaron Rock, Chris Eelman]]></author>
   <enclosure url="https://app.dropwave.io/episode/1a2e0dbd-0761-47f5-930c-f54028b1e4b6/what-we-can-learn-from-woke-marxists.mp3" length="3499" type="audio/mp3"/>
   <guid isPermaLink="false"><![CDATA[1a2e0dbd-0761-47f5-930c-f54028b1e4b6]]></guid>
   <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023 18:29:00 +0000</pubDate>
   <source url=""><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></source>
   <itunes:author><![CDATA[Aaron Rock, Chris Eelman]]></itunes:author>
   <itunes:image href="https://assets-cdn2.dropwave.io/3312a6b0-2b88-4186-bfdd-e9c55d3d7e0f/cover-art/DJmJxOQEoRfGbs693sV6kEnKEGWstWUfdEXbQra8.png"/>
   <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
   <itunes:duration>3499</itunes:duration>
   <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title><![CDATA[Daily News Brief for Friday, June 16th, 2023 [Daily News Brief]]]></title>
   <link>https://app.dropwave.io/episode/af91a7e9-e174-4d70-8f0c-c7b37cbec95c/daily-news-brief-for-friday-june-16th-2023.mp3</link>
   <description><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">This is Garrison Hardie with your CrossPolitic Daily News Brief for Friday, June 16th, 2023.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">It&rsquo;s been awhile guys, how about we start today with a little &ldquo;On this day in history!&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">June 16th, on this day in history:</span></p>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">1779 Spain declares war on Great Britain in support of France and the USA, starting the Great Siege of Gibraltar which goes on to last 3 years, 7 months and 2 weeks</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">1858 Abraham Lincoln says "A house divided against itself cannot stand" accepting Illinois Republican Party's nomination for the Senate</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">1963 Soviet space mission Vostok 6 is launched with Valentina Tereshkova onboard, who becomes the 1st woman in space</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">2000 Israel complies with UN Security Council Resolution 425 after 22 years, which calls on Israel to completely withdraw from Lebanon. Israel withdraws from all of Lebanon, except the disputed Sheba Farms</span></li>
</ul>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Film &amp; TV</span></p>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">1960 "Psycho", psychological horror film directed by Alfred Hitchcock, starring Janet Leigh, Anthony Perkins, and Vera Miles, opens in New York City</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">1978 Film "Grease" opens, starring John Travolta and Olivia Newton-John, based on the 1971 musical</span></li>
</ul>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://www.baptistpress.com/resource-library/news/southern-baptists-pass-first-approval-of-constitutional-amendment-over-women-pastors/"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.baptistpress.com/resource-library/news/southern-baptists-pass-first-approval-of-constitutional-amendment-over-women-pastors/</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>Southern Baptists pass first approval of constitutional amendment over women pastors</strong></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">A motion to clarify Southern Baptists&rsquo; stance on women and men filling the role of pastor was passed by messengers on June 14.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The motion, first brought last year by Virginia pastor Mike Law, received the required two-thirds vote by messengers. Another two-thirds vote of approval is necessary at next year&rsquo;s annual meeting to proceed with the amendment to Article III of the SBC Constitution.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The motion that was passed was amended from its original version, which was referred to the SBC Executive Committee last year at the SBC annual meeting in Anaheim, Calif.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Juan Sanchez, senior pastor of High Pointe Baptist Church in Austin, Texas, offered the amendment to Law&rsquo;s motion. Both pastors had discussed and agreed on its merits the previous weekend, Sanchez told fellow messengers.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Article III lists five points that place churches within the definition of cooperation with the SBC. The amended motion calls for a sixth, adding churches that affirm, appoint, or employ &ldquo;only men as any kind of pastor or elder as qualified by Scripture.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Sanchez initially presented his amendment as a &ldquo;substitute motion.&rdquo; SBC President Bart Barber, with no objection from the crowd, clarified later that it was being treated as an amendment.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The Executive Committee agreed at its meeting on June 12 to bring Law&rsquo;s motion to the messengers at this year&rsquo;s meeting. However, the EC&rsquo;s recommendation included EC opposition to the motion itself, stating that matters of belief ought to be addressed in the Baptist Faith and Message rather than the constitution.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Article VI of the Baptist Faith and Message 2000 addresses The Church, stating that &ldquo;While both men and women are gifted for service in the church, the office of pastor is limited to men as qualified by Scripture.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Bob Bender, pastor emeritus of Cross Fellowship Church in Colorado Springs, Colo., spoke in opposition to the motion.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">&ldquo;Southern Baptist brothers and sisters, I beg of you,&rdquo; he said. &ldquo;Do not do this. All the liberals have left us. It looks like we conservatives are left to fight amongst ourselves.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Women in associate pastoral roles need to be recognized for their contributions, Bender said.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Denny Burk, a messenger from Kenwood Baptist Church in Louisville, Ky., said the amendment &ldquo;does nothing to diminish [women&rsquo;s] calling and their work among us.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">&ldquo;We all believe they must be a part of the Great Commission,&rdquo; said Burk, who also serves as the director of the Center for Gospel and Culture at Boyce College.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The heart of the amendment, he continued, &ldquo;is about how to apply our doctrinal statement to our cooperation when it comes to female pastors.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The vote took place at noon just prior to scheduled luncheons by seminaries and other groups. Before the final vote, a motion to extend time was defeated.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://townhall.com/tipsheet/mattvespa/2023/06/14/ma-middle-schoolers-foment-a-pronoun-rebellion-during-pride-month-and-the-media-is-aghast-n2624491"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://townhall.com/tipsheet/mattvespa/2023/06/14/ma-middle-schoolers-foment-a-pronoun-rebellion-during-pride-month-and-the-media-is-aghast-n2624491</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>Middle Schoolers' USA Rebellion at Pride Event Causes Libs to Melt Down</strong></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">As the kids say nowadays, these middle schoolers are based. And by that, I mean they did something that sent shockwaves through a local Massachusetts community, stunned the local school board, and sent the liberal media into meltdown mode. Marshall Simonds Middle School in Burlington, Massachusetts, just outside of Boston, saw an LGBT event wrecked by a pronoun rebellion. Pride flags were destroyed, and chants of 'USA' rang throughout the school. To be more precise, they were chanting, &ldquo;My pronouns are USA,&rdquo; while decked out in patriotic colors. The event caused some local school board members to lose sleep over the incident, which proves that some people in this community need to go outside and touch some grass. Now, the LGBT mob is pushing to punish these kids for exercising their constitutional right to free speech and expression&hellip;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Listen to the reaction they caused: </span><a href="https://twitter.com/i/status/1669005086167560194"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://twitter.com/i/status/1669005086167560194</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> -Play Video</span></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Nancy Bonassera, co-chair of the Burlington Equity Coalition, said that students were invited to wear rainbow clothing on June 2 in celebration of Pride Month.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The coalition is calling for "consequences" for the students who participated in the counter-protest and is urging the district to fill a diversity, equity and inclusion role that they say has been vacant for almost a year.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Select Board member Michael Espejo said a "bad light has been cast over our town."&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">"I was very upset, I've lost sleep over it," Espejo said about the incident. "It kind of shocked me to my core. I didn't think something like that could happen in Burlington."&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Burlington School Committee Chair Martha Simon condemned the incident at a meeting Tuesday night, but declined any specifics on disciplinary actions, stressing the offenders were mere eighth graders.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">But a room full of parents, mostly of LGBTQ kids, argued that school officials needed to take a stronger stand and use the incident as a "teaching moment" refuting the notion that overt pride displays are somehow not appropriate for schools.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">This is just a reminder to get your kids out of public school, and here&rsquo;s a way to do that!</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>Classical Conversations</strong></span></p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Classical Conversations supports homeschooling parents by cultivating the love of learning through a Christian worldview in fellowship with other families. They provide a classical Christ-centered curriculum, local like-minded communities across the United States and in several countries, and they train parents who are striving to be great classical&nbsp; educators in the home. For more information and to get connected, please visit their website at ClassicalConversations.com. </span><span style="font-weight: 400;">Again that&rsquo;s </span><span style="font-weight: 400;">ClassicalConversations.com.</span></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://thenationalpulse.com/2023/06/14/farage-climate-lockdowns-are-coming-mark-my-words/"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://thenationalpulse.com/2023/06/14/farage-climate-lockdowns-are-coming-mark-my-words/</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>Farage: Climate Lockdowns Are Coming, &lsquo;Mark My Words&rsquo;.</strong></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Brexit leader Nigel Farage has foretold of impending, authoritarian measures by Western governments designed to limit people&rsquo;s movements and vehicle usage under the guise of &ldquo;climate change&rdquo; action. Speaking to supporters via social media, Farage warns: &ldquo;climate lockdowns are coming,&rdquo; citing a recent limit placed on automobile usage by the far left Mayor of London, Sadiq Khan.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">In response to one of Khan&rsquo;s tweets, which encouraged Londoners to &ldquo;avoid unnecessary car journeys,&rdquo; Farage argued: &ldquo;he&rsquo;s telling us: don&rsquo;t use your car unnecessarily, no engine idling, no burning of wood or waste.&rdquo;&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Khan has often warned of the dangers of climate change and used it to justify London&rsquo;s &ldquo;Ultra Low Emission Zone (ULEZ),&rdquo; which charges Brits &pound;12.50 per day to drive in the capitol.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://twitter.com/i/status/1668555766670802944"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://twitter.com/i/status/1668555766670802944</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> - Play Video&nbsp;</span></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Now it&rsquo;s time for my favorite topic, sports!</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://www.breitbart.com/sports/2023/06/14/huston-report-mlb-quietly-tells-teams-to-ditch-pride-uniforms/"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.breitbart.com/sports/2023/06/14/huston-report-mlb-quietly-tells-teams-to-ditch-pride-uniforms/</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>MLB Quietly Tells Teams to Ditch &lsquo;Pride&rsquo; Uniforms</strong></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Major League Baseball has quietly told teams that they can stop forcing players to wear uniforms and hats adorned with gay pride rainbow colors during their &ldquo;Pride Night&rdquo; games.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The decision comes as the L.A. Dodgers are taking major heat for inviting the radical, anti-Catholic hate group, the Sisters of Perpetual Indulgence, to its gay pride night game on June 16. And also as several major corporations, including Bud Light and Target, are facing serious economic losses thanks to their wild-eyed support of the far-left LGBTQ agenda.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The Tampa Bay Rays was the first MLB team to announce that players would not wear any rainbow-colored patches or jerseys during the June pride game this year.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">But, the league kept this change to its pride celebrations very quiet since giving teams dispensation to dump the pride colors and special jerseys back in February, according to the Washington Examiner.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The Rays had trouble with the pride night plans last year when several players balked at being forced to wear rainbow colors. At the time, several players rebelled against the pride jerseys and refused to wear them during last year&rsquo;s pride game.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Not all teams are dumping the forced fealty to the groomer agenda. The L.A. Dodgers and San Francisco Giants have announced their intentions to continue wearing the pride jerseys.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">There has been one team that has eschewed the pride business from the beginning. The Texas Rangers is the only team that has consistently refused to indulge in any demonstrations of &ldquo;pride&rdquo; and has never scheduled any &ldquo;Pride Night&rdquo; games.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Pro baseball is not the only sport to see growing resistance to having &ldquo;pride&rdquo; forced on players, games, and their sport. A growing number of NHL players and teams are also turning away from blatant expressions of the groomer agenda.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Teams, including the Chicago Blackhawks and the Buffalo Sabres, have experienced issues with using pride jerseys.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">In addition, San Jose Sharks goalie James Reimer opted out of wearing the jersey, citing his religious convictions. In January, Philadelphia Flyers defenseman Ivan Provorov also decided not to wear his team&rsquo;s gay pride jersey for similar reasons. And that same month, the New York Rangers opted out of wearing the gay pride jersey.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">It seems to all be part of a growing trend of Americans finally getting sick and tired of the gay agenda being shoved down everyone&rsquo;s throats by multi-billion-dollar corporations.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Major League Baseball was one of the last major sports to succumb to the extreme woke agenda. It&rsquo;s time it goes back to being the sport that welcomes everyone to come play baseball, not to be inundated with politics.</span></p>]]></description>
   <author><![CDATA[Garrison Hardie]]></author>
   <enclosure url="https://app.dropwave.io/episode/af91a7e9-e174-4d70-8f0c-c7b37cbec95c/daily-news-brief-for-friday-june-16th-2023.mp3" length="862" type="audio/mp3"/>
   <guid isPermaLink="false"><![CDATA[af91a7e9-e174-4d70-8f0c-c7b37cbec95c]]></guid>
   <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
   <source url=""><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></source>
   <itunes:author><![CDATA[Garrison Hardie]]></itunes:author>
   <itunes:image href="https://assets-cdn2.dropwave.io/2ab40ac0-e99d-4f25-a6d2-541d2c9b290a/cover-art/hUZu1H9lrRY0wXg66WHC8eLwYBA3hbRNTAHQmHt2.png"/>
   <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
   <itunes:duration>862</itunes:duration>
   <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title><![CDATA[Exodus 3:13-16 [Up and Ready]]]></title>
   <link>https://app.dropwave.io/episode/0caf687e-823d-4879-8547-5f83f6d9995a/exodus-313-16.mp3</link>
   <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
   <author><![CDATA[Mark Dewey]]></author>
   <enclosure url="https://app.dropwave.io/episode/0caf687e-823d-4879-8547-5f83f6d9995a/exodus-313-16.mp3" length="288" type="audio/mp3"/>
   <guid isPermaLink="false"><![CDATA[0caf687e-823d-4879-8547-5f83f6d9995a]]></guid>
   <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
   <source url=""><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></source>
   <itunes:author><![CDATA[Mark Dewey]]></itunes:author>
   <itunes:image href="https://assets-cdn2.dropwave.io/60c9e557-5882-401d-abb8-06de47904be4/cover-art/zZ8CYlYBUAUu8KNyZzjE092h2WlBblW8upM7tmFg.png"/>
   <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
   <itunes:duration>288</itunes:duration>
   <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title><![CDATA[Education Over Indoctrination, ONDP Hate Hoax, and Punishment for Pride Non-Conformity [Liberty Dispatch]]]></title>
   <link>https://app.dropwave.io/episode/5fd05e4c-f94b-48d1-a848-6d085d37472f/education-over-indoctrination-ondp-hate-hoax-and-punishment-for-pride-non-conformity.mp3</link>
   <description><![CDATA[<p class="p1"><strong>Liberty Dispatch</strong> ~ June 15, 2023<br />On this episode of the Dispatch, hosts Andrew and Matty re-cap the massive <em>Education Not Indoctrination </em>Protest hosted by Josh Alexander and Billboard Chris, at which an Ontario NDP MPP, Joel Harden, faked a hate hoax. They are also joined by concerned parents and students who have been reprimanded for failing to pay obeyance to the Rainbow during the "high, holy" Pride Festival. Apparently, you can get suspended for wearing shirts that state basic facts. Who Knew? This is our Canada. Time to wake up yet?<br /><br /><strong style="font-family: '-apple-system', BlinkMacSystemFont, 'Segoe UI', Roboto, Oxygen, Ubuntu, Cantarell, 'Open Sans', 'Helvetica Neue', sans-serif;">[Segment 1] - Education Over Indoctrination Protest ft. Josh Alexander &amp; Billboard Chris RECAP &amp; ONDP Hate Hoax <strong>(08:54-31:27)</strong>:<br /></strong>Billboard Christ Twitter: <a href="https://twitter.com/BillboardChris">https://twitter.com/BillboardChris</a>;<br />Rupa Subramanya: The progressive left discards Muslims as un-Canadian <span style="font-family: '-apple-system', BlinkMacSystemFont, 'Segoe UI', Roboto, Oxygen, Ubuntu, Cantarell, 'Open Sans', 'Helvetica Neue', sans-serif;">| </span><em style="font-family: '-apple-system', BlinkMacSystemFont, 'Segoe UI', Roboto, Oxygen, Ubuntu, Cantarell, 'Open Sans', 'Helvetica Neue', sans-serif;">National Post</em><span style="font-family: '-apple-system', BlinkMacSystemFont, 'Segoe UI', Roboto, Oxygen, Ubuntu, Cantarell, 'Open Sans', 'Helvetica Neue', sans-serif;">:</span> <a href="https://nationalpost.com/opinion/the-progressive-left-discards-muslims-as-un-canadian#Echobox=1686589069" data-doc-id="2726862000000716001" data-doc-type="writer">https://nationalpost.com/opinion/the-progressive-left-discards-muslims-as-un-canadian#Echobox=1686589069</a>;<br />The Hate Hoax CONTINUES!!! Mehdi Hasan LIES! Bogus Canadian Polls AND MORE! | Viva Frei Live: <a href="https://rumble.com/v2txtfm-the-hate-hoax-continues-mehdi-hasan-lies-bogus-canadian-polls-and-more-viva.html?mref=71v3&amp;mc=bp3oa">https://rumble.com/v2txtfm-the-hate-hoax-continues-mehdi-hasan-lies-bogus-canadian-polls-and-more-viva.html?mref=71v3&amp;mc=bp3oa</a>;&nbsp;&nbsp;<br /><span style="font-family: '-apple-system', BlinkMacSystemFont, 'Segoe UI', Roboto, Oxygen, Ubuntu, Cantarell, 'Open Sans', 'Helvetica Neue', sans-serif;">ONDP MPP's Hate Hoax | </span><em style="font-family: '-apple-system', BlinkMacSystemFont, 'Segoe UI', Roboto, Oxygen, Ubuntu, Cantarell, 'Open Sans', 'Helvetica Neue', sans-serif;">True North News</em><span style="font-family: '-apple-system', BlinkMacSystemFont, 'Segoe UI', Roboto, Oxygen, Ubuntu, Cantarell, 'Open Sans', 'Helvetica Neue', sans-serif;">:</span> <a href="https://tnc.news/2023/06/12/ndp-mpp-claimed-punched/">https://tnc.news/2023/06/12/ndp-mpp-claimed-punched/</a>;<br /><br /><strong>[Segment 2] - The Rainbow Mob Desires Sacrifice and They Want Your Children (32:51-54:08):<br /></strong>Blue Jays Celebrate Pride Weekend | <em>MLB</em>: <a href="https://www.mlb.com/bluejays/tickets/theme-days/pride-weekend">https://www.mlb.com/bluejays/tickets/theme-days/pride-weekend</a>;<br />Blue Jays ditch pitcher Anthony Bass over gender ideology criticism <span style="font-family: '-apple-system', BlinkMacSystemFont, 'Segoe UI', Roboto, Oxygen, Ubuntu, Cantarell, 'Open Sans', 'Helvetica Neue', sans-serif;">| </span><em style="font-family: '-apple-system', BlinkMacSystemFont, 'Segoe UI', Roboto, Oxygen, Ubuntu, Cantarell, 'Open Sans', 'Helvetica Neue', sans-serif;">True North News</em><span style="font-family: '-apple-system', BlinkMacSystemFont, 'Segoe UI', Roboto, Oxygen, Ubuntu, Cantarell, 'Open Sans', 'Helvetica Neue', sans-serif;">:</span><span style="font-family: -apple-system, BlinkMacSystemFont, 'Segoe UI', Roboto, Oxygen, Ubuntu, Cantarell, 'Open Sans', 'Helvetica Neue', sans-serif;"> </span><a style="font-family: -apple-system, BlinkMacSystemFont, 'Segoe UI', Roboto, Oxygen, Ubuntu, Cantarell, 'Open Sans', 'Helvetica Neue', sans-serif;" href="https://tnc.news/2023/05/28/york-u-christianity-colonialism">https://tnc.news/2023/05/28/york-u-christianity-colonialism</a><span style="font-family: -apple-system, BlinkMacSystemFont, 'Segoe UI', Roboto, Oxygen, Ubuntu, Cantarell, 'Open Sans', 'Helvetica Neue', sans-serif;">; <br />Anthony</span>&nbsp;Bass Apology | <em>Sports Illustrated</em>: <a href="https://www.si.com/mlb/2023/05/31/blue-jays-anthony-bass-apologizes-anti-lgbtq-social-media-post">https://www.si.com/mlb/2023/05/31/blue-jays-anthony-bass-apologizes-anti-lgbtq-social-media-post</a>;<br />California Seeks to Fine "Non-Affirming" Parents | <em>Free Beacon</em>: <a href="https://freebeacon.com/california/california-bill-would-punish-parents-who-dont-affirm-their-childs-gender-identity" data-doc-id="2726862000000716001" data-doc-type="writer">https://freebeacon.com/california/california-bill-would-punish-parents-who-dont-affirm-their-childs-gender-identity</a>;<br />Heartbreaking Testimony By Mother of Suicidal "Trans" Teen: <a href="https://twitter.com/i/status/1669038296381509632">https://twitter.com/i/status/1669038296381509632</a>;&nbsp;<br />AB-957 |&nbsp;<em>Calfironia Legislature</em>: <a href="https://leginfo.legislature.ca.gov/faces/billNavClient.xhtml?bill_id=202320240AB957">https://leginfo.legislature.ca.gov/faces/billNavClient.xhtml?bill_id=202320240AB957</a>;<br /><br /><strong>[Segment 3] - Interviews with Concerned High-school Students and Parents (55:00-01:27:08):</strong><br /><strong><br />JOIN PASTORS, CHURCHES, AND CHRISTIAN COMMUNITIES ACROSS CANADA WITH LCC'S NEWEST INITIATIVE, "<em>TRUE READINGS FROM TRUE ROYALTY."&nbsp; <br /></em></strong><strong>Sign up today:&nbsp;</strong><a href="https://libertycoalitioncanada.com/storyhour/">https://libertycoalitioncanada.com/storyhour/</a>&nbsp;<br /><br /><strong>Support Josh's Stand and Help Us Defend His Liberties! Sign Our Petition Here: <a href="https://libertycoalitioncanada.com/i-stand-with-josh-alexander/">https://libertycoalitioncanada.com/i-stand-with-josh-alexander/</a>;<br /><br /></strong><strong>SHOW SPONSORS:<br /></strong><strong>Join&nbsp;<em>Red Balloon&nbsp;</em>Today!:</strong> <a href="https://www.redballoon.work/lcc;">https://www.redballoon.work/lcc;</a>&nbsp;<br /><strong>Invest with Rocklinc:</strong> <a href="mailto:info@rocklinc.com">info@rocklinc.com</a>&nbsp;or call them at 905-631-546;&nbsp;<br /><strong>Diversify Your Money with Bull Bitcoin:&nbsp;</strong><a href="https://mission.bullbitcoin.com/lcc">https://mission.bullbitcoin.com/lcc</a>;<br /><strong>BarterPay: </strong><a href="https://barterpay.ca/">https://barterpay.ca/</a>;&nbsp; <strong>Barter It: </strong><a href="https://vip.barterit.ca/launch;">https://vip.barterit.ca/launch; </a><strong><br />Carpe Fide - "Seize the Faith": Store: </strong><a href="https://carpe-fide.myshopify.com/">https://carpe-fide.myshopify.com</a><a href="https://carpe-fide.myshopify.com/">/</a>, use Promo Code LCC10 for 10% off (US Store Only), or shop Canadian @ <a href="https://canadacarpefide.myshopify.com/">https://canadacarpefide.myshopify.com/</a> | <strong>Podcast: </strong><a href="https://www.carpefide.com/episodes">https://www.carpefide.com/episodes</a>;<br /><br /><strong>Sick of Mainstream Media Lies? Help Support Independent Media! DONATE TO LCC TODAY!:&nbsp;</strong><strong><a href="https://libertycoalitioncanada.com/donate/">https://libertycoalitioncanada.com/donate/</a>&nbsp;</strong><strong> &nbsp;</strong></p>
<p class="p1">Please Support us in bringing you honest, truthful reporting and analysis from a Christian perspective.<br /><br /><strong>SUBSCRIBE TO OUR SHOWS/CHANNELS:<br /></strong>LIBERTY DISPATCH PODCAST: <a href="https://libertydispatch.podbean.com">https://libertydispatch.podbean.com</a>; <a href="https://rumble.com/c/c-1687093">https://rumble.com/LDshow</a>;&nbsp;<br />OPEN MIKE WITH MICHAEL THIESSEN: <a href="https://openmikewithmichaelthiessen.podbean.com">https://openmikewithmichaelthiessen.podbean.com</a>; <a href="https://rumble.com/c/c-1412501">https://rumble.com/openmike</a>;<br />THE OTHER CLUB: <a href="https://rumble.com/c/c-2541984">https://rumble.com/c/c-2541984</a>;&nbsp;<br />THE LIBERTY LOUNGE WITH TIM TYSOE: <a href="https://rumble.com/LLwTT">https://rumble.com/LLwTT</a>;<br /><br /><strong>CONTACT US:</strong><br />Questions/comments about podcasts/news/analysis: <a href="mailto:mailbag@libertycoalitioncanada.com">mailbag@libertycoalitioncanada.com</a>;<br />Questions/comments about donations: <a href="mailto:give@libertycoalitioncanada.com">give@libertycoalitioncanada.com</a>;<br />Questions/comments that are church-related: <a href="mailto:churches@libertycoalitioncanada.com">churches@libertycoalitioncanada.com</a>;<br />General Inquiries: <a href="mailto:info@libertycoalitioncanada.com">info@libertycoalitioncanada.com</a>.&nbsp;<br /><br /></p>
<p class="p1"><strong>STAY UP-TO-DATE ON ALL THINGS LCC:<br /></strong>Gab: <a href="https://gab.com/libertycoalitioncanada">https://gab.com/libertycoalitioncanada</a>&nbsp;</p>
<p class="p2">Telegram: <a href="https://t.me/libertycoalitioncanadanews">https://t.me/libertycoalitioncanadanews</a>&nbsp;</p>
<p class="p2">Instagram: <a href="https://instagram.com/libertycoalitioncanada">https://instagram.com/libertycoalitioncanada</a>&nbsp;</p>
<p class="p2">Facebook: <a href="https://facebook.com/LibertyCoalitionCanada">https://facebook.com/LibertyCoalitionCanada</a>&nbsp;</p>
<p class="p2">Twitter: @LibertyCCanada - <a href="https://twitter.com/LibertyCCanada">https://twitter.com/LibertyCCanada</a>&nbsp;</p>
<p class="p2">Rumble: <a href="https://rumble.com/user/LibertyCoalitionCanada">https://rumble.com/user/LibertyCoalitionCanada</a>&nbsp;</p>
<p class="p2">YouTube: <a href="https://www.youtube.com/@liberty4canada">https://www.youtube.com/@liberty4canada</a> -&nbsp;<strong>WE GOT CANCELLED AGAIN!!!</strong></p>
<p class="p1"><strong>Please LIKE, SUBSCRIBE, RATE &amp; REVIEW and SHARE it with others!</strong></p>]]></description>
   <author><![CDATA[Matthew Hallick, Andrew DeBartolo, SDG Media]]></author>
   <enclosure url="https://app.dropwave.io/episode/5fd05e4c-f94b-48d1-a848-6d085d37472f/education-over-indoctrination-ondp-hate-hoax-and-punishment-for-pride-non-conformity.mp3" length="5955" type="audio/mp3"/>
   <guid isPermaLink="false"><![CDATA[5fd05e4c-f94b-48d1-a848-6d085d37472f]]></guid>
   <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
   <source url=""><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></source>
   <itunes:author><![CDATA[Matthew Hallick, Andrew DeBartolo, SDG Media]]></itunes:author>
   <itunes:image href="https://prod-assets-spc1.nyc3.digitaloceanspaces.com/69893365-4165-4498-b0ac-e9ddf57a000f/cover-art/E86eLfK3NgjrpuXtk9kW9Qv6KcfzQpkJpToltreR.png"/>
   <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
   <itunes:duration>5955</itunes:duration>
   <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title><![CDATA[The Forgotten War Over Law in America [God, Law, and Liberty]]]></title>
   <link>https://app.dropwave.io/episode/b632dc96-2183-4bd2-a9f3-13cfe304250e/the-forgotten-war-over-law-in-america.mp3</link>
   <description><![CDATA[<p style="font-weight: 400;">Few today know of the contest between Thomas Jefferson and U.S. Supreme Court Justice Joseph Story over the conception of law that would guide the newly formed United States.</p>
<p style="font-weight: 400;">The legacy of Story&rsquo;s victory&mdash;the triumph of common law over positivist law&mdash;is available to us today if we will employ it against the legal positivists of our day.</p>]]></description>
   <author><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></author>
   <enclosure url="https://app.dropwave.io/episode/b632dc96-2183-4bd2-a9f3-13cfe304250e/the-forgotten-war-over-law-in-america.mp3" length="1641" type="audio/mp3"/>
   <guid isPermaLink="false"><![CDATA[b632dc96-2183-4bd2-a9f3-13cfe304250e]]></guid>
   <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 15:49:00 +0000</pubDate>
   <source url=""><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></source>
   <itunes:author><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></itunes:author>
   <itunes:image href="https://assets-cdn2.dropwave.io/467f99a9-2921-459a-b63d-9710f4355795/cover-art/rIr4IHhzphL9sTK0H1WHOWtIatyPN6WB6fK4PmuT.jpg"/>
   <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
   <itunes:duration>1641</itunes:duration>
   <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title><![CDATA[Daily News Brief for Thursday, June 15th, 2023 [Daily News Brief]]]></title>
   <link>https://app.dropwave.io/episode/2af7c390-01f0-4a94-b4b2-62173cb2f9da/daily-news-brief-for-thursday-june-15th-2023.mp3</link>
   <description><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">This is Garrison Hardie with your CrossPolitic Daily News Brief for Thursday, June 15th, 2023.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">New Saint Andrews:</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Today&rsquo;s culture shifts like sand, but New Saint Andrews College is established on Christ, the immovable rock. The college is a premier institution that forges evangelical leaders who don&rsquo;t fear or hate the world. Guided by God&rsquo;s word, equipped with the genius of classical liberal arts and God-honoring wisdom, with a faculty dedicated to academic rigor and to God&rsquo;s kingdom, New Saint Andrews College offers an education that frees people.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Logic and language, hard work and joyful courage, old books and godly professors &mdash; New Saint Andrews Colleges provides time-tested resources that can equip your student for any vocation. To find out more, visit: nsa.edu</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">There has been some drama at this years&rsquo; Southern Baptist Convention over whether or not to disfellowship Pastor Rick Warren&rsquo;s Saddleback Church. Before we get to the decision, Rick Warren and Al Mohler had a mini debate on the issue&hellip;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://twitter.com/i/status/1668999347420164100"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://twitter.com/i/status/1668999347420164100</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> - Play Video&nbsp;</span></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">And here&rsquo;s the result!</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://www.christianitytoday.com/news/2023/june/saddleback-sbc-women-pastors-appeal-rick-warren-southern-ba.html"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.christianitytoday.com/news/2023/june/saddleback-sbc-women-pastors-appeal-rick-warren-southern-ba.html</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>Southern Baptists Reject Rick Warren&rsquo;s Saddleback Appeal</strong></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Nobody expected Rick Warren&rsquo;s appeal to be successful&mdash;not even Rick Warren. But he still stood up in front of 13,000 Southern Baptists gathered in New Orleans to make his case.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">For messengers at the SBC annual meeting, employing women pastors was not an agree-to-disagree issue. A vast majority&mdash;88 percent&mdash;voted to uphold the decision made back in February to disfellowship Saddleback.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The vote concludes two years of scrutiny and criticism toward the California megachurch for ordaining female pastors from its stage, welcoming a female teaching pastor to preach on Sundays, and naming a female campus pastor. This was the only chance to appeal.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">After the vote, Warren said he wasn&rsquo;t counting the appeal to succeed. Instead, &ldquo;I wanted to push the conversation that&rsquo;s been stagnant for years.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">&ldquo;I wanted to speak up for millions of Southern Baptist women &hellip; I believe their spiritual gifts, their leadership gifts and talents, are being wasted,&rdquo; said Warren, who considered himself well-positioned to make the case given his prominence, &ldquo;tender heart, and thick skin.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">But the messengers were largely unified against the appeal. As Warren offered up arguments for Saddleback, Southern Baptists online and at events ahead of the meeting countered with their own defense of the SBC&rsquo;s historic stance and their own complementarian convictions.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The messengers also voted to uphold decisions to disfellowship Fern Creek Baptist, another church removed for having a female pastor, and Freedom Church, which was found to have mishandled abuse allegations.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">At the direction of SBC president Bart Barber, the messengers were largely silent as the results of the appeals were announced on Wednesday morning. A small smattering of applause broke out from the back of the giant hall when the Saddleback results were read.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">This year was the first time Southern Baptists have removed churches over female pastors, declaring Saddleback and four others &ldquo;no longer in friendly cooperation&rdquo; with the convention.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://notthebee.com/article/paul-ryan-calls-on-gop-to-stop-focusing-on-the-culture-war-calling-it-polarizing"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://notthebee.com/article/paul-ryan-calls-on-gop-to-stop-focusing-on-the-culture-war-calling-it-polarizing</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>Paul Ryan calls on GOP to stop focusing on the culture war, calling it "polarizing."</strong></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Guys, pack it in! Paul Ryan thinks you're being too divisive.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://twitter.com/i/status/1668604854539804674"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://twitter.com/i/status/1668604854539804674</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> - Play Video&nbsp;</span></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Let's see, the left wants perfectly healthy kids who have been convinced that they're in the wrong body to chop their privates off. They want abortion on demand until birth, and, heck, even after birth sometimes. They want drag queens to be able to strip and twerk in front of kids wherever they want.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">And if you oppose that, according to Paul Ryan, YOU are the one who's divisive.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Yes, first let's fix the unbearably big debt crisis and China policy. Then we can leave a better America for our kids.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Oh, wait, they're all aborted and mutilated now? And America is a shell of its former self because the culture has been given over to people in the rainbow jihad?</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Well, at least we got that GDP under control!</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Of course, the thinks Ryan cares about are important. But if we cave on the culture war, what exactly are we fighting for?</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://thepostmillennial.com/former-philly-starbucks-manager-wins-25-6-million-after-being-fired-for-being-white?utm_campaign=64487"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://thepostmillennial.com/former-philly-starbucks-manager-wins-25-6-million-after-being-fired-for-being-white?utm_campaign=64487</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>Former Philly Starbucks manager wins $25.6 million after being fired for being white</strong></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">A former regional manager for Starbucks was awarded $25.6 million on Monday after a federal jury in New Jersey unanimously found that she had been fired because of her race. Shannon Phillips, who is white, received $25 million in punitive damages and $600,000 in compensatory damages. She is reportedly seeking further compensation for lost wages.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Phillips was terminated in 2018 in response to backlash against Starbucks after two black men, Rashon Nelson and Donte Robinson, were arrested while waiting for a business associate at one of the many Philadelphia locations she oversaw. Employees at the Center City Philadelphia cafe called the police on the pair after they asked to use the washroom but hadn't ordered anything.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Phillips claimed in her 2020 lawsuit that her firing had been racially motivated. She said she was targeted despite not having had any direct influence on the decision to call the police.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Her allegations were backed up by the testimony of Paul Sykes, the black supervisor of the employee who made the 911 call that day. Sykes argued that the fact he did not face any disciplinary action while Phillips was let go showed that Starbucks had acted in a manor that exhibited racial bias.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The coffee giant tried to claim that Phillips had been fired for being an ineffective regional manager, but they failed to convince even a single member of the jury.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The Starbucks employee in 2018 had called 911 claiming Nelson and Robinson were "trespassing" after they violated company policy by asking to use the washroom, which they said was only for paying customers.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Cops showed up, and hauled the pair out of the cafe as onlookers recorded the interaction on their phones. The men were released from custody hours later after the district attorney found that they hadn't committed any crimes.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The incident sparked backlash against Starbucks, and Phillips alleged that she had been used as a scapegoat by the company to show that they were not racist. Nonetheless, protests persisted, and Starbucks eventually shut down hundreds of locations across the country for one day so that staff could undergo racial bias training.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Nelson and Robinson settled with Starbucks for an undisclosed amount.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Now finally, it&rsquo;s time for my favorite topic sports!</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://fox8.com/sports/denver-nuggets-win-first-nba-title-beat-miami-heat-in-five-games/"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://fox8.com/sports/denver-nuggets-win-first-nba-title-beat-miami-heat-in-five-games/</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>Denver Nuggets win first NBA title, beat Miami Heat in five games</strong></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The Denver Nuggets have won their first NBA championship in team history, beating the Miami Heat in Game 5 on Monday.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The Nuggets edged out the Heat, 94-89, in Denver, overcoming dreadful shooting and a late flurry from Miami&rsquo;s Jimmy Butler.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Center Nikola Jokic, had 28 points and 16 rebounds for the Nuggets, who missed 20 of their first 22 3-point attempts and seven of their first 13 free throws but figured out how to close out the series on their home floor.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Jokic, who finished as the runner-up to Joel Embiid in the MVP race, was named to the All-NBA Second Team. He nearly averaged a triple-double over the season with 24.5 points, 11.8 rebounds and 9.8 assists per game over the 69 games he played.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Butler scored eight straight points to help the Heat take an 87-86 lead with 2:45 left after trailing by seven. He made two more free throws with 1:58 remaining to help Miami regain a one-point lead. Then, Bruce Brown got an offensive rebound and tip-in to give the Nuggets the lead for good.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Butler finished with 21 points for the Heat.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The Nuggets finished the regular season with 53 wins and 29 losses, the best record in the Western Conference and fourth-best overall for the NBA. They were one of 11 teams to have never won a championship.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">This is the first NBA championship for the Nuggets, who joined the league from the American Basketball Association in 1976 along with the New York (now Brooklyn) Nets, Indiana Pacers and San Antonio Spurs.</span></p>]]></description>
   <author><![CDATA[Garrison Hardie]]></author>
   <enclosure url="https://app.dropwave.io/episode/2af7c390-01f0-4a94-b4b2-62173cb2f9da/daily-news-brief-for-thursday-june-15th-2023.mp3" length="1002" type="audio/mp3"/>
   <guid isPermaLink="false"><![CDATA[2af7c390-01f0-4a94-b4b2-62173cb2f9da]]></guid>
   <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
   <source url=""><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></source>
   <itunes:author><![CDATA[Garrison Hardie]]></itunes:author>
   <itunes:image href="https://assets-cdn2.dropwave.io/2ab40ac0-e99d-4f25-a6d2-541d2c9b290a/cover-art/hUZu1H9lrRY0wXg66WHC8eLwYBA3hbRNTAHQmHt2.png"/>
   <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
   <itunes:duration>1002</itunes:duration>
   <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title><![CDATA[Ecclesiastes 2:9-11 [Up and Ready]]]></title>
   <link>https://app.dropwave.io/episode/1dbc3003-4706-4d95-86ea-57235055c3e5/ecclesiastes-29-11.mp3</link>
   <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
   <author><![CDATA[Mark Dewey]]></author>
   <enclosure url="https://app.dropwave.io/episode/1dbc3003-4706-4d95-86ea-57235055c3e5/ecclesiastes-29-11.mp3" length="272" type="audio/mp3"/>
   <guid isPermaLink="false"><![CDATA[1dbc3003-4706-4d95-86ea-57235055c3e5]]></guid>
   <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
   <source url=""><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></source>
   <itunes:author><![CDATA[Mark Dewey]]></itunes:author>
   <itunes:image href="https://assets-cdn2.dropwave.io/60c9e557-5882-401d-abb8-06de47904be4/cover-art/zZ8CYlYBUAUu8KNyZzjE092h2WlBblW8upM7tmFg.png"/>
   <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
   <itunes:duration>272</itunes:duration>
   <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
  </item>
 </channel>
</rss>
