<?xml version="1.0"?>
<?xml-stylesheet href="/storage/feed-stylesheet.xsl" type="text/xsl"?>

<rss xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
 <channel>
  <title>FLF - Daily News Brief</title>
  <link>https://dropwave.io</link>
  <description><![CDATA[FIGHT LAUGH FEAST PRESENTS SHOWS PROCLAIMING THE LORDSHIP OF CHRIST OVER ALL OF LIFE.
]]></description>
  <language>en</language>
  <managingEditor><![CDATA[fightlaughfeast@gmail.com (FLF, LLC)]]></managingEditor>
  <webMaster><![CDATA[support@dropwave.io (DropWave Support)]]></webMaster>
  <pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2023 07:25:46 +0000</pubDate>
  <lastBuildDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2023 07:25:46 +0000</lastBuildDate>
  <image>
   <url>https://is4-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Podcasts113/v4/58/56/52/5856525c-2973-cf29-3db9-21faa8595391/mza_1144696925612154085.png/1200x1200bb.jpg</url>
   <link>https://dropwave.io</link>
   <title><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></title>
  </image>
  <itunes:author><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></itunes:author>
  <itunes:image href="https://is4-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Podcasts113/v4/58/56/52/5856525c-2973-cf29-3db9-21faa8595391/mza_1144696925612154085.png/1200x1200bb.jpg"/>
  <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
  <itunes:owner>
   <itunes:name><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></itunes:name>
   <itunes:email>fightlaughfeast@gmail.com</itunes:email>
  </itunes:owner>
  <itunes:category text="News"/>
  <item>
   <title><![CDATA[Daily News Brief for Tuesday, October 10th, 2023 [Daily News Brief]]]></title>
   <link/>
   <description><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">This is Garrison Hardie with your CrossPolitic Daily News Brief for Tuesday, October 10th, 2023.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Gravity Jack:</strong></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Gravity Jack is a full service digital agency specializing in the development of Virtual &amp; Augmented Reality experiences, mobile apps, blockchain and Web3 projects. Founded in 2009 as the first American agency to offer augmented reality, they even patented it; Gravity Jack's digital experiences have been a source of innovation for small business, Fortune 500 Companies, and the US Military. Get your vision in motion at </span><a href="http://www.gravityjack.com/"><span style="font-weight: 400;">gravityjack.com</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://townhall.com/tipsheet/mattvespa/2023/10/08/100000-israeli-troops-mobilized-for-first-declared-war-since-1973-n2629547"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://townhall.com/tipsheet/mattvespa/2023/10/08/100000-israeli-troops-mobilized-for-first-declared-war-since-1973-n2629547</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Israel Mobilizes 100,000 Troops for Gaza Incursion</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">It might be the worst intelligence failure since the 1973 Yom Kippur War, a conflict that almost destroyed Israel after a surprise attack from Syria and Egypt. Israel was on the brink as Syrian forces reclaimed the Golan Heights, and it was by sheer luck that this invading force didn&rsquo;t move further to capture the key bridges along the Jordan River. Israel&rsquo;s heartland would&rsquo;ve been wide open. The game could&rsquo;ve been over, so Israel continues to respond forcefully against incursion by terrorists and its Arab neighbors since it&rsquo;s a nation with no strategic depth. How Jerusalem was caught sleeping amid this latest assault by Hamas on October 7 must be investigated since Shin Bet and Mossad are some of the most capable agencies in the world.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">This attack occurred on the 50th anniversary of the Yom Kippur War, and like that last war, the assault began during a Jewish holiday. Hamas launched thousands of rockets as cover for a land, sea, and air assault that could only have been made possible with outside help, considering its sophisticated nature. Iran has admitted they helped plan the assault.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The death toll has risen to 700, with reports of kidnappings, rapes, and murder of Israeli citizens caught in the fighting. Hamas operatives paraglided into Southern Israel, with other terrorists attacking over two dozen areas along the Gaza border. Some Americans were also kidnapped and murdered by these terrorists.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The footprint from Hamas was around 1,000 terrorists who stormed the infiltrated Israeli territory. Border Police and other forces are still fighting to restore order to the security situation in the area, but tanks and troops are being mobilized for a ground assault. Around 100,000 Israeli troops are ready to go into Gaza, with more reservists expected to be called up as Israel expects this to erupt into a multi-front war. Hezbollah has already launched rocket and mortar attacks in the northern Israel (via Associated Press):</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">More than 24 hours after Hamas launched its unprecedented incursion out of Gaza, Israeli forces were still battling with militants holed up in several locations Monday morning. At least 700 people have reportedly been killed in Israel &mdash; a staggering toll on a scale the country has not experienced in decades &mdash; and more than 400 have been killed in Gaza.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Israel said it brought in special forces to try to wrest control of four sites from Hamas fighters, including two points that militants entered earlier in their attacks.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Meanwhile, Hamas and the smaller Islamic Jihad group claimed to have taken captive more than 130 people from inside Israel and brought them into Gaza, saying they would be traded for the release of thousands of Palestinians imprisoned by Israel. The announcement, though unconfirmed, was the first sign of the scope of abductions.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The captives are known to include soldiers and civilians, including women, children and older adults &mdash; mostly Israelis but also some people of other nationalities. The Israeli military said only that the number of captives is &ldquo;significant.&rdquo;&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">As many as 1,000 Hamas fighters were involved in Saturday morning&rsquo;s assault, U.S. Secretary of State Antony Blinken said, speaking on ABC&rsquo;s &ldquo;This Week.&rdquo; The high figure underscored the extent of planning by the militant group ruling Gaza, which has said it launched the attack in response to mounting Palestinian suffering under Israel&rsquo;s occupation and blockade of Gaza.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">In northern Israel, a brief exchange of strikes with Lebanon&rsquo;s Hezbollah militant group fanned fears that the fighting could expand into a wider regional war. Hezbollah fired rockets and shells Sunday at Israeli positions in a disputed area along the border, and Israel fired back using armed drones. The Israeli military said the situation was calm after the exchange.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Israelis were still reeling from the breadth, ferocity and surprise of the Hamas assault. The group&rsquo;s fighters broke through Israel&rsquo;s security fence surrounding the Gaza Strip early Saturday. Using motorcycles and pickup trucks, even paragliders and speedboats on the coast, they moved into nearby Israeli communities &mdash; as many as 22 locations.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://themessenger.com/news/hamas-threatens-to-start-executing-hostages-if-gaza-strikes-continue"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://themessenger.com/news/hamas-threatens-to-start-executing-hostages-if-gaza-strikes-continue</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Hamas Threatens to Start Executing Hostages If Gaza Strikes Continue</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Hamas on Monday threatened to execute Israeli hostages being held in Gaza if Israel continues to conduct airstrikes without warning.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&ldquo;Any targeting of innocent civilians without warning will be met regretfully by executing one of the captives in our custody, and we will be forced to broadcast this execution,&rdquo; Abu Obeida, a spokesman for Hamas&rsquo; Qassam Brigades, said in a statement to Al Jazeera.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Hamas has claimed to be holding more than 100 Israelis prisoner in the Gaza Strip, according to the Qatar-based network.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The warning from Hamas came as Israeli Defense Forces intensified a bombardment of Gaza as dusk fell on Monday.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Images shown live on CNN showed heavy rocket fire lighting up the sky above Gaza, a Palestinian enclave about the size of Omaha, Nebraska, that's home to some two million people and considered one of the most densely populated places in the world.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">There are reports that American citizens are among those being held captive in Gaza. The State Dept. said it was working to confirm those reports.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://www.foxnews.com/politics/christian-baker-faces-new-lawsuit-over-gender-transition-cake-after-supreme-court"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.foxnews.com/politics/christian-baker-faces-new-lawsuit-over-gender-transition-cake-after-supreme-court</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Christian baker faces new lawsuit over gender-transition cake after Supreme Court</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The Colorado Supreme Court agreed to hear the case against Christian cake baker Jack Phillips, which he says is the "light at the end of the tunnel" after more than 11 years in court.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Phillips, owner of Masterpiece Cakeshop in Colorado, declined to create a custom cake for a same-sex wedding in a move that sparked a 2012 lawsuit that ultimately landed him at the U.S. Supreme Court. In 2018, the nine justices ruled that the state of Colorado was hostile to Phillip&rsquo;s religious beliefs and that the government can&rsquo;t force anyone to create custom works of art that communicate a message.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">But in 2018, Phillips faced a second lawsuit, this time from a transgender lawyer who requested a cake celebrating a gender transition. When Phillips declined, he was back in court on grounds that he discriminated against the lawyer. The Colorado Supreme Court just agreed to hear his case.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">"I hope it is the light at the end of the tunnel. I&rsquo;m pretty excited about it," Phillips told Fox News Digital in an interview. "The state court turned us down in our first case, but I think they realize now that I serve everybody."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">"This case is not who I serve, but it&rsquo;s always the what I&rsquo;m going to create not the who that&rsquo;s asking for it. And I hope they get that right this time," said Phillips.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Jake Warner, attorney for the Alliance Defending Freedom (ADF) defending Phillips, said that the lawsuit from the beginning was "clearly a set-up" with the intent of "targeting" Phillips and his beliefs.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">In 2018, Autumn Scardina, who identifies as transgender, asked Phillips to make a cake celebrating a gender transition &ndash; pink on the inside, blue on the outside. When Phillips declined, Scardina asked for a cake depicting Satan smoking a marijuana joint &ndash; which Phillips also declined.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">During the trial phase, "Scardina promised Phillips that, were this suit dismissed, Scardina would call Phillips the next day to request another cake and start another lawsuit," legal documents state.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Despite being in court for more than a decade, "numerous threatening emails" and death threats, Phillips says the case has helped to "strengthen" his faith.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">"We just celebrated our 30th anniversary of being in business Labor Day weekend. And so for 30 years we&rsquo;ve served everybody who&rsquo;s come into our shop," he said.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">"But this whole legal battle has helped strengthen my faith in Jesus Christ and strengthen our family, brought us all closer together. It&rsquo;s brought together a lot of people who have helped support us in so many ways."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Phillips mentioned that a gay man testified on his behalf in court "because he understood that I serve everybody, gladly served him, but he knows that I couldn&rsquo;t create every cake that people would ask me for."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">"It&rsquo;s been an encouraging time to see people stand beside us like that," he said.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">When it comes to this latest challenge, Phillips said Scardina is "not the enemy" and that he has "nothing to forgive."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">"This person isn&rsquo;t fighting against me, this case is against the state and my right to express my religious freedom and do so without fear of punishment in the marketplace," said Phillips.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Oral arguments for the case have yet to be set but likely will be scheduled for the springtime next year.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">ADF will argue that because of the Supreme Court&rsquo;s ruling in Phillip&rsquo;s previous case and the latest ruling in 303 Creative vs. Elenis involving a website designer, which determined that the government can&rsquo;t compel an artist to speak a message with which they disagree, that the law is on Phillips&rsquo; side.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">"What's critical now after 303 is the fact that this cake actually does communicate a message. The trial court found that this cake symbolizes the transition from male to female and went into great detail about the symbolism of the cake. The court found that blue represents male and pink represents female and that this cake communicates a message given the context of how cake artists are often asked to create custom cakes," Warner said.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">"In light of 303 Creative, the Colorado Supreme Court should reverse the decision below and affirm Jack's right to speak consistently with his beliefs. He shouldn't be punished for declining to create a custom cake promoting a message that goes against his beliefs," Warner added.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://www.theepochtimes.com/us/in-depth-us-gives-more-than-4-1-billion-in-grants-for-lgbt-and-transgender-initiatives-worldwide-5498747?utm_source=partner&amp;utm_campaign=BonginoReport"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.theepochtimes.com/us/in-depth-us-gives-more-than-4-1-billion-in-grants-for-lgbt-and-transgender-initiatives-worldwide-5498747?utm_source=partner&amp;utm_campaign=BonginoReport</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>US Gives More Than $4.1 Billion in Grants for LGBT and Transgender Initiatives Worldwide</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">During the past three fiscal years, $4.1 billion in federal money from taxpayers has been flowing to LGBT initiatives in the United States and around the world, an Epoch Times investigation has revealed.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">From Oct. 1, 2020, through Sept. 30, 2023, the U.S. government issued more than 1,100 grants to fund LGBT-promoting projects around the world, according to the Epoch Times review of a federal spending website.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The scope of projects varies widely.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Plans to create a "safe space for LGBTQ youth and adults to seek support and resources" earned a $1.8 million grant from the U.S. government in 2022 for the LGBT Life Center in Norfolk, Virginia.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">A proposal for encouraging "diversity, equity, and inclusion in Serbia's workplaces and business communities by promoting economic empowerment of and opportunity for LGBTQI+ people in Serbia" also was a winning plan. To fund it, the U.S. government awarded a Serbian activist group a grant of $500,000.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">An Armenian activist group, the Pink Human Rights Defender, received $1 million from the United States "to empower the LGBTI community" in Armenia, a tiny country next to Turkey.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The federal spending website can be filtered to show entries that include specific keywords. A list of payouts filtered by using the keyword "LGBT" included 1,181 grants, 31 loans, and nine direct payments during the past three fiscal years.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Overall, during the past fiscal year that ended Sept. 30, the government issued 454,821 grants.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Government grants provide free money for specific purposes. Federal loans can be repaid over long periods of time at low interest rates. Direct payments from the government give money to groups&mdash;they may be unrestricted, or for a specific use.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Of grants connected to the keyword "LGBT," individual payouts of at least $1 million totaled more than $3.7 billion combined. Many additional smaller grants also were awarded for LGBT initiatives but were not reviewed.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">When the list was filtered for grants including the word "transgender," 574 were listed. In that category, grants that paid out at least $1 million totaled nearly $478 million. Seven direct payments and nine loans with the keyword "transgender" also were issued by the U.S. government.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Yet money flows to these projects.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The U.S. Department of Education (DOE) gave $1.2 million to "LGBTQIA+ pride centers" in the San Diego Community College District.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Another DOE grant of almost $1.6 million was awarded for North Dakota's &ldquo;indigenous, LGBTQIA+, rural and underserved school-based mental health needs.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">A DOE grant gave $1.4 million to Boston College to study "mechanisms of health promotion in diverse youth through gay-straight alliances."&nbsp; In plain speak, the grant funded the promotion of gay-straight alliance clubs in Massachusetts middle and high schools.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">"The federal government thumbs their nose at the American people and continues to push this ideology into our schools,"&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">"They're doing it all over the world."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">And that - is your news for today&hellip; this has been your CrossPolitic Daily NewsBrief. Just so y&rsquo;all are aware - this will be the only newsbrief for the next week or so, as I will be out of town for our Fight Laugh Feast Conference at the Ark Encounter - as well as visiting my brother in North Carolina after that&hellip; if you liked the show &hellip;..</span></p>]]></description>
   <author><![CDATA[Garrison Hardie]]></author>
   <enclosure url="https://app.dropwave.io/episode/91befb2c-29af-424c-b413-285f79bee212/daily-news-brief-for-tuesday-october-10th-2023.mp3" length="828" type="audio/mp3"/>
   <guid isPermaLink="false"><![CDATA[91befb2c-29af-424c-b413-285f79bee212]]></guid>
   <pubDate>Tue, 10 Oct 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
   <source url=""><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></source>
   <itunes:author><![CDATA[Garrison Hardie]]></itunes:author>
   <itunes:image href="https://assets-cdn2.dropwave.io/2ab40ac0-e99d-4f25-a6d2-541d2c9b290a/cover-art/mUK8zsnHkCK3vep7E1W6UgYb9dTnLenASAMEFha3.jpg"/>
   <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
   <itunes:duration>828</itunes:duration>
   <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
  
  </item><item>
   <title><![CDATA[Daily News Brief for Friday, October 6th, 2023 [Daily News Brief]]]></title>
   <link/>
   <description><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">This is Garrison Hardie with your CrossPolitic Daily News Brief for Friday, October 6th, 2023.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Dropwave</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Do you have a podcast, or thinking about starting one? Does your church have a podcast feed for sermons? Then Dropwave.io is for you. Cancel culture is like walking on a thin glass bridge over the Grand Canyon. Every step you take could get you killed, I mean canceled. Since the beginning CrossPolitic has been working on being antifragile, so no matter what happens, our content can still be delivered to your tv and to your podcast. This past year, the Waterboy and his friend Jeremi, have been working on building a podcast hosting solution for rowdy platforms like CrossPolitic, so that you can be confident your podcast will never fall through that glass bridge. Dropwave offers seamless onboarding for shows that have been around for years to easy to use solutions for starting your own podcast. Dropwave will track all your show&rsquo;s downloads by city, state, and country, and it offers network and enterprise packages for solutions like the Fight Laugh Feast Network. Free to speak, Free to podcast, free to start your journey now at www.Dropwave.io.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://www.theblaze.com/news/child-allegedly-shoots-two-teens-at-football-practice-over-bag-of-chips"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.theblaze.com/news/child-allegedly-shoots-two-teens-at-football-practice-over-bag-of-chips</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Child allegedly shoots two teens at football practice over 'bag of chips'</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">An 11-year-old was arrested Monday after allegedly opening fire at a Pop Warner youth football practice in Apopka, Florida.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Police say that while only one shot was fired, two kids were ultimately struck &mdash; one in the back and the other in the arm.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The suspect is presently facing one count of attempted second-degree murder, though Apopka Police Chief Michael McKinley indicated prosecutors may pursue additional charges.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">WOFL-TV reported that the APD received a report of a shooting around 8:20 p.m. near a football field at the Northwest Recreation Center on Jason Dwelley Parkway where a kids' soccer game was also taking place.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">In the 911 call obtained by WESH-TV, one victim's mother can be heard saying, "My son got shot, miss! ... In his back!"</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The first officer arrived on the scene just four minutes later, finding one victim on the ground and another victim holding his grazed elbow.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The two victims, both 13 years old, were taken to Arnold Palmer Hospital and are expected to make a full recovery.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Surveillance footage shows juveniles crewing at the edge of the parking lot around 8:17 p.m., some still wearing their football jerseys.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The first victim, a heavy-set male with red shorts, can be seen chasing the alleged shooter toward his mother's vehicle around 8:18 p.m. Seconds later, the suspect opens the front passenger door and reaches into the vehicle, where his mother was reportedly in the driver's seat.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Inside and under the passenger seat was a purple handgun, according to the arrest report.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Brandishing the weapon, the suspect appears to turn the tables and chase the heavy-set victim, ultimately firing one shot into the victim's back. The same round proceeded to graze the second victim's elbow.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Following the shooting, WOFL indicated the alleged shooter was brought back to his mother's vehicle. He is now being held at a juvenile detention center.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">According to the arrest report, some witnesses claimed the victims had been "bullying" the alleged shooter. Others suggested the dispute was over "a bag of chips," reported the Orlando Sentinel.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Apopka Police Chief Michael McKinley told reporters, "It's unbelievable that young kids out here to play football and have a good time would get into an altercation."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">McKinley indicated the APD would be pursuing second-degree misdemeanor charges against the mother for allegedly having her firearm in an unlocked box, reported WKMG-TV.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Orange-Osceola State Attorney Andrew Bain, who took over for Monique Worrell after her suspension by Gov. Ron DeSantis, said his office will ensure there will be a reckoning.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">"The level of violence unacceptable right now, especially from our youth," said Bain. "We&rsquo;re going to stand strong to deal with those cases and try to end or put a big slow-down to what&rsquo;s going on in the streets right now."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Apopka Pop Warner canceled its Wednesday practice, noting in a statement, "One of our players was involved in a shooting incident that resulted in the injury of two players. We are deeply saddened by this event and our thoughts and prayers are with the families affected."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://www.breitbart.com/europe/2023/10/04/uk-announced-new-zealand-style-plan-to-ban-smoking-altogether/"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.breitbart.com/europe/2023/10/04/uk-announced-new-zealand-style-plan-to-ban-smoking-altogether/</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>UK Announces New Zealand Style Plan to Ban Smoking Altogether</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The United Kingdom is to phase out smoking altogether, the government says, by banning young people from buying cigarettes at all with a minimum age to buy rising from 18 every year until there isn&rsquo;t anyone left alive old enough to enjoy the habit.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Conservative Prime Minister Rishi Sunak announced his intention to steer the UK towards becoming tobacco-free by increasing the minimum age to buy products every year from here on, so the teenagers of today will never be old enough to legally take the habit up. Sunak acknowledged restricting personal freedoms was not always an easy choice for an instinctive Conservative but &mdash; underlining the way government decisions are driven by socialised healthcare &mdash; said it was important because smokers cost taxpayers through needing more hospital care.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">This is about &ldquo;preventative care&rdquo; to keep people out of hospitals, the Prime Minister said and told his governing party&rsquo;s annual conference that: &ldquo;I propose that in future, we raise the smoking age by one year every year. That means a 14-year-old today will never legally be sold a cigarette, and that they and their generation can grow up smoke-free&rdquo;.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">This would work, Sunak said, because the UK&rsquo;s previous experience with increasing the smoking age from 16 to 18 saw a drop in the number of people starting smoking. The Prime Minister said he would also look at cracking down on &lsquo;vapes&rsquo;, the electronic tobacco alternative.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">A report explaining the system as already implemented in New Zealand, which is becoming known for its draconian health interventions, stated in 2022:</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The law states that tobacco can&rsquo;t ever be sold to anybody born on or after January 1, 2009 &ndash; and from now on, the minimum age for buying cigarettes will keep going up and up.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">In theory, somebody trying to buy a pack of cigarettes 50 years from now would need ID to show they were at least 63 years old. But health authorities hope smoking will fade away well before then. They have a stated goal of making New Zealand smoke-free by 2025.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">New Zealand also took other measures in its law shakeup, including making getting hold of cigarettes more difficult for those who could legally use them. They are no longer sold in regular stores, but can only be bought at specialist tobacconists, cutting the number of locations where smokes are sold nationwide from thousands of locations to hundreds.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/policy/defense-national-security/biden-faa-nominee-promises-end-work-from-home"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/policy/defense-national-security/biden-faa-nominee-promises-end-work-from-home</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Biden pick to lead FAA promises hard push to end work-from-home policies</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">President Joe Biden's nominee to lead the Federal Aviation Administration would prioritize ending pandemic telework policies for federal employees and bring the out-of-date agency into the 21st century.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Former FAA Deputy Administrator Michael Whitaker told Senate Commerce, Science, and Transportation Committee members during his confirmation hearing on Wednesday that, if approved, he would focus heavily on matters with agency employees.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">"I do believe that it's important to be in person for collaboration and working together," said Whitaker, a pilot and former aviation industry executive. "This has been a challenging issue for all organizations, private or public. And I think what needs to happen is after understanding the situation that we're in and the limitations that might be there, issuing very clear guidance, what the expectations are to get people in the office."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">In July, the FAA announced that employees would have to return to the office no fewer than three days per week starting on Oct. 9. The union pushed back against a 100% return to office, complicating the agency's attempt to reinstate the policy.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Sen. Ted Cruz (R-TX) egged Whitaker on over the work-from-home policies and claimed the federal government was the only employer that had not returned to pre-pandemic policies.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">"When I talk to businesses in the private sector, virtually all of them, employees are going back to work, and they're physically present. And yet, throughout the Biden administration, we have a pattern in just about every agency where large portions of the workforce have apparently decided going into the office is optional," Cruz said. "That seriously limits the effectiveness of an agency and particularly an agency whose mission is protecting people's lives and the airspace."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">When asked by Cruz if he would commit to "working diligently" to bring employees back into the office, Whitaker agreed.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Whitaker was second in command at the FAA from 2012 through 2015. The agency has had a gap in leadership over the past 18 months. Returning to the FAA at this point, Whitaker said, would warrant three actions he would take in his five-year term as administrator.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">"First, I will work not just to maintain the safety record we have collectively achieved but build upon it. The two Boeing MAX crashes remind us that we must be ever-vigilant," Whitaker said.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The agency ought to ensure gaps in the FAA certification process are closed so that undisclosed changes manufacturers make to aircraft can still be caught before being put into use.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Second, the FAA should be more "agile and creative" and willing to "adapt quickly" and plan for the future rather than focus on the present.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The FAA has but one academy that takes years to complete, and it can only accommodate 1,800 air traffic controllers at a time.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Whitaker's final point was that the government should make the FAA a place where people interested in aviation careers, particularly air traffic controllers, want to work.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">He was tasked with hiring 6,000 air traffic controllers during his previous stint at the FAA but came up far short.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://dailycaller.com/2023/10/05/rnc-republican-presidential-primary-debates-donald-trump/"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://dailycaller.com/2023/10/05/rnc-republican-presidential-primary-debates-donald-trump/</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Even The RNC&rsquo;s Own Members Are Admitting Trump-less Debates May Be A Waste Of Time</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Members of the Republican National Committee (RNC) are frustrated with the current direction of their GOP primary debates, admitting that without President Donald Trump the events may not be worth it, according to Politico.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The frontrunner for the Republican nomination, Trump has skipped the first two presidential debates, a decision that has drawn criticism from rival candidates. After the first two debates were widely panned, some within the RNC think they need the President on the stage to make the forums worth it.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&ldquo;I think the only way you salvage it is if you get the frontrunner there,&rdquo; Tyler Bowyer, a national committeeman from Arizona, told Politico. &ldquo;Plan a debate where you get the frontrunner to agree to it.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The first GOP presidential debate, sponsored by the conservative youth organization Young America&rsquo;s Foundation (YAF), was aired exclusively on Fox News, Fox Business and Rumble. The debate was moderated by Fox News&rsquo; Bret Baier and Martha MacCallum in Milwaukee, Wisconsin.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The second debate was aired by the exact same networks, in addition to Spanish-language network Univision. The moderators included Univision anchor Ilia Calder&oacute;n, Fox Business host Stuart Varney and Fox News host Dana Perino.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">That debate fell flat, with many prominent conservative media figures criticizing the moderators for asking poor questions while candidates bickered and talked over one another. The RNC previously promised in 2022 to use debates to &ldquo;raise conservative media up&rdquo; and incorporate other outlets, but after the first two debates, conservative media companies outside of the mainstream media told the Daily Caller that they are feeling snubbed by the committee.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&ldquo;You can&rsquo;t put your head in the sand and pretend these debates are going to result in someone other than Donald Trump getting the nomination,&rdquo; Patti Lyman, the RNC&rsquo;s national committeewoman from Virginia, told Politico, adding that the debates were &ldquo;embarrassing&rdquo; and &ldquo;reflected very poorly on our party.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Despite some members pushing for Trump to take the debate stage, top officials are reportedly not attempting to get the front runner on the debate stage, a person with knowledge of the committee&rsquo;s operations told Politico. That reportedly includes RNC chairwoman Ronna McDaniel and chairman for the RNC&rsquo;s Temporary Committee on Presidential Debates David Bossie.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Trump himself doesn&rsquo;t think the debates should go on; the President told the Daily Caller that the RNC &ldquo;has to stop the debates&rdquo; because they are &ldquo;bad for the Republican party.&rdquo; Trump and his advisors have additionally urged the RNC to &ldquo;refocus its manpower and money&rdquo; on election integrity efforts rather than the debates, Politico reported.</span></p>]]></description>
   <author><![CDATA[Garrison Hardie]]></author>
   <enclosure url="https://app.dropwave.io/episode/209c7c1e-8ae8-4f94-8d42-c0a5726e5bd4/daily-news-brief-for-friday-october-6th-2023.mp3" length="745" type="audio/mp3"/>
   <guid isPermaLink="false"><![CDATA[209c7c1e-8ae8-4f94-8d42-c0a5726e5bd4]]></guid>
   <pubDate>Fri, 06 Oct 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
   <source url=""><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></source>
   <itunes:author><![CDATA[Garrison Hardie]]></itunes:author>
   <itunes:image href="https://assets-cdn2.dropwave.io/2ab40ac0-e99d-4f25-a6d2-541d2c9b290a/cover-art/mUK8zsnHkCK3vep7E1W6UgYb9dTnLenASAMEFha3.jpg"/>
   <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
   <itunes:duration>745</itunes:duration>
   <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
  
  </item><item>
   <title><![CDATA[Daily News Brief for Thursday, October 5th, 2023 [Daily News Brief]]]></title>
   <link/>
   <description><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">This is Garrison Hardie with your CrossPolitic Daily News Brief for Thursday, October 5th, 2023.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>Redballoon</strong></span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Not so long ago, the American dream was alive and well. Employees who worked hard were rewarded, and employers looked for people who could do the job, not for people who had the right political views.&nbsp; RedBalloon.work is a job site designed to get us back to what made American businesses successful: free speech, hard work, and having fun.&nbsp; If you are a free speech employer who wants to hire employees who focus on their work and not identity politics, then post a job on RedBalloon.&nbsp; If you are an employee who is being censored at work or is being forced to comply with the current zeitgeist, post your resume on RedBalloon and look for a new job. redballoon.work, the job site where free speech is still alive!</span></p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="http://www.redballoon.work/"><span style="font-weight: 400;">www.redballoon.work</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://www.breitbart.com/environment/2023/10/03/the-guardian-climate-change-has-made-rainstorms-20-wetter/"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.breitbart.com/environment/2023/10/03/the-guardian-climate-change-has-made-rainstorms-20-wetter/</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>The Guardian: Climate Change Has Made Rainstorms &lsquo;20% Wetter&rsquo;</strong></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The UK-based Guardian newspaper has made the remarkable assertion that rainstorms are now 20 percent &ldquo;wetter&rdquo; than they used to be, thanks to climate change.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">New York City&rsquo;s recent storm and accompanying flooding show the &ldquo;unmistakable influence of the climate crisis,&rdquo; the Guardian contended Monday, warning the city may not be &ldquo;prepared for severe climate shocks.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The type of storm seen on Friday &ldquo;is now 10-20% wetter than it would have been in the previous century, because of climate change,&rdquo; the Guardian alleged, citing a new &ldquo;rapid attribution study.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The Guardian said that such a pounding rainfall is &ldquo;a symptom of a warming planet&rdquo; because a hotter atmosphere is &ldquo;able to hold more moisture.&rdquo; Curiously, at this time last year, the Guardian declared that droughts are &ldquo;at least 20 times more likely&rdquo; than without &ldquo;human-caused global heating.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">In Monday&rsquo;s article, the newspaper cited climate expert Tommaso Alberti, who said the rainstorm that hit New York was predictable and &ldquo;aligns with climate change projections.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Human-driven climate change is the &ldquo;primary driver&rdquo; of major storms, which underscores &ldquo;the urgent need for climate mitigation and adaptation efforts,&rdquo; Alberti argued.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Michael Mann, who invented the thoroughly debunked hockey stick graph and has falsely presented himself as a Nobel Prizewinner, agreed that the New York storm was clearly attributable to global warming.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">&ldquo;New York is experiencing a very clear increase in these extreme &ndash; more than 2in per hour &ndash; rainfall events, and that&rsquo;s clearly tied to a warming atmosphere,&rdquo; he said.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Rohit Aggarwala, the New York City commissioner of environmental protection, has also blamed the city&rsquo;s reprehensible response to the storm on climate change, a convenient, if mendacious, dog-ate-my-homework excuse.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">&ldquo;The sad reality is our climate is changing faster than our infrastructure can respond,&rdquo; he said.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Daniel Zarrilli, the former chief climate policy adviser to New York City, uttered similar lamentations.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">&ldquo;It&rsquo;s clear that our cities and our aging infrastructure were built for a climate that no longer exists, particularly as a warmed atmosphere holds and releases more water,&rdquo; he said.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Reuters joined in the climate change blame game as well, suggesting that New York City&rsquo;s flooding is just part of the &ldquo;new normal&rdquo; ushered in by global warming.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://thepostmillennial.com/trudeaus-internet-censorship-plan-kicks-off-with-government-operated-streaming-registry?utm_campaign=64487"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://thepostmillennial.com/trudeaus-internet-censorship-plan-kicks-off-with-government-operated-streaming-registry?utm_campaign=64487</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>Trudeau's internet censorship plan kicks off with government-operated streaming registry</strong></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Friday's announcement from the Canadian Radio-television and Telecommunications Commission (CRTC) that online streaming services in Canada must register with the government agency has sent a chill throughout independent media.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Critics say it is the beginning of a broad registry of all online news media, even if the CRTC is currently maintaining that a $10 million threshold exists for broadcasters before they must register.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Previous CRTC vice-chairman and former editor of the Calgary Herald posted Monday on X: "Essentially and eventually, @crtceng intends to regulate everything on the Internet pretty much the way it regulates TV, radio and cable. Say g'bye to a free and open internet in Canada."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Noted journalist Glenn Greenwald posted on X: "The Canadian government, armed with one of the world's most repressive online censorship schemes, announces that all "online streaming services that offer podcasts" must formally register with the government to permit regulatory controls."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">In a news release, the CRTC announced that it is setting out which online streaming services need to provide information about their activities in Canada. Online streaming services that operate in Canada, offer broadcasting content, and earn $10 million or more in annual revenues will need to complete a registration form by November 28, 2023."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The declaration is part of the Trudeau government's Online Streaming Act, or Bill C-11, which was called a "dangerous first step towards government control of the internet" by Justice Centre for Constitution Freedoms President John Carpay, who wrote that "In the long run, the CRTC could end up regulating much of the content posted on major social media, even where the content is generated or uploaded by religious, political, and charitable non-profits."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">However, reading further down in the news release, the CRTC uses ambiguous language and apparently contradicts its own guidelines by stating, "online services that offer podcasts must register; however, individuals who use social media to share podcasts do not."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The CRTC has previously stated that: "individuals that host podcasts on their own websites or make them available on a subscription service platform other than a social media service are not explicitly excluded from the Broadcasting Act under subsection 2(2.1)"</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">University of Ottawa law professor Michael Geist was quick to comprehensively comment on the CRTC announcement in an essay.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Geist suggested the government's plans are "not as bad as critics would suggest, but not nearly as benign as the CRTC would have you believe."&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">But Geist says the real danger of the CRTC's announcement is that it is "the thin edge of the wedge with the registration requirement being the first step toward a far broader regulatory framework."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">"In fact, the rationale for the CRTC to include many of the services is that without such information it is not well positioned to regulate. This creates an obvious contradiction: the Commission claims that the registration requirement is de minimis requiring the disclosure of only limited information but then also argues that such information is important to future decision making on compliance with the Broadcasting Act objectives," he writes.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The CRTC hints that a broad registry is in the works: that "exempting online undertakings that provide news services from the requirement to register would prevent the Commission from having an adequate understanding of the players providing such services. Without information about the online broadcasting undertakings involved in the Canadian broadcasting system, it would be much harder for the Commission to develop policies aimed at implementing the above-noted policy objectives of the Broadcasting Act and conform to the proposed direction."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The CRTC says "[a] third consultation is ongoing. It considers contributions traditional broadcasters and online streaming services will need to make to support Canadian and Indigenous content. The CRTC will hold a three-week public proceeding starting on November 20, 2023, and will hear from 129 intervenors representing a broad range of interests."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://www.foxnews.com/world/swiss-writer-called-journalist-fat-lesbian-sentenced-60-days-prison-lgbtq-groups-applaud-decision"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.foxnews.com/world/swiss-writer-called-journalist-fat-lesbian-sentenced-60-days-prison-lgbtq-groups-applaud-decision</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>Swiss writer who called journalist 'fat lesbian' sentenced to 60 days in prison, LGBTQ groups applaud decision</strong></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">A court in Switzerland sentenced a writer and commentator to 60 days in jail for calling a journalist a "fat lesbian," and the decision is being lauded by LGBTQ+ groups.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">On Monday, French-Swiss polemicist Alain Bonnet, who goes by Alain Soral, was sentenced by the Lausanne court for the crimes of defamation, discrimination and incitement to hatred after he criticized Catherine Macherel, a journalist for Swiss newspapers Tribune de Geneve and 24 Heures, in a Facebook video two years ago.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">"This court decision is an important moment for justice and rights of LGBTQI people in Switzerland," said Murial Waeger, co-director of a lesbian activist group. "The conviction of Alain Soral is a strong signal that homophobic hatred cannot be tolerated in our society."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">In addition to the prison time, Soral was subsequently ordered to pay legal fees and fines totaling thousands of Swiss francs.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Soral&rsquo;s sentencing came after he called Macherel a "fat lesbian," criticized her work as a "queer activist" and said she was "unhinged" in a social media video, according to Swiss public broadcaster RTS.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Pascal Junod, a lawyer for Soral, mockingly blasted the conviction for a "crime of opinion" in an email to The Associated Press. He said the case aimed to probe whether a person had "sinned against the dogmas of single thought."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Soral will appeal to Swiss federal court and "if necessary" to the European Court of Human Rights, his lawyer added.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">In 2020, Swiss voters approved a measure that made it illegal to discriminate against people on the basis of sexual orientation.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">This conviction was not the first time Soral has gotten into trouble over his words as he was previously and repeatedly convicted in France for denying the Holocaust, which is a crime in France. He was sentenced to jail time in 2019 over the denials.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://dailycaller.com/2023/10/03/sports-governing-body-scraps-open-category-trans-athletes-no-one-signs-up/"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://dailycaller.com/2023/10/03/sports-governing-body-scraps-open-category-trans-athletes-no-one-signs-up/</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>Sports Governing Body Scraps &lsquo;Open&rsquo; Category For Trans Athletes After No One Signs Up</strong></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">World Aquatics (WA), the international water sports governing body, announced in a press release Tuesday that it is getting rid of its transgender &ldquo;open&rdquo; category for the 2023 World Cup since no athletes had decided to sign up.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">WA said in August that it was opening a category for athletes to swim the 50-meter and 100-meter distances regardless of gender. After athletes failed to show, WA decided to scrap the category for the World Cup in Berlin, Germany, from Oct. 6 to Oct. 8 but noted that the &ldquo;Open Category Working Group&rdquo; would still consider reopening the division if demand increased in the future, according to the press release.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">&ldquo;The World Aquatics Open Category Working Group will continue its work and engagement with the aquatics community on Open Category events,&rdquo; the announcement reads. &ldquo;Even if there is no current demand at the elite level, the working group is planning to look at the possibility of including Open Category races at Masters events in the future.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">WA originally planned to debut the open category in July in Fukuoka, Japan, during its congressional meeting but later decided against it. The organization announced its new &ldquo;gender inclusion policy&rdquo; in 2022, which made it possible to create the &ldquo;open category&rdquo; for future competitions and required male athletes looking to compete in the female division to have transitioned and experienced no puberty symptoms before the age of 12, as well maintaining regular testosterone levels below 2.5 nanomoles per liter.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">&ldquo;When World Aquatics instituted its Policy on Eligibility for the Men&rsquo;s and Women&rsquo;s Competition Categories, we committed to exploring the creation of an open category,&rdquo; World Aquatics President Husain Al-Musallam said, according to the press release. &ldquo;True to our word, a team of experts has diligently worked to make this a reality. I would like to thank all those who have helped World Aquatics to deliver this opportunity.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Other sport governing bodies have opted to not allow transgender athletes to compete in divisions outside of their biological sex, such as the International Cycling Union, which announced in July that males who had transitioned after puberty could not compete in the female category. The International Angling Sports Federation made a similar decision on Sept. 29 after England&rsquo;s team said that it would boycott the world championship if men were allowed to compete with women.</span></p>]]></description>
   <author><![CDATA[Garrison Hardie]]></author>
   <enclosure url="https://app.dropwave.io/episode/fa06579e-1a13-4220-aacb-2f554b89505b/daily-news-brief-for-thursday-october-5th-2023.mp3" length="756" type="audio/mp3"/>
   <guid isPermaLink="false"><![CDATA[fa06579e-1a13-4220-aacb-2f554b89505b]]></guid>
   <pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
   <source url=""><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></source>
   <itunes:author><![CDATA[Garrison Hardie]]></itunes:author>
   <itunes:image href="https://assets-cdn2.dropwave.io/2ab40ac0-e99d-4f25-a6d2-541d2c9b290a/cover-art/mUK8zsnHkCK3vep7E1W6UgYb9dTnLenASAMEFha3.jpg"/>
   <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
   <itunes:duration>756</itunes:duration>
   <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
  
  </item>
 </channel>
</rss>
