<?xml version="1.0"?>
<?xml-stylesheet href="/storage/feed-stylesheet.xsl" type="text/xsl"?>

<rss xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
 <channel>
  <title>FLF - Daily News Brief</title>
  <link>https://dropwave.io</link>
  <description><![CDATA[FIGHT LAUGH FEAST PRESENTS SHOWS PROCLAIMING THE LORDSHIP OF CHRIST OVER ALL OF LIFE.
]]></description>
  <language>en</language>
  <managingEditor><![CDATA[fightlaughfeast@gmail.com (FLF, LLC)]]></managingEditor>
  <webMaster><![CDATA[support@dropwave.io (DropWave Support)]]></webMaster>
  <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2023 07:25:46 +0000</pubDate>
  <lastBuildDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2023 07:25:46 +0000</lastBuildDate>
  <image>
   <url>https://is4-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Podcasts113/v4/58/56/52/5856525c-2973-cf29-3db9-21faa8595391/mza_1144696925612154085.png/1200x1200bb.jpg</url>
   <link>https://dropwave.io</link>
   <title><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></title>
  </image>
  <itunes:author><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></itunes:author>
  <itunes:image href="https://is4-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Podcasts113/v4/58/56/52/5856525c-2973-cf29-3db9-21faa8595391/mza_1144696925612154085.png/1200x1200bb.jpg"/>
  <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
  <itunes:owner>
   <itunes:name><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></itunes:name>
   <itunes:email>fightlaughfeast@gmail.com</itunes:email>
  </itunes:owner>
  <itunes:category text="News"/>
  <item>
   <title><![CDATA[Daily News Brief for Friday, June 9th, 2023 [Daily News Brief]]]></title>
   <link>https://app.dropwave.io/episode/5ff4e2d9-6666-4f00-8116-bb573c04feb5/daily-news-brief-for-friday-june-9th-2023.mp3</link>
   <description><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">This is Garrison Hardie with your CrossPolitic Daily News Brief for Friday, June 9th, 2023.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>Olive Tree Biblical Software:</strong></span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Discover why more than a million people use the free Olive Tree Bible App as their go-to for reading, studying, and listening to the God&rsquo;s Word.&nbsp;&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Download one of many free Bibles and start taking notes, highlighting verses, and bookmarking your favorite passages.&nbsp;&nbsp;</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Read at your own pace, or choose from a large selection of Reading Plans, including the Bible Reading Challenge.&nbsp;</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">When you are ready to go deeper into your studies, Olive Tree is right there with a large selection of study Bibles, commentaries, and other helpful study resources available for purchase.&nbsp;&nbsp;</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">An extensive bookstore allows you to build your digital library one book at a time.&nbsp;</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Olive Tree&rsquo;s sync technology lets you pick up where you left off on your tablet, pc or phone and get right to studying on another supported device.&nbsp;</span></li>
</ul>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">&nbsp;</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Now here's the best part &ndash; You can start with the Olive Tree Essentials Bundle for FREE. Visit www.olivetree.com/FLF and download it today! </span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">We start today&rsquo;s news, with world news&hellip;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://justthenews.com/government/security/china-place-secret-base-cuba-spy-us-report"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://justthenews.com/government/security/china-place-secret-base-cuba-spy-us-report</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>China to place secret base in Cuba to spy on US:</strong></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">China reportedly reached an agreement with Cuba to allow them to create an electronic eavesdropping facility on the Caribbean island, which is located about 100 miles south of Florida, as tensions between Beijing and Washington have been rising dramatically over the past several months.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The Cuban facility would allow Chinese intelligence officials to monitor U.S. ship traffic and to listen to electronic communications throughout the southeastern United States, according to U.S. officials with knowledge of highly classified intelligence, The Wall Street Journal reported Thursday.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">China reached an agreement in principle to pay several billion dollars to the impoverished Marxist-Leninist nation of Cuba, officials familiar with the matter also said.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The Biden administration is especially concerned about the report due to Cuba's close proximity to the United States, and the fact that the eavesdropping facility could try to listen to communications from the many military bases in the southeast. U.S. intelligence indicates that the base would allow China to monitor communications ranging from satellite transmissions to emails to phone calls.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">This brings to mind the 1962 Cuban Missile Crisis, when the Soviet Union attempted to extend its influence in the Western Hemisphere, as the Journal points out. "The U.S. and the Soviet Union came to the brink of nuclear war after the Soviets deployed nuclear-capable missiles to Cuba, prompting a U.S. Navy quarantine of the island."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">This new report comes after China sent a spy balloon across most of the continental United States in February reportedly to gather intelligence from several sensitive military sites.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">More U.S. states are banning or considering banning foreign farmland ownership after China bought 370 acres of land in North Dakota about 12 miles from the Grand Forks Air Force Base. According to a 2021 Agriculture Department report, China owns approximately 384,000 acres of agricultural land in the U.S.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Additionally, China is placing its own police officers in New York City to target Chinese dissidents, according to the U.S. Justice Department.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://www.foxnews.com/us/canadian-wildfires-pour-smoke-us-heavy-haze-creates-martian-like-scene-new-york-city"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.foxnews.com/us/canadian-wildfires-pour-smoke-us-heavy-haze-creates-martian-like-scene-new-york-city</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>Canadian wildfires pour smoke into US, heavy haze creates Martian-like scene in NYC</strong></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Canadian wildfires are continuing to pour smoke along the East Coast of the United States, including the New York City area, which Wednesday afternoon, appeared red like it was on the planet Mars.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Canadian officials have reached out to other countries to help fight the more than 400 fires across the country that have displaced 20,000 people.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The Canadian officials also said this is shaping up to be the nation&rsquo;s worst wildfire season ever, after being sparked on drier-than-usual ground and accelerating quickly.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">In Quebec, more than 100 fires were burning uncontrollably Tuesday.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">One of the biggest concerns from the fires is the air quality.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">New York City is experiencing its worst air quality in recorded history, per FOX Weather&rsquo;s analysis of EPA historical data, affecting millions of people.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">NYC officials like Mayor Eric Adams and health and emergency management officials warned residents to remain indoors as much as possible and limit their time outside. If residents must go outside, officials suggested masking up.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The governor also posted an update from the New York Department of Environmental Conservation and issued another Air Quality Health Advisory tomorrow for all of New York.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Because of the smoke, the Federal Aviation Administration grounded all planes at New York City&rsquo;s LaGuardia Airport on Wednesday.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Delays are also expected at other area airports.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Many other officials turned to Twitter regarding the fires.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The mayor of Ottawa. Mark Sutcliffe, said he was very concerned about the conditions and sympathetic to those who have reduced lung capacity and asthma, and might be having difficulty today.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Ottawa Public Health advised citizens to keep an eye on their health symptoms as the Air Quality Health Index continues to degrade.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">"If you experience symptoms such as tightness in your chest, wheezing or shortness of breath, seek medical attention," the agency said.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">We now turn our attention to Matt Walsh&hellip;&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://www.dailywire.com/news/matt-walsh-undercover-investigation-catches-trans-health-care-providers-falsifying-patient-info-to-fast-track-sex-change-surgeries"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.dailywire.com/news/matt-walsh-undercover-investigation-catches-trans-health-care-providers-falsifying-patient-info-to-fast-track-sex-change-surgeries</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>Matt Walsh Undercover Investigation Catches Trans Health Care Providers &lsquo;Rubber-Stamping&rsquo; Sex-Change Surgeries</strong></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Some of the nation&rsquo;s largest transgender &ldquo;health care&rdquo; providers are rubber-stamping approvals for life-altering sex-change procedures &mdash; and even falsely representing health diagnoses of patients &mdash; so insurance companies will cover the medical expenses, Daily Wire host Matt Walsh revealed in a tweet thread Wednesday.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">In an undercover investigation, Walsh and his team discovered how easy it is to get approved for sex-change surgery when one of the host&rsquo;s producers got a thumbs up for an orchiectomy &mdash; a procedure to remove testicles &mdash; after just a 22-minute virtual appointment with Plume, the largest transgender health care provider in the U.S.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Walsh&rsquo;s producer Gregg Re got scheduled for a video call with Plume after providing a fake name on an intake form. Re made it clear that he had not been experiencing gender dysphoria for six months or more, he mispronounced the name of the surgery he wanted, and he said he didn&rsquo;t know what effect the surgery would have on him. Yet, Plume&rsquo;s nurse practitioner told Re &ldquo;she wanted to write the most &lsquo;solid&rsquo; letter possible to justify surgery,&rdquo; Walsh explained.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Three days later, Plume sent a letter to Re, who said his name was &ldquo;Chelsea Bussey,&rdquo; saying Re was experiencing &ldquo;significant, ongoing gender dysphoria&rdquo; &mdash; despite &ldquo;Bussey&rdquo; stating unequivocally that this was not the case &mdash; and recommending &ldquo;Chelsea&rdquo; for testicle removal. Walsh said that in a text message to Re, Plume explained that the letters of recommendation are sent using a template based on standards provided by the radical World Professional Association for Transgender Health, also known as WPATH. Plume sells letters of recommendation for $150 to those seeking transgender surgeries.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Now I&rsquo;m about to play a brief audio clip for you guys&hellip; Gregg also tells Plume&rsquo;s nurse practitioner that his father has been prescribing him hormones for years. The nurse doesn&rsquo;t question this in any way. Instead, she says that arrangement is &ldquo;perfect.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://twitter.com/i/status/1666496338035367937"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://twitter.com/i/status/1666496338035367937</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> - Play Video&nbsp;</span></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Folx, another popular transgender telehealth service, also approves patients for sex-change procedures even if they are not diagnosed with &ldquo;gender dysphoria,&rdquo; according to Walsh.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">&ldquo;Folx, which provides letters authorizing surgeries for a nominal fee, goes on to admit that &lsquo;it&rsquo;s quite possible&rsquo; patients will receive a letter indicating a gender dysphoria diagnosis, even though they &lsquo;really do not have dysphoria,&rsquo;&rdquo; Walsh noted. &ldquo;We reached out to Folx about this. A staff member confirmed that a &lsquo;diagnosis&rsquo; of gender dysphoria &mdash; with the word &lsquo;diagnosis&rsquo; in scare quotes &mdash; is a &lsquo;requirement&rsquo; for insurance purposes, even if it &lsquo;doesn&rsquo;t apply.&rsquo;&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Ari Groner, a licensed clinical social worker who educates doctors on &ldquo;trans healthcare,&rdquo; openly admitted in a video that those seeking transgender surgeries can easily get letters of recommendation.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://twitter.com/i/status/1666496309535072257"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://twitter.com/i/status/1666496309535072257</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> - Play Video&nbsp;</span></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Groner tells her audience to treat the letters as a &ldquo;persuasive essay," and to green-light even suicidal patients.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://twitter.com/i/status/1666496312433336324"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://twitter.com/i/status/1666496312433336324</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> - Play Video&nbsp;</span></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Walsh and his team dug deeper into how Plume and Folx have expanded across the U.S. with Plume reaching people in 41 states and Folx present in 47 states.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">&ldquo;The answer is that there&rsquo;s big money behind this,&rdquo; Walsh said. &ldquo;Plume and Folx raised more than $45 million last year. [Craft Ventures] just led Plume&rsquo;s $14 million fundraising round. Is [Craft general partner David Sacks] aware this is going on?&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">With Plume and Folx operating in most of the U.S., The Daily Wire host asked if medical insurance companies were aware that the transgender medical providers were sending letters of recommendation &ldquo;based on obviously false information.&rdquo;&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Walsh concluded his thread by arguing that his investigation revealed yet another dark secret in the &ldquo;corrupt and fraudulent&rdquo; transgender medical industry.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Moving on&hellip; The White House may have a back up plan if SCOTUS strikes down Student Loan giveaways.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://dailycaller.com/2023/06/08/white-house-plots-backup-plan-scotus-student-debt-cancellation-overturn-biden/"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://dailycaller.com/2023/06/08/white-house-plots-backup-plan-scotus-student-debt-cancellation-overturn-biden/</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>White House Quietly Prepares Backup Plan If SCOTUS Strikes Down Student Loan Giveaway</strong></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The Biden administration is quietly preparing for the possibility that the Supreme Court will strike down its controversial student loan forgiveness plan later in June, according to a Wall Street Journal report.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The White House&rsquo;s public position is that it expects the court to uphold the debt cancellation package, but several administration officials have conveyed private doubts about its prospects of survival upon review, according to the report. Behind the scenes, administration officials are exploring various legal and communications strategies to pursue in the event that the Supreme Court eventually overturns the signature Biden policy, according to the report.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">As you might recall, the federal student debt cancellation plan allows for millions of individual borrowers to cancel up to $20,000 in federal student loan debt as currently constructed. The court&rsquo;s majority signaled its critical attitude of the sweeping policy action in oral arguments in February 2023, according to the report.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Observers anticipate that the Supreme Court will issue a ruling on the debt cancellation plan later in June 2023. Biden administration officials privately have discussed more precisely targeted policy alternatives to the current plan, according to the report. However, it is unlikely the president and his staff will be keen to engage in another similar protracted legal battle should the administration opt to try a different legal approach to widespread student debt cancellation, according to the report.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">These preparations come on the heels of the bipartisan debt-ceiling negotiations, a condition of which included the resumption of student loan payments by Aug. 29 of this year.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">After that date, the administration is planning to establish a three-month grace period for borrowers who miss payments so that they will not immediately be considered delinquent to the detriment of their personal credit, according to the WSJ report. Administration officials have informed companies that process the affected loan payments of the plan for the grace period, but have not yet received other guidelines from the Department of Education (DOE) which were supposed to have been delivered in April, according to the WSJ report.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The DOE is also considering options to work around a prospective Supreme Court slap down, seeking to expand targeted debt cancellation already available to disabled borrowers and public servants, according to the WSJ report. Additionally, the White House is making plans to highlight its proposed alterations to income-based payment options which the administration is to finalize by year&rsquo;s end.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">And before we go today&hellip;.. It&rsquo;s time for my favorite topic, sports!!!</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://www.breitbart.com/sports/2023/06/06/damar-hamlin-practices-with-bills-for-first-time-since-suffering-cardiac-arrest-on-monday-night-football/"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.breitbart.com/sports/2023/06/06/damar-hamlin-practices-with-bills-for-first-time-since-suffering-cardiac-arrest-on-monday-night-football/</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>Damar Hamlin Practices with Bills for First Time Since Suffering Cardiac Arrest on Monday Night Football</strong></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Bills safety Damar Hamlin is on the field and practicing with his teammates for the first time since suffering cardiac arrest during a Monday Night Football game less than six months ago.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The practice was not without difficulty for Hamlin, however. At one point, he was slow getting up after a play and had to be evaluated by team trainers who seemed to focus on his right arm and shoulder, Alaina Getzenberg reports.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Hamlin&rsquo;s presence is not a complete surprise. He was cleared to resume football activities in April. Though, his full participation with a helmet may have come as a bit of a surprise to his head coach Sean McDermott. Before practice on Tuesday, McDermott said the team was &ldquo;going to continue to take it one day at a time and just support Damar in every way possible.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">He further said that Hamlin wasn&rsquo;t practicing but was &ldquo;in the building working.&rdquo; Well, as seen in the video, he did much more than stay in the building.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Hamlin was cleared to return by multiple specialists in and out of the NFL. Hamlin is entering his third season with Buffalo.</span></p>]]></description>
   <author><![CDATA[Garrison Hardie]]></author>
   <enclosure url="https://app.dropwave.io/episode/5ff4e2d9-6666-4f00-8116-bb573c04feb5/daily-news-brief-for-friday-june-9th-2023.mp3" length="872" type="audio/mp3"/>
   <guid isPermaLink="false"><![CDATA[5ff4e2d9-6666-4f00-8116-bb573c04feb5]]></guid>
   <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jun 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
   <source url=""><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></source>
   <itunes:author><![CDATA[Garrison Hardie]]></itunes:author>
   <itunes:image href="https://assets-cdn2.dropwave.io/2ab40ac0-e99d-4f25-a6d2-541d2c9b290a/cover-art/hUZu1H9lrRY0wXg66WHC8eLwYBA3hbRNTAHQmHt2.png"/>
   <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
   <itunes:duration>872</itunes:duration>
   <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
  
  </item><item>
   <title><![CDATA[Daily News Brief for Thursday, June 8th, 2023 [Daily News Brief]]]></title>
   <link>https://app.dropwave.io/episode/85b15126-eb29-4505-92bb-bb012123c4a3/daily-news-brief-for-thursday-june-8th-2023.mp3</link>
   <description><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">This is Garrison Hardie with your CrossPolitic Daily News Brief for Thursday, June 8th, 2023.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>Club Membership Plug: (1/9)</strong></span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Ladies and gentleman, it&rsquo;s never been a better time to become a club member at CrossPolitic. This year, CrossPolitic will be dropping exclusive content into our club portal for club members ONLY. Some of this content will include a pilot TV Show called This America, a Bible study series with Pastor Toby, a special with New Saint Andrew&rsquo;s President, Ben Merkle, our backstage content, and our conference talks! You can grab a club membership for 10 bucks per month&hellip; that&rsquo;s two cups of coffee. So again, head on over to fightlaughfeast.com to get signed up today! That&rsquo;s fightlaughfeast.com.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">We start today&rsquo;s news brief in the city of Greensboro, NC. Shout out to Wade Choate for sending in this story, and by the way, if you want to send me a news story, email me at </span><a href="mailto:garrison@fightlaughfeast.com"><span style="font-weight: 400;">garrison@fightlaughfeast.com</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> - or you can find me on Facebook, or our own fightlaughfeast.com website, where we have our own social media page set up.&nbsp;</span></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://greensboro.com/news/local/after-greensboro-firefighter-fired-over-straight-pride-and-other-facebook-posts-crowd-erupts-at-city/article_2a1fe822-04c6-11ee-8f48-078ab7addc66.html"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://greensboro.com/news/local/after-greensboro-firefighter-fired-over-straight-pride-and-other-facebook-posts-crowd-erupts-at-city/article_2a1fe822-04c6-11ee-8f48-078ab7addc66.html</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>After Greensboro firefighter fired over 'Straight Pride' and other Facebook posts, crowd erupts at city council meeting</strong></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The City of Greensboro has fired Capt. Dustin Jones of the Greensboro Fire Department, citing a history of social media posts criticizing transgender people and Black Lives Matter along with an unwillingness to accept training and heed warnings from his supervisors.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Jones was fired on May 12, according to the city. On Tuesday night, citizens packed the council meeting, which was punctuated by loud outbursts as some protested Jones' firing and others supported it.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">North Carolina Lt. Gov. Mark Robinson, a politician known for his anti-transgender and anti-LGBTQ+ positions had weeks earlier urged "normal people" to "take a stand and absolutely flood this hall" in an interview shared on Jones' Facebook page.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Jones had gone to Facebook to protest his termination in a video in which he claimed he was fired because of a "Straight Pride" meme post made on April 16.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The image, covered with pink and white stripes, featured a white, heterosexual couple being married with the title "Straight Pride" and the caption "It&rsquo;s natural, it&rsquo;s worked for thousands of years and you can make babies."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">After Jones appealed his termination by the Greensboro Fire Department, the City Manager a upheld the decision in a letter obtained by the News &amp; Record in a records request. In his response, Jaiyeoba defended the termination, citing Jones' "misuse of social media" and "disrespectful behavior." Jaiyeoba wrote that Jones had "grown defiant" after numerous coaching sessions and warnings from supervisors.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The response letter includes other instances of posts and re-posts attributed to Jones included one that stated: "You know what&rsquo;s insane... A white person can paint their face black and be accused of being a racist. Yet a man can dress as a woman and be called a hero&hellip; [shrug emoji]".</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">All sides of the political spectrum flocked to the Greensboro City Hall to make their voices heard, and more than 40 people signed up to speak during the public comment period.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Members of Guilford For All, an organization advocating for the rights of the LGBTQ+ community, wore green shirts and packed the inside of the assembly room. Outside the building, the Communist Party of America flew Pride flags and displayed a sign that read "FASCIST FIREMAN, YOU'RE FIRED."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Jennifer Ruppe, the executive director of the Guilford Green Foundation and LGBTQ Center, addressed the room: "The true test of your commitment to creating a diverse, equitable and inclusive city is how you all show up when it's not all rainbows and parades. Because freedom of speech is not freedom of consequences."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://thepostmillennial.com/breaking-bidens-doj-tells-trump-he-will-be-indicted-next-week-on-charges-of-gathering-transmitting-or-losing-national-defense-docs?utm_campaign=64487"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://thepostmillennial.com/breaking-bidens-doj-tells-trump-he-will-be-indicted-next-week-on-charges-of-gathering-transmitting-or-losing-national-defense-docs?utm_campaign=64487</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>Biden's DOJ tells Trump he will be indicted next week on charges of 'gathering, transmitting or losing' national defense docs</strong></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Former President Donald Trump has reportedly been notified by federal prosecutors that he is a criminal target and is likely to face imminent indictment in the classified document probe.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">People familiar with the case told Just The News that the revelation comes as the Justice Department has declined to delay charges to allow an investigation into allegations of witness tampering in connection with a senior prosecutor working on the case attempting to influence a key witness by discussing federal judgeship with the lawyer representing the witness provided by Trump&rsquo;s legal team.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The sources said that the allegation is still pending in a secret case before Chief US District Judge James E Boasberg in Washington, DC.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">A federal indictment brought by Special Counsel Jack Smith could be handed by a federal grand jury to Trump as early as next week.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Smith&rsquo;s prosecutorial team informed Trump&rsquo;s team in recent days that the charges he faces include a violation of 18 US Code Chapter 37 Section 793 which prohibits the &ldquo;gathering, transmitting or losing&rdquo; of national defense information. Other charges reportedly being considered are alleged false statements and obstruction of justice.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Sources told the outlet that Trump&rsquo;s lawyers have been preparing their defense for months based on months of legal research in anticipation of charges. The 2024 presidential candidate&rsquo;s lawyers are prepared to argue that Trump had Constitutional powers to declassify documents during his presidency and take them with him when his term ended.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">His lawyers will reportedly rely heavily on a US District Court case out of Washington over a decade ago regarding former President Bill Clinton, which concluded that a president had the power to determine what documents from his presidency can be kept in personal possession.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">A document posted to Twitter on Wednesday from the Federal Registrar has revealed that Trump declassified certain materials pertaining to the FBI&rsquo;s Crossfire Hurricane investigation during his last days in office.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">"At my request, on December 30, 2020, the Department of Justice provided the White House with a binder of materials related to the Federal Bureau of Investigation&rsquo;s Crossfire Hurricane investigation. Portions of the documents in the binder have remained classified and have not been released to Congress or the public," the document states.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">"I requested the documents so that a declassification review could be performed and so I could determine to what extent materials in the binder should be released in unclassified form," the document continues. "I determined that the materials in that binder should be declassified to the maximum extent possible."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The document states that FBI had objected to further declassification of the materials, and gave suggestions as to redactions that the documents needed, which Trump obliged to.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Crossfire Hurricane was the name given to the investigation into allegations of coordination between Trump and Russia that surfaced during the 2016 election. The Durham report, released in May, found that the FBI "failed to uphold their mission of strict fidelity to the law" in their launching of the investigation.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://thepostmillennial.com/cessna-pilot-was-slumped-over-in-cockpit-before-virginia-crash-that-killed-4?utm_campaign=64487"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://thepostmillennial.com/cessna-pilot-was-slumped-over-in-cockpit-before-virginia-crash-that-killed-4?utm_campaign=64487</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>Cessna pilot was 'slumped over' in cockpit before Virginia crash that killed 4</strong></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">National Guard F-16 fighter pilots revealed that the pilot operating the Cessna plane that flew over restricted airspace in Washington D.C. on Sunday was found "slumped over" moments before the plane crashed in a remote area of Virginia, which killed four people.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">United States Military officials said that the US fighter pilots attempted to get the civilian pilots attention for around 30 minutes before the plane plummeted at approximately 3 pm, Fox News reports.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">"The Federal Aviation Administration confirmed that the pilot did not respond to air traffic control instruction around 1:28 p.m. EDT," North American Aerospace Defense Command (NORAD) said in a statement. "Subsequently, the NORAD pilots visually inspected the Cessna as it was still airborne and confirmed that the pilot was unresponsive. NORAD pilots described the Cessna pilot as being slumped over."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The people killed in the crash have been identified as Hamptons realtor Adina Azarian, 49, her daughter Aria Azarian, 2, Evadnie Smith, the child's nanny, and the pilot Jeff Hefner. Adina Azarian is the adopted daughter of a longtime GOP donor, John Rumpel, who owned the plane, according to Washington Post.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The fatal crash sparked a flurry on Sunday after a loud "supersonic boom" could be heard in Washington D.C. following reports of an unidentified plane flying above restricted US airspace.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">According to Fox News, the US deployed six F-16 jets to intercept the plane, including two from Washington, DC, two from New Jersey and two out of South Carolina.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">&nbsp;</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Rumpel, who is a pilot and runs Encore Motors of Melbourne Inc., said his family was returning to their home in East Hampton after visiting his house in North Carolina, Fox reports.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">On Monday, the White House expressed its "deepest condolences" and National Security spokesman John Kirby said during a press brief regarding the US military response, "What I saw was just a classic, textbook response."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Authorities are still investigating the cause of the crash but experts say it's likely that the plane lost pressurization, causing hypoxia, a condition that occurs when someone's brain is deprived of adequate oxygen, according to Fox News.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://www.dailyfetched.com/cnn-ceo-chris-licht-to-leave-network-after-just-16-months/"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.dailyfetched.com/cnn-ceo-chris-licht-to-leave-network-after-just-16-months/</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>CNN CEO Chris Licht to Leave Network after Just 16 Months</strong></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">On Wednesday, Licht announced he would leave CNN after meeting with Warner Bros. Discovery CEO David Zaslav.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The CEO will be replaced in the interim by a three-person leadership team, including CNN executive Amy Entelis, who worked closely with former cable news boss Jeff Zucker who left in February of 2022.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">&ldquo;For a number of reasons, things didn&rsquo;t work out, and that&rsquo;s unfortunate,&rdquo; Zaslav said.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">&ldquo;It&rsquo;s really unfortunate. And ultimately, that&rsquo;s on me. And I take full responsibility for that.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Zaslav said CNN is &ldquo;in the process of conducting a wide search&rdquo; for a new leader that could &ldquo;take a while.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">As The Daily Wire reported:</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Licht&rsquo;s tenure at CNN was rough from the start. Weeks after Licht took over the reins, the cable news giant&rsquo;s attempt at launching a streaming service failed after a month in operation, attracting fewer than 10,000 daily users. The CNN executive also faced criticism from his employees and poor ratings performances in the news channel&rsquo;s primetime slots.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Familiar faces on the network, such as longtime journalist Brian Stelter and host Don Lemon, were axed under Licht&rsquo;s reign. The tumultuous leadership of Licht came to a boiling point when the network hosted a town hall with&nbsp; President Donald Trump in May. Leftist critics ripped the company for giving Trump a platform.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Politicians and media personalities from Alexandria Ocasio-Cortez to Joe Scarborough were angered by CNN&rsquo;s decision to host Trump on the platform that has consistently offered friendly coverage to Democrats.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Licht faced fire last week after the Atlantic published a 15,000-word profile titled &ldquo;Inside the Meltdown at CNN,&rdquo; which angered executives at Warner Bros. Discovery.</span></p>]]></description>
   <author><![CDATA[Garrison Hardie]]></author>
   <enclosure url="https://app.dropwave.io/episode/85b15126-eb29-4505-92bb-bb012123c4a3/daily-news-brief-for-thursday-june-8th-2023.mp3" length="693" type="audio/mp3"/>
   <guid isPermaLink="false"><![CDATA[85b15126-eb29-4505-92bb-bb012123c4a3]]></guid>
   <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jun 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
   <source url=""><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></source>
   <itunes:author><![CDATA[Garrison Hardie]]></itunes:author>
   <itunes:image href="https://assets-cdn2.dropwave.io/2ab40ac0-e99d-4f25-a6d2-541d2c9b290a/cover-art/hUZu1H9lrRY0wXg66WHC8eLwYBA3hbRNTAHQmHt2.png"/>
   <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
   <itunes:duration>693</itunes:duration>
   <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
  
  </item><item>
   <title><![CDATA[Daily News Brief for Thursday, June 1st, 2023 [Daily News Brief]]]></title>
   <link>https://app.dropwave.io/episode/9362c7c6-17ba-4d6e-b65f-db49b0702a14/daily-news-brief-for-thursday-june-1st-2023.mp3</link>
   <description><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">This is Garrison Hardie with your CrossPolitic Daily News Brief for Thursday, June 1st, 2023.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://www.theepochtimes.com/chick-fil-a-faces-growing-backlash-over-diversity-equity-and-inclusion-efforts_5300643.html?utm_source=partner&amp;utm_campaign=BonginoReport"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.theepochtimes.com/chick-fil-a-faces-growing-backlash-over-diversity-equity-and-inclusion-efforts_5300643.html?utm_source=partner&amp;utm_campaign=BonginoReport</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>Chick-fil-A Faces Growing Backlash Over &lsquo;Diversity, Equity, and Inclusion&rsquo; Efforts</strong></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Some conservatives have suggested a boycott of Chick-fil-A after the fast-food chain was discovered to have a vice president of &ldquo;diversity, equity, [and] inclusion,&rdquo; or DEI.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">In a previously issued Chick-fil-A news release, the company said that Erick McReynolds serves as its vice president of DEI, saying: &ldquo;Chick-fil-A restaurants have long been recognized as a place where people know they will be treated well. Modeling care for others starts in the restaurant, and we are committed to ensuring mutual respect, understanding, and dignity everywhere we do business.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">DEI is a set of principles that large corporations, government agencies, and schools have increasingly incorporated into their work environments, often mandating employees receive such training. However, these principles are rooted in Marxism, according to prominent critics including Christopher Rufo and James Lindsay, that are essentially vehicles for &ldquo;left-wing racialist ideology and partisan political activism.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">&ldquo;They are designed to replace the system of academic merit with a system of race-based preferences and discrimination&mdash;which, in many cases, explicitly violates federal civil rights law,&rdquo; wrote Rufo for his Substack page earlier this year.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The Chick-fil-A announcement was highlighted this week by several prominent conservative accounts. According to McReynolds&rsquo;s LinkedIn page, he was hired as Chick-fil-A&rsquo;s vice president for &ldquo;Diversity, Equity [and] Inclusion&rdquo; in late 2021.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The chicken-based fast-food chain has been generally well respected among conservatives due to the company&rsquo;s religious values and its prior support for religious groups. In the McReynolds DEI announcement, Chick-fil-A makes reference to its corporate purpose, which is &ldquo;to glorify God by being a faithful steward of all that is entrusted to us&rdquo; and &ldquo;to have a positive influence on all who come into contact with Chick-fil-A.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">In recent weeks, a number of companies have faced backlash for embracing what critics say are left-wing values or a pro-LGBT agenda. Since early April, Bud Light has seen a significant backlash after it produced a beer can with transgender activist and influencer Dylan Mulvaney&rsquo;s face and as Mulvaney suggested a partnership with the brand.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Sales of Bud Light have dropped significantly year-over-year, with consumers opting to drink brands like Coors or Miller in its place, according to data released by industry analysts. Data published by Bump Williams Consulting and Nielsen IQ shows that by the week ending May 20, Bud Light sales declined 29.5 percent year-over-year, while revenue is down 25.7 percent.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The CEO of Anheuser-Busch has, on multiple occasions, said that Bud Light did not partner with Mulvaney, a man who identifies as a woman, and that only &ldquo;one can&rdquo; with Mulvaney&rsquo;s face was produced. Local distributors in some areas also released advertisements saying as much in a bid to lure back customers, while Bud Light has marketed several deals to move cases of beer.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Another major boycott was directed at Target after the company released a line of LGBT clothing for children&mdash;including onesies for infants&mdash;for its &ldquo;pride collection,&rdquo; according to its website. Other companies, like Kohl&rsquo;s and PetSmart, have similarly been criticized for selling similar products.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Last week, Target said in a news release that it would be moving its &ldquo;pride&rdquo; merchandise to other areas of the store. The company, meanwhile, has seen its stock drop considerably since mid-May, falling another 3.5 percentage points on Tuesday.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://www.dailywire.com/news/9-teenagers-arrested-over-brutal-assault-of-3-u-s-marines"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.dailywire.com/news/9-teenagers-arrested-over-brutal-assault-of-3-u-s-marines</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>9 Teenagers Arrested Over Brutal Assault Of 3 U.S. Marines</strong></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Sheriff&rsquo;s deputies in San Clemente, California, arrested nine teenagers over the brutal assault of three U.S. Marines last Saturday.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">San Clemente Mayor Chris Duncan announced that Orange County Sheriff&rsquo;s Department had charged the teenagers, five of whom were accused of assault with a deadly weapon and the other four with misdemeanor assault and battery.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">&ldquo;They think they have the people they are looking for,&rdquo; Duncan stated. &ldquo;Not to say that there might not be a few others out there. They feel pretty confident that they have the main perpetrators. &hellip; They had some videotape that wasn&rsquo;t readily available to the public that had a lot better images of the individuals involved.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">&ldquo;In today&rsquo;s age, you&rsquo;re going to get caught &mdash; people are going to record it,&rdquo; Duncan continued. &ldquo;I hope this serves as a learning lesson for young folks in the community not to let themselves get out of control when something like this happens.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">As many as 40 young people were involved when the three U.S. Marines near a California beach Saturday night were attacked in a horrific moment caught on now-viral video.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The Marines were enjoying time off from their service at Camp Pendleton in Oceanside at approximately 10 p.m. along the beach in San Clemente. One of the Marines, Hunter Antonino, said a piece of debris hit him in the face, prompting him to ask the group to stop lighting fireworks.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">&ldquo;They were lighting off fireworks, they were being belligerent and obnoxious and annoying other people, so I went up to them and told them to stop,&rdquo; he recalled. Antonio said the group then followed the Marines as they returned to the pier, whereupon Antonio and another Marine informed the group that they were Marines so the group would leave them alone.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Instead, the group savagely attacked the Marines. One individual punched a Marine in the back, prompting the Marine to turn and charge at him, sparking the melee. Video shows two of the Marines lying in the fetal position on the ground as the group kicked them and hurled racial epithets at them. The Marines were kicked in the head and upper body.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Although the Marines were injured, they refused to go to a hospital, according to Orange County Sheriff&rsquo;s deputies. Antonio thought he may have suffered a concussion.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/policy/healthcare/anti-abortion-protesters-beaten-baltimore-planned-parenthood"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/policy/healthcare/anti-abortion-protesters-beaten-baltimore-planned-parenthood</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>Two anti-abortion protesters beaten outside Planned Parenthood in Baltimore</strong></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Two senior citizen anti-abortion protesters were attacked outside of a Planned Parenthood clinic in North Baltimore on Friday morning, sending one to the University of Maryland Medical Center.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">&ldquo;Please pray for my dear friend, Mark Crosby,&rdquo; President of the Baltimore County Right to Life organization Jay Walton said on Facebook Friday. &ldquo;He was viciously attacked yesterday, May 26, 2023 while he was praying in front of Planned Parenthood in Baltimore City. He and another prolifer were attacked from behind and the thug ran away.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Mark Crosby and Dick Shafer have been confirmed as the victims in Friday's attack. Both men are over the age of 70, according to police reports.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">WMAR reported that surveillance video shows the suspect tackling Shafer, disturbing a large flower planter outside of the abortion facility. When Crosby came to Shafer&rsquo;s aid, the assailant shoved Crosby to the ground, and the person was seen punching and kicking him in the face.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Baltimore anti-abortion advocate John Roswell told LifeSiteNews that while Shafer is recovering well, Crosby &ldquo;is bleeding from some unidentified area behind his eye and the bone eye orbit is completely shattered.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Walton said on Monday morning that Crosby, who had been released from the hospital, had to be transported back to the emergency room due to further complications.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Roswell told LifeSiteNews that a Planned Parenthood escort, who guides abortion patients into the organization's facilities, was present at the scene and engaged with the assailant prior to the attack. In his experience, Roswell said that escorts are usually present in the rare cases that pro-abortion rights activists engage in violent altercations with anti-abortion advocates.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Investigators told local news outlets WBAL and WMAR that they are searching for the suspect.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://www.theblaze.com/news/tony-holford-us-canada-border-explosives-sign"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.theblaze.com/news/tony-holford-us-canada-border-explosives-sign</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>Police open fire on driver at US-Canada border; truck had 'sign' indicating 'explosive device on- board'</strong></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Police opened fire on a truck driver on Memorial Day as the driver aproached the U.S.-Canadian border with a sign indicating he had an explosive device on board.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The motorist, 42-year-old Tony Holford of Providence, Rhode Island, faces charges of aggravated reckless conduct, a class B crime; terrorizing, a Class D crime, and failure to stop, a class E crime, the Maine State Police Major Crimes Unit said in a press release.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">At 10:39 a.m. Monday, Maine State Police Trooper Denver Roy attempted to stop a vehicle heading north on Interstate 95 in Houlton, Maine. The driver did not stop, instead continuing north.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Trooper Roy "observed a sign indicating that the operator had an explosive device on-board," the MSP wrote. It is not clear what sort of sign was displayed.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">When the vehicle eventually stopped between the U.S. and Canadian ports of entry, troopers commanded him to get out of the vehicle.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">When the vehicle's operator reportedly maneuvered the truck toward the Canadian port of entry, Corporal Eric Paquette shot at him.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Holford, who was uninjured, surrendered to Main State Police troopers and was taken to the Aroostook County Jail after being medically cleared.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">MSP say the scene is contained and there is no ongoing danger to the public.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Authorities in Canada and the United States are collaborating on an investigation into the incident.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The Maine State Police Bomb Squad and crime scene technicians advised motorists to use alternative points of entry as they processed the scene. The Woodstock, New Brunswick, border crossing was reopened Monday night, according to a tweet posted by the Canada Border Services Agency's Atlantic Region.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The Office of the Maine Attorney General and the Maine State Police will work together "in the coming days to continue the investigation and the events that led up to the officer-involved shooting."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://justthenews.com/politics-policy/education/virginia-eliminates-degree-requirements-most-state-jobs"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://justthenews.com/politics-policy/education/virginia-eliminates-degree-requirements-most-state-jobs</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>Virginia eliminates degree requirements for most state jobs</strong></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Virginia Republican Gov. Glenn Youngkin on Tuesday announced a change in state hiring practices that would eliminate requirements or preferences that applicants for most state positions have a college degree.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">A press release from Youngkin indicated that the change will take effect on July 1 and affect roughly 90% of state positions. The Old Dominion's myriad agencies post as many as 20,000 job listings per year.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">"On day one we went to work reimagining workforce solutions in government and this key reform will expand opportunities for qualified applicants who are ready to serve Virginians," Youngkin said in a statement.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">State Secretary of Labor Bryan Slater further, in the same release, indicated that the state was looking into heavily regulated private industries to streamline the professional certification processes.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The move comes as American high school graduates increasingly opt against pursuing college degrees to due affordability and return on investment concerns.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">President Joe Biden has moved to lessen the financial burden of incurring debt to pay for college by offering up to $10,000 in repayment relief for most loan recipients and up to $20,000 for those who received a Pell Grant, though that plan has faced legal scrutiny and may well end up permanently blocked by the judiciary. The proposed deal to raise the debt limit facing Congress includes a measure to end a temporary freeze on student loan repayments.</span></p>]]></description>
   <author><![CDATA[Garrison Hardie]]></author>
   <enclosure url="https://app.dropwave.io/episode/9362c7c6-17ba-4d6e-b65f-db49b0702a14/daily-news-brief-for-thursday-june-1st-2023.mp3" length="687" type="audio/mp3"/>
   <guid isPermaLink="false"><![CDATA[9362c7c6-17ba-4d6e-b65f-db49b0702a14]]></guid>
   <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
   <source url=""><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></source>
   <itunes:author><![CDATA[Garrison Hardie]]></itunes:author>
   <itunes:image href="https://assets-cdn2.dropwave.io/2ab40ac0-e99d-4f25-a6d2-541d2c9b290a/cover-art/hUZu1H9lrRY0wXg66WHC8eLwYBA3hbRNTAHQmHt2.png"/>
   <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
   <itunes:duration>687</itunes:duration>
   <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
  
  </item><item>
   <title><![CDATA[Daily News Brief for Wednesday, May 31st, 2023 [Daily News Brief]]]></title>
   <link>https://app.dropwave.io/episode/d3dd0c7c-0e15-4226-bbf7-a7ee772f1207/daily-news-brief-for-wednesday-may-31st-2023.mp3</link>
   <description><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">This is Garrison Hardie with your CrossPolitic Daily News Brief for Wednesday, May 31st, 2023.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://www.christiantoday.com/article/archbishop.distressed.by.attacks.on.christians.in.india/140278.htm"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.christiantoday.com/article/archbishop.distressed.by.attacks.on.christians.in.india/140278.htm</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>Archbishop 'distressed' by attacks on Christians in India</strong></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The Archbishop of Canterbury has lamented violent attacks on indigenous tribal Christians in north-eastern India.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Archbishop Justin Welby said he was "distressed" by the reports of violence coming out of Manipur state in recent weeks.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Writing on Twitter, the Archbishop said he was praying that "justice and peace would prevail" in the region.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The violence, carried out by Hindu nationalists, has killed dozens and displaced around 10,000 people, mostly Christians.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Many churches and buildings belonging to Christians have also been destroyed.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The Archbishop said he was praying "that regional authorities would protect all minority groups, including Christians and their places of worship, and that justice and peace would prevail".&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Open Doors last week shared reports from Christian partners on the ground fear that the violence will lead to a civil war.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">They have expressed disappointment at what they see as a lack of action by the Indian government and local authorities to quell the violence.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">According to Open Doors, at least 300 churches have been burned or demolished and 1,000 Christian homes have been destroyed in Manipur in the last few weeks.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The NGO is providing support to Christians caught up in the violence but has warned that conditions are "grim", and many are still fearing for their lives.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">"If the situation continues civil war is inevitable," said an Open Doors partner who cannot be named for security reasons.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">"If there is a civil war the situation will only become more gruesome, more lives lost, properties destroyed and further open persecution of religious minorities."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://taskandpurpose.com/news/taliban-humvee-m240-iran-fight/"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://taskandpurpose.com/news/taliban-humvee-m240-iran-fight/</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>The Taliban is using leftover American gear to fight a border skirmish with Iran</strong></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">A gunfight broke out between Iranian border guards and Taliban fighters along the border between Iran and Afghanistan this weekend. Fighting killed three people in the biggest escalation between the two countries over water. And the Taliban brought out a big gun to help.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Video posted to social media offered an up-close view of the skirmish, inside an unexpected place: an Humvee kitted out with an M240 machine gun. If that looks familiar it&rsquo;s because those are some of the pieces of military equipment captured by the Taliban, now put into use for fighting other parties.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Other accounts shared online reported heavy machine gun fire, as well as purported use of mortars and other explosives. Outside of the Humvee, Taliban fighters were spotted using AK-style rifles and RPGs to attack the Iranian position on the border.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">At least three people are confirmed to have died in Saturday&rsquo;s gunfight, although accounts vary on how many belonged to each side. The Taliban claimed at least one of its fighters was killed, while an Iranian paper said all deaths were on Iran&rsquo;s side, per al-Jazeera. The fighting took place in the Nimroz province of Afghanistan. As a result, the border crossing between Milak and Zaranj in Iran and Afghanistan, respectively, closed (it was not where the fighting took place). Both nations accused the other of starting the gunfight.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The fighting between the two nations broke out amid political fights over water rights. Drought has been a serious issue in Afghanistan for the last three years. The Helmand River flows from Afghanistan into Iran and is dammed on the Afghan side. Earlier in May, Iranian President Ebrahim Raisi called on the Taliban not to restrict the flow of water.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">More than a year since the Taliban took control of Afghanistan, the group is using all kinds of seized American and NATO weapons.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">It&rsquo;s not a new development. The Taliban regularly used captured American-provided equipment when fighting the U.S.-backed government. In the later years of the war, special Taliban units were spotted wearing American-style driving Humvees and even wielding weapons belonging to special operations units. During the fall of Kabul in 2021, Los Angeles Times reporter Nabih Bulos captured footage of Taliban fighters in the city dressed like special operations forces.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">When the U.S.-backed government fell and the Afghan security forces collapsed, the Taliban got its hand on a lot of leftover weapons and equipment. A 2022 report from the Pentagon&rsquo;s lead inspector general for Operation Enduring Sentinel and Operation Freedom&rsquo;s Sentinel found that approximately $7.12 billion in equipment was still in the country when the Taliban took over. That included everything from rifles to aircraft.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://www.newsmax.com/world/globaltalk/africa-uganda-gay-rights/2023/05/29/id/1121533/"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.newsmax.com/world/globaltalk/africa-uganda-gay-rights/2023/05/29/id/1121533/</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>Uganda Signs Anti-gay Law With Death Penalty for 'Aggravated Homosexuality'</strong></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Uganda's president has signed into law tough new anti-gay legislation supported by many in this East African country but widely condemned by rights activists and others abroad.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The version of the bill signed by President Yoweri Museveni does not criminalize those who identify as LGBTQ, a key concern for campaigners who condemned an earlier draft of the legislation as an egregious attack on human rights.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">But the new law still prescribes the death penalty for "aggravated homosexuality," which is defined as cases of sexual relations involving people infected with HIV as well as with minors and other categories of vulnerable people.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">A suspect convicted of "attempted aggravated homosexuality" can be imprisoned for up to 14 years, according to the legislation.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Parliamentary Speaker Anita Among said in a statement the president had "answered the cries of our people" in signing the bill.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">"With a lot of humility, I thank my colleagues the Members of Parliament for withstanding all the pressure from bullies and doomsday conspiracy theorists in the interest of our country," the statement said.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Museveni had returned the bill to the national assembly in April, asking for changes that would differentiate between identifying as LGBTQ and actually engaging in homosexual acts. That angered some lawmakers, including some who feared the president would proceed to veto the bill amid international pressure. Lawmakers passed an amended version of the bill earlier in May.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Homosexuality was already illegal in Uganda under a colonial-era law criminalizing sexual activity "against the order of nature." The punishment for that offense is life imprisonment.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The U.S. has warned of economic consequences over legislation described by Amnesty International as "draconian and overly broad."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The leaders of the U.N. AIDS program, the U.S. President's Emergency Plan for AIDS Relief and the Global Fund in a joint statement Monday said they "are deeply concerned about the harmful impact" of the legislation on public health and the HIV response.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">"Uganda's progress on its HIV response is now in grave jeopardy," the statement said. "The Anti-Homosexuality Act 2023 will obstruct health education and the outreach that can help end AIDS as a public health threat."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">That statement noted that "stigma and discrimination associated with the passage of the Act has already led to reduced access to prevention as well as treatment services" for LGBTQ people.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Anti-gay sentiment in Uganda has grown in recent weeks amid news coverage alleging sodomy in boarding schools, including a prestigious one for boys where a parent accused a teacher of abusing her son.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The February decision of the Church of England 's national assembly to continue banning church weddings for same-sex couples while allowing priests to bless same-sex marriages and civil partnerships inflamed many in Uganda and elsewhere in Africa.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Homosexuality is criminalized in more than 30 of Africa's 54 countries. Some Africans see it as behavior imported from abroad and not a sexual orientation.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://www.foxnews.com/politics/house-oversight-committee-taking-steps-to-hold-fbi-director-wray-in-contempt-of-congress-over-biden-document"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.foxnews.com/politics/house-oversight-committee-taking-steps-to-hold-fbi-director-wray-in-contempt-of-congress-over-biden-document</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>Republicans to hold FBI Director Wray in contempt of Congress over Biden document</strong></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">House Oversight Committee Chairman James Comer is taking steps to hold FBI Director Christopher Wray in contempt of Congress after the Bureau notified the panel it will not comply with its subpoena related to a possible criminal scheme involving then-Vice President Joe Biden.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The FBI, though, said Tuesday evening it remains committed to cooperating with Congress, and will provide access to the document "in a format and setting that maintains confidentiality and protects important security interests and the integrity of FBI investigations."&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Comer, R-Ky., has subpoenaed the FBI for a document that allegedly describes a criminal scheme involving Biden and a foreign national and relating to the exchange of money for policy decisions. The document is an FBI-generated FD-1023 form.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Comer first subpoenaed the document earlier this month. The FBI did not turn it over and instead explained that it needed to protect the Bureau's confidential human source program.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Comer set another deadline last week, giving Wray until Tuesday, May 30, to turn over the document. After the deadline was set, Wray set up a call with Comer for Wednesday, May 31.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">However, the FBI notified the panel it would not provide the document to the committee by the Tuesday afternoon deadline.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">He added, "Americans deserve the truth, and the Oversight Committee will continue to demand transparency from this nation&rsquo;s chief law enforcement agency."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">In response, the FBI told Fox News Digital that the bureau "remains committed to cooperating with the Committee in good faith."</span></p>]]></description>
   <author><![CDATA[Garrison Hardie]]></author>
   <enclosure url="https://app.dropwave.io/episode/d3dd0c7c-0e15-4226-bbf7-a7ee772f1207/daily-news-brief-for-wednesday-may-31st-2023.mp3" length="578" type="audio/mp3"/>
   <guid isPermaLink="false"><![CDATA[d3dd0c7c-0e15-4226-bbf7-a7ee772f1207]]></guid>
   <pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
   <source url=""><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></source>
   <itunes:author><![CDATA[Garrison Hardie]]></itunes:author>
   <itunes:image href="https://assets-cdn2.dropwave.io/2ab40ac0-e99d-4f25-a6d2-541d2c9b290a/cover-art/hUZu1H9lrRY0wXg66WHC8eLwYBA3hbRNTAHQmHt2.png"/>
   <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
   <itunes:duration>578</itunes:duration>
   <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
  
  </item>
 </channel>
</rss>
