<?xml version="1.0"?>
<?xml-stylesheet href="/storage/feed-stylesheet.xsl" type="text/xsl"?>

<rss xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
 <channel>
  <title>FLF - Daily News Brief</title>
  <link>https://dropwave.io</link>
  <description><![CDATA[FIGHT LAUGH FEAST PRESENTS SHOWS PROCLAIMING THE LORDSHIP OF CHRIST OVER ALL OF LIFE.
]]></description>
  <language>en</language>
  <managingEditor><![CDATA[fightlaughfeast@gmail.com (FLF, LLC)]]></managingEditor>
  <webMaster><![CDATA[support@dropwave.io (DropWave Support)]]></webMaster>
  <pubDate>Tue, 03 Oct 2023 13:25:45 +0000</pubDate>
  <lastBuildDate>Tue, 03 Oct 2023 13:25:45 +0000</lastBuildDate>
  <image>
   <url>https://is4-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Podcasts113/v4/58/56/52/5856525c-2973-cf29-3db9-21faa8595391/mza_1144696925612154085.png/1200x1200bb.jpg</url>
   <link>https://dropwave.io</link>
   <title><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></title>
  </image>
  <itunes:author><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></itunes:author>
  <itunes:image href="https://is4-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Podcasts113/v4/58/56/52/5856525c-2973-cf29-3db9-21faa8595391/mza_1144696925612154085.png/1200x1200bb.jpg"/>
  <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
  <itunes:owner>
   <itunes:name><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></itunes:name>
   <itunes:email>fightlaughfeast@gmail.com</itunes:email>
  </itunes:owner>
  <itunes:category text="News"/>
  <item>
   <title><![CDATA[Daily News Brief for Tuesday, October 3, 2023 [Daily News Brief]]]></title>
   <link/>
   <description><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">This is Garrison Hardie with your CrossPolitic Daily News Brief for Tuesday, October 3, 2023.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Accountable2You</strong></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Jesus is Lord. In public and in private, every area of life must be subject to his Lordship&mdash;and our use of technology is no exception. What captures our attention on the screen either glorifies or dishonors our Lord. That&rsquo;s why Accountable2You is committed to promoting biblical accountability in our families and churches. Their monitoring and reporting software makes transparency easy on all of your devices, so you can say with the Psalmist, &ldquo;I will not set anything worthless before my eyes.&rdquo; Guard against temptation with Accountable2You, and live for God&rsquo;s glory! Learn more and try it for free at Accountable2You.com/FLF</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://www.foxnews.com/politics/white-house-prohibiting-official-travel-fossil-fuel-conferences-internal-memo-shows"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.foxnews.com/politics/white-house-prohibiting-official-travel-fossil-fuel-conferences-internal-memo-shows</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>White House prohibiting official travel to fossil fuel conferences, internal memo shows</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The White House is prohibiting senior administration officials from traveling for international energy engagements that promote carbon-intensive fuels, including oil, natural gas and coal, Fox News Digital has learned.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The guidance &mdash; which originated from the White House National Security Council (NSC) &mdash; was revealed in a Department of Energy (DOE) memo issued internally to agency staff on Sept. 15 and obtained by Fox News Digital. The memo was authored by Deputy Secretary of Energy David Turk who outlined travel restrictions and stated officials are required to obtain approval from the NSC before attending any global energy engagement.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">"This guidance sets out a presumption that agencies and departments will pursue international energy engagement that advances clean energy projects," Turk wrote in the memo. "It also outlines a process for seeking limited exceptions to pursue carbon-intensive engagements on a justified geostrategic imperative or energy-for-development/energy access basis."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">"The guidance rules out any U.S. Government &lsquo;engagement related to unabated or partially abated coal generation,&rsquo;" he continued. "Carbon-intensive international energy engagements are those 'directly related and dedicated to the production, transportation, or consumption of carbon-intensive fuels that would lead to additional greenhouse gas emissions.'"</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">According to the memo, carbon-intensive fossil fuels include coal, oil and natural gas.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">In addition, the memo notes that the guidance became effective in November 2021 and applies to all international energy engagements. Turk issued a separate memo in early April 2022, which first outlined how the DOE would implement the NSC guidance and stated that energy engagements that promote carbon-intensive fuels may only be exempt if they advance national security or are essential to support energy access in vulnerable areas.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Turk's September memo updated that guidance, stating that for all future engagements, "Departments and Agencies are required to submit exemption justifications to the NSC and receive NSC concurrence before proceeding with a covered engagement."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The DOE referred Fox News Digital to the NSC, which didn't respond to multiple requests for comment.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Since taking office, President Biden has pursued an aggressive climate agenda, seeking to boost green energy technologies like solar and wind while curbing domestic reliance on fossil fuels like those listed by the administration as "carbon intensive." Biden has issued federal goals to ensure 50% of U.S. car purchases are zero-emissions by 2030 and that the power sector is carbon-free by 2035.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">However, vehicles with internal combustion engines (gasoline-powered), make up more than 99% of all cars in the U.S. and about 99% of new car sales, according to J.D. Power. And approximately 60% of electricity in the U.S. is generated from fossil fuels, mainly natural gas, while 17% is produced form wind or solar power.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">As part of his agenda, Biden and senior administration officials have traveled to global energy conference to boost green energy development.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">And officials have largely been absent from global fossil fuel summits like the World Gas Conference, which former Energy Secretary Rick Perry attended during the Trump administration. The Biden administration also opted against inviting oil and gas industry representatives to the White House Methane Summit in July.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://www.foxnews.com/us/judge-orders-new-york-dole-out-nearly-half-million-legal-fees-nra-supreme-court-victory"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.foxnews.com/us/judge-orders-new-york-dole-out-nearly-half-million-legal-fees-nra-supreme-court-victory</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Judge orders New York to dole out nearly half a million in legal fees to NRA after Supreme Court victory</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">A New York judge ordered the state to pay nearly half a million dollars in legal feels to the National Rifle Association (NRA) after the gun rights group won a major case at the Supreme Court.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">In a case decided last summer, the Supreme Court ruled that a New York public carry licensing law was unconstitutional and that the ability to carry a pistol in public was a constitutional right guaranteed by the Second Amendment.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The NRA was a party in that case, New York State Rifle &amp; Pistol Association v. Bruen, and last week a New York judge ordered the state to pay $447,700.82 in legal fees.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">"The NRA regards the $447K award in the NYSRPA V. Bruen case as a pivotal victory, a symbol that justice is definitively on our side," Michael Jean, NRA&rsquo;s director of the Office of Litigation Counsel, told Fox News Digital in a statement.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">"This triumph in Bruen has fortified the Second Amendment in an unprecedented manner, and we continue our unrelenting fight to uphold our rights and challenge those who endeavor to infringe upon them," he added.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Jean noted, however, that the payout "only scratches the surface" and covers "merely a third" of the group's legal expenses. Jean thanked the generosity of "devoted NRA members" that helped to cover the brunt of the legal fees for the case, noting that "New York refuses to fully compensate."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Before the high court weighed in, the standard for carrying a weapon required an applicant to show "proper cause" for seeking a license, and allowed New York officials to exercise discretion in determining whether a person has shown a good enough reason for needing to carry a firearm. Stating that one wished to protect themselves or their property was not enough.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">"In this case, petitioners and respondents agree that ordinary, law-abiding citizens have a similar right to carry handguns publicly for their self-defense. We too agree, and now hold, consistent with Heller and McDonald, that the Second and Fourteenth Amendments protect an individual&rsquo;s right to carry a handgun for self-defense outside the home," Justice Clarence Thomas wrote in the court's opinion, referencing two previous gun cases.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">"Because the State of New York issues public-carry licenses only when an applicant demonstrates a special need for self-defense, we conclude that the State&rsquo;s licensing regime violates the Constitution."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Thomas noted that the state statute does not define what "proper cause" means, and that courts had ruled that the standard was met by people who showed a "special need for self-protection."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Following the court's decision New York legislators immediately passed the Concealed Carry Improvement Act, which prohibits carrying a gun in "sensitive areas," such as stadiums, houses of worship, museums, parks and other public places; imposes revised record-keeping and new safety requirements on retailers; and mandates background checks on all ammunition purchases.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Gun retailers immediately appealed to the Supreme Court in January to stop that law from going into effect while the litigation proceeds, but the high court rejected their bid.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">"We are challenging the ability of the state of New York to target dealers in firearms in the lawful stream of commerce, to put them out of business, which is what the new laws will do," Paloma Capanna, the lead attorney for the New York gun retailers, said. "So it really was unfortunate to see that we couldn't get any emergency temporary injunction against those laws."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://bongino.com/former-kamala-harris-adviser-who-doesnt-appear-to-live-in-california-picked-to-fill-late-dianne-feinsteins-seat"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://bongino.com/former-kamala-harris-adviser-who-doesnt-appear-to-live-in-california-picked-to-fill-late-dianne-feinsteins-seat</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Former Kamala Harris Adviser Who Doesn&rsquo;t Appear to Live in California Picked to Fill Late Dianne Feinstein&rsquo;s Seat</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">So eager were Democrats to find a replacement for the late Dianne Feinstein&rsquo;s Senate seat that they apparently didn&rsquo;t even bother to pick someone living in California.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">According to the Washington Examiner:&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The appointment of Laphonza Butler to become California's newest senator is already raising some eyebrows as she appears to be registered to vote in Maryland with an address in that state.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Registration records indicate that Butler lives in Silver Spring, Maryland, with her mailing address the same as her residential. She registered as a Democrat as of Sept. 12, 2022.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Butler is the president of EMILYs List, the self-described "nation's largest resource dedicated to electing Democratic pro-choice women to office," and a longtime leader in California before her move to Maryland.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">On Sunday night, the newest California senator's biography on the EMILYs List website listed that "Laphonza grew up in Magnolia, MS, and attended one of the country's premier HBCUs, Jackson State University. She lives in Maryland with her partner Neneki Lee and their daughter Nylah."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">As of 7 a.m. Monday, the organization has removed the line that she lives in Maryland.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Butler was formally Kamala Harris' 2020 campaign adviser.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">As radio host Dan O&rsquo;Donnell noticed in real-time, Butler removed part of her biography on her Twitter account that listed Maryland as her location.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Similarly, The Spectator&rsquo;s Matt Foldi found that Butler&rsquo;s LinkedIn page also listed her location as Maryland.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Yet, merely hours after Foldi&rsquo;s post, Butler&rsquo;s location according to LinkedIn changed to the &ldquo;Los Angeles Metropolitan Area.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Before we wrap up today&hellip; how about a little on this day in history? It&rsquo;s been awhile!</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">On this day in history&hellip; October 3rd&hellip;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">42 BC First Battle of Philippi: Triumvirs Mark Antony and Octavian fight an indecisive battle with Caesar's assassins Brutus and Cassius.</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">1735 France and Holy Roman Emperor Charles VI sign peace accord</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">1778 Explorer and Captain James Cook anchors at Alaska</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">1849 American author Edgar Allan Poe is found delirious in a gutter in Baltimore, Maryland under mysterious circumstances; it is the last time he is seen in public before his death.</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">1863 US President Abraham Lincoln designates last Thursday in November as Thanksgiving Day</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">1913 US Federal income tax signed into law (at 1%) by President Woodrow Wilson</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">1941 Adolf Hitler says Russia is "already broken and will never rise again" in a broadcast to the German people</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">1945 Elvis Presley's 1st public performance, at age of 10, singing "Old Shep" in youth talent contest at the Mississippi-Alabama Fair and Dairy Show, in Tupelo, Mississippi; contest is broadcast over WELO Radio, he wins fifth prize - $5.00 in fair ride tickets</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">1951 CBS-TV airs the first coast-to-coast telecast of a prize fight; Australian light-heavyweight Dave Sands outpoints American Carl 'Bobo' Olson in 10 rounds at Chicago Stadium</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">1976 Future Baseball Hall of Fame right fielder Hank Aaron singles in his last MLB at-bat &amp; drives in his 2,297th run as Milwaukee Brewers lose, 5-2 v Detroit Tigers</span></li>
</ul>]]></description>
   <author><![CDATA[Garrison Haride]]></author>
   <enclosure url="https://app.dropwave.io/episode/f301e3ae-086a-4997-bb95-07d0aa8d7337/daily-news-brief-for-tuesday-october-3-2023.mp3" length="708" type="audio/mp3"/>
   <guid isPermaLink="false"><![CDATA[f301e3ae-086a-4997-bb95-07d0aa8d7337]]></guid>
   <pubDate>Tue, 03 Oct 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
   <source url=""><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></source>
   <itunes:author><![CDATA[Garrison Haride]]></itunes:author>
   <itunes:image href="https://assets-cdn2.dropwave.io/2ab40ac0-e99d-4f25-a6d2-541d2c9b290a/cover-art/mUK8zsnHkCK3vep7E1W6UgYb9dTnLenASAMEFha3.jpg"/>
   <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
   <itunes:duration>708</itunes:duration>
   <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
  
  </item><item>
   <title><![CDATA[Daily News Brief for Thursday, September 28th, , 2023 [Daily News Brief]]]></title>
   <link/>
   <description><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">This is Garrison Hardie with your CrossPolitic Daily News Brief for Thursday, September 28th, , 2023.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>Classical Conversations</strong></span></p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Classical Conversations supports homeschooling parents by cultivating the love of learning through a Christian worldview in fellowship with other families. They provide a classical Christ-centered curriculum, local like-minded communities across the United States and in several countries, and they train parents who are striving to be great classical&nbsp; educators in the home. For more information and to get connected, please visit their website at ClassicalConversations.com. </span><span style="font-weight: 400;">Again that&rsquo;s </span><span style="font-weight: 400;">ClassicalConversations.com.</span></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://www.newsmax.com/world/globaltalk/brazil-amazon-environment-drought/2023/09/26/id/1135958/"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.newsmax.com/world/globaltalk/brazil-amazon-environment-drought/2023/09/26/id/1135958/</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>Brazil's Amazon Rainforest Faces a Severe Drought That May Affect around 500,000 People</strong></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The Amazon rainforest in Brazil is facing a severe drought that may affect around 500,000 people by the end of the year, authorities said Tuesday.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Many are already struggling to access essential supplies such as food and water, because the principal means of transportation in the region is waterways, and river levels are historically low. Droughts also impact fishing, a means of subsistence for many riverside communities.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Amazonas state declared an environmental emergency two weeks ago in response to the prolonged drought and launched a response plan valued at $20 million. Authorities will also distribute food and water supplies as well as personal hygiene kits, the state&rsquo;s civil defense agency said in a statement.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Gov. Wilson Lima was in Brazil&rsquo;s capital, Brasilia, on Tuesday to meet with representatives of the federal government. Lima spoke with President Luiz In&aacute;cio Lula da Silva to discuss the drought.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The different levels of government will &ldquo;coordinate measures in support of the people living in the affected municipalities,&rdquo; Lima said on X, the platform formerly known as Twitter, on Sunday.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Fifteen municipalities were in a state of emergency on Tuesday, while 40 others were on a state of alert, the civil defense authority said.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">According to the port of Manaus, which monitors water levels, the river stood at 16.7 meters (55 feet) on Tuesday, around six meters (20 feet) below the same day last year. The lowest level of water was recorded on Oct. 24, 2010, when the river dropped to 13.6 meters (about 45 feet).</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The drought is forecast to last longer and be more intense because of El Ni&ntilde;o climate phenomenon, which inhibits the formation of rain clouds, the civil defense authority said.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://www.foxnews.com/politics/house-approves-bill-striking-down-bidens-crackdown-hunting-archery-overwhelmingly-bipartisan-vote"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.foxnews.com/politics/house-approves-bill-striking-down-bidens-crackdown-hunting-archery-overwhelmingly-bipartisan-vote</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>House approves bill striking down Biden's crackdown on hunting and archery in overwhelmingly bipartisan vote</strong></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The House voted late Tuesday evening in favor of legislation striking down the Biden administration's decision to block federal funding for school shooting sports courses.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">In a 424-1 vote, the House approved the Protecting Hunting Heritage and Education Act with 216 Republicans and 208 Democrats voting in favor, and just one lawmaker, Rep. Veronica Escobar, D-Texas, voting against. Rep. Mark Green, R-Tenn., introduced the bill on Aug. 1, days after a Fox News Digital report in late July revealed the Department of Education was withholding funds for school hunting and archery courses.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">"Hunters and fishers are the best conservationists," Green told Fox News Digital after the vote Tuesday. "Hunting, whether it be with a firearm or bow, is one of the most effective ways to control wildlife populations, protect our beautiful lands, and connect with nature. My Protecting Hunting Heritage and Education Act is critical for our children."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">He added in a separate statement that American students should be encouraged to "participate in enriching athletic activities that foster an appreciation for nature and the ability to focus on a goal." According to Green, in his state alone, the Biden administration's funding decision impacts an estimated 50,000 students.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Fox News Digital reported in July that the Education Department shared federal guidance to hunting education groups highlighting that hunting and archery programs in schools would be stripped of funding. The guidance explained that the administration interpreted the 2022 Bipartisan Safer Communities Act (BSCA) to mean such programs can no longer receive taxpayer funds.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">In the guidance, obtained first by Fox News Digital, senior agency official Sarah Martinez wrote that archery, hunter education and wilderness safety courses use weapons that are "technically dangerous weapons" and therefore "may not be funded under" the 1965 Elementary and Secondary Education Act (ESEA), which is the primary source of federal aid for elementary and secondary education across the country.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">According to advocates, many schools that offer such courses have already nixed them from curriculums due to the federal guidance.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">"The Department of Education and Secretary Cardona are blatantly misconstruing the law to withhold funding from schools that choose to teach beneficial courses like hunter safety and archery," Lawrence Keane, the National Shooting Sports Foundation's senior vice president, told Fox News Digital in July.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">"Congress must hold Secretary Cardona and the department accountable for violating the letter and spirit of the law to unilaterally deny America&rsquo;s students access to these valuable programs as part of the Administration&rsquo;s continued attacks on the Second Amendment," Keane added.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Tommy Floyd, the president of the National Archery in the Schools Program, said his organization boasts roughly 1.3 million students from nearly 9,000 schools across 49 states who are enrolled in archery courses.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">However, the Department of Education has doubled down on its interpretation of the BSCA, saying it would only reverse course if legislation was passed explicitly revising the 2022 law to allow funding for shooting sport programs in schools.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The law included an amendment to a subsection in the ESEA listing that prohibited uses for federal school funding. That amendment prohibits ESEA funds from helping provide any person with a dangerous weapon or to provide "training in the use of a dangerous weapon," but, according to the BSCA's sponsors, was included to prevent ESEA funding for school resource officer training.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://www.foxnews.com/us/philadelphia-swarmed-alleged-juvenile-looters-targeting-apple-store-lululemon-footlocker-others"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.foxnews.com/us/philadelphia-swarmed-alleged-juvenile-looters-targeting-apple-store-lululemon-footlocker-others</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>Philadelphia swarmed by alleged juvenile looters targeting the Apple Store, Lululemon, Footlocker and others</strong></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Philadelphia police responded to popular retailers like the Apple Store, Lululemon and Footlocker after they were allegedly being ravaged by swarms of looters taking over the City of Brotherly Love Tuesday evening.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">At about 8 p.m. Tuesday, police responded to reports of large crowds of juveniles allegedly looting stores in the Center City business corridor of the 9th District.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">"In a proactive measure, officers from the 9th District stopped a group of males dressed in black attire and wearing masks at the intersection of 17th and Chestnut Streets," a police spokesperson said in a statement to Fox News Digital.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">As of midnight on Wednesday, police confirmed between 15 and 20 people were arrested during the looting and at least two firearms were recovered.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">As officers were speaking with these individuals, they began to receive reports of looting at the Foot Locker on Chestnut Street.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Responding officers arrived at the Foot Locker and discovered the store had been ransacked in a "coordinated attack," according to the statement. A number of juveniles then fled the scene and at least one adult was arrested.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Subsequent incidents of looting were reported in quick succession.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Officers responded to a report of looting at the Lululemon on Walnut Street, where multiple individuals were apprehended.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">A short time later, looting was reported at the Apple Store on Walnut Street. No arrests were made in connection with this incident. Phones and tablets were taken from the store, but several stolen items have since been recovered.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Videos posted to X, showed retail stores like Lululemon, the Apple Store and Footlocker ravaged by crowds of looters.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">FOX 29's Steve Keeley obtained video of a ransacked Apple Store with iPhones and iPads scattered across the display tables. Keeley wrote on X that many of the stolen Apple products were left behind due to the device's comprehensive anti-theft technology.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">A police officer told local outlet WCAU-TV that more than 100 juveniles took items from the Lululemon store. No injuries were immediately reported, according to The Philadelphia Inquirer.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Police also responded to several other reports of property damage and thefts throughout the city.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">"The Philadelphia Police Department is committed to maintaining public safety and order," police said in the statement Wednesday morning. "We are actively investigating these incidents and working diligently to identify and apprehend those responsible for these unlawful acts. We appreciate the cooperation of our community and urge anyone with information related to these incidents to come forward and assist with the ongoing investigations."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The statement continued: "We would like to thank our dedicated officers who swiftly responded to these incidents, as well as our community members who continue to support law enforcement efforts to keep Philadelphia safe."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The looting came following a Philadelphia judge dismissed charges against former police officer Mark Dial in the shooting death of 27-year-old Eddie Irizarry. Interim Commissioner John Stanford said in a press conference that the thieves were not part of the peaceful protest against the judge's decision.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">"This had nothing to do with the protests," Stanford said. "What we had tonight was a bunch of criminal opportunists take advantage of a situation to make an attempt to destroy our city."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The news comes as Philadelphia Police Commissioner Danielle Outlaw resigned in the beginning of September.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Crime data from the Philadelphia Police Department shows there has been a 21% drop in homicides this year to date compared to the same day in 2021, when the city recorded 562 homicides throughout the year. But prior to Outlaw leading the department, the data shows Philadelphia annually recorded between 246 to 391 homicides each year between 2007 and 2019.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">In 2020, when she took over, there were 499 homicides, followed by 562 in 2021 and 516 in 2022.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Meanwhile in California&hellip;.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">In August, a Nordstrom store was ransacked by a "flash mob" of more than 30 people in a large smash-and-grab. The thieves made out with nearly $100,000 worth of designer handbags and clothes.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Similarly to Philadelphia, video captured shows a group of 30 to 50 people wearing sweatshirts with hoods over their heads.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The suspects are seen inside the department store as they rush to the front entrance with bags in hand, scooping up whatever merchandise they can while tripping on racks to which some items were still attached.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Police estimate the stolen merchandise to be worth between $60,000 and $100,000.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://www.dailyfetched.com/wuhan-institute-of-virology-warns-the-world-prepare-for-another-covid-19-pandemic/"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.dailyfetched.com/wuhan-institute-of-virology-warns-the-world-prepare-for-another-covid-19-pandemic/</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>Wuhan Institute of Virology Warns the World: Prepare for Another COVID-19 Pandemic</strong></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">As many as 20 coronavirus species are likely to cause a new outbreak, according to a study from the Wuhan Institute of Virology (WIV), a stark warning to prepare for another COVID-19 pandemic.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">In a study in Emerging Microbes &amp; Infections in July, the WIV has been making headlines, as many social media users have begun coming to their own conclusions online.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The Wuhan scientists documented their study of 40 coronavirus species, identifying 20 as &ldquo;high risk &hellip; including 6 of which jumped to human, 3 with evidence of spillover but not to human and 11 without evidence of spillover yet.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">&ldquo;It is almost certain that there will be future disease emergence, and it is highly likely a CoV [coronavirus] disease again,&rdquo; the study said.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">&ldquo;Thus, the early preparation for the animal CoVs with risk of spillover is important for future disease preparedness, regarding the likely animal origin of SARS, MERS, and COVID-19.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">SARS (Severe Acute Respiratory Syndrome) is a disease that caused a deadly outbreak in China over 20 years ago.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">MERS (Middle East Respiratory Syndrome) is a coronavirus disease first identified in Saudi Arabia in 2012.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The study&rsquo;s auhtors included Shi Zhengli, a Chinese coronavirus expert known as &ldquo;batwoman&rdquo; for her academic studies on the coronavirus.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">She became a figure of international focus during the coronavirus pandemic.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Shi stopped public appearances in early 2020 but reemerged to defend the Chinese government from claims that the coronavirus came from a lab in Wuhan.</span></p>]]></description>
   <author><![CDATA[Garrison Hardie]]></author>
   <enclosure url="https://app.dropwave.io/episode/ee46dfe4-a780-4c69-b5ce-ea21e6da5f71/daily-news-brief-for-thursday-september-28th-2023.mp3" length="760" type="audio/mp3"/>
   <guid isPermaLink="false"><![CDATA[ee46dfe4-a780-4c69-b5ce-ea21e6da5f71]]></guid>
   <pubDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
   <source url=""><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></source>
   <itunes:author><![CDATA[Garrison Hardie]]></itunes:author>
   <itunes:image href="https://assets-cdn2.dropwave.io/2ab40ac0-e99d-4f25-a6d2-541d2c9b290a/cover-art/mUK8zsnHkCK3vep7E1W6UgYb9dTnLenASAMEFha3.jpg"/>
   <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
   <itunes:duration>760</itunes:duration>
   <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
  
  </item><item>
   <title><![CDATA[Daily News Brief for Wednesday, September 27th, , 2023 [Daily News Brief]]]></title>
   <link/>
   <description><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">This is Garrison Hardie with your CrossPolitic Daily News Brief for Wednesday, September 27th, , 2023.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Olive Tree Biblical Software:</strong></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Discover why more than a million people use the free Olive Tree Bible App as their go-to for reading, studying, and listening to the God&rsquo;s Word.&nbsp;&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Start by downloading one of many free Bibles and start taking notes, highlighting verses, and bookmarking your favorite passages. You can read at your own pace, or choose from a large selection of Reading Plans, including the Bible Reading Challenge. When you are ready to go deeper into your studies, Olive Tree is right there with a large selection of study Bibles, commentaries, and other helpful study resources available for purchase. There&rsquo;s also an extensive bookstore that allows you to build your digital library one book at a time and Olive Tree&rsquo;s sync technology lets you pick up where you left off on your tablet, pc or phone and get right to studying on another supported device.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&nbsp;</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Now here's the best part &ndash; You can start with the Olive Tree Essentials Bundle for FREE. Visit www.olivetree.com/FLF and download it today! </span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://dailycaller.com/2023/09/26/bankruptcy-filings-13-month-consecutive-increase-biden-administration/"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://dailycaller.com/2023/09/26/bankruptcy-filings-13-month-consecutive-increase-biden-administration/</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Now this! </span><a href="https://youtu.be/T_d3teq6pWw"><span style="font-weight: 400;" data-rich-links="{&quot;fple-t&quot;:&quot;The Office ( US ) : Michael declares Bankruptcy&quot;,&quot;fple-u&quot;:&quot;https://youtu.be/T_d3teq6pWw&quot;,&quot;fple-mt&quot;:null,&quot;type&quot;:&quot;first-party-link&quot;}">The Office ( US ) : Michael declares Bankruptcy</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;">- Play 0:03-0:10</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Bankruptcy Filings Spiked In 2023 Under The Biden Administration, And You Should Expect More Financial Chaos To Come</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Data released Tuesday showed that Americans filed more than 39,000 bankruptcy cases in Aug. 2023, an 18 percent increase from the same time last year.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The data released by Unusual Whales details how, along with personal bankruptcy filings, there were more than 41,600 new bankruptcy cases recorded in August, including for businesses. This marks the thirteenth consecutive month that bankruptcy filings have shown a year-over-year increase under the Biden administration&rsquo;s embarrassing and dangerous economic policies.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The bankruptcy filings are not a surprise to anyone with a finger on the pulse of the domestic and global economy, but likely come as a shock to those just trying to keep afloat. As so many families were lulled into a false sense of financial security during and after the COVID-19 pandemic, their ill-advised spending habits have landed them in hot water.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Many folks bought homes they couldn&rsquo;t afford in the last two years, often with minimal down payments, bad credit and sky-high mortgage rates. Some of these individuals were banking on a pause or total relief of their student loan debt to keep the lights on, but this hasn&rsquo;t really materialized like people thought it would (duh).</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The most terrifying thing is that a lot of folks set-up interest-only payments for property purchases for the first five years or so of their mortgage. This means lower payments today, but zero equity build-up in homes these individuals won&rsquo;t be able to afford once they&rsquo;re forced to pay the equity and interest &mdash; which will almost definitely lead to more bankruptcies, foreclosures and worse.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://dailycaller.com/2023/09/25/mayors-fault-blue-city-average-40-vehicle-thefts/"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://dailycaller.com/2023/09/25/mayors-fault-blue-city-average-40-vehicle-thefts/</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>&lsquo;The Mayor&rsquo;s Fault&rsquo;: Blue City Reports An Average Of 40 Vehicle Thefts A Day</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Police officers in Oakland, California, have reported more than 10,000 motor vehicle thefts in the city since the start of 2023, data from the Oakland Police Department (OPD) shows.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The OPD recorded a total of 10,547 motor vehicle thefts &mdash; an average of 40 vehicle thefts a day &mdash; and a 51% increase from the year-to-date reported number of thefts in 2022, CBS News Bay Area reported. At least 133 vehicles were stolen between Sept. 11 and Sept. 17, and an additional 12 vehicles were carjacked during the same time period, according to the OPD data.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Now I&rsquo;m no math wiz - but that&rsquo;s a lot of thefts!</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Oakland residents have placed pressure on their district attorney and mayor for months to increase the town&rsquo;s police force and security response as crime in the city has continued to escalate. Residents became even more frustrated with local officials over the past week after the city failed to submit an application to the California government to receive additional crime-fighting funds.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&ldquo;The buck stops with the mayor. This is the mayor&rsquo;s fault. It stops with the mayor. We need to hear from the mayor,&rdquo; Oakland NAACP President Cynthia Adams told CBS on Sept. 18.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Officers admitted that the number of overall crimes in the area is likely much higher because many residents have stopped reporting crimes to the police, according to CBS. Total crime in Oakland has gone up 27% since 2022 while violent crime has increased by 20%, OPD data shows.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The Oakland mayor&rsquo;s office and the OPD did not immediately respond to the Daily Caller News Foundation&rsquo;s request for comment.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/policy/healthcare/desire-large-families-50-year-high-america"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/policy/healthcare/desire-large-families-50-year-high-america</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Desire for large families hits 50-year high in America: Gallup</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">A growing number of people in America prefer families of three or more children, hitting the highest desire for large families since 1971.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">According to a Gallup survey released Monday, the number of people who prefer smaller and larger family sizes are statistically tied, bouncing back from a decadeslong trend of believing one or two children was ideal.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">"Overall, this recent survey shows that Americans might finally be climbing out of the anti-family bomb shelter caused by the myths of the 1960&rsquo;s of a population explosion disaster," Terry Schilling, the president of the American Principles Project, told the Washington Examiner. "Favoring more children is a sign that Americans are returning to basic principles and values that life was made for &mdash; bringing forth the next generation through the family."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Forty-five percent now favor larger families, with 29% finding three children as ideal, 12% who prefer four, and 2% each who prefer five, six, or more.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">That is compared to 47% who believe two or fewer children is ideal, with 44% preferring two children and 3% preferring one. Two percent believe the ideal family should not include children.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Gallup pointed to several social trends from past decades that may have contributed to the decline in having children, including the preference for larger families "plummeting" from 70% in 1967 to 52% in 1972 "fueled at least in part by concerns about a global population explosion, resulting from the 1968 bestselling book entitled The Population Bomb."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The organization started tracking this data in 1936, when 64% preferred three children, reaching a peak in 1945 at 77%. However, by 1973, the strong preference for families of one or two children became the norm, evidenced by the 50% drop in children-per-family from the peak of the baby boom to 1.8 children in 1980.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">What stands out to Schilling, however, is that only 8% do not wish to have children, leaving over 90% with the desire for children at any amount.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">"The 8% of America that&rsquo;s anti-family has way too much representation in our culture &mdash; especially in entertainment, politics, news media, academia, and even corporations," Schilling said.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Gallup notes that people under the age of 30 are at least twice as likely to say they do not want children, but the "vast majority" continue to prefer having children. Twenty-one percent of that age group already has children, and 63% hope to have children in the future.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Moreover, 69% of those who already have children want more, as well as 15% of 18- to 40-year-olds who want to be parents someday. Six percent of childless people aged 41 and older also wished they had children.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">While ideal family size is not significantly different from men to women, other demographic traits do trend in certain directions.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Young people aged 18-29 are more likely than any other age group to prefer larger family sizes, and black and Hispanic people are also more likely to prefer larger families. In addition, Republicans, conservative independents, and lower-income residents tend to prefer families with more children.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">By contrast, Democrats, non-religious, and wealthy residents are more likely to prefer only one or two children.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Despite stated preferences, birth rates have been on the decline, and adults are starting families much later in life, which is highly correlated to smaller family sizes.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">In 2021, the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention reported the average age of a woman who had her first child was 27.3 years, a record high.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Part of the answer for fertility declines, author Melanie Notkin writes in a piece for the Institute for Family Studies, is that much like the effect of The Population Bomb in the 1960s and 1970s, "we have a similar trend with the rise of anti-natalism where its nihilistic supporters believe the world is too sad a place to bring children into, along with climate change 'doomerism.' More practically, the current economy makes family forming more challenging for many young Americans."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">However, the public has appeared to cut through some of the popular trends, Schilling told the Washington Examiner.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">"There are so many policies across the cultural and economic spectrum that make family formation much more difficult, and it&rsquo;s a true testament to the beauty and intrinsic value of the family that in spite of all the hurdles before us, we still desire children and family," he said.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://www.newsmax.com/world/globaltalk/biden-poland-billions-aid-ukraine-defense-russia/2023/09/25/id/1135800/"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.newsmax.com/world/globaltalk/biden-poland-billions-aid-ukraine-defense-russia/2023/09/25/id/1135800/</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>US Offers Poland Rare Loan of $2 Billion to Modernize Its Military</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">My goodness - we&rsquo;re giving out loans everywhere! You get a loan, you get a loan, and you Hawaiins get $700&hellip;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The Biden administration announced Monday that it is offering a $2 billion loan to Poland, which has been a hub for weapons going into Ukraine, to support the ally's defense modernization.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The State Department said in a statement that Poland is a &ldquo;stalwart&rdquo; ally of the U.S. whose &ldquo;security is vital to the collective defense&rdquo; of NATO &rsquo;s eastern flank, and that such funding is reserved for Washington&rsquo;s most important security partners.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The U.S. government is also providing Warsaw up to $60 million for the cost of the loan in Foreign Military Financing (FMF) which would support &ldquo;urgent procurements of defense articles and services from the United States,&rdquo; the State Department said. The $60 million is a loan subsidy meant to ensure that Warsaw can secure favorable terms for the loan.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Poland has been a staunch supporter of Ukraine since Russia&rsquo;s full-scale invasion of the country, handing over large numbers of its own tanks, fighter jets and other equipment. It has also been a hub for most of the Western weapons going to Ukraine.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">It has been undergoing a process of modernization to replace what it gave away, much of which was based on old Soviet technology, putting in orders with U.S. and South Korean defense companies.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Recently the Polish-Ukrainian relationship has seen strains due to a trade dispute centered on Ukrainian grain entering the Polish market and driving down the prices Polish farmers can get. Amid the spat Poland&rsquo;s Prime Minister said his country was no longer sending any more weapons to Ukraine.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The comment created some confusion. Analysts noted that Poland has already in fact given Ukraine most of what it has to give, and the statement was made ahead of a Polish election and did not mean much. But it also raised concerns that Western support for Ukraine could be weakening.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">U.S. officials have sought to play down the spat, praising Poland&rsquo;s role in helping Ukraine and noting that it is in Poland&rsquo;s strategic interest for Ukraine to prevail against Russia.</span></p>]]></description>
   <author><![CDATA[Garrison Hardie]]></author>
   <enclosure url="https://app.dropwave.io/episode/0285280c-d9d3-4730-a0b1-adf0b76a392b/daily-news-brief-for-wednesday-september-27th-2023.mp3" length="705" type="audio/mp3"/>
   <guid isPermaLink="false"><![CDATA[0285280c-d9d3-4730-a0b1-adf0b76a392b]]></guid>
   <pubDate>Wed, 27 Sep 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
   <source url=""><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></source>
   <itunes:author><![CDATA[Garrison Hardie]]></itunes:author>
   <itunes:image href="https://assets-cdn2.dropwave.io/2ab40ac0-e99d-4f25-a6d2-541d2c9b290a/cover-art/mUK8zsnHkCK3vep7E1W6UgYb9dTnLenASAMEFha3.jpg"/>
   <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
   <itunes:duration>705</itunes:duration>
   <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
  
  </item><item>
   <title><![CDATA[Daily News Brief forTuesday, September 26th, , 2023 [Daily News Brief]]]></title>
   <link/>
   <description><![CDATA[<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">This is Garrison Hardie with your CrossPolitic Daily News Brief forTuesday, September 26th, , 2023.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Samaritan Ministries</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Tired of someone else telling you where to go when you have a medical need? Are you ready to take control of your health care? Then it&rsquo;s time to take a look at Samaritan Ministries. It&rsquo;s Biblical, affordable health care sharing, with no restrictive networks. Here&rsquo;s how it works. When a medical need arises, you choose the health care provider that&rsquo;s right for you, and have a say in the treatment you receive. Send your medical bills to Samaritan Ministries, and they&rsquo;ll notify fellow members to pray for you and send money directly to you to help you pay those bills. Join 80,000 Christian households across the nation who have already taken control of their health care. Go to samaritan ministries dot org slash cross politic.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://thepostmillennial.com/biden-admin-moves-to-give-federal-ids-to-illegal-immigrants?utm_campaign=64487"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://thepostmillennial.com/biden-admin-moves-to-give-federal-ids-to-illegal-immigrants?utm_campaign=64487</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Biden admin moves to give federal IDs to illegal immigrants</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The Biden administration is moving forward with its plan to provide identification cards to illegal immigrants via Immigration and Customs Enforcement. The agency announced the ICE Secure Docket Card program in 2022, however new details recently emerged revealing how the cards will look.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">In appearance, they looks like drivers licenses or non-driver IDs. ICE has stressed, however, that they "will not be an official form of federal identification," simply acting as a more modern alternative to the paper documents issued to those who make the crossing into the United States. Many Democrat-run cities have also offered ID cards to illegal immigrants, and some cities have even tried to push through the ability for illegal immigrants to vote.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Images obtained by Fox News show that the cards will be clearly marked with ICE logos, and include all the relevant information about the holder. In the top right corner there will be a QR code, which officials can scan to gain access to a case file. The cards will also include bigraphic data, and be fitted with "cutting edge" security features.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">"The ICE secure docket card concept is a pilot program that would modernize documentation provided to some noncitizens," an ICE spokesperson told the outlet. "While the specifics of the program are under development, it is important to note the secure card will not be an official form of federal identification. The secure card will indicate it is for use by DHS agencies and would be provided only after national security background checks have been performed."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">ICE claimed that "moving to a secure card will save the agency millions, free up resources, and ensure information is quickly accessible to DHS officials while reducing the agency&rsquo;s FOIA backlog."&nbsp;</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&nbsp;</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">"Paper documents," the spokesperson added, "pose a security risk, are easily lost, and degrade rapidly in real-world use, creating inefficiencies for the government and noncitizens."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Not everyone is thrilled at the prospect of issuing ID cards to those who entered the country illegally. When the plan was introduced last year, for example, members of the House Oversight Committee said it was "yet another Biden Administration move encouraging illegal immigration by rewarding illegal immigrants for breaking our laws."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://www.dailyfetched.com/far-left-group-takes-credit-for-demonetizing-russell-brand/"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.dailyfetched.com/far-left-group-takes-credit-for-demonetizing-russell-brand/</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Far-Left Group Takes Credit for Demonetizing Russell Brand</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Not long after major advertisers, including Burger King and HelloFresh, pulled the plug on Rumble following the sexual assault against comedian Russell Brand, a far-left group took credit for the ad rug pull.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">As reported last week, the brands pulled their adverts from the platform, where Brand has amassed a following of 1.4m.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">News Movement reported that Burger King paused advertising with the platform, while Asos said it had manually removed its ads from Rumble.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Meanwhile, video-sharing giant YouTube also demonetized Russell Brand&rsquo;s videos on his channel following sexual assault allegations against the comedian.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&ldquo;We have suspended monetization on Russell Brand&rsquo;s channel for violating our creator responsibility policy,&rdquo; the platform announced Tuesday.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Brand is accused of rape, sexual abuse, and emotional abuse from 2006 to 2013, according to The Times.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">However, the comedian has not been charged with any crimes or found guilty.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Brand has now become a left&rsquo;s enemy, and he is about to witness for himself the lengths they will go to in order to destroy someone&rsquo;s life if they don&rsquo;t toe the line.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Over the weekend, far-left radicals Nandini Jammi and her business partner Claire Atkin took the credit for Rumble&rsquo;s advertisers dropping Brand.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Jammi is a co-founder of far-left company Sleeping Giants, makes her money by attacking any companies that advertise on conservative platforms, like what has happened with Russell Brand.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The Guardian reported:</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">A number of large companies have pulled their advertisements from the video platform Rumble, where Russell Brand broadcasts his weekly show, in the week since allegations of rape and sexual assault against the comedian came to light.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The News Movement reported on Friday that Burger King, Asos, the Barbican, and HelloFresh, the recipe box delivery service, had removed their ads. The Brand has 1.4m followers on the platform. YouTube suspended Brand&rsquo;s ability to earn money on its platform on Tuesday, but Rumble has rejected calls to do the same. On Friday, Brand said the moves to block him from receiving advertising revenue for his videos on social media platforms have occurred &ldquo;in the context of the online safety bill.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">On Thursday, Rumble accused a parliamentary committee of &ldquo;deeply inappropriate&rdquo; behavior after Caroline Dinenage, the Conservative chair of the culture, media, and sport committee, wrote a letter to the company&rsquo;s chief executive, Chris Pavlovski, to express concern that Brand &ldquo;may be able to profit from his content on the platform.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Last week, the UK parliament asked Rumble why they have not demonetized the comedian&rsquo;s channel.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://twitter.com/i/status/1704092016764670139"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://twitter.com/i/status/1704092016764670139</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> - Play Video&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">British Member of Parliament, Dame Caroline Dinenage, wrote to Rumble CEO Chris Pavlovski asking whether he would suspend monetization of Brand&rsquo;s account, noting that Brand had posted his pre-emptive message regarding the allegations.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://www.breitbart.com/news/hollywood-writers-studios-reach-tentative-deal-to-end-strike/"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.breitbart.com/news/hollywood-writers-studios-reach-tentative-deal-to-end-strike/</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Hollywood writers, studios reach tentative deal to end strike</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Striking writers whose industrial action has paralyzed Hollywood said Sunday they had reached an &ldquo;exceptional&rdquo; deal with studios that could see them go back to work.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The apparent breakthrough will raise hopes that striking actors can also reach terms with studios to end a months-long impasse that has seen film and TV production largely halted, costing the California economy billions of dollars.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&ldquo;We have reached a tentative agreement on a new 2023 (minimum basic agreement), which is to say an agreement in principle on all deal points, subject to drafting final contract language,&rdquo; said a letter the Writers Guild of America sent to members.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&ldquo;We can say, with great pride, that this deal is exceptional &mdash; with meaningful gains and protections for writers in every sector of the membership.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The letter, which AFP has seen, gave no details. It said language was being ironed out and that the final say on whether to accept what was on offer rested with the membership.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&ldquo;To be clear, no one is to return to work until specifically authorized to by the Guild. We are still on strike until then. But we are, as of today, suspending WGA picketing,&rdquo; it said.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">A terse joint statement from the WGA and the AMPTPT, the umbrella group representing studios and streamers confirmed an agreement.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Thousands of film and television scribes downed their pens in early May over demands including better pay for writers, greater rewards for creating hit shows, and protection from artificial intelligence.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">They have manned picket lines for months outside offices including Netflix and Disney, and were joined by striking actors in mid-July, leaving normally busy Hollywood lots all but vacant, in an ebullient and united show of force.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Actors&rsquo; union SAG-AFTRA congratulated the WGA, praising the &ldquo;incredible strength, resiliency and solidarity on the picket lines.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&ldquo;While we look forward to reviewing the WGA and AMPTP&rsquo;s tentative agreement, we remain committed to achieving the necessary terms for our members,&rdquo; it said.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Negotiations between studios and writers had been moribund for weeks until a new sense of urgency appeared to have been injected into the process in the last few days, with the heads of Netflix, Disney, Universal and Warner Bros Discovery personally attending the talks.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Among their demands, writers say their salaries have not kept up with inflation, and that the rise of streaming has diminished the &ldquo;residuals&rdquo; they earn when a show they work on becomes a smash hit.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Studios had offered greater transparency in streaming audience numbers, while stopping short of offering to revise the way residual payments are calculated.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Writers have also demanded curbs on the use of AI, which they fear could be used to partially replace them in generating future films or show scripts, and therefore further undercut their pay.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">$5 billion</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The Financial Times reported Milken Institute research at the start of September that put the cost of the current Hollywood standstill at $5 billion.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">At 146 days, the WGA strike is significantly longer than the writers&rsquo; 2007-08 walkout &mdash; which lasted 100 days and cost the California economy $2.1 billion.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Even if the writers deal is finalized, the actors&rsquo; strike would continue.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">There have been no known contract talks between the studios and the actors&rsquo; 160,000-strong SAG-AFTRA guild since that strike began.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">But the two unions share many similar demands, and insiders say that a WGA deal could help to pave the way for a resolution to the actors&rsquo; strike.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&ldquo;We remain on strike in our TV/Theatrical contract and continue to urge the studio and streamer CEOs and the AMPTP to return to the table and make the fair deal that our members deserve and demand,&rdquo; SAG-AFTRA said.</span></p>]]></description>
   <author><![CDATA[Garrison Hardie]]></author>
   <enclosure url="https://app.dropwave.io/episode/ca41f764-10b0-4156-94c4-3168443c24f9/daily-news-brief-fortuesday-september-26th-2023.mp3" length="666" type="audio/mp3"/>
   <guid isPermaLink="false"><![CDATA[ca41f764-10b0-4156-94c4-3168443c24f9]]></guid>
   <pubDate>Tue, 26 Sep 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
   <source url=""><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></source>
   <itunes:author><![CDATA[Garrison Hardie]]></itunes:author>
   <itunes:image href="https://assets-cdn2.dropwave.io/2ab40ac0-e99d-4f25-a6d2-541d2c9b290a/cover-art/mUK8zsnHkCK3vep7E1W6UgYb9dTnLenASAMEFha3.jpg"/>
   <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
   <itunes:duration>666</itunes:duration>
   <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
  
  </item><item>
   <title><![CDATA[Daily News Brief for Friday, September 22nd, 2023 [Daily News Brief]]]></title>
   <link/>
   <description><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">This is Garrison Hardie with your CrossPolitic Daily News Brief for Friday, September 22nd, 2023.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Samaritan Ministries</strong></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Tired of someone else telling you where to go when you have a medical need? Are you ready to take control of your health care? Then it&rsquo;s time to take a look at Samaritan Ministries. It&rsquo;s Biblical, affordable health care sharing, with no restrictive networks. Here&rsquo;s how it works. When a medical need arises, you choose the health care provider that&rsquo;s right for you, and have a say in the treatment you receive. Send your medical bills to Samaritan Ministries, and they&rsquo;ll notify fellow members to pray for you and send money directly to you to help you pay those bills. Join 80,000 Christian households across the nation who have already taken control of their health care. Go to samaritan ministries dot org slash cross politic.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://townhall.com/tipsheet/leahbarkoukis/2023/09/21/migrants-traveling-north-trade-n2628700"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://townhall.com/tipsheet/leahbarkoukis/2023/09/21/migrants-traveling-north-trade-n2628700</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Massive Number of Migrants Traveling Toward US Border Is Now Affecting International Trade</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The massive number of migrants heading north, most toward the U.S. border, is now affecting international trade, as a Mexican railway operator was forced to temporarily suspend operations over the hitchhikers.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">On Tuesday, Ferromex halted 60 trains carrying cargo due to recent spate of injuries and deaths occurring from migrants catching rides.&nbsp;&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&ldquo;Despite the grave danger,&rdquo; some hitchhikers even jumped aboard moving freight cars, the company said.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&ldquo;There has been a significant increase in the number of migrants in recent days,&rdquo; Ferromex said in the statement, according to AP, noting that the temporary suspension of operations was being done &ldquo;to protect the physical safety of the migrants.&rdquo;&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">On Wednesday, President Andres Manuel Lopez Obrador called the company's decision "strange" and "unusual."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">According to Ferromex, the worst problems appeared to be further north.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The company said there were about 1,500 people gathered at a rail yard in the city of Torreon. The company also reported about 800 migrants waiting at the freight yards in Irapuato, in the north-central state of Guanajuato.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">About 1,000 people were reported to be riding freight cars on the train line that connects the northern border city of Ciudad Juarez.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Ferromex is Mexico&rsquo;s largest concessionary rail operator and the impact of the train stoppage will be &ldquo;very important,&rdquo; said Ana Bertha Guti&eacute;rrez, the international trade coordinator for the Mexican Institute for Competitiveness.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">According to estimates from the company, the decision to halt the 60 trains translated into a daily loss of about $2.34 million.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">On Wednesday, some operations had been restarted for routes where there was no "heightened risk," Reuters reported, but company executives are set to meet on Friday with members of the U.S. Customs and Border Protection and members of the Mexican government to discuss next steps.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://www.dailyfetched.com/opening-the-floodgates-greg-abbott-accuses-biden-admin-of-cutting-razor-wire-at-border/"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.dailyfetched.com/opening-the-floodgates-greg-abbott-accuses-biden-admin-of-cutting-razor-wire-at-border/</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>&lsquo;OPENING THE FLOODGATES:&rsquo; Greg Abbott Accuses Biden Admin of Cutting Razor Wire at Border</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The news comes amid tension between Texas officials and the White House over the migrant crisis at the Southern border.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Abbott made the announcement Wednesday.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&ldquo;Texas installed razor wire in Eagle Pass to stop illegal crossings,&rdquo; Abbott explained on X, formerly known as Twitter.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&ldquo;Today the Biden Admin CUT that wire, opening the floodgates to illegal immigrants.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&ldquo;I immediately deployed more Texas National Guard to repel illegal crossings &amp; install more razor wire,&rdquo; the Republican governor added after accusing the Biden admin of cutting it at the border.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Abbot later posted a letter he sent to Joe Biden, declaring that the President&rsquo;s policies caused &ldquo;an invasion at our border,&rsquo; The New York Post reported.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&ldquo;We are building a border wall, razor wire &amp; marine barriers,&rdquo; Abbott wrote.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&ldquo;We are also repelling migrants,&rdquo; he added.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Earlier this year, the Department of Justice (DOJ) sued Texas for installing a buoy barrier, which was designed to prevent illegal immigration, on the Rio Grande.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The barrier was part of Abbott&rsquo;s Operation Lone Star.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The DOJ claimed that the barrier obstructed &ldquo;the navigable capacity of waters of the United States,&rdquo; adding that it raised humanitarian, environmental, and public safety concerns.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">A federal judge initially told Texas to move the buoys, but a US Court of Appeals upheld that decision.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The case is currently being deliberated through courts.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The Daily Fetched reported earlier in September that the Biden administration allowed thousands of illegal immigrants to pour into America through &ldquo;welded open&rdquo; floodgates on the Arizona border.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The open floodgates in Tuscan are now the busiest point of illegal entry into the country.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">A post on Instagram by James Breeden showed illegal aliens arriving &ldquo;from as far away as Senegal, India, and China.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The Biden administration is also dismantling, disposing, and auctioning portions of the Mexican-American border wall constructed under Donald Trump.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Border wall material, including &ldquo;thick wall tubes,&rdquo; has been sold on the auction site GovPlanet since April 2022.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/policy/defense-national-security/poland-stop-weapons-ukraine-grain-imports"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/policy/defense-national-security/poland-stop-weapons-ukraine-grain-imports</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Poland to stop providing weapons to Ukraine as dispute over grain imports intensifies</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Poland will stop providing weapons to Ukraine the Prime Minister announced on Wednesday, due to a growing dispute over grain.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&ldquo;We no longer transfer weapons to Ukraine because we are now arming Poland,&rdquo; Morawiecki said on social media.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">While Poland has been one of Ukraine&rsquo;s staunchest allies since Russia invaded in February 2022, due in part to concerns about further aggression from Moscow should it successfully topple Kyiv, they are currently in dispute over Poland, Hungary, and Slovakia's intention to defy a European Union decision to suspend a ban on Ukrainian grain imports which had been in place to protect the livelihood of local farmers.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The ban had been put in place earlier this year by several EU nations to protect local farmers who were worried about being undercut by low prices of Ukrainian grain. Ukraine has filed lawsuits against each of the three countries at the World Trade Organization over their intent to defy the ending of the restrictions.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Ukrainian President Volodymyr Zelensky referenced the subject during his address to the United Nations General Assembly, saying, &ldquo;It is alarming to see how some in Europe, some of our friends in Europe, play out solidarity in a political theater &mdash; making a thriller from the grain.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The remarks prompted immediate condemnation from Polish leaders, who went as far as to summon the Ukrainian ambassador to Warsaw to share their &ldquo;strong protest.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Polish Foreign Minister Pawel Jablonski told Ukraine&rsquo;s ambassador that Zelensky&rsquo;s statement was &ldquo;untrue,&rdquo; given Poland had been &ldquo;supporting Ukraine since the first days of the war.&rdquo; He also said, &ldquo;Putting pressure on Poland in multilateral forums or sending complaints to international tribunals are not appropriate methods of resolving disputes between our countries,&rdquo; according to a statement from the ministry.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The Polish-Ukrainian standoff has escalated ahead of Poland's upcoming elections on Oct. 15.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Poland has provided Ukraine with Soviet-era tanks, fighter jets, and other weapons, making it the sixth biggest military donor to Ukraine, according to the Kiel Institute for the World Economy, and it has taken in more than 1.5 million refugees. Now, Poland, Morawieki told Polsat News, "will protect our country." &ldquo;We are no longer transferring any weapons, because we will now arm ourselves with the most modern weapons.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://www.newsmax.com/newsfront/kevin-mccarthy-volodymyr-zelenskyy-joint-address/2023/09/21/id/1135367/"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.newsmax.com/newsfront/kevin-mccarthy-volodymyr-zelenskyy-joint-address/2023/09/21/id/1135367/</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>McCarthy Denied Zelenskyy's Wish to Address Congress</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">House Speaker Kevin McCarthy, R-Calif., declined Ukraine President Volodymyr Zelenskyy's request to deliver a joint address to Congress, as he did last December, multiple outlets reported.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The New York Times first reported the denial Wednesday.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Zelenskyy is in Washington, D.C., in part, to beseech lawmakers for more aid in Ukraine's war against Russia.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Instead, McCarthy met with Zelenskyy privately along with House Minority Leader Hakeem Jeffries, D-N.Y., and other committee chairs and ranking members. Zelenskyy met with senators after that meeting.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">McCarthy's denial, citing time constraints of a busy week, comes amid House Republicans' struggle to beat a Sept. 30 deadline to pass spending bills in order to prevent a government shutdown.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The U.S. has sent more than $100 billion to Ukraine in military, financial, and humanitarian aid since Russia invaded in February, 2022, but Republican lawmakers are pushing back on sending any more.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">In an exclusive interview with Newsmax on Wednesday, Zelenskyy said the cost of Russia prevailing in Ukraine is greater than American dollars.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Zelenskyy is also meeting with President Joe Biden at the White House and will visit the Pentagon.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://thenationalpulse.com/2023/09/21/almost-3-4-of-americans-think-the-nation-is-becoming-a-police-state/"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://thenationalpulse.com/2023/09/21/almost-3-4-of-americans-think-the-nation-is-becoming-a-police-state/</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Almost 3/4 of Americans Think The Nation is Becoming a Police State</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Almost three-quarters of Americans &ndash; 72 percent &ndash; admit to being concerned that the United States is becoming a &ldquo;police state&rdquo; engaging in mass surveillance, censorship, ideological indoctrination, and the targeting of political opponents, according to a recent survey from Rasmussen Reports.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Of those concerned, 46 percent told pollsters that they were &ldquo;very concerned&rdquo; that the state is becoming tyrannical, with 26 percent answering &ldquo;somewhat concerned.&rdquo; Only 23 percent of Americans said they were not concerned, with less than one in ten Americans answering &ldquo;not at all concerned.&rdquo;&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Rasmussen also asked the 998 likely American vetoers whether they agreed with the statement: &ldquo;The FBI is a danger to the freedom and security of law-abiding Americans?&rdquo; Half of the respondents agreed with the statement, with the majority answered &ldquo;strongly agree.&rdquo; Republicans overwhelmingly agreed, with 45 percent answering &ldquo;strongly agree&rdquo; and another 23 percent answered &ldquo;somewhat agree.&rdquo;&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">A total of 45 percent disagreed with the statement, with 26 percent strongly disagreeing. Democrats felt more strongly that the FBI assists freedom and security as 36 percent strongly disagreed, and a further 22 percent somewhat disagreed.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Lastly, Rasmussen asked whether those surveyed: &ldquo;Which political party is a bigger threat to basic liberties in America: Democrats or Republicans?&rdquo; Unsurprisingly, the vast majority of both parties &ndash; 76 percent of Republicans and 65 percent of Democrats &ndash; told pollsters the opposition party was the greater threat. However, more Democrats believe their party is a bigger threat at 26 percent than Republicans at 20 percent.</span></p>]]></description>
   <author><![CDATA[Garrison Hardie]]></author>
   <enclosure url="https://app.dropwave.io/episode/5198d602-67c9-4294-94f1-d31aea9345fe/daily-news-brief-for-friday-september-22nd-2023.mp3" length="651" type="audio/mp3"/>
   <guid isPermaLink="false"><![CDATA[5198d602-67c9-4294-94f1-d31aea9345fe]]></guid>
   <pubDate>Fri, 22 Sep 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
   <source url=""><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></source>
   <itunes:author><![CDATA[Garrison Hardie]]></itunes:author>
   <itunes:image href="https://assets-cdn2.dropwave.io/2ab40ac0-e99d-4f25-a6d2-541d2c9b290a/cover-art/mUK8zsnHkCK3vep7E1W6UgYb9dTnLenASAMEFha3.jpg"/>
   <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
   <itunes:duration>651</itunes:duration>
   <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
  
  </item><item>
   <title><![CDATA[Daily News Brief for Thursday, September 21st, 2023 [Daily News Brief]]]></title>
   <link/>
   <description><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">This is Garrison Hardie with your CrossPolitic Daily News Brief for Thursday, September 21st, 2023.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>Olive Tree Biblical Software:</strong></span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Discover why more than a million people use the free Olive Tree Bible App as their go-to for reading, studying, and listening to the God&rsquo;s Word.&nbsp;&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Start by downloading one of many free Bibles and start taking notes, highlighting verses, and bookmarking your favorite passages. You can read at your own pace, or choose from a large selection of Reading Plans, including the Bible Reading Challenge. When you are ready to go deeper into your studies, Olive Tree is right there with a large selection of study Bibles, commentaries, and other helpful study resources available for purchase. There&rsquo;s also an extensive bookstore that allows you to build your digital library one book at a time and Olive Tree&rsquo;s sync technology lets you pick up where you left off on your tablet, pc or phone and get right to studying on another supported device.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">&nbsp;</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Now here's the best part &ndash; You can start with the Olive Tree Essentials Bundle for FREE. Visit www.olivetree.com/FLF and download it today! </span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://thepostmillennial.com/nyc-may-remove-george-washington-statues-as-part-of-new-reparations-plan?utm_campaign=64487"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://thepostmillennial.com/nyc-may-remove-george-washington-statues-as-part-of-new-reparations-plan?utm_campaign=64487</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>NYC may REMOVE George Washington statues as part of new &lsquo;reparations&rsquo; plan</strong></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">While New York City continues to grapple with a crisis of illegal immigrants flooding the city as well as a consequential need for budget cuts, members of its city council have been plotting some new changes that seek to, among other things, delete monuments dedicated to important American figures such as George Washington.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Also on the agenda for New York City&rsquo;s council is to launch a reparations task force, according to Fox News.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">President Trump famously predicted that leftists would go after the monuments of America's first president back in August 2017.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">&ldquo;Robert E Lee, Stonewall Jackson - who&rsquo;s next, Washington, Jefferson? So foolish!&rdquo; Trump said at the time.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The city council's Cultural Affairs Committee is reportedly set to host a public hearing on an initiative to nix any type of city property that "depict[s] a person who owned enslaved persons or directly benefited economically from slavery, or who participated in systemic crimes against indigenous peoples or other crimes against humanity."&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">This set of standards would of course mean that figures such as European explorer Christopher Columbus and America&rsquo;s first president, George Washington would promptly have their statues removed throughout the city.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">In cases where a work of art is not decided to be removed, the Public Design Commission (PDC) will be made to oversee the installation of an "explanatory plaque" beside the object. The initiative also instructs the PDC to correspond with the Department of Education regarding placing plaques on sidewalks or other public spaces near schools that are named after a historical figure that meets the standards.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Tuesday's agenda also lists a proposal for the formation of a task force that will "consider the impact of slavery and past injustices for African Americans in New York City and reparations for such injustices."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Fox News reported that other proposals include a call for human services contractors as well as city employees to be subjected to anti-racism training, and mandating that a sign be put up around the intersection of Wall and Pearl Streets "to mark the site of New York&rsquo;s first slave market."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://www.breitbart.com/education/2023/09/20/federal-judge-blocks-newsom-policy-barring-parental-notification-for-trans-kids/"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.breitbart.com/education/2023/09/20/federal-judge-blocks-newsom-policy-barring-parental-notification-for-trans-kids/</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>Federal Judge Blocks Newsom Policy Barring Parental Notification for &lsquo;Trans Kids&rsquo;</strong></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">U.S. District Court Judge Roger Benitez of San Diego ruled last week that a California state policy barring schools from notifying parents when their children want to change genders violates the constitutional rights of parents.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The ruling comes as Gov. Gavin Newsom (D) and his administration are cracking down on school districts that pass parental notification policies, which are favored by 84% of California voters, according to a recent Rasmussen poll.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">&ldquo;A parent&rsquo;s right to make decisions concerning the care, custody, control and medical care of their children is one of the oldest of the fundamental liberty interests that Americans enjoy,&rdquo; U.S. District Judge Roger Benitez of San Diego said in a ruling Sept. 14. That means, he said, that when a school learns that a student has questioned his or her birth gender, or identified as transgender, it must notify the parents, even if the student objects.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">It&rsquo;s no different, Benitez wrote, than a school&rsquo;s obligation to inform parents if a child suffers a life-threatening concussion during soccer practice, is the victim of a sexual assault or has suicidal thoughts &mdash; the parents must be informed, even if the student objects.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">And in this case, he said, the Escondido Union School District in San Diego County, and the state whose regulations the district is enforcing, are also violating the rights of teachers to speak to their students, parents and the religious freedom of two teachers who said the policy conflicts with their faith.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The judge&rsquo;s ruling conflicts with that of U.S. District Judge John Mendez in Sacramento, who tossed a lawsuit in July against the Chico Unified School District for a policy against notifying parents of children&rsquo;s gender transitions, saying that the proper venue for the issue to be resolved was the state legislature, and not the judicial system.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">That logic was lost on Newsom and California Attorney General Rob Bonta (D), who sued the Chino Valley Unified School District last month over a parental notification policy, claiming that &ldquo;outing&rdquo; students violated their rights.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Chino Valley school board president Sonja Shaw noted at the time that there was no state law barring parental notification, and argued that it was a parent&rsquo;s fundamental right to know about life-altering treatments for children.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://townhall.com/tipsheet/madelineleesman/2023/09/18/cash-bail-illinois-n2628569#google_vignette"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://townhall.com/tipsheet/madelineleesman/2023/09/18/cash-bail-illinois-n2628569#google_vignette</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>One State Just Did Away With Cash Bail</strong></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Illinois became the first state to abolish cash bail as a piece of legislation called the Pre-Trial Fairness Act took effect on Monday.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The Pre-Trial Fairness Act is part of the SAFE-T Act, a broader piece of legislation that &ldquo;enacts extensive reform impacting many areas of the criminal justice system,&rdquo; according to the Illinois Criminal Justice Information Authority.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">According to the Chicago Sun-Times, going forward, people charged with the state&rsquo;s lowest level offenses will most likely never set foot in a jail cell, including at a police station, after their arrest. These people will likely be released with a citation and a court date without being processed at the police station. Law enforcement will be allowed to take certain individuals into custody if they cannot be properly identified or if they believe the person is a danger to the community. Police will be required to explain why the person was held.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Judges will decide if a defendant poses a public safety threat. If they do not, they will be released without being required to post any money. Those arrested for violent crimes will likely be detained by a judge.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Fox 32 Chicago noted that opponents of the legislation are concerned that it will allow dangerous criminals to &ldquo;slip through the cracks&rdquo; and commit crimes.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">"We feel very strongly that it is a serious public safety issue," Will County State's Attorney James Glasgow told ABC 7 Chicago.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Cook County State's Attorney Office&rsquo;s Kim Foxx told the outlet that it &ldquo;stands ready to implement the Pre-Trial Fairness Act.&rdquo;&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">In addition, Cook County Board President Toni Preckwinkle claimed that they are &ldquo;focused on effective equitable and sustainable solutions that address the root causes of crime and violence not just now but for future generations.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">"The full implementation of the Pretrial Fairness Act and the end of money bond is a critical milestone on the path toward economic and racial justice in Cook County and Illinois. This important reform is long overdue. Today, we finally end the harmful practice of wealth-based pretrial incarceration and welcome a new system that centers community safety to better guarantee equal justice for all,&rdquo; Preckwinkle added.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/policy/defense-national-security/air-force-hourslong-search-missing-stealth-jet"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/policy/defense-national-security/air-force-hourslong-search-missing-stealth-jet</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>How the Air Force spent 25 hours hunting for missing $80 million stealth jet after in-air 'mishap'</strong></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The hunt for an F-35 fighter jet that went missing due to a "mishap" was finally discovered on Monday afternoon, bringing an end to the almost 25-hour search for the aircraft.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The pilot had ejected from the stealth fighter jet but the jet was unable to be located, prompting an hourslong investigation into its disappearance.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Here is what is known about the missing F-35 jet and what comes next.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">What happened?</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">On Sunday at 5:26 p.m., Joint Base Charleston released a notice on social media that personnel from the base and the Marine Corps Air Station Beaufort were responding to a "mishap" involving an F-35 jet.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The Marine Corps had confirmed to the Washington Examiner that the aircraft was an F-35B Lightning II jet and that "search-and-recovery efforts for the aircraft" were ongoing.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The pilot ejected safely and the base confirmed on Facebook the pilot was taken to a local medical center in stable condition. The plane was last located north of the air base around Lake Moultrie and Lake Marion.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Almost 25 hours later, a debris field was located in South Carolina, two hours northeast of Joint Base Charleston, the base announced at 6:25 p.m. No other additional details have been provided at this time.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">"The mishap is currently under investigation, and we are unable to provide additional details to preserve the integrity of the investigative process," the joint base said in a post on Monday evening. "We would like to thank all of our mission partners, as well as local, county, and state authorities, for their dedication and support throughout the search and as we transition to the recovery phase."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Members of the community in Williamsburg County were urged on Monday night to avoid the debris field area while recovery efforts continue.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">What is a "mishap"?</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The U.S. Air Force will typically use the term "mishap" to refer to several possible scenarios, such as "any unintended occurrence in the Air or Space Force that results in death, injury, illness or property damage," according to the Air Force Safety Center website.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Have there been similar crashes before?</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">There have been several F-35 crashes since the jets started flying in 2012, including one caused by a software glitch in October 2022 and one caused by pilot error in January 2022.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">What we know about the jet</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The F-35 had been left in autopilot mode when its operator ejected from the plane, leaving open the possibility that the F-35 could have been airborne. The transponder on the plane was also not working, and it had stealth technology turned on, making it harder to track.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Lockheed Martin manufactures the jets, which are described by the company as the world's most advanced stealth aircraft. Each F-35 jet costs roughly $80 million.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The military aircraft is known for its low observable stealth, with reduced engine signatures, edges, and an internal carriage of weapons designed to make it hard to see. It can travel more than 1,000 miles without refueling.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The jet belonged to the 2nd Marine Aircraft Wing, the training squadron confirmed.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">All Marine Corps aircraft within and outside the United States were required to be grounded following the incident, following a Monday order from acting Marines Corps Commandant Gen. Eric Smith.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Some aircraft abroad or with upcoming missions were able to briefly delay the order, but they will now be expected to stand down for two days, with the order ending Thursday.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The suspension is aimed at allowing units to "discuss aviation safety matters and best practices" after &ldquo;three Class-A aviation mishaps over the last six weeks,&rdquo; a press release from the Pentagon stated.</span></p>]]></description>
   <author><![CDATA[Garrison Hardie]]></author>
   <enclosure url="https://app.dropwave.io/episode/3590adf8-c418-4110-9c57-faa14a944715/daily-news-brief-for-thursday-september-21st-2023.mp3" length="735" type="audio/mp3"/>
   <guid isPermaLink="false"><![CDATA[3590adf8-c418-4110-9c57-faa14a944715]]></guid>
   <pubDate>Thu, 21 Sep 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
   <source url=""><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></source>
   <itunes:author><![CDATA[Garrison Hardie]]></itunes:author>
   <itunes:image href="https://assets-cdn2.dropwave.io/2ab40ac0-e99d-4f25-a6d2-541d2c9b290a/cover-art/mUK8zsnHkCK3vep7E1W6UgYb9dTnLenASAMEFha3.jpg"/>
   <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
   <itunes:duration>735</itunes:duration>
   <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
  
  </item>
 </channel>
</rss>
