<?xml version="1.0"?>
<?xml-stylesheet href="/storage/feed-stylesheet.xsl" type="text/xsl"?>

<rss xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
 <channel>
  <title>FLF - Daily News Brief</title>
  <link>https://dropwave.io</link>
  <description><![CDATA[FIGHT LAUGH FEAST PRESENTS SHOWS PROCLAIMING THE LORDSHIP OF CHRIST OVER ALL OF LIFE.
]]></description>
  <language>en</language>
  <managingEditor><![CDATA[fightlaughfeast@gmail.com (FLF, LLC)]]></managingEditor>
  <webMaster><![CDATA[support@dropwave.io (DropWave Support)]]></webMaster>
  <pubDate>Wed, 20 Dec 2023 13:26:18 +0000</pubDate>
  <lastBuildDate>Wed, 20 Dec 2023 13:26:18 +0000</lastBuildDate>
  <image>
   <url>https://is4-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Podcasts113/v4/58/56/52/5856525c-2973-cf29-3db9-21faa8595391/mza_1144696925612154085.png/1200x1200bb.jpg</url>
   <link>https://dropwave.io</link>
   <title><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></title>
  </image>
  <itunes:author><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></itunes:author>
  <itunes:image href="https://is4-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Podcasts113/v4/58/56/52/5856525c-2973-cf29-3db9-21faa8595391/mza_1144696925612154085.png/1200x1200bb.jpg"/>
  <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
  <itunes:owner>
   <itunes:name><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></itunes:name>
   <itunes:email>fightlaughfeast@gmail.com</itunes:email>
  </itunes:owner>
  <itunes:category text="News"/>
  <item>
   <title><![CDATA[Daily News Brief for Wednesday , December 20th, 2023 [Daily News Brief]]]></title>
   <link/>
   <description><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">This is Garrison Hardie with your CrossPolitic Daily News Brief for Wednesday , December 20th, 2023.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>Rowdy Christian Merch Plug:</strong></span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">If you&rsquo;re a fan of CrossPolitic, or the Fight Laugh Feast Network, then surely, you know we have a merch store right? Rowdy Christian Merch is your one-stop-shop for everything CrossPolitc merchandise. We&rsquo;ve got T-Shirts, hoodies, hats, but we&rsquo;ve also got specialty items like backpacks, mugs, coffee, even airpod cases! Visit Rowdy Christian Merch at rowdychristian.com, and buy that next gift, or a little something for yourself. Again, that&rsquo;s rowdychristian.com.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://thepostmillennial.com/kamala-harris-to-take-pro-abortion-reproductive-freedoms-tour-across-us?utm_campaign=64487"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://thepostmillennial.com/kamala-harris-to-take-pro-abortion-reproductive-freedoms-tour-across-us?utm_campaign=64487</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>Kamala Harris launches 'Reproductive Freedoms' pro-abortion tour across US</strong></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Vice President Kamala Harris announced Tuesday that she plans to travel around the United States in what she calls a "Reproductive Freedoms" tour. Harris announced that these trips will be taken "to organize, build community, and fight back" against what she calls a "full-on attack on a woman's fundamental freedom to make decisions about her own body" across the nation.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The pro-abortion tour will kick off in Wisconsin on Jan. 22, which marks the 51st anniversary of the now-overturned Roe v. Wade.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The White House promises that "Vice President Harris will also hold extremists accountable for proposing a national abortion ban," although it does not specify what those consequences may be.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://thenationalpulse.com/2023/12/18/britain-bans-prayer-near-abortion-clinics/"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://thenationalpulse.com/2023/12/18/britain-bans-prayer-near-abortion-clinics/</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>Britain BANS PRAYER Near Abortion Clinics.</strong></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">England&rsquo;s High Court has upheld a local government order establishing a so-called &ldquo;buffer zone&rdquo; against prayers being said near an abortion clinic. Livia Tossici-Bolt, who heads the pro-life group 40 Days for Life Bournemouth, and Christian Concern had attempted to overturn the ban, arguing it &ldquo;criminalized prayer and reading from the Bible&rdquo;.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Judges determined on Friday that the banning order &ldquo;lawfully followed the democratic and consultative procedures&rdquo;. They said any infringements of freedom of religion, speech, and the right to protest were &ldquo;justified by the legitimate aim of protecting the rights of women attending the clinic.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Christian Concern intends to appeal the decision. &ldquo;Peaceful witness near abortion centers are helpful to many women in crisis pregnancies, offering genuine choice by providing support,&rdquo; argued Christian Legal Centre chief executive Andrea Williams. British police are exceptionally rigid in enforcing &ldquo;buffer zones&rdquo; protecting abortionists. Lone Christians have in some cases been arrested or fined for praying silently inside their heads near clinics.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/policy/immigration/border-officials-encounter-14-509-illegal-immigrants-new-record"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/policy/immigration/border-officials-encounter-14-509-illegal-immigrants-new-record</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>Biden border crisis shatters record with 14,509 illegal immigrants encountered in one day</strong></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">U.S. border officials encountered the highest number of illegal immigrants at the U.S.-Mexico border on Monday than any day, upending all other records that the Biden administration has set over the past three years.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The Washington Examiner obtained internal U.S. Customs and Border Protection data Tuesday that revealed 14,509 immigrants were encountered by federal law enforcement at the southern border on Monday. The large majority of encounters were of immigrants who walked around the port of entry and crossed into the country illegally, while a small percentage tried to enter at the port of entry but were denied admission.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The most recent record of 12,000 was set last week, according to Fox News. If yesterday's rate of 14,509 arrests per day continued for a month, it would translate to more than 435,000 immigrant arrests.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Rep. Tony Gonzales (R-TX), whose district runs along 800 miles of the 2,000-mile border, described the situation in his region as "all very sad." Gonzales told the Washington Examiner in a text message Tuesday morning that he believes the situation in Eagle Pass, Texas, a border town where 2,500 immigrants were arrested on Sunday, will continue to decline but that the extent would depend on how the Biden administration responds.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">"Depends on how much pressure gets put on U.S. and Mexican officials," Gonzales wrote.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">House Homeland Security Committee Chairman Mark Green (R-TN) reacted to the new one-day record on X, formerly Twitter.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">"Another Record: Over 14,500 illegal immigrants have been encountered while entering our country," Green wrote. "This has been the single worst 24 hours for our Southwest border in our nation&rsquo;s history."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Border officials in the Eagle Pass-Del Rio region encountered 3,100 illegal immigrants Monday, while officials in the Tucson region of Arizona encountered 3,089 people.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Government numbers obtained Tuesday show 26,758 immigrants were in custody as of Tuesday morning, including 5,197 in Del Rio, Texas; 5,004 in Tucson, Arizona; 4,968 in the Rio Grande Valley of Texas; and 4,722 in El Paso, Texas.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Existing Border Patrol stations in the Eagle Pass area are too small to accommodate more than several hundred people, so immigrants are being processed at a large tent facility outside town known as "Firefly" for the road that it is located on. The tent facility was set up last year with the intent of holding up to 1,000 immigrants, but as of Tuesday, more than 3,000 immigrants were at the site &mdash; putting the facility three times over the legal limit.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Border Patrol is also busing immigrants to other regions for processing. One official at the tent facility told the Washington Examiner that it sends out 30 to 50 large buses of immigrants to other regions each day.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Border Patrol highway checkpoints, including the only one north of Eagle Pass, were shuttered this week as agents were pulled to transport and process migrants.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">President Joe Biden has yet to react to the situation.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The Department of Homeland Security did not respond to a request for comment.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://www.dailyfetched.com/germany-begins-deploying-troops-for-first-time-since-world-war-ii/"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.dailyfetched.com/germany-begins-deploying-troops-for-first-time-since-world-war-ii/</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>Germany Begins Deploying Troops for First Time since World War II</strong></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The announcement was made on Monday in Lithuania, where Defense Minister Arvydas Anusauskas met Boris Pistoriusto to outline a &ldquo;Roadmap Action Plan&rdquo; involving 4,800 permanently stationed German soldiers.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The new move was described as &ldquo;historical&rdquo; for both nations and NATO.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">German troops will be stationed in the Lithuanian cities of Kaunas and Vilnius in early 2024, with the majority of troops being deployed in 2025 and 2026 and full-operation capability expected by 2027.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Meanwhile, Lithuania committed to providing all necessary civilian and military infrastructure.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">&ldquo;The German commitment of permanently stationing a brigade in Lithuania is a historical step for both Germany and Lithuania,&rdquo; Anusauskas said Monday, according to a press release.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">&ldquo;We are turning over to a page of even deeper strategic partnership.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Pistorius noted the step as being positive for defense relations, considering the war between Ukraine and Russia,</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">We will ensure reliable deterrence, and we will be ready to [defend] NATO. We are sending a clear signal with this step to those who present a threat to peace and security in Europe.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Newsweek reported that experts within the two defense ministries formulated the plan:</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">&ldquo;Most of the German troops will be stationed in the territory of Rūdninkai military training ground, while the rest will be deployed in the town of Rukla, where some 1,000 allied troops already reside.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Logistical hubs will cater to the new brigade, including three maneuver battalions and combat support and supply units formed by new and existing units.&ldquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">&ldquo;The 203rd Panzer Battalion, based in North Rhine-Westphalia, and the 122nd Armored Infantry Battalion, based in Bavaria, will be moved to Lithuania. Lithuania&rsquo;s enhanced Forward Presence Battalion Battle Group will be transformed into a multinational battalion to become &ldquo;an integral part of the brigade,&rdquo; the release said.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The head of the parliamentary National Security and Defense Committee, Laurynas Kasciunas, said the country would allocate 0.3 percent of its gross domestic product to help fund the deployment and to build housing.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Earlier this year, Germany faced pressure from the US to provide Leopard 2 tanks to Ukraine.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://pjmedia.com/vodkapundit/2023/12/18/americans-yawn-at-cdc-warnings-about-tripledemic-n4924835"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://pjmedia.com/vodkapundit/2023/12/18/americans-yawn-at-cdc-warnings-about-tripledemic-n4924835</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>Americans Yawn at CDC Warnings About 'Tripledemic'</strong></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">While America's public health officials issue one warning after another about this winter's "tripledemic" of COVID, flu, and RSV, the American public is responding with a collective yawn &mdash; if vaccination rates are anything to go by.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The CDC's most recent weekly vaccination update says that "receipt of the COVID-19 vaccine is low across all socio-demographic subgroups and has consistently varied by age, race and ethnicity, poverty status, health insurance status, and urbanicity." As of December 2, fewer than 18% of adults reported getting the updated COVID-19 vaccine since Sept. 14, and about another 15% of adults said they would "definitely" get vaccinated.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">RSV &mdash; respiratory syncytial virus infection &mdash; is another one of those bugs that poses its most serious risk to the 60-and-over crowd. Although a serious RSV infection might require hospitalization, the uptake rate among the eligible 60-plus cohort is just 16%.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Vaccinations for the ordinary flu are down a bit, too. "Adult vaccination rates for influenza reached their peak for the 2020-2021 cycle," the Washington Examiner reported on Monday, "with 50.2% of those over 18 getting vaccinated. For the 2022-2023 season, however, only 46.9% of the same population obtained their shot." Rates are expected to be about the same or lower for the current 2023-2024 flu season.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The drop isn't huge but the trendline is clear: Americans don't seem to be all that worried about the flu &mdash; and aren't concerned at all about COVID or RSV.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">That's not for any lack of effort on the part of our public health system.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The CDC began its big vaccination push more than two months ago, with this tragically hip tweet from CDC director Mandy Cohen.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Chicago health officials took a more traditional (and much less wince-inducing) approach on Monday, with Dr. Colleen Nash, associate professor of pediatrics in the division of infectious diseases at Rush University Medical Center, warning, "We&rsquo;ve now been lucky enough to kind of live with COVID but still enjoy normal life and activities and things. And that is directly attributable, at least in part, to vaccinations. So I would really encourage people to do that if they haven&rsquo;t already."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">While reports show that Illinois' hospitalization rate for COVID is "ticking up," the actual numbers aren't anything like 2020, with an additional 1,251 COVID hospital admissions this week statewide. And yet according to the Chicago Tribune, only about 11% of city residents are fully up to date on their COVID vaccinations.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The CDC tried on Twitter/X again on Saturday, reminding readers, "&lsquo;Tis the season for joy and family. Now is the time to get vaccinated against COVID-19 and flu before you see your loved ones again."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">"Visit vaccines.gov to find vaccines near you."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The ratio, as the kids like to say, is epic.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">While the replies were all over the place in tone, this one reasonable-sounding tweet captured the general sentiment.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">When vaccination rates are down even for the innocuous (and generally trusted) flu shot, it's clear that the CDC no longer enjoys the clout it used to with the American public.</span></p>]]></description>
   <author><![CDATA[Garrison Hardie]]></author>
   <enclosure url="https://app.dropwave.io/episode/9793ede3-9d1b-4806-a25e-46e929864bde/daily-news-brief-for-wednesday-december-20th-2023.mp3" length="729" type="audio/mp3"/>
   <guid isPermaLink="false"><![CDATA[9793ede3-9d1b-4806-a25e-46e929864bde]]></guid>
   <pubDate>Wed, 20 Dec 2023 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
   <source url=""><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></source>
   <itunes:author><![CDATA[Garrison Hardie]]></itunes:author>
   <itunes:image href="https://assets-cdn2.dropwave.io/2ab40ac0-e99d-4f25-a6d2-541d2c9b290a/cover-art/mUK8zsnHkCK3vep7E1W6UgYb9dTnLenASAMEFha3.jpg"/>
   <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
   <itunes:duration>729</itunes:duration>
   <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
  
  </item><item>
   <title><![CDATA[Daily News Brief for Tuesday, December 19th, 2023 [Daily News Brief]]]></title>
   <link/>
   <description><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">This is Garrison Hardie with your CrossPolitic Daily News Brief for Tuesday, December 19th, 2023.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Pub Membership Plug:</strong></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Public Houses, or Pubs, are not just places to drink beer, wine, cider or even something a little stronger. It is also a unique social centre, very often the focus of community life in villages, towns and cities throughout the length and breadth of the world. We here at CrossPolitic hope to emulate that for you and yours. That&rsquo;s why you should grab yourself a pub membership at fightlaughfeast.com&hellip; we need you on this ride with us. So pull up a chair, grab a pint, and join us on this ride at fightlaughfeast.com - that&rsquo;s fightlaughfeast.com.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://www.foxnews.com/media/navy-vet-defends-beheading-iowa-capitols-satanic-baphomet-statue-christian-civil-disobedience"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.foxnews.com/media/navy-vet-defends-beheading-iowa-capitols-satanic-baphomet-statue-christian-civil-disobedience</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Navy vet defends beheading Iowa capitol's satanic Baphomet statue: 'Christian civil disobedience'</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">A Mississippi Navy reserve pilot instructor who admitted to beheading a statue of the satanic half-man, half-goat Baphomet inside the Iowa State Capitol told Fox News he was simply engaging in "Christian civil disobedience."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Michael Cassidy said he decided "spur of the moment" to travel north to Des Moines and take action against the statue, which had been permitted to be erected not far from the rotunda's Nativity display for Christmas.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">He told "Jesse Watters Primetime" he wrecked the statue then went straight to Capitol security to tell them what he did.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">"I wasn't running away or anything like that. I told them what I did," he said, thanking law enforcement for their professionalism following the incident.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">He was cited for criminal mischief in the fourth degree and released.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">"I saw that this was going on, I was surprised that the legislature allowed it up and that they didn't do anything to take it down," Cassidy added.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">He said he wasn't sure what to expect when he came upon the Capitol, citing a prior incident in Springfield, Ill., where groups were chanting after a 2021 erection of a satanic statue in the Illinois State House.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">In a Tuesday statement, Iowa Republican Gov. Kim Reynolds said she found the statue "absolutely objectionable," but that the best response to objectionable speech is more speech and prayer.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">After he was charged, several conservative figures rallied to Cassidy's defense, including Florida Gov. Ron DeSantis and conservative commentator Matt Walsh.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">DeSantis promised to "chip in" for Cassidy's legal fees, writing on X, formerly Twitter, that "Satan has no place in our society and should not be recognized as a &lsquo;religion&rsquo; by the federal government." Walsh similarly tweeted he will contribute to Cassidy's defense.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Host Jesse Watters noted the contrast between reaction to Cassidy's act and the dozens of protests in recent years that featured left-wing activists tearing down statues of Confederate officers, former U.S. presidents and historical figures like Christopher Columbus.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">He pointed to then-Speaker Nancy Pelosi's, D-Calif., dismissal of the crowd in her home neighborhood of Little Italy, Baltimore, who leveled the Columbus statue and tossed it in the Patapsco River.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">"People will do what they do," Pelosi said at a July 2020 press conference.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The city of Richmond, Va., in recent years removed an entire street's worth of statuary dedicated to Confederate Gens. A. P. Hill, "Stonewall" Jackson and J. E. B. Stuart, all of which lined the former Confederate capital's "Monument Avenue" for decades.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Left-wing protesters notably failed to topple the statue of Andrew Jackson, the first Democratic president, near the White House in 2020 after being rebuffed by law enforcement.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">In that respect, Watters said there appears to be a dichotomy between what statuary destruction causes mainstream or left-wing outrage.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Cassidy's attorney, Davis Younts, said his client's case is a question of good versus evil, and that he and those who have come to his defense will continue to stand by him to make sure he gets equal protection under law.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">He also said there has not yet been a First Amendment suit in case law that has found Satanism to be considered a religion under the Constitution, and that anti-blasphemy laws still exist in the United States.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://www.breitbart.com/europe/2023/12/17/church-of-england-blesses-same-sex-couples-for-the-first-time/"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.breitbart.com/europe/2023/12/17/church-of-england-blesses-same-sex-couples-for-the-first-time/</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Church of England Blesses Same-Sex Couples For the First Time</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Church of England priests offered officially sanctioned blessings of same-sex partnerships for the first time on Sunday, though a ban on church weddings for gay couples remains in place amid deep divisions within global Anglicanism over marriage and sexuality.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">In one of the first ceremonies, the Rev. Catherine Bond and the Rev. Jane Pearce had their union blessed at St John the Baptist church, in Felixstowe, eastern England, where both are associate priests.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The couple knelt in front of Canon Andrew Dotchin, who held their heads as he gave &ldquo;thanks for Catherine and Jane, to the love and friendship they share, and their commitment to one another as they come before you on this day.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The church&acute;s national assembly voted in February to allow clergy to bless the unions of same-sex couples who have had civil weddings or partnerships. The words used for the blessings, known as prayers of love and faith, were approved by the church&acute;s House of Bishops on Tuesday and used for the first time on Sunday.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The compromise was struck following five years of discussions about the church&acute;s position on sexuality. Church leaders offered an apology for the church&acute;s failure to welcome LGBTQ people, but also endorsed the doctrine that marriage is the union of one man and one woman. Clergy won&acute;t be required to perform same-sex blessings if they disagree with them.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The blessings can be used in regular church services. The church&acute;s governing body has also drawn up a plan for separate &ldquo;services of prayer and dedication&rdquo; for same-sex couples that would resemble weddings, but it has not yet been formally approved.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Public opinion surveys consistently show that a majority of people in England support same-sex marriage, which has been legal since 2013. The church didn&acute;t alter its teaching on marriage when the law changed.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Archbishop of Canterbury Justin Welby has said he won&acute;t personally bless any same-sex couples because it&acute;s his job to unify the world&rsquo;s 85 million Anglicans. Welby is the spiritual leader of both the Church of England and the global Anglican Communion of which it is a member.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Several Anglican bishops from Africa, Asia, Latin America and the Pacific said after the February decision that they no longer recognize Welby as their leader.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://www.breitbart.com/politics/2023/12/18/poll-54-of-democrat-voters-want-to-replace-joe-biden-as-2024-nominee/"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.breitbart.com/politics/2023/12/18/poll-54-of-democrat-voters-want-to-replace-joe-biden-as-2024-nominee/</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Poll: 54% of Democrat Voters Want to Replace Joe Biden as 2024 Nominee</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Democrat party voters are unhappy President Joe Biden, 81, is the presumptive Democrat nominee to likely challenge former President Donald Trump, Fox News polling revealed Sunday.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The poll highlights the disconnect and discord inflicting the Democrat party after Biden refused to step aside and allow a different Democrat to lead the party.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The survey showed:</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">54 percent of Democrat primary voters prefer an alternative to Biden.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Just 43 percent of Democrat primary voters want to keep Biden.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The polling showed a slight uptick in negative sentiment against the president:</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">October: 53 percent prefer an alternative, while 45 want to keep Biden</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">March: 52 percent prefer an alternative, while 44 want to keep Biden</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Biden previously told reporters in December he must run for reelection after prominent Democrats implored him to reconsider a second bid against Trump. &ldquo;Would you be running if Trump wasn&rsquo;t running?&rdquo; a reporter asked Biden.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&ldquo;I expect so,&rdquo; Biden replied. &ldquo;But he is running, and &mdash; I just &mdash; I have to run.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Biden&rsquo;s comment came on the same day he told donors he probably would not run if Trump was not running. &ldquo;If Trump wasn&rsquo;t running, I&rsquo;m not sure I&rsquo;d be running,&rdquo; Biden said, adding that Democrats &ldquo;cannot let him [Trump] win.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">National and battleground state polling shows Biden losing to Trump:</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Morning Consult: Trump leads Biden in six of seven crucial swing states.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">NBC News: Trump leads Biden by two points.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Fox News: Trump trounces Biden by four points.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The poll surveyed 1,0007 registered voters from December 10-13 with a 4.5 point margin of error.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://thepostmillennial.com/eric-adams-admits-biden-admin-will-not-help-nyc-with-illegal-immigrant-crisis?utm_campaign=64487"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://thepostmillennial.com/eric-adams-admits-biden-admin-will-not-help-nyc-with-illegal-immigrant-crisis?utm_campaign=64487</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Eric Adams admits Biden admin will not help NYC with illegal immigrant crisis</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">On Sunday, New York City Mayor Eric Adams said that Democrats "underestimated" the impact that illegal immigration would have on their cities, and warned New Yorkers to brace for "extremely painful" budget cuts to pay back the debt created by it.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">In an interview with WPIX-TV, Adams said, that a low for the city in 2023 was "150,000 migrants and asylum seekers that put a real bump in the road of our recovery effort in the city."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://twitter.com/i/status/1736507664308277364"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://twitter.com/i/status/1736507664308277364</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> - Play Video&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://twitter.com/i/status/1736512831963430927"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://twitter.com/i/status/1736512831963430927</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> - Play Video </span><strong>Combine these videos</strong></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">After a meeting with the congressional leaders of the Biden administration earlier this month, Adams said he was not optimistic about getting help from the federal government to deal with the illegal immigrant crisis plaguing New York City.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Adams was forced to cut the budget for the New York City Police Department last month, taking the department below 30,000 personnel.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://www.foxnews.com/sports/aaron-rodgers-likely-cleared-return-ruptured-achilles-next-week-report"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.foxnews.com/sports/aaron-rodgers-likely-cleared-return-ruptured-achilles-next-week-report</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Aaron Rodgers likely to be cleared for return from ruptured Achilles next week</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Aaron Rodgers' bold prediction is apparently about to play out.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The four-time MVP ruptured his Achilles Sept. 11 on just his fourth snap as a New York Jet.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Four days later, he shocked the world when he said, "Give me your doubts,then watch what I do."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">At that time, Rodgers did not rule out a return this season, saying that "anything is possible." Most doubted, but it may actually become a reality.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">According to ESPN, the 40-year-old is likely to be medically cleared to return next week.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Rodgers returned to practice Nov. 29, roughly seven weeks since his injury. It was an unprecedented time frame to practice after such an injury.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">However, Rodgers said he underwent "innovative" surgery in his best effort to get back on the field this season.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Rodgers has said he wanted a return on Christmas Eve. The Jets have until Wednesday to decide whether to activate Rodgers from injured reserve. Otherwise, he would miss the rest of the season.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Rodgers has wowed just about everyone in the organization with how quickly he has progressed. Earlier this week, he even lined up as a linebacker for the scout team and made a one-handed interception.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">However, being cleared isn't exactly a guarantee Rodgers would play.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The quarterback and the Jets have said the team's playoff chances will play a role in whether he returns. He likely would not return if they are mathematically eliminated from the playoffs, which could happen this weekend.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Rodgers recently said there are hardly any risks in taking the field this season.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">"My thing is, what&rsquo;s the worst that can happen?" he told reporters shortly after returning to practice. "Something unfortunate again, and then you just slow the rehab down. I think by my own timetable that if you take the rehab slower and a little more deliberate &mdash; five months, six months max &mdash; is probably the length to get back to 100% if you really take it slow. So, in my opinion, there's not like a downside to coming back and reinjuring it."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The Jets face the Washington Commanders on Christmas Eve.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p><br /><br style="font-weight: 400;" /></p>]]></description>
   <author><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></author>
   <enclosure url="https://app.dropwave.io/episode/b5af4df7-c0f1-4993-b0fe-db46e54c830d/daily-news-brief-for-tuesday-december-19th-2023.mp3" length="746" type="audio/mp3"/>
   <guid isPermaLink="false"><![CDATA[b5af4df7-c0f1-4993-b0fe-db46e54c830d]]></guid>
   <pubDate>Tue, 19 Dec 2023 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
   <source url=""><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></source>
   <itunes:author><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></itunes:author>
   <itunes:image href="https://assets-cdn2.dropwave.io/2ab40ac0-e99d-4f25-a6d2-541d2c9b290a/cover-art/mUK8zsnHkCK3vep7E1W6UgYb9dTnLenASAMEFha3.jpg"/>
   <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
   <itunes:duration>746</itunes:duration>
   <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
  
  </item><item>
   <title><![CDATA[Daily News Brief for Friday,, December 15th, 2023 [Daily News Brief]]]></title>
   <link/>
   <description><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">This is Garrison Hardie with your CrossPolitic Daily News Brief for Friday,, December 15th, 2023.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Download our new app!:</strong></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">You guys are aware that we have a new app right? If not you should download it right now! Head on over to your app store, and type in &ldquo;CrossPolitic&rdquo;, &ldquo;Fight Laugh Feast&rdquo;, or &ldquo;PubTV&rdquo;. Once you find the app, you may need to update your app, or if you have a droid phone, you may need to delete your current FLF app, and re-download it! Once downloaded you&rsquo;ll be able to view or listen to our content right on your mobile device! As always, if you&rsquo;d like to sign up for a pub membership, you can head on over to fightlaughfeast.com&hellip; that&rsquo;s fightlaughfeast.com.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2023/12/13/fed-interest-rate-decision-december-2023.html"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.cnbc.com/2023/12/13/fed-interest-rate-decision-december-2023.html</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Fed holds rates steady, indicates three cuts coming in 2024</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The Federal Reserve on Wednesday held its key interest rate steady for the third straight time and set the table for multiple cuts to come in 2024 and beyond.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">With the inflation rate easing and the economy holding in, policymakers on the Federal Open Market Committee voted unanimously to keep the benchmark overnight borrowing rate in a targeted range between 5.25%-5.5%.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Along with the decision to stay on hold, committee members penciled in at least three rate cuts in 2024, assuming quarter percentage point increments. That&rsquo;s less than market pricing of four, but more aggressive than what officials had previously indicated.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Markets had widely anticipated the decision to stay put, which could end a cycle that has seen 11 hikes, pushing the fed funds rate to its highest level in more than 22 years. There was uncertainty, though, about how ambitious the FOMC might be regarding policy easing. Following the release of the decision, the Dow Jones Industrial Average jumped more than 400 points, surpassing 37,000 for the first time.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The committee&rsquo;s &ldquo;dot plot&rdquo; of individual members&rsquo; expectations indicates another four cuts in 2025, or a full percentage point. Three more reductions in 2026 would take the fed funds rate down to between 2%-2.25%, close to the long-run outlook, though there was considerable dispersion in the estimates for the final two years.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Markets, though, followed up the meeting and Chair Jerome Powell&rsquo;s press conference by pricing in an even more aggressive rate-cut path, anticipating 1.5 percentage points in reductions next year, double the FOMC&rsquo;s indicated pace.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">In a possible nod that hikes are over, the statement said that the committee would take multiple factors into account for &ldquo;any&rdquo; more policy tightening, a word that had not appeared previously.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Along with the interest rate hikes, the Fed has been allowing up to $95 billion a month in proceeds from maturing bonds to roll off its balance sheet. That process has continued, and there has been no indication the Fed is willing to curtail that portion of policy tightening.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">That echoed new language in the post-meeting statement. The committee added the qualifier that inflation has &ldquo;eased over the past year&rdquo; while maintaining its description of prices as &ldquo;elevated.&rdquo; Fed officials see core inflation falling to 3.2% in 2023 and 2.4% in 2024, then to 2.2% in 2025. Finally, it gets back to the 2% target in 2026.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Economic data released this week showed both consumer and wholesale prices were little changed in November. By some measures, though, the Fed is nearing its 2% inflation target. Bank of America&rsquo;s calculations indicate that the Fed&rsquo;s preferred inflation gauge will be around 3.1% year over year in November, and actually could hit a 2% six-month annualized rate, meeting the central bank&rsquo;s goal.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The statement also noted that the economy &ldquo;has slowed,&rdquo; after saying in November that activity had &ldquo;expanded at a strong pace.&rdquo;&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">In the news conference, Powell said: &ldquo;Recent indicators suggest that growth in economic activity has slowed substantially from the outsized pace seen in the third quarter. Even so, GDP is on track to expand around 2.5% for the year as a whole.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Committee members upgraded gross domestic product to grow at a 2.6% annualized pace in 2023, a half percentage point increase from the last update in September. Officials see GDP at 1.4% in 2024, roughly unchanged from the previous outlook. Projections for the unemployment rate were largely unchanged, at 3.8% in 2023 and rising to 4.1% in subsequent years.&nbsp;&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Officials have stressed their willingness to hike rates again if inflation flares up. However, most have said they can be patient now as they watch the impact the previous policy tightening moves are having on the U.S. economy.&nbsp;&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Stubbornly high prices have exacted a political toll on President Joe Biden, whose approval rating has suffered in large part because of negative sentiment on how he has handled the economy. There had been some speculation that the Fed could be reluctant to make any dramatic policy actions during a presidential election year, which looms large in 2024.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">However, with real rates, or the difference between the fed funds rate and inflation, running high, the Fed would be more likely to act if the inflation data continues to cooperate.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://thenationalpulse.com/2023/12/11/even-leftist-governments-around-the-world-are-moving-to-slash-migration/"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://thenationalpulse.com/2023/12/11/even-leftist-governments-around-the-world-are-moving-to-slash-migration/</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Even Leftist Governments Around the World Are Moving to Slash Migration.</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Leftist governments in Denmark and Australia are adopting a more hardline stance on immigration than many notionally conservative governments. Australia&rsquo;s governing Labor Party has pledged to cut net immigration in half. Denmark&rsquo;s Social Democrats have pledged zero net immigration, a.k.a. balanced immigration.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Australia, with a population of only around 25 million, suffered net immigration of around 510,000 in the year to June. The government has conceded the system is &ldquo;broken&rdquo; and &ldquo;in tatters&rdquo; &ndash; blaming the previous center-right government. They say they will reduce it to around 250,000 by June 2025.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">There is growing acknowledgment that an ongoing housing crisis cannot be resolved if mass migration continues at current levels.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Denmark, a generous welfare state, is going even further. They aim to balance the number of people entering the country against the number of people leaving, with the government insisting: &ldquo;If you want to be a party of the working class and middle class, you have to ensure that migration has a manageable level.&rdquo;&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Social Democrat lawmaker Rasmus Stoklund explained his party&rsquo;s increasingly anti-immigration stance is the true left-wing position.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&ldquo;The part of society that bears the brunt of unchecked migration is the working-class population that we should be representing,&rdquo; he said. &ldquo;It is their children who have to go to schools that experience cultural clashes. It is those people who have to experience the criminality and social problems that follow. The more privileged people in society will only meet migrants if they are the children of diplomats, so for them the issue is not so clear.&rdquo;&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Denmark is also taking radical action to integrate the existing migration background population. Vollsmose, a notorious suburban &ldquo;no go zone&rdquo;, is being bulldozed, to help integrate its predominantly &ldquo;non-Western&rdquo; residents.</span></p>
<p><br /><br /></p>
<p><a href="https://thenationalpulse.com/2023/12/11/suicide-is-consistently-killing-more-u-s-soldiers-than-anything-else-including-war/"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://thenationalpulse.com/2023/12/11/suicide-is-consistently-killing-more-u-s-soldiers-than-anything-else-including-war/</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Suicide Is Consistently Killing More U.S. Soldiers Than Anything Else, Including War.</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Suicide accounted for just under 40 percent of United States active military deaths as of December 2022, according to the Defense Casualty Analysis System, which found that U.S. military suicide rates have dramatically increased over the past several decades.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Indeed, the current leading cause of death among servicemen is currently categorized as &ldquo;self-inflicted,&rdquo; with a total of 333 incidents last year. Suicide was recorded as almost ten percent higher in prevalence than accidents, of which there were 265.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Yet, last year represents a slight decrease in the rate of self-inflicted deaths compared to October 2020, in which suicide rates were just under 41 percent.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Suicide accounted for roughly ten percent of military deaths when records began in 1980, with that figure remaining mostly stable until the 1990s, in which the rate jumped to 23 percent in 1995. The rate of self-inflicted deaths fell sharply in the mid-2000s, however, much of the decline can be attributed to the increase in &ldquo;hostile action&rdquo; fatalities in 2008.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Suicide rates across American society have reached unprecedented levels under the Biden government, with just under 50,000 people killing themselves in 2022. The rate was 14.3 three people per 100,000 &ndash; the highest since 1941.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://www.dailyfetched.com/donations-to-harry-and-meghans-woke-charity-collapse-by-11-million/"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.dailyfetched.com/donations-to-harry-and-meghans-woke-charity-collapse-by-11-million/</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Donations to Harry and Meghan&rsquo;s &lsquo;Woke&rsquo; Charity Collapse by $11 Million</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Prince Harry and Meghan Markle&rsquo;s Archewell charitable foundation has reported a massive loss of a $11 million year-on-year collapse in donations.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">According to the foundation&rsquo;s website, Harry and Meghan aimed to &ldquo;uplift and unite communities, both local and global, online and offline.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">But that didn&rsquo;t happen.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">In a tax filing disclosed Tuesday, the non-profit organization received just over $2 million in charitable contributions in 2022, compared to $13 million in 2021.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">However, some $8.2 million funds remain in the Archewell Foundation accounts.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The 28-page report also details the charitable work the foundation has undertaken during 2023.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The report stated:</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&ldquo;We are committed to a simple but profound mission: Show Up, Do Good.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">But &ldquo;doing good&rdquo; has not come cheap for the woke pair, who recently made the decision only to have two children to help fight climate change.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://twitter.com/i/status/1734930901883129891"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://twitter.com/i/status/1734930901883129891</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> - Play Video&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Breitbart reported that Archewell&rsquo;s total expenses exceeded its revenue the year before, leaving it down by more than $674,000, according to the public filing. Its revenue in 2021 had exceeded $9 million.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The organization&rsquo;s executive director, James Holt, earned a salary of $227,405, including a $20,000 bonus, in 2022.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The figure represents a 280 percent increase from his salary of less than $60,000 in 2021.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Prince Harry and Meghan Markle also faced more bad news earlier this week after they named Showbusiness&rsquo; biggest losers of 2023.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">They also faced a belittling on South Park and were dropped from their lucrative $20 million Spotify deal.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The Royal couple also faced a roasting in the Hollywood Reporter&rsquo;s &ldquo;brutally honest rundown.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">James Hibberd contributed the scathing review, noting they were labeled &ldquo;f**king grifters&rdquo; by top executive Bill Simmons.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Earlier this week, NBC reported a judge ordered Prince Harry on Monday to pay nearly 50,000 pounds (more than $60,000) in legal fees to the publisher of the Daily Mail tabloid for his failed court challenge in a libel lawsuit.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The Duke of Sussex is suing Associated Newspapers Ltd. over an article that said Harry tried to hide his efforts to retain publicly funded protection in the U.K. after leaving his role as a working member of the royal family.</span></p>]]></description>
   <author><![CDATA[Garrison Hardie]]></author>
   <enclosure url="https://app.dropwave.io/episode/2c0b6ada-c6b9-42b1-952b-1ce9ce8a8713/daily-news-brief-for-friday-december-15th-2023.mp3" length="862" type="audio/mp3"/>
   <guid isPermaLink="false"><![CDATA[2c0b6ada-c6b9-42b1-952b-1ce9ce8a8713]]></guid>
   <pubDate>Fri, 15 Dec 2023 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
   <source url=""><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></source>
   <itunes:author><![CDATA[Garrison Hardie]]></itunes:author>
   <itunes:image href="https://assets-cdn2.dropwave.io/2ab40ac0-e99d-4f25-a6d2-541d2c9b290a/cover-art/mUK8zsnHkCK3vep7E1W6UgYb9dTnLenASAMEFha3.jpg"/>
   <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
   <itunes:duration>862</itunes:duration>
   <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
  
  </item><item>
   <title><![CDATA[Daily News Brief for Thursday,, December 7th, 2023. [Daily News Brief]]]></title>
   <link/>
   <description><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">This is Garrison Hardie with your CrossPolitic Daily News Brief for Thursday,, December 7th, 2023.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Fight Laugh Feast Magazine</strong></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Our Fight Laugh Feast Magazine is a quarterly issue that packs a punch like a 21 year Balvenie, no ice. We don&rsquo;t water down our scotch, why would we water down our theology? Order a yearly subscription for yourself and then send a couple yearly subscriptions to your friends who have been drinking luke-warm evangelical cool-aid. Every quarter we promise quality food for the soul, wine for the heart, and some Red Bull for turning over tables. Our magazine will include cultural commentary, a Psalm of the quarter, recipes for feasting, laughter sprinkled through out the glossy pages, and more. Sign up today, at fightlaughfeast.com.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-12833565/Biden-Russia-Ukraine-Congress-war-conflict-aid-NATO.html"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-12833565/Biden-Russia-Ukraine-Congress-war-conflict-aid-NATO.html</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Joe Biden raises the specter of American troops having to fight Russians in Europe if Congress stands by and allows Ukraine to fall</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">President Joe Biden on Wednesday warned that American troops could have to fight Russian forces if Congress prevents further aid being sent to Ukraine.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">He demanded that lawmakers approve his request for tens of billions in military and economic assistance.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Republicans have said they are not willing to countenance another major package of aid unless the administration takes action on the southern border.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">But Biden said Republicans were handing Russian President Vladimir Putin a gift.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">'This cannot wait,' he said in a televised address.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">'Congress needs to pass supplemental funding for Ukraine before they break for the holiday recess, simple as that, frankly.'</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://youtu.be/7UBC-UluphU?list=RDNS7UBC-UluphU"><span style="font-weight: 400;" data-rich-links="{&quot;fple-t&quot;:&quot;Biden presses Congress to pass Ukraine aid to prevent Russian win&quot;,&quot;fple-u&quot;:&quot;https://youtu.be/7UBC-UluphU?list=RDNS7UBC-UluphU&quot;,&quot;fple-mt&quot;:null,&quot;type&quot;:&quot;first-party-link&quot;}">Biden presses Congress to pass Ukraine aid to prevent Russian win</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;" data-rich-links="{&quot;fple-t&quot;:&quot;Biden presses Congress to pass Ukraine aid to prevent Russian win&quot;,&quot;fple-u&quot;:&quot;https://youtu.be/7UBC-UluphU?list=RDNS7UBC-UluphU&quot;,&quot;fple-mt&quot;:null,&quot;type&quot;:&quot;first-party-link&quot;}"> </span><span style="font-weight: 400;">Play 1:24-3:00</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">He accused Republicans of holding aid 'hostage' over the border and of being willing to 'kneecap' Ukrainian forces on the battlefield</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">But he hinted that he was ready to do a deal with Republicans, even if they would have to accept they were not going to get everything they wanted.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Biden's speech came soon after he held a video call with leaders of the Group of Seven advanced democracies, who have all backed Ukraine, and Ukrainian President Volodymyr Zelensky.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Biden has asked Congress for more than $100 billion to fund conflicts in Ukraine and Israel, as well as other matters of national security. However, Republicans on Capitol Hill have resisted the request, some insisting that Biden first take measures to secure the nation's southern border.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The White House has warned repeatedly of the consequences of failing to back Ukraine.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">In a blunt letter sent to Congress on Monday, Office of Management and Budget Director Shalanda Young wrote: 'We are out of money to support Ukraine in this fight. This isn't a next year problem. The time to help a democratic Ukraine fight against Russian aggression is right now.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">However, Republican leaders quickly dug in.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Speaker Mike Johnson promised there would be no funding for Ukraine without 'transformative' border security provisions.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://americanmilitarynews.com/2023/12/us-troops-suing-govt-for-billions-in-backpay-over-covid-vaccine-mandate/"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://americanmilitarynews.com/2023/12/us-troops-suing-govt-for-billions-in-backpay-over-covid-vaccine-mandate/</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>US troops suing gov&rsquo;t for &lsquo;billions&rsquo; in backpay over Covid vaccine mandate</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">In a groundbreaking development, three lawsuits with the potential for a class action suit are being filed on behalf of former United States service members. The service members, represented by attorneys Dale Saran, Andy Meyer, and Brandon Johnson, allege they were unjustly discharged or prevented from drilling, causing significant financial loss, as a result of the Biden administration&rsquo;s vaccine mandate policies.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">According to Breitbart, the lawsuits, which are currently in the U.S. Court of Federal Claims, could involve backpay claims totaling billions of dollars.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Saran, a retired Marine, emphasized the massive scale of the compensation, telling Breitbart, &ldquo;It&rsquo;s worth billions. That&rsquo;s just flat-out. That&rsquo;s what it is in backpay. It&rsquo;s billions of dollars.&rdquo; This statement underscores the potential magnitude of the lawsuit&rsquo;s financial implications for the Department of Defense.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The court, with its roots in the Reconstruction Era, is known for handling cases of illegal discharge and pay-related grievances in the military. Saran explained its unique role, saying that the Court of Claims is where service members can go when they have a claim and say, &ldquo;Hey, I was illegally discharged, or the military did something to impede my pay.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">According to Breitbart, the lawsuits allege that 80,000 to 100,000 service members, including both active-duty personnel and reservists, were impacted by the Biden administration&rsquo;s actions. Saran detailed the lack of due process in the cases, noting, &ldquo;They were basically [without] the benefit of any due process. No boards were held. They didn&rsquo;t hold any administrative separation boards; they didn&rsquo;t hold any hearings. They didn&rsquo;t do any federal recognition boards; none of the administrative or judicial procedures were used. They just flat-out did it.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">One notable case involves former Coast Guard member Zach Loesch, who was commended by President Joe Biden for his heroics during Hurricane Ian but faced discharge for not complying with a vaccine mandate, according to Breitbart.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The claims also involve the repayment of enlistment bonuses, adding to the financial stakes. Saran stated, &ldquo;Not only did they throw them out &mdash; unceremoniously [and] wrongfully &mdash; now they&rsquo;re&hellip;without a job instantly, no separation pay, none of that. And instead, they&rsquo;re standing out in the cold, and worse yet, here comes the government&hellip;here comes the debt collectors. Now you owe us money.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Saran drew parallels between the current situation with the service members who were negatively impacted by the COVID-19 vaccine mandate policies and his past experience defending service members who refused the Anthrax vaccine in the late 1990s.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&ldquo;I did some work on the lawsuit Doe v. Rumsfeld that shut down the anthrax vaccine,&rdquo; he said. &ldquo;And so&hellip;here we are, second go around again, 15 years in, and we&rsquo;re right back at the mass vaccination of unlicensed vaccines like the government didn&rsquo;t learn last time.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">According to Saran, those interested in more information about the current lawsuits can learn more at militarybackpay.com. The ongoing legal battle, with cases like Bassen v. USA, Botello v. USA, and Harkins v. USA, marks a significant moment in military legal history, raising questions about due process, financial responsibility, and the broader implications for the rights of U.S. service members.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://www.foxnews.com/world/israel-constructs-large-pumps-flood-hamas-terror-tunnels-seawater-wall-street-journal"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.foxnews.com/world/israel-constructs-large-pumps-flood-hamas-terror-tunnels-seawater-wall-street-journal</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Israel constructs large pumps to flood Hamas terror tunnels with seawater</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The Israeli military has assembled several large pumps it could use to flood the Hamas tunnels beneath the Gaza Strip with seawater, driving out terrorists hiding there, The Wall Street Journal reported, citing U.S. officials.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Construction of five large seawater pumps was completed in November about one mile north of the Al-Shati refugee camp. Each pump is capable of drawing water from the Mediterranean Sea and can move thousands of cubic meters of water per hour, which would flood the tunnels within weeks, the report said.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Israel has not yet committed to the plan, and it is unclear whether it would attempt to flood the tunnels while there are still hostages, including Americans, held by Hamas. The Palestinian terror group took some 240 people captive during the Oct. 7 attack on Israel and brought them back to the Gaza Strip.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">According to the report, Israel has identified about 800 tunnels beneath Gaza that Hamas has used to move fighters, store weapons and plan terror attacks on Israel. However, Israeli officials believe the tunnel network is much larger.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">By flooding the tunnels over several weeks, Israel would enable Hamas terrorists and potentially hostages to move out, the outlet reported, citing a source familiar with the plan.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">"We are not sure how successful pumping will be since nobody knows the details of the tunnels and the ground around them," the source said. "It&rsquo;s impossible to know if that will be effective because we don&rsquo;t know how seawater will drain in tunnels no one has been in before."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The Wall Street Journal said an Israel Defense Forces official declined to comment on the flooding plan, but said: "The IDF is operating to dismantle Hamas&rsquo;s terror capabilities in various ways, using different military and technological tools."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">U.S. officials were informed of the plan last month, the Wall Street Journal reported, but the U.S. does not know how close Israeli Prime Minister Benjamin Netanyahu's government is to executing the plan.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Israel has committed to continuing its war effort until Hamas is eradicated in Gaza. The Israeli military said it launched its 10,000th airstrike against the terror group in the Gaza Strip late Sunday.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://thepostmillennial.com/dem-witness-who-cannot-define-what-a-woman-is-says-women-should-learn-to-lose-gracefully-against-trans-athletes?utm_campaign=64487#google_vignette"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://thepostmillennial.com/dem-witness-who-cannot-define-what-a-woman-is-says-women-should-learn-to-lose-gracefully-against-trans-athletes?utm_campaign=64487#google_vignette</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Dem witness who cannot define what a woman is says women should 'learn to lose gracefully' against trans athletes</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Head of the National Women's Law Center, Fatima Goss Graves, encouraged women who are forced to compete against men in women's sports to "lose gracefully." This she sees as the preferable alternative to keeping men out of women's sports at the scholastic level altogether. She made these remarks at a hearing over Title IX in the US House.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">"The reality is, that like their peers, trans girls and women, they sometimes lose at sports and sometimes they win. And success in school sports depends on a whole range of factors including how hard you work and coaching and access to really good resources and facilities," Goss Graves said. Goss Graves is married to Matthew Graves, a key prosecutor in J6 cases. She also co-founded Times Up to hold high-profile men accountable for sexual misconduct.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">She did not address the problems that arise when boys shower in girls locker rooms and expose themselves, or when girls miss out on opportunities because men have taken their places in the winners' circle.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://twitter.com/i/status/1732214013499412976"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://twitter.com/i/status/1732214013499412976</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> - Play Video (If you can find it somewhere else that&rsquo;s fine.)&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Goss Graves also does not know what a woman is. Or at least she refused to define the term when asked. She was asked in July 2022 by Rep Andrew Clyde - </span><a href="https://www.youtube.com/shorts/2Uo111tBKd4?feature=share"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.youtube.com/shorts/2Uo111tBKd4?feature=share</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> - Play Video&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The hearing was to consider changes proposed by the Department of Education to Title IX of the Civil Rights Act of 1964. The change would prevent schools from having women's or girl's-only sports. It would bring a new understanding and interpretation of Title IX, removing protections for women and girls and changing that to protection against discrimination for gender identity as a protected class. Under those provisions, the male student's stated gender identity would give him the standing to shower with girls and use other facilities that were previously women only.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://thepostmillennial.com/auto-makers-seek-to-remove-am-radio-from-all-new-models?utm_campaign=64487"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://thepostmillennial.com/auto-makers-seek-to-remove-am-radio-from-all-new-models?utm_campaign=64487</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Automakers seek to remove AM radio from all new models</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">As vehicles become more and more complex, many manufacturers have begun doing away with AM radios, citing concerns that the proximity of electrical components could potentially negatively interact with signals from short-wave broadcasts.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">While it could be argued that the AM radio one day going the way of the dashboard tape deck was inevitable, the fact that many Americans still tune into, and in some cases rely on, the technology has led to pushback against the companies attempting to omit it from new cars.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">In May, Sens. Ted Cruz (R-TX) and Ed Markey (D-MA) joined a bipartisan group of their colleagues in the House to introduce the AM for Every Vehicle Act, which, if passed, will direct the National Highway Traffic Safety Administration to require manufacturers to ensure AM radio is included free of charge in every model for the foreseeable future.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">According to a press release that announced the bill in May, eight of the world's 20 leading car makers, BMW, Ford, Mazda, Polestar, Rivian, Tesla, Volkswagen and Volvo, have done away with AM radio in their vehicles.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&nbsp;</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">"I would think that if Elon Musk has enough money to buy Twitter and send rockets to space, he can afford to include AM radio in his Teslas," New Jersey Rep. Josh Gottheimer lamented. "Instead, Elon Musk and Tesla and other car manufacturers are putting public safety and emergency response at risk."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">While many of the bill's proponents cited the use of AM radio for emergency alerts, others pointed out that despite its archaic reputation, it is still an integral part of many people's technology arsenal.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Arkansas Rep. Bruce Westerman, for example, said that his constituents "rely on AM broadcast radio for breaking news and entertainment as they make their daily commutes, especially in rural areas where constituents spend a lot of time in their vehicles."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">As Spectrum News covered, a report from the Center for Automotive Research found that the electromagnetic interference generted by EVs can make the AM signals fuzzy and unlistenable, and that while there is a workaround, it may cost automakers an estimated $3.8 billion over the next seven years.</span></p>]]></description>
   <author><![CDATA[Garrison Hardie]]></author>
   <enclosure url="https://app.dropwave.io/episode/5826c57a-dca6-48b7-994f-eaa9dfbac9c2/daily-news-brief-for-thursday-december-7th-2023.mp3" length="996" type="audio/mp3"/>
   <guid isPermaLink="false"><![CDATA[5826c57a-dca6-48b7-994f-eaa9dfbac9c2]]></guid>
   <pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
   <source url=""><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></source>
   <itunes:author><![CDATA[Garrison Hardie]]></itunes:author>
   <itunes:image href="https://assets-cdn2.dropwave.io/2ab40ac0-e99d-4f25-a6d2-541d2c9b290a/cover-art/mUK8zsnHkCK3vep7E1W6UgYb9dTnLenASAMEFha3.jpg"/>
   <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
   <itunes:duration>996</itunes:duration>
   <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
  
  </item><item>
   <title><![CDATA[Daily News Brief for Wednesday, December 6th, 2023 [Daily News Brief]]]></title>
   <link/>
   <description><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">This is Garrison Hardie with your CrossPolitic Daily News Brief for Wednesday, December 6th, 2023.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Tactics Conference</strong></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The Tactics Conference is coming! Learn how to build Christ&rsquo;s kingdom from those that are doing it. Join C.R. Wiley, the campus preacher Keith Darrel, Gabe Rench, Chocolate Knox, and Pastor Toby Sumpter for two days of boots on the ground training on how to take your community for Christ. Great talks, great food, and great people. Come see us in Lafayette, Louisiana (that's only about 2 and a half hours east of Houston, Texas) on January 19th-20th.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">And take note - Seating is limited. Families are welcome, come experience some Cajun hospitality, while we labor together to build the new Christendom.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Beer and psalms, panel discussions, Cajun dancing, and more&hellip;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Go to TacticsCon.com to buy your tickets today AND use the coupon code &ldquo;FLFPUB&rdquo; to get 20$ off your ticket price. That&rsquo;s TacticsCon.com - and we&rsquo;ll see you in South Louisiana this January.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://thepostmillennial.com/72-of-canadians-want-trudeau-gone-poll?utm_campaign=64487"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://thepostmillennial.com/72-of-canadians-want-trudeau-gone-poll?utm_campaign=64487</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>72% of Canadians want Trudeau gone</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Canadian Prime Minister Justin Trudeau is in political free-fall.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">In the latest Ipsos poll, 72 percent of Canadians want Trudeau to exit federal politics and leave as leader of the Liberal Party of Canada.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Ipsos says that number is up from 60 percent in September. Even within his own party, 33 percent of Liberal supporters would like Trudeau to resign.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">That's consistent with other recent polls that show the Conservative Party of Canada, under its leader Pierre Poilievre, 19 percentage points ahead of the Liberals and headed for one of the larger majority governments in Canadian history.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Nanos Research founder Nik Nanos described what the Liberals need to stand a chance in the next federal election is a "complete reboot."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">"Either with a new leader or&hellip; Justin Trudeau with a renewed vision of why he believes that he should deserve another mandate," Nanos said in a recent episode of CTV News Trend Line.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Canadians have even taken to the internet to try to remove Trudeau from office through the traditional legislative process.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">As of Monday morning, more than 175,000 Canadians have signed a petition for a vote of non-confidence in the House of Commons against the minority Liberal government.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The petition is sponsored by MP Michelle Ferreri (CPC-Peterborough-Kawartha) and reads:</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&nbsp;"The policies of this government aren't aligning with the crisis Canada is facing: housing costs, infringement of civil liberties, highest inflation in history, unbalanced immigration policies, taxation to the point of poverty, weakening of our economy by importing natural resources that Canada already has and under-utilizes; and based on the past eight years of this Prime Minister, Canadians do not have confidence in this Prime Minister, after five ethics investigations and Canada's reputation being tarnished on a global scale under his leadership. To the extent that Canada is being discluded from participating in statements regarding important geopolitical events."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Sen. Percy Downe, a Liberal who was chief of staff to former Prime Minister Jean Chretien, recently wrote that it is time Trudeau left office.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Trudeau laughed off the appeal. There is considerable doubt that his departure would save the Liberals' fortunes in the next federal election.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Trudeau's father, Pierre Trudeau, who was prime minister of Canada from 1968-1984 with the exception of a nine-month period in 1979 when a minority Progressive Conservative government was in power, famously took "a walk in the snow" on Feb. 28, 1984 when he decided to leave politics.&nbsp;&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">He announced his resignation the following day, Feb. 29 &ndash; a date that only occurs on a leap year.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://www.foxnews.com/media/doctor-treating-freed-hamas-hostages-reveals-unprecedented-abuse-rewrite-textbooks"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.foxnews.com/media/doctor-treating-freed-hamas-hostages-reveals-unprecedented-abuse-rewrite-textbooks</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Doctor treating freed Hamas hostages reveals unprecedented abuse: 'We have to rewrite the textbooks'</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">A doctor treating freed Hamas hostages in Israel says survivors are suffering from an unprecedented level of "extremely severe psychological abuse" endured during captivity.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">"I can tell you that on behalf of all the medical and psychological teams treating those who return, the mental states we encountered have no precedent in medical literature. We feel that we have to rewrite the textbooks of post-trauma," Dr. Renana Eitan told "Sunday Night in America."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Eitan revealed the Tel Aviv Medical Center is actively treating more than 15 former hostages and described their "severe physical and mental abuse."</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">"Those held captive were subject to starvation, to beating, to sexual abuse. They were being held in inhumane sanitary conditions. Extremely severe psychological abuse was inflicted on them, including separation from family members, separation of siblings, separation of children from their mothers. They were held in solitary confinement and spent long days in total darkness until they developed severe hallucinations," Eitan claimed. "Children were forced to watch brutal videos. They were under constant threats by weapons and threats to harm them even after they were released. They refer to the forced use of psychiatric drugs and other substances."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Eitan also detailed cases where individuals, though appearing physically unharmed, are dealing with "severe post-traumatic symptoms."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">"Some of the home comers, they look happy, they look fine, they look physically fine, and we try to hold on to those optimistic signs, but still, even those who seem fine, we know that most of them [are] suffering from severe post-traumatic symptoms, they have painful, traumatic memories. And they are entering into dissociative states, where for a moment they feel as if they are still in captivity and only later do they return to the understanding that they have been released," she said.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">This week marks two months since the Hamas terror attack on Israel which left 1,200 dead and 240 held hostage. According to the Israeli Ministry of Health, 73 Israelis and 24 foreign citizens have been released from Hamas to date.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Eitan urged the release of the remaining hostages "as soon as possible" as they face a long road ahead of physical and mental rehabilitation.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://www.breitbart.com/2nd-amendment/2023/12/04/israeli-security-minister-we-are-approving-up-to-3000-gun-license-applications-day/"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.breitbart.com/2nd-amendment/2023/12/04/israeli-security-minister-we-are-approving-up-to-3000-gun-license-applications-day/</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Israeli Security Minister: We Are Approving &lsquo;Up to 3,000&rsquo; Gun License Applications A Day</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Israel Security Minister Itamar Ben Gvir says his ministry is now approving &ldquo;up to 3,000&rdquo; gun license applications a day.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The Times of Israel quoted Ben Gvir saying, &ldquo;When the war started, we knew that we were right when we said that every place that has a weapon can save a life.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">He went on to say, &ldquo;My policy within the office was to permit as many people as possible to get a weapon&hellip;[and] in a short period of time, we were giving up to 3,000 approvals a day.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Ben Gvir indicated over 260,000 gun license applications have been approved since October 7, 2023.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">On November 15, 2023, Breitbart News pointed to a Times of Israel report which indicated over 236,000 gun license applications had been filed in Israel at that point in time.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">In mid-November roughly 1,700 applications were being approved daily, and the number of daily approvals has nearly doubled since then.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Breitbart News noted that an armed civilian opened fire Thursday on terrorists who attacked a Jerusalem bus stop. Two off-duty soldiers opened fire as well and the terrorists were killed.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://thepostmillennial.com/arlington-home-explodes-after-suspect-sets-off-flares-as-police-serve-search-warrant?utm_campaign=64487"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://thepostmillennial.com/arlington-home-explodes-after-suspect-sets-off-flares-as-police-serve-search-warrant?utm_campaign=64487</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Arlington home explodes after suspect sets off flares as police serve search warrant</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">On Monday, a home in the Bluemont neighborhood of Arlington, Virginia exploded as police were attempting to serve a search warrant following reports that a flare gun had been fired from within earlier in the evening.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">While three members of law enforcement suffered minor injuries, the fate of the suspect, who is believed to have been in the home at the time, has not been revealed.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">According to the Arlington County Police Department, officers were called to a duplex on the 800 block of North Burlington Street around 4:45 pm to investigate reports that someone had "discharged a flare gun 30 - 40 times from inside his residence into the surrounding neighborhood."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">While his actions did not result in any injuries or property damage, officers nonetheless obtained a search warrant and tried to make contact with him via telephone and loudspeaker. Their attempts proved fruitless, and the suspect remained "barricaded" inside.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">At around 8:25 pm, he "discharged several rounds" from what authorities believe was a firearm, resulting in the aforementioned explosion. The blast sent shockwaves through the surrounding area as residents watched debris fly into the air and the structure burn to the ground.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The fire department arrived on the scene a short time later, and by 10:30 pm, the blaze was extinguished.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">While police have not released the name of the suspect, local outlet ARLNow has reported that public records show the resident of the now-leveled home to be a man named James Yoo.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">According to Newsweek, Yoo's social media posts were reportedly filled with rants about the government, the police, and his own neighbors, who he repeatedly labeled "spies," suggesting they had fake identities and were assigned to monitor him for their "handlers." His YouTube channel included videos with pictures from his LinkedIn page depicting people he claimed were his neighbors entering and leaving their homes, according to the outlet.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">One of Yoo's neighbors, Alex Wilson, told ARLNow that he kept to himself and often had his windows covered with aluminum foil. Yoo also allegedly chased away prospective buyers with a knife while his house was on the market.</span></p>]]></description>
   <author><![CDATA[Garrison Hardie]]></author>
   <enclosure url="https://app.dropwave.io/episode/d6574dcf-b79a-4017-b782-aeaf678a8d4c/daily-news-brief-for-wednesday-december-6th-2023.mp3" length="592" type="audio/mp3"/>
   <guid isPermaLink="false"><![CDATA[d6574dcf-b79a-4017-b782-aeaf678a8d4c]]></guid>
   <pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
   <source url=""><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></source>
   <itunes:author><![CDATA[Garrison Hardie]]></itunes:author>
   <itunes:image href="https://assets-cdn2.dropwave.io/2ab40ac0-e99d-4f25-a6d2-541d2c9b290a/cover-art/mUK8zsnHkCK3vep7E1W6UgYb9dTnLenASAMEFha3.jpg"/>
   <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
   <itunes:duration>592</itunes:duration>
   <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
  
  </item><item>
   <title><![CDATA[Daily News Brief for Tuesday, December 5th, 2023 [Daily News Brief]]]></title>
   <link/>
   <description><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">This is Garrison Hardie with your CrossPolitic Daily News Brief for Tuesday, December 5th, 2023.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>VanGelder Technologies:</strong></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">VanGelder Technologies is a US-based custom software development company specializing in cross-platform mobile applications, web applications, and desktop programs. Leveraging open-source frameworks, they quickly and efficiently build custom software solutions that are tailor made to fit your specific needs.   </span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">There&rsquo;s no need for New Christendom companies to be content with offering sub-par mobile or web experiences. VanGelder Technologies can help you build better software for the glory of God! You can learn more, view examples of their work, or get in touch, at www.vangelder.tech  </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">That&rsquo;s V-A-N, G-E-L, D-E-R dot T-E-C-H VanGelder Technologies, where technology and tradition meet.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://hotair.com/jazz-shaw/2023/12/04/congress-freezes-6-billion-for-iran-n596478#google_vignette"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://hotair.com/jazz-shaw/2023/12/04/congress-freezes-6-billion-for-iran-n596478#google_vignette</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Congress Freezes $6 Billion for Iran</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">This took place on Thursday, but it&rsquo;s looking increasingly real. In a move that the Daily Mail described as &ldquo;humiliating&rdquo; for Joe Biden, lawmakers cast a bipartisan vote to freeze the six billion dollars that the President had previously freed up for Iran as part of his hostage negotiation deal. The move drew the support of nearly every Republican but also attracted nearly 100 Democrats. Now it&rsquo;s looking as if it might pass in the Senate as well. During a time when it&rsquo;s been seeming as if common sense had been banned in Washington, we have lawmakers seemingly conceding that sending billions of dollars to the world&rsquo;s largest state sponsor of terrorism might not be such a great idea.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">President Biden is facing a humiliating foreign policy setback as $6 billion he used to leverage the release of five imprisoned Americans from Iran could be frozen.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Lawmakers including members of Biden&rsquo;s own party voted on Thursday to approve a bill that would permanently freeze the funds, which were unfrozen by the White House in September as part of a controversial deal.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The bill, named the No Funds for Iranian Terrorism Act, passed in a 307 to 119 vote &ndash; which was approved by almost every Republican and 90 Democrats.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The money is being held in Qatar, where most negotiations between the West and terror groups take place these days. The reality is that Joe Biden had already &ldquo;refrozen&rdquo; the money after the October 7 Hamas terror attacks. Congress is now close to locking the door to those funds indefinitely.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Keep in mind that the money was originally leveraged to free five American hostages as well as five Iranian prisoners. But before the cash transfer was even complete, an even larger number of Americans were taken hostage by Hamas, which is almost entirely funded by Iran. In that sense, the United States was losing ground in the exchange, rather than getting something of value for the money.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Plenty of people were warning the Biden administration about this when the talks first began. This is why we&rsquo;ve long had a rule about not negotiating with terrorists. If you pay to secure the release of hostages, you will inevitably wind up with more hostages because the terrorists see that their tactics are working. And that&rsquo;s precisely where we are today.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://www.dailyfetched.com/blm-rioters-in-atlanta-who-burnt-down-wendys-get-500-fine/"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.dailyfetched.com/blm-rioters-in-atlanta-who-burnt-down-wendys-get-500-fine/</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>BLM Rioters in Atlanta Who Burnt Down Wendy&rsquo;s Get $500 Fine</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Two Black Lives Matter (BLM) rioters who pleaded guilty to torching Wendy&rsquo;s fast food restaurant in Atlanta in 2020 were sentenced to five years of probation and a $500 fine.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Chisom Kingston and Natalie White were charged with conspiracy to commit arson in the first degree, and two counts of first-degree arson.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Both pleaded guilty in a plea deal, according to court records.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Kingston and White must complete 150 hours of community service.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">In addition to charges, John Wesley Wade, 35, was indicted for the same fire in January this year.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Initially, all three pleaded not guilty and waived their arraignments in March 2022,</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The charges stem from BLM riots, which took place over the death of Rayshard Brooks, who was killed in a police-involved shooting in June 2020.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Brooks allegedly punched police officer David Brosnan and stole his taser while under investigation for a DUI in the parking lot of the Wendy&rsquo;s restaurant.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Brooks reportedly aimed the Taser at Officer Brosnan.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">However, a second officer, Garrett Rolfe, shot and killed rooks during the altercation.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Brooks allegedly punched Brosnan, causing a concussion.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">In response to the incident, BLM rioters burnt down Wendy&rsquo;s in protest of Brooks&rsquo; death.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Later, violent demonstrations exploded over the city in the months following.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Former Fulton County District Attorney charged officers Rolfe and Brosnan.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Brosnan was charged with aggravated assault, while Rolfe faces felony murder and assault charges.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Ninety-nine percent of charges brought against BLM rioters in 2020 were dropped by local prosecutors, according to an analysis from The Guardian.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Earlier this year, the United States Court of Appeals in Washington, DC, admitted that BLM rioters were treated better compared to some pro-life protesters.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The news comes just under a month after New York City officials agreed to pay $13 million to violent &ldquo;2020 Summer of Love&rdquo; BLM and Antifa protesters after they caused damage to 45 businesses.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://www.foxnews.com/us/derek-chauvin-returns-prison-after-alleged-blm-inspired-stabbing"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.foxnews.com/us/derek-chauvin-returns-prison-after-alleged-blm-inspired-stabbing</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Derek Chauvin returns to prison after alleged BLM-inspired stabbing</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Former Minneapolis police officer Derek Chauvin has returned to a federal prison in Arizona more than a week after a fellow inmate allegedly stabbed him 22 times with a shank in the library in a Black Friday attack partially inspired by the Black Lives Matter movement.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Chauvin is serving more than 20 years for the death of George Floyd and for depriving him of his civil rights in a May 2020 encounter that kicked off nationwide protests.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Chauvin's family is "very concerned about the facility&rsquo;s capacity to protect Derek from further harm," his lawyer, Greg Erickson, told the Minneapolis Star Tribune. "They remain unassured that any changes have been made to the faulty procedures that allowed Derek&rsquo;s attack to occur in the first place."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">John Turscak, 52, allegedly told federal correction officers that he targeted Chauvin because he was a high-profile inmate, that he plotted the attack for a month and that he would have killed him if guards had not intervened, according to court documents.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Turscak could see 60 years added to his federal sentence if he gets the maximum punishment on the four new charges he faces, which includes attempted murder. He was due for release in 2026, according to the Bureau of Prisons.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Turscak, a former gang member and snitch, was dropped as an FBI informant for dealing drugs, greenlighting assaults and extorting money, according to prosecutors.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">He allegedly told investigators that he picked Black Friday for the attack to symbolize both BLM and the "Black Hand" of the Mexican Mafia prison gang.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The attack took place from behind in the law library inside Federal Correctional Institution Tucson on Nov. 24.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Authorities said guards intervened "immediately," but Erickson questioned how fast the response really was &ndash; noting Chauvin's 22 stab wounds.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">"Why was Derek allowed into the law library without a guard in close enough proximity to stop a possible attack?" he asked. "His family continues to wonder."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Prison experts have warned that Chauvin, like other high-profile inmates, is at increased risk.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">"He was a dead man walking his first day in prison," said Keith Rovere, a former prison minister and the host of the "Lighter Side of Serial Killers" podcast. "This definitely won't be the last attack."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">In an appeal filed last month, Chauvin claimed new evidence shows he was not responsible for the death. Separately, the Supreme Court rejected his appeal for a new trial just days before the stabbing.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Chauvin was one of four officers who arrested Floyd that day after he allegedly passed a counterfeit $20 bill at a coffee shop and refused to cooperate with police.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Chauvin, who was seen on a video that prompted riots around the country, knelt on Floyd's neck for more than nine minutes leading up to his death.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Erickson previously slammed the prison for "poor procedures and lack of institutional control" &ndash; referencing an incident last year in which an inmate allegedly smuggled a firearm into the facility and tried to shoot someone.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Prison officials said they "[take] seriously our duty to protect the individuals entrusted in our custody, as well as maintain the safety of correctional employees and the community."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Citing privacy and safety concerns, authorities said they do not discuss the medical status or other "conditions of confinement" for inmates.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://www.worldofreel.com/blog/2023/12/1/hb03oy7zedb5m0rhj557tbnr6znepm"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.worldofreel.com/blog/2023/12/1/hb03oy7zedb5m0rhj557tbnr6znepm</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Raves for &lsquo;Godzilla Minus One&rsquo;</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Who&rsquo;s seen Toho&rsquo;s &ldquo;Godzilla Minus One&rdquo;? The reviews are almost all glowing. Unless I somehow missed my invitation, I don&rsquo;t believe there was a press screening for this one. Regardless, it made $11 million domestically this weekend, a real success.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&ldquo;Godzilla Minus One&rdquo; has a 97% (8.2/10) with critics, from 75 reviews. On Metacritic it&rsquo;s scoring a very strong 79/100 from 24 reviews. On IMDB, it has an impressive 8.5 user rating.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The film takes place in a devastated post-war Japan where Godzilla goes on a rampage. This is the second of the live-action Reiwa era &lsquo;Godzilla&rsquo; films, the first being 2016&rsquo;s &ldquo;Shin Godzilla&rdquo;. It looks as though director Takashi Yamazaki has made one of the better films of the franchise.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">This is the 37th film in the &lsquo;Godzilla&rsquo; franchise, and Toho's 33rd Godzilla film.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>It&rsquo;s been awhile guys&hellip; how about a little on this day in history?&nbsp;</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">On this day December 5th</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">771 Charlemagne becomes the sole King of the Franks after the death of his brother Carloman</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">1848 US President James K. Polk triggers gold rush of 1849 by confirming a gold discovery in California</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">1933 Prohibition ends in the US when 21st Amendment to the US Constitution ratified, 18th Amendment repealed (5:32 PM EST)</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">1973 Apple Records releases Paul McCartney &amp; Wings album "Band on the Run" in US; the commercial and critical pinnacle of his post-Beatle work tops the charts in 7 countries</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">2001 "Ocean's Eleven" directed by Steven Soderbergh, starring George Clooney, Brad Pitt, Matt Damon and Julia Roberts premieres in Westwood, California</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">2017 Russia is banned from the next Winter Olympics in South Korea over state-sponsored doping</span></li>
</ul>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Did you know? Ship the Mary Celeste is discovered mysteriously abandoned by her crew in the Atlantic Ocean on December 5th, 1872?&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">On November 7, 1872, the Mary Celeste set sail from New York City, with more than 1,700 barrels of alcohol destined for Genoa, Italy. On board were 10 people, including Captain Briggs, his wife, and their two-year-old daughter. Over the next two weeks, the ship encountered harsh weather. According to the last log entry&mdash;dated November 25&mdash;the Mary Celeste was some 6 nautical miles (11 km) from the Azores. Ten days later, December 5th, the vessel was spotted by the British brig Dei Gratia. Crew from that ship boarded the Mary Celeste and discovered it deserted. Although there was more than 3 feet (1 metre) of water in the hold&mdash;an amount that would not have caused panic&mdash;the vessel was seaworthy. Adding to the mystery was the fact that the cargo and personal belongings were largely undisturbed, although a longboat was missing. It appeared that the ship had been abandoned quickly. Crewmen from the Dei Gratia sailed the Mary Celeste to Gibraltar, some 800 miles (1,482 km) away. There British authorities conducted an investigation, which ultimately found no evidence of foul play.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">How about some famous birthdays for December 5th?</span></p>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Martin Van Buren was born on December 5th - 1782</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">George Armstrong Custer - 1839</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Walt Disney - 1901</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Little Richard - 1932</span></li>
</ul>]]></description>
   <author><![CDATA[Garrison Hardie]]></author>
   <enclosure url="https://app.dropwave.io/episode/9becad44-c74d-43be-ab58-78eeb4540012/daily-news-brief-for-tuesday-december-5th-2023.mp3" length="789" type="audio/mp3"/>
   <guid isPermaLink="false"><![CDATA[9becad44-c74d-43be-ab58-78eeb4540012]]></guid>
   <pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
   <source url=""><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></source>
   <itunes:author><![CDATA[Garrison Hardie]]></itunes:author>
   <itunes:image href="https://assets-cdn2.dropwave.io/2ab40ac0-e99d-4f25-a6d2-541d2c9b290a/cover-art/mUK8zsnHkCK3vep7E1W6UgYb9dTnLenASAMEFha3.jpg"/>
   <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
   <itunes:duration>789</itunes:duration>
   <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
  
  </item>
 </channel>
</rss>
