<?xml version="1.0"?>
<?xml-stylesheet href="/storage/feed-stylesheet.xsl" type="text/xsl"?>

<rss xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
 <channel>
  <title>FLF - Daily News Brief</title>
  <link>https://dropwave.io</link>
  <description><![CDATA[FIGHT LAUGH FEAST PRESENTS SHOWS PROCLAIMING THE LORDSHIP OF CHRIST OVER ALL OF LIFE.
]]></description>
  <language>en</language>
  <managingEditor><![CDATA[fightlaughfeast@gmail.com (FLF, LLC)]]></managingEditor>
  <webMaster><![CDATA[support@dropwave.io (DropWave Support)]]></webMaster>
  <pubDate>Fri, 19 Jan 2024 01:25:47 +0000</pubDate>
  <lastBuildDate>Fri, 19 Jan 2024 01:25:47 +0000</lastBuildDate>
  <image>
   <url>https://is4-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Podcasts113/v4/58/56/52/5856525c-2973-cf29-3db9-21faa8595391/mza_1144696925612154085.png/1200x1200bb.jpg</url>
   <link>https://dropwave.io</link>
   <title><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></title>
  </image>
  <itunes:author><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></itunes:author>
  <itunes:image href="https://is4-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Podcasts113/v4/58/56/52/5856525c-2973-cf29-3db9-21faa8595391/mza_1144696925612154085.png/1200x1200bb.jpg"/>
  <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
  <itunes:owner>
   <itunes:name><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></itunes:name>
   <itunes:email>fightlaughfeast@gmail.com</itunes:email>
  </itunes:owner>
  <itunes:category text="News"/>
  <item>
   <title><![CDATA[Daily News Brief for Thursday, January 18th, 2024 [Daily News Brief]]]></title>
   <link/>
   <description><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">This is Garrison Hardie with your CrossPolitic Daily News Brief for Thursday, January 18th, 2024.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>VanGelder Technologies:</strong></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">VanGelder Technologies is a US-based custom software development company specializing in cross-platform mobile applications, web applications, and desktop programs. Leveraging open-source frameworks, they quickly and efficiently build custom software solutions that are tailor made to fit your specific needs.   </span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">There&rsquo;s no need for New Christendom companies to be content with offering sub-par mobile or web experiences. VanGelder Technologies can help you build better software for the glory of God! You can learn more, view examples of their work, or get in touch, at www.vangelder.tech  </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">That&rsquo;s V-A-N, G-E-L, D-E-R dot T-E-C-H VanGelder Technologies, where technology and tradition meet.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://redstate.com/nick-arama/2024/01/17/tucker-decimates-nikki-haley-n2168832"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://redstate.com/nick-arama/2024/01/17/tucker-decimates-nikki-haley-n2168832</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Tucker Carlson Takes Down Nikki Haley With Brutal Video</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">In the wake of the Iowa caucuses, there are a lot of interesting reactions including those who believe that President Donald Trump is now the likely nominee, like Vivek Ramaswamy and Sen. Ted Cruz (R-TX), who both endorsed Trump.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Vivek even went on the road with him to New Hampshire to encourage people to vote for him.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Tucker Carlson, who is supportive of Trump, noted that Trump's win was historic, but the media was dealing with it with some pretty hilarious reactions - with Chris Wallace looking "sick" and Joy Reid blaming "white Christians" in Iowa and calling them racist.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">They were very upset, he observed.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">But he warned that Haley might do better in New Hampshire, that she had been spending far more money than Florida Gov. Ron DeSantis there. She also has the support of N.H. Gov. Chris Sununu.&nbsp; He said a lot of Haley's money came from "committed Democratic partisans." She's gotten money from people like Democratic megadonor Reid Hoffman, who has been a supporter of Joe Biden, a friend of Jeffrey Epstein, and the guy who funded the E. Jean Carroll lawsuit.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://twitter.com/i/status/1747274232093110614"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://twitter.com/i/status/1747274232093110614</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> - Play 4:48-9:03</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Never change Tucker&hellip;as always, you can find the link to Tucker&rsquo;s video in my show notes.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://www.dailywire.com/news/federal-government-to-spend-700k-on-trans-inclusive-sex-ed-for-14-year-olds"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.dailywire.com/news/federal-government-to-spend-700k-on-trans-inclusive-sex-ed-for-14-year-olds</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Federal Government To Spend $700k On Trans-Inclusive Sex Ed For 14-Year-Olds</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The Department of Health and Human Services (HHS) is awarding nearly $700,000 taxpayer dollars to back pregnancy prevention programs for young girls who identify as boys, warning that &ldquo;heteronormative&rdquo; sexual education is inadequate.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The $698,736 grant, which began in September 2023 and will continue until June 2027, according to government disclosures, will be allocated to the Center for Innovative Public Health Research, a non-profit that seeks to create &ldquo;an inclusive teen pregnancy program for transgender boys.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&ldquo;Youth who are assigned female at birth &hellip; are at risk for negative sexual health outcomes yet are effectively excluded from sexual health programs because gender-diverse youth do not experience the cisgender, heteronormative teen sexual education messaging available to them as salient or applicable,&rdquo; the award description claims.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The Center for Innovative Public Health Research aims to provide sex education via a program called &ldquo;Girl2Girl,&rdquo; which the organization describes as &ldquo;a text messaging based-sexual health program designed for cisgender sexual minority girls 14-18 years of age.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The center will then &ldquo;test the resulting adaptation&rdquo; in a national cohort of &ldquo;700 trans-identified AFAB youth 14-18 years of age,&rdquo; measuring their use of contraception and testing for sexually transmitted diseases, as well as pregnancy rates.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The funding from the HHS specifically comes from the National Institutes of Health&rsquo;s National Institute of Nursing Research. The National Institute of Nursing Research was given authority to spend a total of $57 million taxpayer dollars in fiscal year 2024.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The Center for Innovative Public Health Research is slated to receive another $1.4 million taxpayer dollars from HHS to develop a &ldquo;population-based HIV prevention program for trans girls,&rdquo; specifying that the program will &ldquo;address the lack of gender inclusive HIV prevention programming.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&ldquo;Messaging will be gender affirming&rdquo; and will &ldquo;reduce internalized transphobia,&rdquo; the award description adds.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">But the award for nearly $700,000 taxpayer dollars is not the only action that the HHS has taken to push transgenderism. The Daily Wire previously revealed that the National Institutes of Health (NIH), a subagency of the HHS, funded a study on the use of puberty blockers and cross-sex hormone treatment to the tune of $3 million despite transgender children&rsquo;s hospitals admitting that the practice could result in permanent sterilization.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://thepostmillennial.com/exclusive-maine-moves-to-create-sanctuary-state-for-child-sex-changes?utm_campaign=64487"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://thepostmillennial.com/exclusive-maine-moves-to-create-sanctuary-state-for-child-sex-changes?utm_campaign=64487</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Maine moves to create 'sanctuary state' for child sex changes</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">A Maine judiciary committee will decide on Wednesday morning whether a bill permitting minors to travel to the state to seek sex changes and granting the state custody over children will move to the floor.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">LD1735, also called An Act to Safeguard Gender-affirming Health Care, was introduced to the House of Representatives in the state in April of 2023 by Rep. Laurie Osher of Orono, and is cosponsored by Reps Erin Sheehan of Biddeford, Nina Milliken of Blue Hill, Suzanne Salisbury of Westbrook, Mark Worth of Ellsworth, and Rep. Matt Moonen of Portland as well as Senator Anne Carney of Cumberland.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Courage is a Habit, a group fighting for parental rights in states across the nation, is leading an effort to stop this bill.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Alvin Lui, president of Courage is a Habit, told The Post Millennial that people who do not live in Maine should contact the committee members as well as Maine residents as the bill "affects everybody&rsquo;s parental rights."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Sample emails provided by the group tell the members that "There is a lack of long-term studies on the benefits of 'gender-affirming care,&rsquo; which could result in the life-long sterilization and surgical mutilation of children," "With lawsuits against hospitals and schools on the rise in 2023, the public is becoming more aware of the potential risks associated with this bill," and "Protecting parental rights and the well-being of children should be our top priority. I urge you to vote "ought not to pass" on LD 1735."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">LD 1735 "prohibits the enforcement of an order based on another state's law authorizing a child to be removed from the child's parent or guardian based on that parent or guardian allowing the child to receive gender-affirming health care or gender-affirming mental health care."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">A law enforcement agency would be prohibited from knowingly making or participating in the arrest or extradition of an individual on an out-of-state warrant for violating another state&rsquo;s laws on bringing a child to Maine to give sex change treatments.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The bill updates rules on abandonment of a child or emergency situations, granting the State temporary emergency jurisdiction over the child if the child "has been unable to obtain gender-affirming health care or gender-affirming mental health care" because of a parent or guardian.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The bill also prevents courts from finding a case was brought forth in an "inconvenient forum," or the wrong court, "if the law or policy of another state that may take jurisdiction limits the ability of a parent to obtain gender-affirming health care or gender-affirming mental health care for a child and the provision of that care is at issue in the case before the court."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">LD1735 "prohibits a court from considering the taking or retention of a child from a person who has legal custody of the child if the taking or retention was for obtaining gender-affirming health care or gender-affirming mental health care for the child."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The bill mirrors similar laws passed in California, New Jersey, New York, Oregon, Washington and Minnesota.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Lui told The Post Millennial, "refuse to let your kindness be weaponized against you."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">"If you're wondering how you got there in Maine, wherever you live ... it's because over time, you've allowed your kindness to be weaponized against you and they kept moving that goalpost and now, even when they're proposing a transgender trafficking bill, they're still using emotional blackmail to try to get you to accept this," he said.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Lui said that "they&rsquo;re quite literally opening up trafficking avenues by inviting children from other states where their parents do not agree to transgender sterilization drugs and mutilating surgeries, and they're going to welcome these kids in Maine using your taxpayer dollars through Medicaid to pay for these procedures, putting them in foster care, opening them up to vulnerabilities like sex trafficking, like abuse, not to mention the lifelong, irreversible procedures and drugs that the transgender&nbsp; cult promotes."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">"So there is no slippery slope. You're here at the bottom now because they're willing to remove kids from parents, and the next step will be to remove your children from your home in Maine," Lui added, noting the instance of California.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://www.theblaze.com/news/teacher-of-the-year-says-he-was-reassigned-for-3-months-after-too-harshly-stopping-2-male-students-from-attacking-female"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.theblaze.com/news/teacher-of-the-year-says-he-was-reassigned-for-3-months-after-too-harshly-stopping-2-male-students-from-attacking-female</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Teacher of the Year says he was reassigned for 3 months after 'too harshly' stopping 2 male students from attacking female</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Kumar Rashad &mdash; who was named the Kentucky Department of Education's Teacher of the Year in September &mdash; told WDRB-TV that in October he was reassigned for three months after "too harshly" stopping two male students from attacking a female student.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">A math teacher in Louisville's Breckinridge Metropolitan High School, Rashad told the station after the incident officials reassigned him to "non-instructional duties" at the Special Needs East Bus Compound.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">WDRB said Jefferson County Public Schools wouldn't say why Rashad was reassigned &mdash; but he gave his side of the story Thursday, one day before he began resuming his teaching duties.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">"I saw two males attack a female, and I went to the female's rescue, and I removed the two students off of that female," Rashad told the station. "The two students said I removed them too harshly."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Rashad noted to WLKY-TV that the two male students complained about him to the powers that be.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">He was not about to apologize, however, telling WLKY: "Please understand, in the community, in school, anywhere I am going, I will never allow a lady to be attacked by a male."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://youtu.be/bJoR4AeYyFc"><span style="font-weight: 400;" data-rich-links="{&quot;fple-t&quot;:&quot;Kentucky's 2024 Teacher of the Year reinstated by JCPS, says he was reassigned for breaking up fight&quot;,&quot;fple-u&quot;:&quot;https://youtu.be/bJoR4AeYyFc&quot;,&quot;fple-mt&quot;:null,&quot;type&quot;:&quot;first-party-link&quot;}">Kentucky's 2024 Teacher of the Year reinstated by JCPS, says he was reassigned for breaking up fight</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;">-Play 0:30-0:49</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Rashad added to WDRB that the investigation is over, and he was cleared to return Friday to the classroom &mdash; which the school district confirmed.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://www.breitbart.com/politics/2024/01/16/here-we-go-wef-hosts-panel-tomorrow-for-disease-x/"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.breitbart.com/politics/2024/01/16/here-we-go-wef-hosts-panel-tomorrow-for-disease-x/</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>WEF Hosts Panel Tomorrow for &lsquo;Disease X&rsquo;</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Klaus Schwab, the World Economic Forum (WEF), and the so-called global elites are gathering for a five-day annual meeting in Davos, Switzerland, from January 15-19. One of the topics on the agenda for January 17 has raised some eyeballs: &ldquo;Preparing for Disease X.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">COVID has been reported to have claimed approximately 7 million lives worldwide, but &ldquo;Disease X,&rdquo; on the other hand, they warn, &ldquo;could result in 20 times more fatalities than the coronavirus pandemic.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Something interesting about people in power is that a not insignificant number of them also happen to believe that the world is overpopulated. If a pandemic 20 times as deadly as COVID did happen, claiming 140 million lives, would global leaders mourn or secretly celebrate that the world&rsquo;s population was curbed?</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Yuval Noah Harari, one of Barack Obama&rsquo;s favorite authors and a frequent speaker at Davos, has said that &ldquo;the big political and economic question of the 21st century will be, &lsquo;What do we need humans for?&rsquo; or at least, &lsquo;What do we need so many humans for?&rsquo;&rdquo;</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Remember, in October 2019 &mdash; just months before COVID-19 was identified in Wuhan &mdash; The Johns Hopkins Center for Health Security in partnership with the WEF and the Bill and Melinda Gates Foundation hosted Event 201, described as &ldquo;a high-level pandemic exercise.&rdquo; Is it out of the question to think another so-called pandemic could be just around the corner?</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Doctors like Peter McCullough and James Thorp stress the importance of being prepared and having life-saving medications on hand for whatever emergency &mdash; pandemic or not &mdash; life throws at you next.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&ldquo;You&rsquo;ve seen all the threats from the establishment suggesting that there&rsquo;s not going to be drug availability in the not-too-distant future,&rdquo; obstetrician-gynecologist and maternal-fetal medicine specialist Dr. James Thorp warns. &ldquo;They tell us &mdash; they&rsquo;re threatening us that there&rsquo;s another pandemic coming. So, look at that and protect yourselves.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">So, what should we be doing?</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&ldquo;Stocking up,&rdquo; urged Dr. Thorp. &ldquo;I&rsquo;ve been doing this since 1995 &mdash; always stocking up I&rsquo;ve been doing that for 20 years, and trust me, even before the pandemic, it saved a lot of my patients and family members because when they need the drugs, they can&rsquo;t get them.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The Wellness Company has put together a Medical Emergency Kit of eight potentially life-saving medications, which includes Ivermectin and Z-Pak, for the treatment of a range of illnesses, including strep throat, pneumonia, COVID-19, nausea and vomiting, and more.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The full list is linked in the article in my show notes.&nbsp;</span></p>]]></description>
   <author><![CDATA[Garrison Hardie]]></author>
   <enclosure url="https://app.dropwave.io/episode/1f43437d-9ebe-432b-9688-8c855bfc0027/daily-news-brief-for-thursday-january-18th-2024.mp3" length="815" type="audio/mp3"/>
   <guid isPermaLink="false"><![CDATA[1f43437d-9ebe-432b-9688-8c855bfc0027]]></guid>
   <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jan 2024 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
   <source url=""><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></source>
   <itunes:author><![CDATA[Garrison Hardie]]></itunes:author>
   <itunes:image href="https://assets-cdn2.dropwave.io/2ab40ac0-e99d-4f25-a6d2-541d2c9b290a/cover-art/mUK8zsnHkCK3vep7E1W6UgYb9dTnLenASAMEFha3.jpg"/>
   <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
   <itunes:duration>815</itunes:duration>
   <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
  
  </item><item>
   <title><![CDATA[Daily News Brief for Wednesday, January 17th, 2024 [Daily News Brief]]]></title>
   <link/>
   <description><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">This is Garrison Hardie with your CrossPolitic Daily News Brief for Wednesday, January 17th, 2024.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>CrossPolitic Email List:</strong></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Are you subscribed to our CrossPolitic email list? If you&rsquo;re not you really should be. Being subscribed to our email list means you won&rsquo;t miss any updates about CrossPolitic or the Fight Laugh Feast Network! You&rsquo;ll hear about what&rsquo;s on the schedule for the week, live events, conference updates, Rowdy Christian Merch, updates from other shows within the Fight Laugh Feast Network, and you&rsquo;ll hear from sponsors on the show, as they seek to take dominion for God&rsquo;s Kingdom in the business world. To subscribe, simply enter your email address at the bottom of the page at fightlaughfeast.com. Again, that&rsquo;s fightlaughfeast.com.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://www.foxnews.com/politics/trump-narrowly-denied-clean-sweep-iowas-99-counties-1-vote"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.foxnews.com/politics/trump-narrowly-denied-clean-sweep-iowas-99-counties-1-vote</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Trump narrowly denied clean sweep of Iowa's 99 counties by 1 vote</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Former President Donald Trump won 98 out of 99 Iowa counties during Monday's dominating victory in the Republican caucuses.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The one county that did not go for Trump was Johnson County, where former South Carolina Gov. Nikki Haley led Trump by one vote with 99% of votes counted. Haley received 1,271 votes, approximately 35.5% of the vote in Johnson County, while Trump received 1,270 votes, according to GOP officials in the state.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Haley finished third statewide behind Florida Gov. Ron DeSantis. Trump pulled in a majority of votes with 51%.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Haley claimed her third-place finish was evidence of momentum when considering polling numbers in upcoming primary states.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">"When you look at how well we&rsquo;re doing in New Hampshire, in South Carolina and beyond, I can safely say tonight Iowa made this Republican primary a two-person race," Haley said.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">DeSantis visited every county and invested significant time and resources in the Hawkeye State, and weeks ago was predicting he would win the caucuses. Recently he had been saying he embraced the underdog role in the state.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">"Because of your support, in spite of all of what they threw at us, we got our ticket punched out of Iowa," DeSantis said in his speech.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">DeSantis outperformed some polling expectations on Monday night, finishing at roughly 21% when the Real Clear Politics average of polls showed him at 15.7% before votes were cast.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">"They threw everything at Ron DeSantis," a senior DeSantis campaign official told Fox News Digital late Monday night. "They couldn&rsquo;t kill him. He is not only still standing, but he&rsquo;s now earned his ticket out of Iowa. This is going to be a long battle ahead, but that is what this campaign is built for. The stakes are too high for this nation and we will not back down."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Trump currently holds large leads in the polls in both New Hampshire and South Carolina. The former president, according to the Real Clear Politics average of polls, holds a 14-point lead in New Hampshire and a 30-point lead in South Carolina.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2024/01/16/nikki-haley-refuses-more-presidential-debates-unless-trump-participates.html"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.cnbc.com/2024/01/16/nikki-haley-refuses-more-presidential-debates-unless-trump-participates.html</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Nikki Haley refuses more presidential debates unless Trump participates</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Nikki Haley said she would not participate in any further primary debates unless front-runner Donald Trump is on stage.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The former president won a landslide victory Monday in the Iowa Caucus, the first contest of the 2024 presidential nomination. Haley placed third in Iowa, with 19.1% of the vote.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Florida Gov. Ron DeSantis accused Haley of not wanting to answer &ldquo;tough questions&rdquo; on topics such as her alleged dealings with aircraft manufacturer Boeing while she was governor of South Carolina.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&ldquo;The reality is that she is not running for the nomination, she&rsquo;s running to be Trump&rsquo;s VP,&rdquo; DeSantis posted to X, formerly known as Twitter, on Tuesday. &ldquo;I won&rsquo;t snub New Hampshire voters like both Nikki Haley and Donald Trump, and plan to honor my commitments. I look forward to debating two empty podiums in the Granite State this week.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The next GOP primary debate is scheduled for Thursday, days before the New Hampshire primary on Jan. 23. Polls have Haley running just behind Trump in the state, some polls by as little as 7 points.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://redstate.com/jenvanlaar/2024/01/15/watch-vivek-ramaswamy-addresses-supporters-in-iowa-n2168776"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://redstate.com/jenvanlaar/2024/01/15/watch-vivek-ramaswamy-addresses-supporters-in-iowa-n2168776</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Vivek Ramaswamy Suspends Presidential Campaign, Endorses Donald Trump</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Presidential candidate Vivek Ramaswamy, fresh off a 4th-place finish in Iowa, addressed his supporters and announced that he is suspending his campaign.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Ramaswamy spoke for just about 10 minutes before taking questions/comments from supporters. He told his supporters that he'd promised them he would tell the truth and be realistic, and that acknowledging hard truths required him to say that there was no path for him to be the nominee. He told his supporters that he is committed to America First principles and that Trump is the candidate who will do things like get rid of the deep state, restore national pride, and eliminate a chunk of federal bureaucracy.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">He ended his comments by assuring supporters that this is just the start of their movement.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://thepostmillennial.com/nypd-stop-man-for-smoking-in-subway-then-arrest-him-on-murder-charges-from-2020?utm_campaign=64487"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://thepostmillennial.com/nypd-stop-man-for-smoking-in-subway-then-arrest-him-on-murder-charges-from-2020?utm_campaign=64487</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>NYPD stop man for smoking in subway&mdash;then arrest him on murder charges from 2020</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">A man was arrested for an alleged murder that took place in Queens in 2020 after he was stopped by the New York Police Department for smoking in the subway.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Brooklyn transit cops stopped the 36-year-old Luis Hernandez after he was seen smoking on the subway on Friday. Under normal circumstances, Hernandez would have been released with a simple court summons, but he was held up after officers scanned his name and found out he was wanted for murder, Daily News reports.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Police took Hernandez to Queens and showed him video and photos showing him at a murder scene on 31st St. near 36th Ave. in Astoria, according to authorities.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Police say Hernandez and three or four others took part in the murder of Richard Hernandez, 21 on Feb. 9, 2020.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&ldquo;Mr. Hernandez has pleaded not guilty and fully intends on fighting the charges against him,&rdquo; his attorney, Mahmoud Rabah, told the Daily News on Monday.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&ldquo;Mr. Hernandez is a committed father of a young child,&rdquo; Rabah claimed. &ldquo;He is a hardworking immigrant who has held a stable job in a meat processing plant for years. He completely maintains his innocence and looks forward to his day in court.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Hernandez has no prior arrests and was arraigned in Queens Criminal Court on Sunday.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The victim, who is not related to Luis, was out with friends when a fight erupted. Witnesses told the Daily News that at least one attacker was armed with a machete, and another a knife. The victim was slain just a few blocks away from where he lived, and ultimately could not be saved after being taken to Mount Sinai Queens. Three other men sustained minor wounds during the brawl, police reported at the time.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Police said on Monday that the attack was linked to gang activity. Authorities remain in pursuit of Hernandez's accomplices.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://notthebee.com/article/coming-soon-someone-made-a-video-showing-what-your-flights-will-look-like-in-our-very-progressive-future"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://notthebee.com/article/coming-soon-someone-made-a-video-showing-what-your-flights-will-look-like-in-our-very-progressive-future</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>"Coming soon": Someone made a parody showing what flights will look like in our progressive future</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Ah, Diversity, Equity, and Inclusion. It's to die for.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://twitter.com/i/status/1747091085736730872"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://twitter.com/i/status/1747091085736730872</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> - Play Video&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Here you thought Final Destination was just a work of fiction! If you want to watch the video rather than just hearing it, you can do so by finding the link in my show notes&hellip;&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://www.breitbart.com/sports/2024/01/14/oh-hes-pssed-the-internet-reacts-to-jerry-jones-visible-anger-after-cowboys-humiliating-loss-to-green-bay/"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.breitbart.com/sports/2024/01/14/oh-hes-pssed-the-internet-reacts-to-jerry-jones-visible-anger-after-cowboys-humiliating-loss-to-green-bay/</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Jerry Jones&rsquo; Visible Anger After Cowboys Humiliating Loss to Green Bay</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">As expected, the Cowboys-Packers game was a blowout. Unexpectedly, it was the Cowboys who got blown out.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The Packers raced to a 27-7 halftime via a fast-paced, deep-ball attacking offense complimented by an explosive running game from Aaron Jones and aided by two interceptions from a defense that seemed determined to make everyone forget about their late-season struggles.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Trailing 48-16 with less than six minutes to go, the Cowboys flurried for two scores to make things look more respectable. But, while things may have looked better on the scoreboard, judging by the expression on Cowboys Owner Jerry Jones&rsquo; face, it didn&rsquo;t really help matters.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Nor did things look any better when Jones walked towards the locker room with his entourage.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Jones&rsquo; words couldn&rsquo;t have been very consoling to head coach Mike McCarthy or QB Dak Prescott, and just a quick warning, there&rsquo;s a little language involved.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://twitter.com/i/status/1746662526643782140"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://twitter.com/i/status/1746662526643782140</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> - Play Video&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Oh I&rsquo;m sorry - what he actually said was:&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&ldquo;I say this to our fans, how much you deserve us not to have this ending,&rdquo; Jones told reporters immediately after the loss. &ldquo;In no way have I spent any of my time over the last three hours asking how and why. And what I&rsquo;m zeroed in on is the fact that I thought we were positioned, everybody in this room thought [we] were in a position, to advance this thing in the playoffs and maybe get as far as our dreams might take us. We didn&rsquo;t do it.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p><br /><br /></p>]]></description>
   <author><![CDATA[Garrison Hardie]]></author>
   <enclosure url="https://app.dropwave.io/episode/8371fe62-0b65-4fca-8e7d-0f1ed63efe6d/daily-news-brief-for-wednesday-january-17th-2024.mp3" length="607" type="audio/mp3"/>
   <guid isPermaLink="false"><![CDATA[8371fe62-0b65-4fca-8e7d-0f1ed63efe6d]]></guid>
   <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jan 2024 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
   <source url=""><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></source>
   <itunes:author><![CDATA[Garrison Hardie]]></itunes:author>
   <itunes:image href="https://assets-cdn2.dropwave.io/2ab40ac0-e99d-4f25-a6d2-541d2c9b290a/cover-art/mUK8zsnHkCK3vep7E1W6UgYb9dTnLenASAMEFha3.jpg"/>
   <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
   <itunes:duration>607</itunes:duration>
   <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
  
  </item><item>
   <title><![CDATA[Daily News Brief for Tuesday, January 16th, 2024 [Daily News Brief]]]></title>
   <link/>
   <description><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">This is Garrison Hardie with your CrossPolitic Daily News Brief for Tuesday, January 16th, 2024.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Page50 ad read concepts:</strong></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Page50 is a distinctly Christian marketing company striving to help Christian-owned businesses grow and succeed in our digital age. They don&rsquo;t want to just make a paycheck, they want to&nbsp;</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">change the world, and that means building it alongside you.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The mission is bigger than just Sunday. Page50 wants to help Christians recapture the work week, economic and political influence, and the public square.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Page50 doesn&rsquo;t work with just anybody, but if you&rsquo;re a believer they want to work with you. Visit pagefifty.com and see what they can do for you. That&rsquo;s pagefifty.com.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://thepostmillennial.com/faa-is-actively-recruiting-people-with-severe-intellectual-and-psychiatric-disabilities-as-part-of-diversity-and-inclusion-plan?utm_campaign=64487"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://thepostmillennial.com/faa-is-actively-recruiting-people-with-severe-intellectual-and-psychiatric-disabilities-as-part-of-diversity-and-inclusion-plan?utm_campaign=64487</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Biden's FAA is actively recruiting people with &lsquo;severe intellectual&rsquo; and &lsquo;psychiatric&rsquo; disabilities as part of 'Diversity and Inclusion' plan</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The Federal Aviation Administration (FAA) places a priority on hiring people with "severe intellectual disability" as part of its diversity and inclusion initiative.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">According to its website, the FAA claims, "Individuals with targeted or 'severe' disabilities are the most under-represented segment of the Federal workforce."&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Under its People with Disabilities Program, the agency says it "actively recruits, hires, promotes, retains, develops and advances people with disabilities." The FAA targets the following disabilities as a matter of policy: "Hearing, vision, missing extremities, partial paralysis, complete paralysis, epilepsy, severe intellectual disability, psychiatric disability and dwarfism."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The FAA told Fox News that it "seeks qualified candidates from as many sources as possible, all of whom must meet rigorous qualifications that of course will vary by position."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Its website reveals that those with disabilities or those who have a veteran status can also be hired via the non-competitive, "on-the-spot" process as long as a manager files the proper paperwork, thus giving them preferential treatment in the hiring process.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The aviation industry has received further scrutiny from the public in the wake of an Alaska Airlines door plug being blown off the side of its two-month-old Boeing 737-9 MAX aircraft causing it to make an emergency landing.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">In a post on X, tech mogul Elon Musk asked, "Do you want to fly in an airplane where they prioritize DEI hiring over your safety?" He added, "That is actually happening."&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">"People will die due to DEI," Musk said.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Musk's comments came in response to a report that revealed in 2022 that Boeing began prioritizing Diversity, Equity, and Inclusion (DEI) as part of its hiring process in 2022.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The Alaskan Airlines situation came on the heels of a shocking report in December, which showed there were 19 instances where planes nearly crashed into each other at airports in the first ten months of 2023.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/news/business/2795955/shark-tank-powerhouse-investor-says-he-wont-invest-in-california-bad-policy/"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/news/business/2795955/shark-tank-powerhouse-investor-says-he-wont-invest-in-california-bad-policy/</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Shark Tank powerhouse investor says he won&rsquo;t invest in California: &lsquo;Bad policy&rsquo;</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Kevin O&rsquo;Leary of Shark Tank revealed he would not make business investments in several Democratic states, including California.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">O&rsquo;Leary explained his reasoning in a yet-to-be-released episode of Sen. Marsha Blackburn&rsquo;s (R-TN) show Unmuted. According to a transcript reviewed by Townhall, the politics of a state help O&rsquo;Leary determine where to invest.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&ldquo;I&rsquo;m not trying to get involved in the partisanship of this statement. Just a fact, I don&rsquo;t invest in New York, I don&rsquo;t invest in Massachusetts, I don&rsquo;t invest in California. In my mind, those are examples of states that are uninvestable because of bad policy,&rdquo; O&rsquo;Leary said. &ldquo;So, I&rsquo;m looking for the path of least resistance. If you make it hard for me to make money, I just take my money and go somewhere else.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">California in particular is ranked in the top ten for sales taxes and corporate taxes, according to the Tax Foundation, while New York is in the top ten only for its sales tax.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">O&rsquo;Leary pointed to Tennessee as an example of a state with &ldquo;fantastic tax policy, reduced regulatory environment, reduced permitting time.&rdquo; Any other state that doesn&rsquo;t implement these business-friendly policies is at risk of &ldquo;killing jobs,&rdquo; according to O&rsquo;Leary.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The Canadian investor started his own venture capital firm O&rsquo;Leary Ventures last year, over 15 years after his first appearance on Shark Tank where he spends episodes deciding in what small businesses he desires to invest.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://www.breitbart.com/politics/2024/01/15/report-white-house-swatted-prank-caller-claiming-residence-on-fire/"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.breitbart.com/politics/2024/01/15/report-white-house-swatted-prank-caller-claiming-residence-on-fire/</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>White House Swatted by &lsquo;Prank Caller&rsquo; Claiming Residence on Fire</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Fire trucks and ambulances reportedly rushed to the White House Monday morning around seven o&rsquo;clock after a &ldquo;prank caller&rdquo; claimed the residence was on fire and someone was trapped inside.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The incident represents the latest swatting event against political officials. Dangerous swatting events appear to have first been instigated by Democrat prank callers against political opponents.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The prank call at the White House forced fire trucks and ambulances to rush to a snow-covered White House, the Daily Mail reported.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">After arriving, the District of Columbia Fire and Emergency Medical Services and the U.S. Secret Service determined the incident was a false alarm.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&ldquo;Fire in the White House, 1600 Pennsylvania Avenue,&rdquo; a Washington, DC, dispatcher said at 7:04 a.m.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Authorities gave an &ldquo;all clear&rdquo; order at 7:15 AM.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">President Joe Biden was located at Camp David on Monday morning, far away from the residence.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Authorities traced the prank call to an apparently spoofed phone number, a source told CNN.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&ldquo;Someone who was reached at the callback number for the 911 report indicated they did not place it, a source told the Associated Press, indicating it was likely spoofed,&rdquo; the Daily Mail reported.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Recent politicians who were swatted include Sen. Rick Scott (R-FL) and Rep. Marjorie Taylor Greene (R-GA), along with celebrities Ashton Kutcher, Justin Bieber, and Kim Kardashian.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://abcnews.go.com/Business/wireStory/yemen-houthi-rebels-fire-missile-us-warship-red-106370679"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://abcnews.go.com/Business/wireStory/yemen-houthi-rebels-fire-missile-us-warship-red-106370679</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Houthi rebels strike a U.S.-owned ship off the coast of Yemen in the Gulf of Aden, raising tensions</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Houthi rebels fired a missile, striking a U.S.-owned ship Monday just off the coast of Yemen in the Gulf of Aden, less than a day after they launched an anti-ship cruise missile toward an American destroyer in the Red Sea.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The attack on the Gibraltar Eagle, later claimed by the Houthis, further escalates tensions gripping the Red Sea after American-led strikes on the rebels. The Houthis' attacks have roiled global shipping, amid Israel's war with Hamas in the Gaza Strip, targeting a crucial corridor linking Asian and Mideast energy and cargo shipments to the Suez Canal onward to Europe.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The United Kingdom Maritime Trade Operations, which oversees Mideast waters, said Monday's attack happened some 110 miles (177 kilometers) miles southeast of Aden. It said the ship&rsquo;s captain reported that the &ldquo;port side of vessel hit from above by a missile.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Private security firms Ambrey and Dryad Global told The Associated Press that the vessel was the Eagle Gibraltar, a Marshall Islands-flagged bulk carrier. The U.S. military's Central Command later acknowledged the strike.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&ldquo;The ship has reported no injuries or significant damage and is continuing its journey,&rdquo; Central Command said.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Houthi military spokesman Brig. Gen. Yahya Saree claimed the attack in a recorded television address that aired Monday night.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&ldquo;The Yemeni armed forces consider all American and British ships and warships participating in the aggression against our country as hostile targets,&rdquo; he said.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The vessel is owned by Eagle Bulk Shipping, a Stamford, Connecticut-based firm traded on the New York Stock Exchange. In a statement to the AP, the company acknowledged the strike and said it caused &ldquo;limited damage to a cargo hold but (the ship) is stable and is heading out of the area.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&ldquo;All seafarers onboard the vessel are confirmed to be uninjured,&rdquo; the firm said. &ldquo;The vessel is carrying a cargo of steel products. Eagle Bulk management is in close contact with all relevant authorities concerning this matter.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Satellite-tracking data analyzed by the AP showed the Eagle Gibraltar had been bound for the Suez Canal, but rapidly turned around at the time of the attack.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Central Command said it detected a separate anti-ship ballistic missile launch toward the southern Red Sea on Monday, though it &rdquo;failed in flight and impacted on land in Yemen."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The U.S. Maritime Administration, under the Transportation Department, also issued a warning Monday saying there continues to be &ldquo;a high degree of risk to commercial vessels&rdquo; traveling near Yemen.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&ldquo;While the decision to transit remains at the discretion of individual vessels and companies, it is recommended that U.S. flag and U.S.-owned commercial vessels&rdquo; stay away from Yemen in the Red Sea and Gulf of Aden &ldquo;until further notice,&rdquo; the advisory said.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Sunday's missile launch toward the American warship also marked the first U.S.-acknowledged fire by the Houthis since America and allied nations began strikes Friday on the rebels following weeks of assaults on shipping in the Red Sea.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The Houthi fire in the direction of the USS Laboon, an Arleigh Burke-class destroyer operating in the southern reaches of the Red Sea, Central Command said.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The missile came from near Hodeida, a Red Sea port city long held by the Houthis, the U.S. said.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&ldquo;An anti-ship cruise missile was fired from Iranian-backed Houthi militant areas of Yemen toward USS Laboon,&rdquo; Central Command said. &ldquo;There were no injuries or damage reported."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The Houthis did not acknowledge that attack.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">It wasn&rsquo;t presently clear whether the U.S. would retaliate for the latest attacks, though President Joe Biden has said he &ldquo;will not hesitate to direct further measures to protect our people and the free flow of international commerce as necessary.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The first day of U.S.-led strikes Friday hit 28 locations and struck more than 60 targets with cruise missiles and bombs launched by fighter jets, warships and a submarine. Sites hit included weapon depots, radars and command centers, including in remote mountain areas, the U.S. has said.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The Houthis have yet to acknowledge how severe the damage was from the strikes, which they said killed five of their troops and wounded six others.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">U.S. forces followed up with a strike Saturday on a Houthi radar site.</span></p>]]></description>
   <author><![CDATA[Garrison Hardie]]></author>
   <enclosure url="https://app.dropwave.io/episode/eac98e01-ec55-42b4-93f1-9af791fa0a0a/daily-news-brief-for-tuesday-january-16th-2024.mp3" length="638" type="audio/mp3"/>
   <guid isPermaLink="false"><![CDATA[eac98e01-ec55-42b4-93f1-9af791fa0a0a]]></guid>
   <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2024 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
   <source url=""><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></source>
   <itunes:author><![CDATA[Garrison Hardie]]></itunes:author>
   <itunes:image href="https://assets-cdn2.dropwave.io/2ab40ac0-e99d-4f25-a6d2-541d2c9b290a/cover-art/mUK8zsnHkCK3vep7E1W6UgYb9dTnLenASAMEFha3.jpg"/>
   <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
   <itunes:duration>638</itunes:duration>
   <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
  
  </item><item>
   <title><![CDATA[Daily News Brief for Thursday, January 11th, 2024 [Daily News Brief]]]></title>
   <link/>
   <description><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">This is Garrison Hardie with your CrossPolitic Daily News Brief for Thursday, January 11th, 2024.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Pub Membership Plug:</strong></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Public Houses, or Pubs, are not just places to drink beer, wine, cider or even something a little stronger. It is also a unique social centre, very often the focus of community life in villages, towns and cities throughout the length and breadth of the world. We here at CrossPolitic hope to emulate that for you and yours. That&rsquo;s why you should grab yourself a pub membership at fightlaughfeast.com&hellip; we need you on this ride with us. So pull up a chair, grab a pint, and join us on this ride at fightlaughfeast.com - that&rsquo;s fightlaughfeast.com.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://thepostmillennial.com/breaking-hunter-biden-shows-up-at-house-while-oversight-considers-contempt-resolution-against-him?utm_campaign=64487"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://thepostmillennial.com/breaking-hunter-biden-shows-up-at-house-while-oversight-considers-contempt-resolution-against-him?utm_campaign=64487</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Hunter Biden makes surprise appearance at Oversight contempt proceeding in congress, then storms out</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">After defying a Congressional subpoena in December, Hunter Biden made a surprise appearance at Wednesday&rsquo;s markup meeting in which lawmakers on the House Oversight Committee are working on a resolution to hold the president&rsquo;s son in contempt of Congress.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">House Oversight member Nancy Mace addressed Biden directly.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://twitter.com/i/status/1745105809439150194"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://twitter.com/i/status/1745105809439150194</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> - Play Video&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">When Rep Marjorie Taylor Greene began speaking Hunter Biden stormed out, with Greene telling him as he left, "Apparently you&rsquo;re afraid of my words."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://twitter.com/i/status/1745108562043437517"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://twitter.com/i/status/1745108562043437517</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> - Play 0:00-0:39</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Then as Hunter Biden was exiting the building, a man asked him on numerous occasions, &ldquo;are you on crack today?&rdquo;&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://twitter.com/i/status/1745107221992632623"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://twitter.com/i/status/1745107221992632623</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> - Play Video&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Hunter Biden attorney Abbe Lowell addressed reporters in the halls of Congress, saying that "Republicans have sought to use [Hunter Biden} as a surrogate to attack his father."</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Lowell said that "we have offered to work with House committees to see what and how relevant information to any legitimate inquiry could be provided."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">"Our first five offers were ignored. And then in November, they issued a subpoena for a behind-closed-doors deposition, a tactic that the Republicans have repeatedly misused in their political crusade to selectively leave and mischaracterize what witnesses have said."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Hunter Biden was subpoenaed to appear for a closed-door deposition on December 13, 2023. He refused to attend this deposition, instead speaking from the Capitol lawn.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Hunter Biden declared that he would only appear in a public session, but Committee on House Administration rules states that depositions of a witness are to take place only in the presence of the "Committee, Committee staff designed by the Chairman or the ranking minority member, an official reporter, the witness, and the witness&rsquo; two designated attorneys." Hunter Biden, however, doesn't think this rule should apply to him.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://www.theblaze.com/news/mexican-president-demands-20-billion-and-work-permits-for-10-million-hispanics-before-offering-immigration-help"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.theblaze.com/news/mexican-president-demands-20-billion-and-work-permits-for-10-million-hispanics-before-offering-immigration-help</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Mexican president demands $20 billion and work permits for 10 million Hispanics before offering immigration help</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Mexican President Andres Manuel Lopez Obrador recently revealed what that U.S. must do in order for the Mexican government to help slow down the flow of migrants crossing the U.S.-Mexico border, and the price is steep.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Fox News Digital reported that Lopez Obrador announced his demands during a press conference on Friday. The development comes just a week after the Mexican president met with Homeland Security Secretary Alejandro Mayorkas and Secretary of State Antony Blinken in Mexico City.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">In order for Mexico to help the U.S., Lopez Obrador demanded that the U.S. provide $20 billion to Latin American and Caribbean countries; provide work visas to 10 million Hispanics who have been working in the U.S. for at least 10 years; end sanctions against Venezuela; and put an end to the blockade of Cuba.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The demands have put pressure on President Joe Biden, who has not polled well on illegal immigration since he took over the presidency in 2021. The report noted that the border experienced a large surge of migrants this fall, with around 240,000 encounters per month toward the end of 2023.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">However, some of the decisions &mdash; if Biden decides to go through with the proposal &mdash; would need to get the approval of Congress.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Lopez Obrador has not been shy about challenging U.S. politicians on the topic of illegal immigration. He recently challenged Texas Governor Greg Abbott on one of the state's new immigration laws just last month.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Blaze News reported last month that Abbott had ratified legislation that would make illegal immigration a state crime. The law, Senate Bill 4, moved forward after the Biden administration seemed unwilling to enforce federal immigration law. The state authorities will now be able to arrest foreign nationals who sneak into the country illegally, and magistrates will be able to order illegal aliens to leave the country.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Lopez Obrador said last month: "The Texas governor acts that way because he wants to be the Republican vice presidential candidate and wants to win popularity with these measures."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">"He&rsquo;s not going to win anything. On the contrary, he is going to lose support because there are a lot of Mexicans in Texas, a lot of migrants."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">However, the law recently ratified in Texas will not punish those who enter the country legally &mdash; only those who attempt to circumvent U.S. law.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://notthebee.com/article/parents-who-refuse-to-go-along-with-their-childs-gender-transition-can-now-face-7-years-in-jail-in-scotland"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://notthebee.com/article/parents-who-refuse-to-go-along-with-their-childs-gender-transition-can-now-face-7-years-in-jail-in-scotland</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Scottish parents could face years in jail for preventing kids from "dressing in a way that reflects their sexual orientation or gender identity"</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Scotland is really making it simple for parents. Let them trans your kids or you go to jail.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">You may think that's overstatement, but that's actually the plan in Scotland.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Parents who do not go along with "affirming" their child's "gender identity" could face jail for SEVEN YEARS!</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Proposals published on Tuesday state that actions designed to "change or suppress" another individual's gender identity, causing them physical or psychological harm, would become illegal under the radical law.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">SNP (Scotland National Party) ministers acknowledged that so-called conversion practices often took place in a "family setting", raising the prospect that parents could be criminalised if they refuse to go along with their child's declaration that they are transgender.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Just so you know the extent of this proposal and how it could apply to families, one of the examples of "conversion therapy" punishable by jail time is preventing a child from wearing clothing of their preferred gender identity.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">So if Billy wants to wear a dress and you stop him you would be guilty of "conversion therapy" and be subject to punishment under the law.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Even if you don't do anything, the state could preemptively take action against you based solely on your beliefs!</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">If they know you're a conservative Christian in Scotland they could issue civil orders against you, warning you not to cross the line of telling your kids what to do.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The Scottish National Party is currently the largest and most represented party in parliament. They hold nearly a majority in the multi-party system. If they're fully on board with this there's not much that can be done to stop them in parliament.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">It's important to note this is in the "public consultation" phase which, in Scotland and the UK, means they have to lay out the plan for public feedback, in this case until April, before moving forward with the proposal.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">So my suggestion, between now and April, is for every freedom and faith-loving Scot to channel his inner Braveheart and publicly oppose this radical anti-family, anti-faith, anti-human proposal from the Scottish liberals.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://youtu.be/S3ubag7dtn4"><span style="font-weight: 400;" data-rich-links="{&quot;fple-t&quot;:&quot;Braveheart - FREEDOM&quot;,&quot;fple-u&quot;:&quot;https://youtu.be/S3ubag7dtn4&quot;,&quot;fple-mt&quot;:null,&quot;type&quot;:&quot;first-party-link&quot;}">Braveheart - FREEDOM</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;">- Play 1:36-1:47</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://mynorthwest.com/3945835/rantz-wa-democrats-deem-ammo-privilege-ammunition-tax-way-end-gun-rights/"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://mynorthwest.com/3945835/rantz-wa-democrats-deem-ammo-privilege-ammunition-tax-way-end-gun-rights/</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Wash. Democrats deem ammo a &lsquo;privilege&rsquo; as way to end gun rights</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Washington Democrats opened the 2024 legislative session with another assault on gun rights. This time they hope to reclassify ammunition as a &ldquo;privilege&rdquo; &mdash; one that should be subject to an onerous tax because the one thing they love more than taking away guns is taking away your money.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">State Representatives My-Linh Thai and Liz Berry, both Democrats, introduced House Bill 2238. Under the auspices of public safety, claiming access to ammunition is the cause of violence and not their soft-on-crime policies that go easy on criminals (including those who use guns in their crimes), the bill imposes an 11% sales and use tax on ammunition statewide. This would be an additional tax on top of the sales tax and any other tax that may levied when purchasing ammunition. The city of Seattle, for example, imposes a per-round tax.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">But the bill also reclassified ammunition, claiming you do not have a right to purchase them as a consumer. Instead, it&rsquo;s labeled a &ldquo;privilege.&rdquo; The legislation creates a new section in pre-existing law that reads, &ldquo;A use tax is levied on every person in this state for the privilege of using ammunition as a consumer at the rate of 11% of the selling price.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Neither Reps. Thai nor Berry responded to inquiries asking the basis for their claim that ammunition is a privilege. But Washington Democrats have set the stage to make this outrageous claim.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Washington Democrats have consistently moved to make gun ownership more onerous for non-criminal Washingtonians. The end goal for Democrats is to ban guns so that we cannot protect ourselves against the criminals they embolden.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Instead of a flat-out ban against guns, they&rsquo;ve hoped to reclassify ammunition as a privilege by severely restricting how much of it a gun owner can use at a time. The Washington Legislature approved a bill to prohibit the sale, distribution, and manufacture of firearm magazines holding more than 10 rounds of ammunition. This is meant to set the precedent claiming Washingtonians do not have a constitutional right to ammunition.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Like most of their clearly unconstitutional bills, they&rsquo;re based on a flimsy and purposefully obtuse understanding of the right to bear arms. The Washington State Constitution, Article I, Section 24, clearly states that &ldquo;the right of the individual citizen to bear arms in defense of himself, or the state, shall not be impaired.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">You cannot bear arms if the firearm has no ammunition in it. This provision, like the Second Amendment of the U.S. Constitution, implicitly includes all necessary components of firearms like ammunition as essential to the protected exercise of the right to bear arms. Without access to ammunition, the right to bear arms would be rendered meaningless, as firearms without ammunition are unable to fulfill their intended purpose in defense of oneself or the state.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">In an ironic twist, Democrats are the best gun salesmen. Their actions are pushing Washingtonians into purchases they might not otherwise make.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Washington Democrats&rsquo; interest in banning guns does not extend to the criminals they support with legislation that keeps them out of prison before the end of their sentences under the claim the criminal justice system is racist. By passing legislation that is clearly tied to the rise in crime, they give every Washingtonian ample reason to purchase firearms for self-defense. We have a rise in violent crime in Seattle, where homicides have hit historic highs. Democrats pretend they hold no blame in this new reality.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">State Reps Tarra Simmons and David Hackney pushed a bill in the 2022 legislative session to lessen charges against drive-by shooters. It would even be applied retroactively to release a drive-by shooter serving time.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">They claimed the change promoted &ldquo;racial equity in the criminal legal system&rdquo; because they implied too many black people commit drive-by shootings and it&rsquo;s unfair for them to be charged more than white people who don&rsquo;t commit as many drive-by shootings. It was as silly an argument as it was racist. Only after considerable public pushback, did the bill die. But it seems reasonable to want a firearm to protect yourself when you have pro-criminal legislators pushing dangerous bills.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">State Rep. Roger Goodman, another anti-gun Democrat, is back this year with HB 1268. It would prevent judges from offering additional years of prison to violent criminals who use guns during their crimes (&ldquo;stacking&rdquo; on gun enhancement charges). It even offers &ldquo;good time credits&rdquo; (or earned release time) to felons serving time on a firearm or deadly weapon enhancement. Any one of these criminals released early is reason enough to own a firearm of your own.</span></p>]]></description>
   <author><![CDATA[Garrison Hardie]]></author>
   <enclosure url="https://app.dropwave.io/episode/8cc7d23c-1574-4d39-a00d-112ac9ae33de/daily-news-brief-for-thursday-january-11th-2024.mp3" length="1056" type="audio/mp3"/>
   <guid isPermaLink="false"><![CDATA[8cc7d23c-1574-4d39-a00d-112ac9ae33de]]></guid>
   <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
   <source url=""><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></source>
   <itunes:author><![CDATA[Garrison Hardie]]></itunes:author>
   <itunes:image href="https://assets-cdn2.dropwave.io/2ab40ac0-e99d-4f25-a6d2-541d2c9b290a/cover-art/mUK8zsnHkCK3vep7E1W6UgYb9dTnLenASAMEFha3.jpg"/>
   <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
   <itunes:duration>1056</itunes:duration>
   <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
  
  </item><item>
   <title><![CDATA[Daily News Brief for Wednesday, January 10th, 2024 [Daily News Brief]]]></title>
   <link/>
   <description><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">This is Garrison Hardie with your CrossPolitic Daily News Brief for Wednesday, January 10th, 2024.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>Samaritan Ministries January 2024</strong></span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Tired of someone else telling you where to go when you have a medical need? Are you ready to</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">take control of your health care? Then it&rsquo;s time to take a look at Samaritan Ministries. It&rsquo;s</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Biblical, affordable health care sharing, with no restrictive networks. Here&rsquo;s how it works. When a medical need arises, you choose the health care provider that&rsquo;s right for you and have a say in the treatment you receive. Send your medical bills to Samaritan Ministries, and they&rsquo;ll notify fellow members to pray for you and send money directly to you to help you pay those bills.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Join 80,000 Christian households across the nation who have already taken control of their</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">health care. Go to samaritan ministries dot org slash cross politic.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://www.foxnews.com/politics/mayorkas-tells-border-patrol-agents-illegal-immigrants-released-into-us-sources"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.foxnews.com/politics/mayorkas-tells-border-patrol-agents-illegal-immigrants-released-into-us-sources</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>Mayorkas tells Border Patrol agents that &lsquo;above 85%&rsquo; of illegal immigrants released into US</strong></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Homeland Security Secretary Alejandro Mayorkas on Monday admitted to Border Patrol agents that the current rate of release for illegal immigrants apprehended at the southern border is "above 85%," sources told Fox News.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Mayorkas made the remarks when meeting privately with agents in Eagle Pass, Texas, according to three Border Patrol sources who were in the room and heard the remarks themselves.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The conversation happened during the muster for agents in the busy border area. Fox is told Mayorkas was asked directly about comments he made on "Special Report" last week when he was asked by anchor Bret Baier about reporting that over 70% of migrants are released into the U.S. each day.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">"It would not surprise me at all. I know the data," Mayorkas said. "And I will tell you that when individuals are released, they are released into immigration enforcement proceedings. They are on alternatives to detention. And we have returned or removed a record number of individuals. We are enforcing the laws that Congress has passed. "</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Fox is told that on Monday agents pushed him on those remarks, saying that the number is even higher than 70%, and then Mayorkas acknowledged a release rate of "above 85%."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Mayorkas had also said last week on "Special Report" that "well more than a million" migrants are released into the U.S. annually, and argued repeatedly that it is up to Congress to provide more funding and immigration reform to fix what he has called a "broken" system. He said that the agency is limited in detention capacity by funding provided by Congress.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">"When somebody enters the country, we place them in immigration enforcement proceedings pursuant to immigration law, and if their claim for relief, their claim to remain in the United States succeeds, then by law they are able to stay here," he said.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The remarks come just two days before the House Homeland Security Committee holds its first impeachment hearing, featuring multiple state attorneys general who will testify about the impact the crisis has had on their states.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The hearing on Wednesday marks the first impeachment hearing after a year of investigations and reports by the House Homeland Security Committee which looked at the handling of the nearly three-year migrant crisis.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Republicans have blamed the historic migrant crisis, which saw 302,000 migrant encounters last month alone on Biden-era policies, including the releases of migrants into the interior -- dubbed "catch-and-release." They have pointed to the broad use of parole, as well as narrowed ICE enforcement and the stopping of wall construction.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The administration says it is dealing with a hemisphere-wide crisis and needs more funding and comprehensive immigration reform from Congress. It has claimed it is expanding "lawful migration pathways" and increasing consequences for illegal entry, but can only do so much with a "broken" system. Mayorkas and other DHS officials have said that it has removed or returned more than 470,000 people since May, which is more than in the entirety of FY 2019.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">At a press availability later on Monday, Mayorkas highlighted the removals and returns, saying it is more than in any other five-month period in the last 10 years.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">"In fact, the majority of all Southwest Border migrant encounters throughout this Administration have been removed, returned, or expelled &ndash; the majority of them," he said. "We are doing everything we can, within a broken system, to incentivize noncitizens to use lawful pathways, to impose consequences on those who do not, and to reduce irregular migration."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The White House has also requested $14 billion in border funding from Congress as part of its emergency supplemental spending proposal, but that is being held up as Republicans demand significantly more restrictions on the release of migrants into the interior.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Mayorkas said last week that it was that broken system, not administration policy, which was the magnet drawing migrants to the border.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Separately, the administration last week announced a lawsuit against the state of Texas after Gov. Greg Abbott signed a law that allows state and local law enforcement to arrest illegal immigrants. The lawsuit claims that the law is unconstitutional and interferes with the federal government's authority on immigration matters.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://thenationalpulse.com/2024/01/09/listen-hot-mic-catches-journos-joking-about-trump-being-assassinated-like-jfk-take-a-convertible/"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://thenationalpulse.com/2024/01/09/listen-hot-mic-catches-journos-joking-about-trump-being-assassinated-like-jfk-take-a-convertible/</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>Hot Mic Catches Journos Joking About Trump Being Assassinated</strong></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Microphones caught journalists waiting for Donald Trump to arrive at the E. Barrett Prettyman Courthouse in Washington D.C. joking about the president being assassinated on Tuesday. Trump is attending the D.C. Court of Appeals to hear the opening oral arguments in his appeal against Jack Smith&rsquo;s efforts to prosecute him over January 6th, and journalists gathered outside the courthouse in substantial numbers ahead of his arrival.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Two of them could be heard in live feeds joking about having a &ldquo;good shot&rdquo; at the America First leader when he arrived, particularly if he showed up driving a convertible like the one the late President John F. Kennedy was riding in when he was shot in the head in 1963:</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://twitter.com/i/status/1744738203616399859"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://twitter.com/i/status/1744738203616399859</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> - Play Video&nbsp;</span></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">If you couldn&rsquo;t hear what they said:</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">First Journalist: You know what the worst part is? Even if he has his window open and he&rsquo;s hanging out of it, he will be on the other side of the street.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Second Journalist: I mean, if he&rsquo;s driving, we&rsquo;ve got a good shot!&nbsp;</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">First Journalist: Yeah, if he&rsquo;s driving with the front window open?&nbsp;</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Second Journalist: Yeah, or if it&rsquo;s a convertible?&nbsp;</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">First Journalist: Yeah. I wasn&rsquo;t thinking about that.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">First Journalist: Like JFK?&nbsp;</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Second Journalist: (laughs)</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Trump&rsquo;s hearing is being overseen by a panel of two Joe Biden-appointed judges and one George H. W. Bush-appointed judge. His lawyers argue the Smith prosecution amounts to double jeopardy, as Trump was already tried and acquitted over January 6th by the U.S. Senate, and that Smith is also violating the principle of presidential immunity for official acts.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://www.dailyfetched.com/man-finds-iphone-that-fell-out-alaska-air-1282-perfectly-intact/"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.dailyfetched.com/man-finds-iphone-that-fell-out-alaska-air-1282-perfectly-intact/</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>Man Discovers iPhone That Fell Out of Alaska Air 1282: &lsquo;Perfectly Intact&rsquo;</strong></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">A Portland man recovered a cell phone, which is believed to be owned by a passenger of Alaska Airlines flight 1282 after it was sucked out of the plane when the door plug blew open.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Writing on X, the man, Sean Bates, posted a photo of the phone:</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">&ldquo;Found an iPhone on the side of the road,&rdquo; he wrote.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">&ldquo;Still in airplane mode with half a battery and open to a baggage claim for #AlaskaAirlines ASA1282.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Bates found the phone when he was out walking before posting it on social media, which also showed what appeared to be an Alaska Airlines baggage flight receipt.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The image showed the baggage receipt for the traveler and a piece of a charger still stuck into the phone&rsquo;s charging port.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Bates claimed the phone was &ldquo;perfectly&rdquo; intact with &ldquo;no scratches on it.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">In a TikTok video, Bates said he was walking in Portland on Sunday after the National Transportation Safety Bureau asked him to report any debris or plane parts.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The door for the plane was also recovered after another Portland resident named Bob found the plug in his yard,</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">&ldquo;Thank you, Bob,&rdquo; NTSB Chair Jennifer Homendy said at a news conference.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Bates found one of the two cell phones that were recovered.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Last week, Alaska Airlines flight was forced to make an emergency landing after its passenger window blew open.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The Boeing 737 Max was heading to Ontario, California w, when a large window busted open, causing severe depressurization.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Alaska Airlines CEO Ben Minicucci said in a statement:</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">&ldquo;Following tonight&rsquo;s event on Flight 1282, we have decided to take the precautionary step of temporarily grounding our fleet of 65 Boeing 737-9 aircraft.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">&ldquo;My heart goes out to those who were on this flight &ndash; I am so sorry for what you experienced.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Video footage showed the plane in the air with the window open as oxygen masks angled over passengers&rsquo; seats.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://www.dailyfetched.com/rebel-news-reporter-arrested-by-trudeaus-police-for-asking-a-question/"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.dailyfetched.com/rebel-news-reporter-arrested-by-trudeaus-police-for-asking-a-question/</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>Rebel News Reporter Arrested by Trudeau&rsquo;s Police for Asking a Question</strong></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">David Menzies, the reporter for Canada&rsquo;s conservative Rebel News Network, was arrested on Monday for asking Deputy Prime Minister Chrystia Freeland a question.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">A police officer reportedly accused Menzies of assault despite the reporter not making any physical contact with Freeland.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The video of the incident, posted by Rebel News chief Ezra Levant, showed Enzies asking Freeland about Canada&rsquo;s refusal to label Iran&rsquo;s Islamic Revolutionary Guard Corps (IGRC) as a terrorist organization.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The video shows Menzies keeping pace with the Deputy Prime Minister as he walks down the street when a Royal Canadian Mounted Police (RCMP) stands in his way and begins claiming Menzies &ldquo;assaulted&rdquo; him.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Menzies does not appear to notice the RCMP officer because his attention is on Freeland.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The officer then appears to set a &ldquo;pick,&rdquo; basketball-style, as a pretext for accusing Menzies of assaulting him.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">However, there is no evidence that Menzies intended to do so.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">&ldquo;You&rsquo;re under arrest for assault,&rdquo; said the officer.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The officer moved Menzies towards a vehicle, identifying himself as police and saying he was under arrest for assault. Menzies said the officer was the person who blocked his way.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">&ldquo;I was just scrumming Chrystia Freeland,&rdquo; he said.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The officer acknowledged Menzies was being arrested for assaulting a police officer. In response, he accused him of assaulting him three years ago.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Another RCMP officer said Menzies was being arrested because of his actions. This is because he was almost pushing people over.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">&ldquo;That was a little bit aggressive for what was happening,&rdquo; said the officer before the arrest occurred.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">True North managing editor Andrew Lawton said Menzies was later released.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">&ldquo;Have confirmed that Menzies was released without charges,&rdquo; said Lawton.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">And before we go, it&rsquo;s time for my favorite topic, sports!</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://youtu.be/EBdREJkch8g"><span style="font-weight: 400;" data-rich-links="{&quot;fple-t&quot;:&quot;CFP National Championship: Michigan Wolverines vs. Washington Huskies | Full Game Highlights&quot;,&quot;fple-u&quot;:&quot;https://youtu.be/EBdREJkch8g&quot;,&quot;fple-mt&quot;:null,&quot;type&quot;:&quot;first-party-link&quot;}">CFP National Championship: Michigan Wolverines vs. Washington Huskies | Full Game Highlights</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;" data-rich-links="{&quot;fple-t&quot;:&quot;CFP National Championship: Michigan Wolverines vs. Washington Huskies | Full Game Highlights&quot;,&quot;fple-u&quot;:&quot;https://youtu.be/EBdREJkch8g&quot;,&quot;fple-mt&quot;:null,&quot;type&quot;:&quot;first-party-link&quot;}"> </span><span style="font-weight: 400;">Play 17:11-17:33</span></span></p>]]></description>
   <author><![CDATA[Garrison Hardie]]></author>
   <enclosure url="https://app.dropwave.io/episode/2584c442-4b2c-49dd-bb8b-3af8c5511e14/daily-news-brief-for-wednesday-january-10th-2024.mp3" length="780" type="audio/mp3"/>
   <guid isPermaLink="false"><![CDATA[2584c442-4b2c-49dd-bb8b-3af8c5511e14]]></guid>
   <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jan 2024 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
   <source url=""><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></source>
   <itunes:author><![CDATA[Garrison Hardie]]></itunes:author>
   <itunes:image href="https://assets-cdn2.dropwave.io/2ab40ac0-e99d-4f25-a6d2-541d2c9b290a/cover-art/mUK8zsnHkCK3vep7E1W6UgYb9dTnLenASAMEFha3.jpg"/>
   <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
   <itunes:duration>780</itunes:duration>
   <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
  
  </item><item>
   <title><![CDATA[Daily News Brief for Tuesday, January 9th, 2024 [Daily News Brief]]]></title>
   <link/>
   <description><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">This is Garrison Hardie with your CrossPolitic Daily News Brief for Tuesday, January 9th, 2024.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>VanGelder Technologies:</strong></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">VanGelder Technologies is a US-based custom software development company specializing in cross-platform mobile applications, web applications, and desktop programs. Leveraging open-source frameworks, they quickly and efficiently build custom software solutions that are tailor made to fit your specific needs.   </span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">There&rsquo;s no need for New Christendom companies to be content with offering sub-par mobile or web experiences. VanGelder Technologies can help you build better software for the glory of God! You can learn more, view examples of their work, or get in touch, at www.vangelder.tech  </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">That&rsquo;s V-A-N, G-E-L, D-E-R dot T-E-C-H VanGelder Technologies, where technology and tradition meet.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://www.breitbart.com/entertainment/2024/01/07/nolte-existential-crisis-woke-hollywood-loses-moviegoers/"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.breitbart.com/entertainment/2024/01/07/nolte-existential-crisis-woke-hollywood-loses-moviegoers/</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>&lsquo;Existential Crisis&rsquo; as Woke Hollywood Loses 20% of Moviegoers</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The start of the COVID pandemic is about four years in the rearview and still being blamed for Hollywood losing 20 percent of moviegoers.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&ldquo;One out of every five moviegoers has vanished since the pandemic, according to research compiled by one Hollywood studio,&rdquo; reports the far-left Hollywood Reporter. &ldquo;Whether they&rsquo;ll ever return to see a film on the big screen is anyone&rsquo;s guess &mdash; and, if they do, when.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Compared to the last pre-pandemic year of 2019, the domestic box office is down 21 percent.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The lengthy article is full of facts and figures. It also accidentally answers the question it asks about why this is happening and how to fix it, but it never acknowledges the answer.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The answer is right here: Spider-Man: No Way Home, Barbie, Oppenheimer, John Wick 4, Top Gun: Maverick, and Sound of Freedom. Those titles were monster hits during and after the pandemic for one very simple reason: people wanted to see them.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The idea that the reasons behind this drop in moviegoing ranks is a whodunnit is absurd. The titles above prove that people will still turn out in droves if they find something appealing. So, how can anyone still blame the pandemic for the drop in moviegoing? If the pandemic was to blame, nothing could succeed in theaters.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Plus, Taylor Swift&rsquo;s big 2023 concert tour proves the moviegoing demo isn&rsquo;t afraid to congregate or come out of their homes. She&rsquo;s packing them in up to the rafters.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The article also suggests moviegoers are tired of aging franchises. How can that be true when the fifth biggest global blockbuster of 2023 was the tenth chapter in the 24-year-old Fast &amp; Furious franchise?</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The article suggests moviegoers are tired of superheroes. How can that be true when Guardians of the Galaxy Vol 3 was 2023&rsquo;s fourth biggest global blockbuster?</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Audiences worn out by franchises and superhero movies would not go to see any aging franchise or superhero movie. Fast X and Guardians became hits because people wanted to see them. But why Fast X and Guardians 3, and not Indiana Jones and the Dial of Destiny? Another simple answer&hellip; Dial of Destiny emasculated and shamed its hero with an unappealing girl sidekick, while Fast X and Guardians 3 remained true to their characters and what made them iconic.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The &ldquo;existential&rdquo; truth, and we all know it, is this: Ever since Donald Trump won the presidency in 2016, Hollywood has sought to punish, insult, and alienate Trump voters (half the country) by way of cinematic tantrums that scold and dehumanize us due to our gender, faith, political beliefs, and overall normalcy.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Hollywood&rsquo;s insane crusade against decent people (and decency) hit warp speed after the murder of George Floyd with a legion of movies where no one behaves or interacts normally. In order to push its social and political agenda, everyone&rsquo;s a simple-minded stand-in for us evil normal people or the oh-so noble BIPOCLGBTQTARDs. Disney is now &ldquo;queering&rdquo; our children. Indiana Jones is criticized as a colonialist. Luke Skywalker is a child murderer. Buzz Lightyear is a GLAAD crusader. Thor learns to wear an apron.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">On top of that, movie after movie tells us sexual deviancy, mental illness, and narcissism are virtues. Worst of all, our heroes, the very characters that made these franchises golden geese for decades, are deconstructed, portrayed as bigots, and replaced with girls and racial minorities for no good reason other than tokenism. Sometimes, as the Equalizer franchise proved, there is a good reason &mdash; Denzel Washington is awesome. Mostly, though, the tokenism is so ham-handed and off-putting that the bad taste in our mouths tells us not to bother purchasing a ticket.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">There&rsquo;s no mystery here: movies suck.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://www.breitbart.com/europe/2024/01/07/two-hikers-killed-by-avalanche-in-the-italian-alps-near-switzerland/"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.breitbart.com/europe/2024/01/07/two-hikers-killed-by-avalanche-in-the-italian-alps-near-switzerland/</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Two Hikers Killed by Avalanche in the Italian Alps Near Switzerland</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Two hikers on snowshoes were killed by an avalanche in the Italian Alps near Switzerland, a rescue service said Sunday.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The avalanche occurred around noon on Sunday at the 2,200-meter (7,200-foot) level in the Formazza valley in the Piedmont region, said Federico Catania, a spokesperson for Italy&rsquo;s alpine rescue service.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The force of the avalanche pushed one of the victims into a lake near the bottom of the slope, while the other body was found in the mass of snow, he said.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Despite strong winds, a helicopter was able to lower a rescue team aided by a dog unit.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The identities of the two victims weren&rsquo;t immediately released.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">A search operation was launched after guards at a nearby dike reported seeing an avalanche strike two hikers, Catania said. An initial search by foot failed to find the hikers, prompting the use of the helicopter.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">A firefighters helicopter carrying divers was dispatched to recover the body from the lake, rescuers said.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://americanmilitarynews.com/2024/01/iran-sends-warship-to-red-sea-after-us-sinks-houthi-boats/#google_vignette"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://americanmilitarynews.com/2024/01/iran-sends-warship-to-red-sea-after-us-sinks-houthi-boats/#google_vignette</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Iran sends warship to Red Sea after US sinks Houthi boats</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Iran dispatched a warship to the Red Sea after the U.S. Navy destroyed three Houthi boats, a move that risks ratcheting up tensions and complicates Washington&rsquo;s goal of securing a waterway that&rsquo;s vital to global trade.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The Alborz destroyer traversed the Bab El-Mandeb strait, a narrow choke point between the Red Sea and the Gulf of Aden, on Monday, Iranian state media said without providing further information on the vessel&rsquo;s mission.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Iran&rsquo;s foray into the Red Sea a day after the U.S. action compounds a highly volatile situation in the channel that handles about 12% of the world&rsquo;s commerce. The move could be seen as a challenge to the U.S.-led maritime task force established last month to halt attacks on ships by the Tehran-backed Houthi rebels who control a swath of Yemen&rsquo;s northwest, including the capital Sanaa and the Red Sea port of Al-Hudaydah.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The Houthis, in November, began attacking vessels they claimed were headed to or owned by entities in Israel in a bid to end an Israeli offensive in Gaza, after Hamas, a U.S.-designated terrorist group, staged a shock attack inside Israel on Oct. 7.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">In one month, the Houthis hijacked one container ship and launched more than 100 drone and ballistic missile attacks, targeting 10 merchant vessels involving more than 35 different nations, according to the Pentagon.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Operation Prosperity Guardian, involving the navies of the U.S. and nine other nations, swung into action from Dec. 19 and had a fierce encounter with the militants on Sunday.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Helicopters aboard two U.S. destroyers in the Red Sea, the USS Eisenhower and the USS Gravely, responded to a distress call by the Maersk Hangzhou as Houthis in four speedboats tried to board the vessel, according to the U.S. military. Houthi fighters ignored verbal warnings, fired at the aircraft and triggered a lethal response in which three of the boats were sunk.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">It was the Houthis&rsquo; second major shipping attack in less than 24 hours and came after Denmark announced it was sending a frigate to the Red Sea to join the U.S.-led maritime coalition.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The U.S. has accused Iran of being &ldquo;deeply involved&rdquo; in the Houthi attacks in the Red Sea, which Tehran has denied, but said that it understood the reason for their actions. Iran hasn&rsquo;t denied supporting the Houthis since the group ousted the internationally recognized government of Yemen in 2014.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">A Houthi spokesperson, Yahya Saree, confirmed the incident and said 10 of the group&rsquo;s fighters were dead or missing. He called on Yemenis, Arabs and Muslims to be &ldquo;ready for all options in confronting the American escalation.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Iran&rsquo;s show of force in the Red Sea coincided with a visit to Tehran by Mohammed Abdulsalam, a Houthi movement spokesperson and chief negotiator. On Monday, he met with officials at Iran&rsquo;s foreign ministry following talks with Ali Akbar Ahmadian, secretary of Iran&rsquo;s Supreme National Security Council, according to Iran&rsquo;s Nour News.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">On Sunday Iran&rsquo;s Foreign Minister Hossein Amirabdollahian denounced what he called double standards by the U.S. and some Western governments after a telephone conversation with the U.K. Foreign Secretary David Cameron, who urged Iran to rein in the Houthis. &ldquo;Israel can&rsquo;t be allowed to massacre women and children and carry out a genocide in Gaza and set fire to the region, but consider stopping an Israeli ship in the Red Sea as endangering the security of this economic waterway,&rdquo; said Amirabdollahian.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Tehran&rsquo;s moves are ultimately in the service of its own agenda of projecting power and driving Washington out of the region, says Joel Rayburn, a former US diplomat and military officer.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&ldquo;This is what the Iranian regime has always been intending to do with their outpost in Yemen,&rdquo; said Rayburn. Iran thinks it can establish itself as &ldquo;a great power sitting astride the region and its waterways.&rdquo;</span></p>]]></description>
   <author><![CDATA[Garrison Hardie]]></author>
   <enclosure url="https://app.dropwave.io/episode/20803311-5004-4f96-9f4c-76efd81d0583/daily-news-brief-for-tuesday-january-9th-2024.mp3" length="606" type="audio/mp3"/>
   <guid isPermaLink="false"><![CDATA[20803311-5004-4f96-9f4c-76efd81d0583]]></guid>
   <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jan 2024 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
   <source url=""><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></source>
   <itunes:author><![CDATA[Garrison Hardie]]></itunes:author>
   <itunes:image href="https://assets-cdn2.dropwave.io/2ab40ac0-e99d-4f25-a6d2-541d2c9b290a/cover-art/mUK8zsnHkCK3vep7E1W6UgYb9dTnLenASAMEFha3.jpg"/>
   <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
   <itunes:duration>606</itunes:duration>
   <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
  
  </item><item>
   <title><![CDATA[Daily News Brief for Friday, January 5th, 2024 [Daily News Brief]]]></title>
   <link/>
   <description><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">This is Garrison Hardie with your CrossPolitic Daily News Brief for Friday, January 5th, 2024.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Download our new app!:</strong></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">You guys are aware that we have a new app right? If not you should download it right now! Head on over to your app store, and type in &ldquo;CrossPolitic&rdquo;, &ldquo;Fight Laugh Feast&rdquo;, or &ldquo;PubTV&rdquo;. Once you find the app, you may need to update your app, or if you have a droid phone, you may need to delete your current FLF app, and re-download it! Once downloaded you&rsquo;ll be able to view or listen to our content right on your mobile device! As always, if you&rsquo;d like to sign up for a pub membership, you can head on over to fightlaughfeast.com&hellip; that&rsquo;s fightlaughfeast.com.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://www.foxnews.com/us/police-investigating-active-shooter-scene-high-school-perry-iowa"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.foxnews.com/us/police-investigating-active-shooter-scene-high-school-perry-iowa</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Multiple people injured in shooting at Perry, Iowa, high school</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Multiple people were injured in a shooting at an Iowa high school on Thursday morning, authorities said.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">At approximately 7:37 a.m., police received reports of an active scene at Perry High School in Perry. Officers responded within seven minutes of the active shooter alarm, Dallas County Sheriff Adam Infante told reporters.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The total number of victims and their status have not been confirmed. Infante said authorities are working to determine that information and that there is no further danger to the public.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">"The community is safe," the sheriff said. "We're just now working backwards, trying to figure out everything that happened and make notifications. There will be another update later on today."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The Associated Press reported two gunshot victims were taken by ambulance to Iowa Methodist Medical Center in the state capital of Des Moines.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">A law enforcement source told the AP the suspect in the shooting has died of what investigators believe is a self-inflicted gunshot wound.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Infante said the shooting happened before school began.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">"Luckily, there was very few students and faculty in the building, which I think contributed to a good outcome in that sense," he said.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Zander Shelley, 15, was in a hallway waiting for the school day to start when he heard gunshots and dashed into a classroom, his father, Kevin Shelley, told the AP. Zander was grazed twice and hid in the classroom before texting his father at 7:36 a.m.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Kevin Shelley, who drives a garbage truck, told his boss he had to run. "It was the most scared I&rsquo;ve been in my entire life," he said.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Rachael Kares, an 18-year-old senior, told the AP she was at jazz band practice when students heard what sounded like four gunshots, spaced apart.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">"We all just jumped," Kares said. "My band teacher looked at us and yelled, &lsquo;Run!&rsquo; So we ran."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Kares said students and faculty ran out past the football field, with people yelling, "Get out! Get out!" as they ran. She said she heard additional shots while she fled, but was most concerned about getting home to her 3-year-old son.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">"At that moment I didn&rsquo;t care about anything except getting out because I had to get home with my son," she told the AP.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The sheriff's office, Perry Police Department and multiple federal agencies also responded to the shooting.&nbsp;&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Authorities have identified a suspect but have not released their name at this time, the sheriff said.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Multiple EMS vehicles were sent to the scene at 1200 18th Street, according to public safety radio traffic.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Federal agents from the FBI and Bureau of Alcohol, Tobacco, Firearms and Explosives (ATF) also said they were on the ground.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Perry High School belongs to the Perry Community School District, about 25 miles northwest of Des Moines. About 1,785 students are enrolled in the school district, according to its website.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Thursday was the first day of school after the winter break, according to the school's calendar.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">"Our hearts are broken by this senseless tragedy. Our prayers are with the students, teachers &amp; families of the Perry Community," Iowa Gov. Kim Reynolds said in a statement. "I have been in contact with law enforcement agencies &amp; am continuing to monitor the situation. I will be joining their press conference today."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://www.theepochtimes.com/us/federal-judge-dismisses-trump-ballot-disqualification-case-with-prejudice-5558227?utm_source=partner&amp;utm_campaign=BonginoReport"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.theepochtimes.com/us/federal-judge-dismisses-trump-ballot-disqualification-case-with-prejudice-5558227?utm_source=partner&amp;utm_campaign=BonginoReport</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Federal Judge Dismisses Trump Ballot Disqualification Case &lsquo;With Prejudice&rsquo;</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">A federal judge in California on Jan. 3 dismissed a lawsuit that sought to keep former President Donald Trump off the 2024 Republican primary ballot in that state.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">District Judge David Carter granted a motion to dismiss the lawsuit &ldquo;with prejudice,&rdquo; which means that it can&rsquo;t be submitted to the same court again, according to court papers.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">A plaintiff attempted to argue that they suffered &ldquo;emotional injury&rdquo; as a result of the breach of the U.S. Capitol on Jan. 6, 2021, while watching the events unfold on television, on the radio, and in various publications. They then argued that the incident caused them &ldquo;severe emotional distress&rdquo; and then filed a lawsuit to keep the former president off California&rsquo;s ballot.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">However, the judge wrote that because the events occurred &ldquo;more than two years before the plaintiff&rdquo; filed suit, it was outside of the two-year statute of limitations.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The decision by Judge Carter, a Clinton-appointed jurist who has ruled against President Trump in a separate case, was posted online by former Republican National Committee for California Chair Harmeet Dhillon.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&ldquo;The remnants of the last California case to keep President Trump off the ballot here were dismissed today by Judge David O. Carter!!&rdquo; she wrote on X, formerly known as Twitter, on Jan. 3.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">In recent days and weeks, a number of lawsuits have been filed in different states seeking to bar President Trump from appearing on the ballot ahead of the 2024 election. Those suits have claimed that the former president engaged in &ldquo;insurrection or rebellion&rdquo; against the United States under an interpretation of the Constitution&rsquo;s 14th Amendment&rsquo;s Section 3, which was written in the immediate aftermath of the U.S. Civil War.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">At least two of those challenges have seen some success in Maine and Colorado, although there has been widespread speculation that higher courts or even the U.S. Supreme Court will strike those rulings down.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Days before Christmas, Colorado&rsquo;s highest court ruled to keep the former president off the primary ballot in the state, which was promptly appealed to the Supreme Court. Last week, Maine Secretary of State Shenna Bellows, a Democrat, unilaterally decided to keep President Trump off the ballot, which also has been appealed.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Ahead of the Supreme Court appeal, Trump campaign spokesman Steven Cheung said that &ldquo;unsurprisingly, the all-Democrat-appointed Colorado Supreme Court has ruled against President Trump, supporting a Soros-funded, left-wing group&rsquo;s scheme to interfere in an election on behalf of Crooked Joe Biden by removing President Trump&rsquo;s name from the ballot and eliminating the rights of Colorado voters to vote for the candidate of their choice.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Legal analysts have suggested that the U.S. Supreme Court would take up those two cases and likely would rule against the plaintiffs at least on procedural grounds. However, it isn&rsquo;t clear whether the court will take up the more thorny questions presented under the 14th Amendment&rsquo;s insurrection clause.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&ldquo;It seems a certainty that SCOTUS will have to address the merits sooner or later,&rdquo; Rick Hasen, a law professor at the University of California&ndash;Los Angeles, wrote on his website last month, referring to the Supreme Court.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Several other federal judges have also dismissed attempts to block the former president from appearing on ballots. In a ruling issued in late December 2023, U.S. District Judge Leonie Brinkema wrote that the plaintiffs&mdash;two activists&mdash;who filed suit against President Trump in Virginia to keep him on that state&rsquo;s ballot lacked standing.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://hotair.com/jazz-shaw/2024/01/03/trans-murderer-sent-to-womens-prison-n602445"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://hotair.com/jazz-shaw/2024/01/03/trans-murderer-sent-to-womens-prison-n602445</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Trans Murderer Sent to Women's Prison</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">In 2012 and 2013, a man named Steven Buchanan murdered two handymen he had hired to do some labor around his farm in Oregon. After killing them, he fed their corpses to his pigs. He was eventually discovered and arrested for the crimes. In 2015 he was convicted, with the judge telling him that he was &ldquo;a cold-blooded killer&rdquo; who &ldquo;valued pigs more than you value human life.&rdquo; Buchanan was sentenced to fifty years in prison. But then things reportedly took a turn for the strange. The killer was no longer Steven Buchanan. Instead, he was &ldquo;Susan Monica,&rdquo; claiming to be a transgender woman. As our colleague Madeline Lessman reports this week at Townhall, Monica nee Buchanan is now being housed at Coffee Creek Correctional Facility, a women&rsquo;s prison located in Wilsonville, Oregon.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">A &ldquo;transgender&rdquo; biological male who was convicted of murdering two men is serving a 50-year sentence in a women&rsquo;s prison, according to a report from Reduxx.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The prisoner, Steven Buchanan, who goes by &ldquo;Susan Monica,&rdquo; dismembered the bodies of his victims and fed them to pigs on a 20-acre farm he owned in Oregon, Reduxx noted. Buchanan bought the farm in 1991 and killed two handymen in 2012 and 2013. In 2015, he was reportedly sentenced to a minimum of 50 years behind bars.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&ldquo;You shot two people and fed them to your pigs,&rdquo; Judge Tim Barnack told Buchanan during sentencing. &ldquo;I don&rsquo;t know how else I can put it. You valued pigs more than you value people. It may sound harsh, but you are a cold-blooded killer.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">By this time, we&rsquo;ve covered enough of these transgender prisoner stories that you should have already noticed a pattern emerging. There are men behaving badly who never seemed to have any problem living as men. Then, why they are facing the possibility of a long stretch in the Crowbar Motel, they suddenly &ldquo;realize&rdquo; that they are actually women trapped in men&rsquo;s bodies and they demand special accommodations. And if they live in a blue state on the West Coast, those demands are almost always met.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">If the details of those two killings don&rsquo;t do enough to send chills down your spine and make you realize how dangerous this guy almost certainly is (even at the age of 75), there is more. During court proceedings, the lead detective in the case told the judge that Buchanan had said he was worried that if police found &ldquo;the other seventeen&rdquo; bodies on his farm, he might never get out of jail. Police searched and did some digging, but additional bodies were not located. That doesn&rsquo;t mean they&rsquo;re not there, though. This guy is a certifiable lunatic who told the police &ldquo;I do not value human life very much.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">This is the sort of person we&rsquo;re putting in a women&rsquo;s prison? I&rsquo;m sure some of the actual females at Coffee Creek Correctional Facility did some bad things to wind up there, though hopefully not involving feeding body parts to swine. But do they deserve to be exposed to a proven homicidal maniac who is pretending to be a woman? Townhall has been covering stories like this for a while and it never seems to end well. One trans inmate in New Jersey wound up impregnating two female inmates. (His own mother said that the trans thing was a scam allowing him access to women.) Another inmate was sexually assaulted by a trans inmate..</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://www.breitbart.com/europe/2024/01/03/sweden-records-coldest-january-evening-in-25-years/"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.breitbart.com/europe/2024/01/03/sweden-records-coldest-january-evening-in-25-years/</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Sweden Records Coldest January Evening in 25 Years</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Europe experienced stark weather contrasts on Wednesday, with extreme cold and snowstorms disrupting transportation and closing schools in Scandinavia while strong winds and heavy rain in western Europe caused flooding and at least one death.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Temperatures fell below minus 40 degrees Celsius (minus 40 degrees Fahrenheit) in the Nordic region for a second day in a row Wednesday. In Kvikkjokk-&Aring;rrenjarka in Swedish Lapland, the mercury dropped to minus 43.6 C (minus 46.5 F), the lowest January temperature recorded in Sweden in 25 years, Sweden&rsquo;s TT news agency reported.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Extremely cold temperatures, snow and gale-force winds disrupted transportation throughout the Nordic region, with several bridges closed and some train and ferry services suspended. Several schools in Scandinavia were closed.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Police across most of Denmark urged motorists to avoid unnecessary trips as wind and snow battered the northern and western parts of the country.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Mild but wet and windy conditions prevailed further south, where a storm wreaked havoc in parts of western Europe.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">In Britain, a driver died after a tree fell on his car in western England. Gloucestershire Police said the man died in the incident near the town of Kemble on Tuesday afternoon.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The storm, which has been named Henk by the official weather services of Britain, Ireland and the Netherlands, has caused power cuts, transport troubles, property damage and disruption across the U.K.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">More than 300 flood warnings were in place across England and Wales on Wednesday, while 10,000 homes remained without power. A severe flood alert, meaning a danger to life, was announced for the River Nene in Northampton in central England. Several residents were evacuated from houseboats and caravans at the nearby Billing Aquadrome.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The U.K.&rsquo;s rail network was hit by flooding and power cuts, with many operators reporting ongoing issues for the Wednesday morning commute into work.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The strongest gales in the U.K. were recorded on the Isle of Wight, just off the coast in southern England, where wind speeds reached 94 miles per hour (151 kilometers per hour).</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">In the Netherlands, police near the city of Eindhoven said strong winds may have played a role in the death of a 75-year-old man who fell off his bicycle late Tuesday as high winds lashed much of the country.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Parts of Germany were also grappling with flooding, which could be aggravated by more rain falling in the worst-affected northwestern state of Lower Saxony.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://www.boundingintosports.com/2024/01/aaron-rodgers-says-jimmy-kimmel-is-worried-about-the-jeffrey-epstein-files-suggests-nfl-is-rigged/"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.boundingintosports.com/2024/01/aaron-rodgers-says-jimmy-kimmel-is-worried-about-the-jeffrey-epstein-files-suggests-nfl-is-rigged/</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Aaron Rodgers Says Jimmy Kimmel Is Worried About The Jeffrey Epstein Files, Suggests NFL Is Rigged</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">If you thought New York Jets quarterback Aaron Rodgers had any designs on pulling back on his opinions in the new year, think again. During an appearance on The Pat McAfee Show, the 40-year-old future NFL Hall of Famer suggested late-night talk show host Jimmy Kimmel might be nervous about the release of the Jeffrey Epstein files. Oh, and he also floated the idea that the NFL is rigged.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Aaron Rodgers kicked off a segment with the host by embracing a conspiracy theory that the Super Bowl logo features the colors of the teams that eventually end up playing in the game.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">An X post by NFL Memes in September included an image that explained the theory and showed recent examples. The group also predicted that based on this theory, the Baltimore Ravens and San Francisco 49ers would be facing each other in Super Bowl LVIII.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&ldquo;If the Super Bowl Baltimore and San Fran, I&rsquo;ll tell you what, that Super Bowl 59 emblem better have Jet green on it,&rdquo; Rodgers said.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&ldquo;I know you&rsquo;ve seen that one &hellip; that&rsquo;s a real interesting one,&rdquo; Rodgers said of the conspiracy theory.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://twitter.com/i/status/1742256969883492467"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://twitter.com/i/status/1742256969883492467</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> - Play Video&nbsp;</span></p>]]></description>
   <author><![CDATA[garrison Hardie]]></author>
   <enclosure url="https://app.dropwave.io/episode/017c1681-8632-424b-804d-0dae83fc3069/daily-news-brief-for-friday-january-5th-2024.mp3" length="957" type="audio/mp3"/>
   <guid isPermaLink="false"><![CDATA[017c1681-8632-424b-804d-0dae83fc3069]]></guid>
   <pubDate>Fri, 05 Jan 2024 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
   <source url=""><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></source>
   <itunes:author><![CDATA[garrison Hardie]]></itunes:author>
   <itunes:image href="https://assets-cdn2.dropwave.io/2ab40ac0-e99d-4f25-a6d2-541d2c9b290a/cover-art/mUK8zsnHkCK3vep7E1W6UgYb9dTnLenASAMEFha3.jpg"/>
   <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
   <itunes:duration>957</itunes:duration>
   <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
  
  </item>
 </channel>
</rss>
