<?xml version="1.0"?>
<?xml-stylesheet href="/storage/feed-stylesheet.xsl" type="text/xsl"?>

<rss xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
 <channel>
  <title>FLF - Daily News Brief</title>
  <link>https://dropwave.io</link>
  <description><![CDATA[FIGHT LAUGH FEAST PRESENTS SHOWS PROCLAIMING THE LORDSHIP OF CHRIST OVER ALL OF LIFE.
]]></description>
  <language>en</language>
  <managingEditor><![CDATA[fightlaughfeast@gmail.com (FLF, LLC)]]></managingEditor>
  <webMaster><![CDATA[support@dropwave.io (DropWave Support)]]></webMaster>
  <pubDate>Thu, 25 Jan 2024 01:25:53 +0000</pubDate>
  <lastBuildDate>Thu, 25 Jan 2024 01:25:53 +0000</lastBuildDate>
  <image>
   <url>https://is4-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Podcasts113/v4/58/56/52/5856525c-2973-cf29-3db9-21faa8595391/mza_1144696925612154085.png/1200x1200bb.jpg</url>
   <link>https://dropwave.io</link>
   <title><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></title>
  </image>
  <itunes:author><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></itunes:author>
  <itunes:image href="https://is4-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Podcasts113/v4/58/56/52/5856525c-2973-cf29-3db9-21faa8595391/mza_1144696925612154085.png/1200x1200bb.jpg"/>
  <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
  <itunes:owner>
   <itunes:name><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></itunes:name>
   <itunes:email>fightlaughfeast@gmail.com</itunes:email>
  </itunes:owner>
  <itunes:category text="News"/>
  <item>
   <title><![CDATA[Daily News Brief for Tuesday, January 23rd, 2024 [Daily News Brief]]]></title>
   <link/>
   <description><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">This is Garrison Hardie with your CrossPolitic Daily News Brief for Tuesday, January 23rd, 2024.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Sales Nexus LLC:&nbsp;</strong></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">SalesNexus is the platform Fight Laugh Feast uses to manage all of our subscribers and email updates.&nbsp; If you&rsquo;re using MailChimp, Hubspot or Salesforce for email marketing, CRM and sales, you probably know they&rsquo;ve been canceling voices of freedom and truth.&nbsp; That&rsquo;s why we switched to SalesNexus.&nbsp; SalesNexus is a complete business marketing and sales solution that won&rsquo;t tell you what you should say or believe. For more information, visit salesnexus.com. That&rsquo;s Salesnexus.com!</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://thepostmillennial.com/breaking-trump-leads-nikki-haley-by-19-points-in-nh-suffolk-boston-poll?utm_campaign=64487"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://thepostmillennial.com/breaking-trump-leads-nikki-haley-by-19-points-in-nh-suffolk-boston-poll?utm_campaign=64487</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Trump leads Nikki Haley by 19 points in NH: Suffolk Boston poll</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">A poll published ahead of Tuesday&rsquo;s primary election in New Hampshire has found that 2024 GOP frontrunner Donald Trump leads Nikki Haley, the only remaining challenger, by nearly 20 points.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">According to a Suffolk University/NBC10 Boston/Boston Globe tracking poll published on Monday, Trump leads Haley by 19 points. Trump received 57 percent support and Haley received 38 percent.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">With DeSantis dropping out of the race on Sunday, Haley gained two points.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The poll was conducted between January 20 and 21 of 500 likely Republican primary voters in the state. The poll has a margin of error of 4.4 percent.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">A Washington Post/Monmouth University poll, also released on Monday, placed Trump 18 points ahead of Haley, with 52 percent supporting the president and 34 percent backing Haley.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">DeSantis received 8 percent support, as the poll was conducted before the Florida governor dropped out of the race.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">This poll was conducted between January 16 and 20 of 712 potential voters in the New Hampshire Republican primary and has a margin of error of 4.2 percent.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://www.frontpagemag.com/vermont-resettled-somalis-shootings-are-up-185/"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.frontpagemag.com/vermont-resettled-somalis-shootings-are-up-185/</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Vermont Resettled Somalis, Shootings Are Up 185%</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Shootings are up 185% in Vermont from 2021 to 2022.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&ldquo;We are not used to this level of violence in Vermont,&rdquo; Burlington Mayor Miro Weinberger complained after the city racked up 5 murders. That may not sound like much, but it gives the normally sleepy city, where Bernie Sanders got his start, a higher murder rate than Philly.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">When James Eaton, a mentally unstable leftist who had praised Hamas, shot and wounded three Arab Muslim men outside his home, the media eagerly diverted attention from the crime wave to the shooter, who was conveniently white, while falsely blaming it on &lsquo;Islamophobia&rsquo;.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The discredited hoax was not only trying to rally support for terrorists, but also to distract attention from the real perpetrators of the violence that has overtaken Bernie&rsquo;s old city.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The shooters in Burlington, VT are much more likely to be Muslim male teens.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Another recent shooting out of Burlington made the national news when Hussein Mohamed, the underage son of Somali immigrants who don&rsquo;t speak English, shot and killed Madden: a local 14-year-old boy. It was reported that &ldquo;state police were able to make an arrest despite at least two eyewitnesses from the car providing multiple false statements about the crime.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The murder wave in Burlington was touched off in 2022 when a Muslim teen, shot and killed Hussein Mubarak, 21.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The 19-year-old had been part of a Somali Muslim refugee family profiled by the New York Times under the headline &ldquo;U.S. a Place of Miracles for Somali Refugees.&rdquo; Of that family, one son was convicted of assault with a firearm, another of &ldquo;aggravated assault for shooting a man in November 2020&rdquo; and the 19-year-old was the grandson of that same family.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The teen had allegedly become a member of a Somali gang that stole cars while &ldquo;wearing surgical gloves to avoid leaving fingerprints behind&rdquo; and two of them had attacked a man in broad daylight while wearing ski masks.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Mubarak had been born in a refugee camp before his family was resettled in America where his &ldquo;older and younger siblings&rdquo; spent time in jail, while he turned to selling drugs.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The reporting on the incident and other violent encounters in Burlington are littered with mentions of drug dealing, stolen cars and guns, shootings in garages and names like Mohamed, Ahmed Mohamed, Badal Khadka and Abukar.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Abukar Hilowle was accused of a few shootings, including one in which he allegedly shot the driver of the car he was in, resulting in a car crash, and another in which he shot two middle-aged American men on the street, one of whom had told him to &ldquo;chill&rdquo;, but the Muslim perpetrator claimed that he was responding to &ldquo;racial slurs&rdquo; by his two victims.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">In 2022 it was reported that, &ldquo;by mid-summer, about half of the city&rsquo;s gunfire incidents were connected to a small group of new American young men.&rdquo; The inaccurate euphemism &ldquo;new Americans&ldquo; was being used to refer to Somali and other often Muslim African immigrants.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The perps are usually repeat offenders who wander in and out of the justice system.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">In 2020, another Somali was arrested for aggravated assault during a fight over drugs. By 2022, when he was accused of trying to shoot his brother, he had racked up 47 police contacts and 11 arrests. Despite being briefly charged with attempted murder, his family refused to testify and he received a plea deal last year for time served.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Mayor Miro Weinberger however has claimed that the role of migrant settler teens in the wave of violence is not &ldquo;particularly relevant&rdquo;.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">When the three Arab Muslim men were shot, State&rsquo;s Attorney Sarah George rushed to claim, without a shred of evidence, that, &ldquo;there is no question this was a hateful act.&rdquo; But the Soros DA&nbsp; has been accused of giving violent drug gang members a pass for the sake of social justice.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Burlington&rsquo;s crime level rose sharply after the City Council had voted to defund 30% of the police department during the peak of the BLM race riots.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Burlington City Councilor Ali Dieng, an African Muslim immigrant who has run for mayor, has attacked the police while introducing resolutions to boycott Israel and has urged funding for social services to explore the &ldquo;root causes&rdquo; of the violence by members of his community.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Only a few hundred Somali Muslims were resettled in Burlington with horrifying consequences.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The question in Burlington, VT and across a nation under siege by hate, extremism, violence, crime and terror spread by first, second and third generation &lsquo;refugees&rsquo; is how much more can we take, how many more lives can we lose and how long can we go on living this way?</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://nypost.com/2024/01/22/business/in-n-out-burger-in-oakland-to-close-doors-for-good-over-of-out-of-control-crime-company-says/"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://nypost.com/2024/01/22/business/in-n-out-burger-in-oakland-to-close-doors-for-good-over-of-out-of-control-crime-company-says/</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>In-N-Out Burger in Oakland to close doors for good over of out-of-control crime, company says</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">In-N-Out Burger&rsquo;s only location in Oakland is closing after the cherished fast-food joint decided it could no longer risk the safety of fed-up workers and patrons in the city plagued by recent crime.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The location will shut its doors in March &mdash; despite the burger spot turning a profit &mdash; because of the constant crime in the community, In-N-Out Chief Operating Officer Denny Warnick said in a sudden announcement over the weekend.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The fast food joint has been in the California city for 18 years.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&ldquo;Despite taking repeated steps to create safer conditions, our Customers and Associates are regularly victimized by car break-ins, property damage, theft, and armed robberies,&rdquo; Warnick wrote, according to CBS East Bay, which obtained the announcement.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&ldquo;Additionally, this location remains a busy and profitable one for the company, but our top priority must be the safety and wellbeing of our Customers and Associates &ndash; we cannot ask them to visit or work in an unsafe environment,&rdquo; he said.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Data released by Oakland police at the start of the new year showed robberies increased 38% from 2022 to 2023, ABC 7 Bay Area reported.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Burglaries jumped 23% year-to-year and motor vehicle theft spiked 44%, the data showed.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Workers at Oakland&rsquo;s In-N-Out can either transfer to another one of the company&rsquo;s fast-food restaurants or accept a severance package.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://www.breitbart.com/sports/2024/01/20/the-kingdom-belongs-to-you-lord-ravens-john-harbaugh-opens-post-game-presser-by-reading-bible-verse/"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.breitbart.com/sports/2024/01/20/the-kingdom-belongs-to-you-lord-ravens-john-harbaugh-opens-post-game-presser-by-reading-bible-verse/</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>&lsquo;The Kingdom Belongs to You, Lord&rsquo;: Ravens&rsquo; John Harbaugh Opens Post-Game Presser by Reading Bible Verse</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">On Saturday, the Baltimore Ravens won their biggest game since they last won the Super Bowl over ten years ago. And in his post-game presser, coach John Harbaugh knew exactly who to thank for it.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">After the Ravens rallied from a 10-10 tie at halftime to thoroughly dominate the second half on their way to a 34-10 victory, Harbaugh opened his presser not by complimenting his future MVP quarterback (probably) but by thanking his Creator.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://twitter.com/i/status/1748892900195438908"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://twitter.com/i/status/1748892900195438908</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> - Play Video</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The verse is from 1 Chronicles 29: 11-13.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Harbaugh&rsquo;s bold statement of faith comes a week after NBC&rsquo;s official Sunday Night Football account edited out Texans quarterback CJ Stroud&rsquo;s comments where he said, &ldquo;All glory to my Lord and Savior Jesus Christ,&rdquo; following Houston&rsquo;s defeat of the Cleveland Browns.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The Ravens coach wasn&rsquo;t the only member of the Harbaugh family to speak out in defense of faith this week. John Harbaugh&rsquo;s brother, Michigan head coach Jim Harbaugh, spoke at the March for Life in Washington, D.C.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://twitter.com/i/status/1748419169358372904"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://twitter.com/i/status/1748419169358372904</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> - Play 0:36-1:55</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The Ravens will play the Kansas City Chiefs for the AFC Championship this weekend.</span></p>]]></description>
   <author><![CDATA[Garrison Hardie]]></author>
   <enclosure url="https://app.dropwave.io/episode/ade4d889-50b2-40b7-99c4-2a27cce4e775/daily-news-brief-for-tuesday-january-23rd-2024.mp3" length="695" type="audio/mp3"/>
   <guid isPermaLink="false"><![CDATA[ade4d889-50b2-40b7-99c4-2a27cce4e775]]></guid>
   <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2024 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
   <source url=""><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></source>
   <itunes:author><![CDATA[Garrison Hardie]]></itunes:author>
   <itunes:image href="https://assets-cdn2.dropwave.io/2ab40ac0-e99d-4f25-a6d2-541d2c9b290a/cover-art/mUK8zsnHkCK3vep7E1W6UgYb9dTnLenASAMEFha3.jpg"/>
   <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
   <itunes:duration>695</itunes:duration>
   <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
  
  </item><item>
   <title><![CDATA[Daily News Brief for Friday, January 19th, 2024 [Daily News Brief]]]></title>
   <link/>
   <description><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">This is Garrison Hardie with your CrossPolitic Daily News Brief for Friday, January 19th, 2024.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Samaritan Ministries January 2024</strong></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Tired of someone else telling you where to go when you have a medical need? Are you ready to</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">take control of your health care? Then it&rsquo;s time to take a look at Samaritan Ministries. It&rsquo;s</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Biblical, affordable health care sharing, with no restrictive networks. Here&rsquo;s how it works. When a medical need arises, you choose the health care provider that&rsquo;s right for you and have a say in the treatment you receive. Send your medical bills to Samaritan Ministries, and they&rsquo;ll notify fellow members to pray for you and send money directly to you to help you pay those bills.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Join 80,000 Christian households across the nation who have already taken control of their</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">health care. Go to samaritan ministries dot org slash cross politic.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://thenationalpulse.com/2024/01/18/gop-led-house-approves-bill-to-avoid-shutdown-without-border-spending-deals/"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://thenationalpulse.com/2024/01/18/gop-led-house-approves-bill-to-avoid-shutdown-without-border-spending-deals/</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>GOP-Led House Approves Bill to Avoid Shutdown Without Border, Spending Deals</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The U.S. House of Representatives voted late Thursday afternoon to extend government funding into early March and avoid a temporary partial government shutdown, sending the continuing resolution to President Biden to sign into law.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The measure, which passed by a vote of 314 to 108, angered conservative Republicans who opposed any continuing resolution to fund the government without concessions by the Democrats on border security and spending. The House Freedom Caucus made an eleventh-hour plea to House Speaker Mike Johnson to permit an amendment to the House&rsquo;s border security package, which Johnson rejected.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Freedom Caucus Chairman Bob Good slammed his fellow Republicans who supported the continuing resolution ahead of the vote. &ldquo;The more things change, the more things stay the same,&rdquo; he said in a floor speech. &ldquo;We&rsquo;re not even willing to risk a temporary pause in the 15 percent of the non-essential part of the government in order to force change in Washington,&rdquo; he said. &ldquo;No, we&rsquo;re going to continue the status quo.&rdquo; Good&rsquo;s statements echoed an official position on the measure released by the Freedom Caucus hours before the vote. &ldquo;Americans did not give Republicans a majority in the House to continue Nancy Pelosi&rsquo;s inflationary spending and Joe Biden&rsquo;s failed policies,&rdquo; the group wrote in a statement. &ldquo;This is not what we promised the American people.&rdquo;&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The vote is also likely to be unpopular with the Republican base, which consistently ranks immigration as one of the top issues facing the country. Over 80 percent of Republican voters agree with President Donald Trump that the ongoing border crisis is &ldquo;poisoning the blood&rdquo; of America.</span></p>
<p><a href="https://dailycaller.com/2024/01/17/blue-state-officials-pay-thousands-barring-church-preschool-lunch-program-beliefs-gender/"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://dailycaller.com/2024/01/17/blue-state-officials-pay-thousands-barring-church-preschool-lunch-program-beliefs-gender/</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Blue State Officials Agree To Pay Thousands After Barring Church From Preschool Lunch Program For Beliefs On Gender</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">California state officials agreed to settle with the Church of Compassion and Dayspring Christian Learning Center Tuesday for nearly $200,000 after trying to exclude the church from the state&rsquo;s preschool lunch program.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The church and the center, alongside Alliance Defending Freedom (ADF), filed a lawsuit in June last year alleging that officials with the U.S. Department of Agriculture and the California Department of Social Services barred them from participating in the &ldquo;Child and Adult Food Care Program&rdquo; because of their religious beliefs on gender and sex. ADF and state officials filed a settlement agreement this week requiring the defendants to pay $30,000 for meals paid out of pocket in the absence of state funding and $160,000 for attorney&rsquo;s fees.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&ldquo;In the name of combatting discrimination, government officials excluded the church and preschool from serving the El Cajon community based solely on their religious beliefs and exercise,&rdquo; Jeremiah Galus, senior counsel for ADF, said in a press release. &ldquo;While it shouldn&rsquo;t have taken a lawsuit to resolve this, at least now Church of Compassion can continue its vital outreach to needy children and families.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The center had been a part of the USDA&rsquo;s program for nearly two decades when the department changed its rules in 2021 requiring all participants to commit to not discriminate on the basis of sexual orientation and gender identity. In May 2023, the department also required state directors of USDA&rsquo;s food and nutrition service programs to prohibit &ldquo;discrimination on the basis of gender identity and sexual orientation.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Church of Compassion and Dayspring Christian Learning Center failed to meet these new requirements for the 2022-2023 school year because of their beliefs on &ldquo;human sexuality&rdquo; and their refusal to &ldquo;use any child or employee&rsquo;s &lsquo;preferred&rsquo; pronouns that do not correspond to biological sex,&rdquo; according to the lawsuit. ADF argued that the department and state officials were deliberately discriminating against the church and the learning center because of its faith in violation of the First Amendment.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&ldquo;The government can&rsquo;t withhold food from families in need simply because their children attend a Christian preschool. The Constitution protects the right of Church of Compassion and its preschool to operate according to the dictates of their faith,&rdquo; Galus said in the press release.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://townhall.com/tipsheet/madelineleesman/2024/01/17/lgbt-activist-arrested-child-predator-sting-n2633750"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://townhall.com/tipsheet/madelineleesman/2024/01/17/lgbt-activist-arrested-child-predator-sting-n2633750</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Director of LGBTQ+ Organization That Helps Minors Arrested in Child Sex Sting</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The executive director of the pro-LGBTQ+ organization Rainbow Research Center was apprehended on suspicion of attempting to engage in sexual activities with a minor, according to The Modesto Bee.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Reportedly, a total of 17 men were arrested on suspicion of eliciting sex with a minor after an undercover sting conducted by the Turlock Police Department in California. Gerard Slayton, 42, was one of them (via the Bee):</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Slayton recently was appointed executive director of the Rainbow Center, a local nonprofit organization that provides resources to LGBTQ+ members of all ages. It particularly offers resources related to mental and physical health.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">In a statement shared on Facebook, the Rainbow Resource Center said that Slayton&rsquo;s actions occurred &ldquo;outside working hours and off-premises.&rdquo;&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&ldquo;Mr. Slayton&rsquo;s actions do not represent our organization&rsquo;s values or mission. In accordance with our unwavering commitment to upholding the highest standards of conduct and integrity, we are addressing the issue within the Rainbow Resource Center,&rdquo; the statement read.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&ldquo;We are dedicated to rebuilding any trust that may have been affected by the situation. As an organization that is at the forefront of advocacy and support for the LGBTQ+ community, our actions must reflect our dedication to these principles,&rdquo; it continued.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://dailycaller.com/2024/01/17/beijing-china-wuhan-covid-19-100-percent-death-mice-study-full-paper/"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://dailycaller.com/2024/01/17/beijing-china-wuhan-covid-19-100-percent-death-mice-study-full-paper/</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Mutant COVID-19 Strain With 100% Kill Rate Developed In China</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">A pre-peer-reviewed study published in early January described how mice were exposed to a human-based &ldquo;lethal infection&rdquo; of COVID-19 with a 100% mortality rate.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The Beijing-based research paper was submitted to the scientific preprint site BioRXiv and published prior to peer review, but the data held within the pages is significant. Two SARS-CoV-2-related pangolin coronaviruses (GD/2019, GX/2017) were identified prior to the major COVID-19 outbreak in late 2019 through early 2020, according to the study&rsquo;s authors.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The researchers then isolated &ldquo;mutant&rdquo; strains, which were cultured in labs between 2017 and 2020. When the infectivity and pathogenicity of the isolates were tested, it was found to easily infect golden hamsters and mice. The first isolate pCoV-GD01 had a higher homology than COVID-19, whereas GX_P2V didn&rsquo;t seem to cause any disease in the animals despite infection.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">But an early passaged GX_P2V isolate, named GX_P2v(short_3UTR) not only infected mice with extremely high viral loads into their lung and brain tissue, but eventually killed 100% of the mice within the study. Even those mice who were given an inoculation (i.e., vaccinated) succumbed to the disease.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Autopsy of the mice showed viral RNA in the brain, lung, turbinate, eye and trachea, killing all of the mice within eight days of infection. All of the mice&rsquo;s eyes also went white the day before they died.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The authors argued this is the first report that COVID-19-related pangolin coronavirus can cause 100% mortality rates in mice, suggesting a significant risk of the disease spilling over into humans.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">But since the study is not peer-reviewed, there are huge questions about the efficacy of the results. &ldquo;I had a look at the preprint. It&rsquo;s a terrible study, scientifically totally pointless. I can see nothing of vague interest that could be learned from force-infecting a weird breed of humanised mice with a random virus. Conversely, I could see how such stuff might go wrong &hellip;&rdquo; University College London genetics director Francois Balloux wrote on Twitter. &ldquo;The preprint does not specify the biosafety level and biosafety precautions used for the research.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Balloux&rsquo;s statements were reiterated by Rutgers University chemistry professor Richard H. Ebright, who wrote &ldquo;concur&rdquo; under the comment.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">It appears the biggest concern is related to why scientists feel the need to develop these horrific diseases. &ldquo;The absence of this information raises the concerning possibility that part or all of this research, like the research in Wuhan in 2016-2019 that likely caused the Covid-19 pandemic, recklessly was performed without the minimal biosafety containment and practices essential for research with potential pandemic pathogens,&rdquo; Balloux concluded. And it&rsquo;s pretty hard to argue with his stance.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">China is already inching back toward lockdowns as mysterious viruses spread throughout the country. Most of these illnesses are being blamed on influenza strains and other respiratory diseases, but no single culprit has been identified to date.</span></p>]]></description>
   <author><![CDATA[Garrison Hardie]]></author>
   <enclosure url="https://app.dropwave.io/episode/434d72d3-785b-419d-98b7-cd7fe29c5f12/daily-news-brief-for-friday-january-19th-2024.mp3" length="582" type="audio/mp3"/>
   <guid isPermaLink="false"><![CDATA[434d72d3-785b-419d-98b7-cd7fe29c5f12]]></guid>
   <pubDate>Fri, 19 Jan 2024 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
   <source url=""><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></source>
   <itunes:author><![CDATA[Garrison Hardie]]></itunes:author>
   <itunes:image href="https://assets-cdn2.dropwave.io/2ab40ac0-e99d-4f25-a6d2-541d2c9b290a/cover-art/mUK8zsnHkCK3vep7E1W6UgYb9dTnLenASAMEFha3.jpg"/>
   <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
   <itunes:duration>582</itunes:duration>
   <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
  
  </item><item>
   <title><![CDATA[Daily News Brief for Thursday, January 18th, 2024 [Daily News Brief]]]></title>
   <link/>
   <description><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">This is Garrison Hardie with your CrossPolitic Daily News Brief for Thursday, January 18th, 2024.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>VanGelder Technologies:</strong></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">VanGelder Technologies is a US-based custom software development company specializing in cross-platform mobile applications, web applications, and desktop programs. Leveraging open-source frameworks, they quickly and efficiently build custom software solutions that are tailor made to fit your specific needs.   </span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">There&rsquo;s no need for New Christendom companies to be content with offering sub-par mobile or web experiences. VanGelder Technologies can help you build better software for the glory of God! You can learn more, view examples of their work, or get in touch, at www.vangelder.tech  </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">That&rsquo;s V-A-N, G-E-L, D-E-R dot T-E-C-H VanGelder Technologies, where technology and tradition meet.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://redstate.com/nick-arama/2024/01/17/tucker-decimates-nikki-haley-n2168832"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://redstate.com/nick-arama/2024/01/17/tucker-decimates-nikki-haley-n2168832</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Tucker Carlson Takes Down Nikki Haley With Brutal Video</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">In the wake of the Iowa caucuses, there are a lot of interesting reactions including those who believe that President Donald Trump is now the likely nominee, like Vivek Ramaswamy and Sen. Ted Cruz (R-TX), who both endorsed Trump.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Vivek even went on the road with him to New Hampshire to encourage people to vote for him.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Tucker Carlson, who is supportive of Trump, noted that Trump's win was historic, but the media was dealing with it with some pretty hilarious reactions - with Chris Wallace looking "sick" and Joy Reid blaming "white Christians" in Iowa and calling them racist.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">They were very upset, he observed.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">But he warned that Haley might do better in New Hampshire, that she had been spending far more money than Florida Gov. Ron DeSantis there. She also has the support of N.H. Gov. Chris Sununu.&nbsp; He said a lot of Haley's money came from "committed Democratic partisans." She's gotten money from people like Democratic megadonor Reid Hoffman, who has been a supporter of Joe Biden, a friend of Jeffrey Epstein, and the guy who funded the E. Jean Carroll lawsuit.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://twitter.com/i/status/1747274232093110614"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://twitter.com/i/status/1747274232093110614</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> - Play 4:48-9:03</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Never change Tucker&hellip;as always, you can find the link to Tucker&rsquo;s video in my show notes.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://www.dailywire.com/news/federal-government-to-spend-700k-on-trans-inclusive-sex-ed-for-14-year-olds"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.dailywire.com/news/federal-government-to-spend-700k-on-trans-inclusive-sex-ed-for-14-year-olds</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Federal Government To Spend $700k On Trans-Inclusive Sex Ed For 14-Year-Olds</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The Department of Health and Human Services (HHS) is awarding nearly $700,000 taxpayer dollars to back pregnancy prevention programs for young girls who identify as boys, warning that &ldquo;heteronormative&rdquo; sexual education is inadequate.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The $698,736 grant, which began in September 2023 and will continue until June 2027, according to government disclosures, will be allocated to the Center for Innovative Public Health Research, a non-profit that seeks to create &ldquo;an inclusive teen pregnancy program for transgender boys.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&ldquo;Youth who are assigned female at birth &hellip; are at risk for negative sexual health outcomes yet are effectively excluded from sexual health programs because gender-diverse youth do not experience the cisgender, heteronormative teen sexual education messaging available to them as salient or applicable,&rdquo; the award description claims.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The Center for Innovative Public Health Research aims to provide sex education via a program called &ldquo;Girl2Girl,&rdquo; which the organization describes as &ldquo;a text messaging based-sexual health program designed for cisgender sexual minority girls 14-18 years of age.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The center will then &ldquo;test the resulting adaptation&rdquo; in a national cohort of &ldquo;700 trans-identified AFAB youth 14-18 years of age,&rdquo; measuring their use of contraception and testing for sexually transmitted diseases, as well as pregnancy rates.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The funding from the HHS specifically comes from the National Institutes of Health&rsquo;s National Institute of Nursing Research. The National Institute of Nursing Research was given authority to spend a total of $57 million taxpayer dollars in fiscal year 2024.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The Center for Innovative Public Health Research is slated to receive another $1.4 million taxpayer dollars from HHS to develop a &ldquo;population-based HIV prevention program for trans girls,&rdquo; specifying that the program will &ldquo;address the lack of gender inclusive HIV prevention programming.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&ldquo;Messaging will be gender affirming&rdquo; and will &ldquo;reduce internalized transphobia,&rdquo; the award description adds.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">But the award for nearly $700,000 taxpayer dollars is not the only action that the HHS has taken to push transgenderism. The Daily Wire previously revealed that the National Institutes of Health (NIH), a subagency of the HHS, funded a study on the use of puberty blockers and cross-sex hormone treatment to the tune of $3 million despite transgender children&rsquo;s hospitals admitting that the practice could result in permanent sterilization.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://thepostmillennial.com/exclusive-maine-moves-to-create-sanctuary-state-for-child-sex-changes?utm_campaign=64487"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://thepostmillennial.com/exclusive-maine-moves-to-create-sanctuary-state-for-child-sex-changes?utm_campaign=64487</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Maine moves to create 'sanctuary state' for child sex changes</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">A Maine judiciary committee will decide on Wednesday morning whether a bill permitting minors to travel to the state to seek sex changes and granting the state custody over children will move to the floor.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">LD1735, also called An Act to Safeguard Gender-affirming Health Care, was introduced to the House of Representatives in the state in April of 2023 by Rep. Laurie Osher of Orono, and is cosponsored by Reps Erin Sheehan of Biddeford, Nina Milliken of Blue Hill, Suzanne Salisbury of Westbrook, Mark Worth of Ellsworth, and Rep. Matt Moonen of Portland as well as Senator Anne Carney of Cumberland.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Courage is a Habit, a group fighting for parental rights in states across the nation, is leading an effort to stop this bill.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Alvin Lui, president of Courage is a Habit, told The Post Millennial that people who do not live in Maine should contact the committee members as well as Maine residents as the bill "affects everybody&rsquo;s parental rights."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Sample emails provided by the group tell the members that "There is a lack of long-term studies on the benefits of 'gender-affirming care,&rsquo; which could result in the life-long sterilization and surgical mutilation of children," "With lawsuits against hospitals and schools on the rise in 2023, the public is becoming more aware of the potential risks associated with this bill," and "Protecting parental rights and the well-being of children should be our top priority. I urge you to vote "ought not to pass" on LD 1735."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">LD 1735 "prohibits the enforcement of an order based on another state's law authorizing a child to be removed from the child's parent or guardian based on that parent or guardian allowing the child to receive gender-affirming health care or gender-affirming mental health care."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">A law enforcement agency would be prohibited from knowingly making or participating in the arrest or extradition of an individual on an out-of-state warrant for violating another state&rsquo;s laws on bringing a child to Maine to give sex change treatments.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The bill updates rules on abandonment of a child or emergency situations, granting the State temporary emergency jurisdiction over the child if the child "has been unable to obtain gender-affirming health care or gender-affirming mental health care" because of a parent or guardian.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The bill also prevents courts from finding a case was brought forth in an "inconvenient forum," or the wrong court, "if the law or policy of another state that may take jurisdiction limits the ability of a parent to obtain gender-affirming health care or gender-affirming mental health care for a child and the provision of that care is at issue in the case before the court."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">LD1735 "prohibits a court from considering the taking or retention of a child from a person who has legal custody of the child if the taking or retention was for obtaining gender-affirming health care or gender-affirming mental health care for the child."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The bill mirrors similar laws passed in California, New Jersey, New York, Oregon, Washington and Minnesota.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Lui told The Post Millennial, "refuse to let your kindness be weaponized against you."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">"If you're wondering how you got there in Maine, wherever you live ... it's because over time, you've allowed your kindness to be weaponized against you and they kept moving that goalpost and now, even when they're proposing a transgender trafficking bill, they're still using emotional blackmail to try to get you to accept this," he said.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Lui said that "they&rsquo;re quite literally opening up trafficking avenues by inviting children from other states where their parents do not agree to transgender sterilization drugs and mutilating surgeries, and they're going to welcome these kids in Maine using your taxpayer dollars through Medicaid to pay for these procedures, putting them in foster care, opening them up to vulnerabilities like sex trafficking, like abuse, not to mention the lifelong, irreversible procedures and drugs that the transgender&nbsp; cult promotes."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">"So there is no slippery slope. You're here at the bottom now because they're willing to remove kids from parents, and the next step will be to remove your children from your home in Maine," Lui added, noting the instance of California.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://www.theblaze.com/news/teacher-of-the-year-says-he-was-reassigned-for-3-months-after-too-harshly-stopping-2-male-students-from-attacking-female"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.theblaze.com/news/teacher-of-the-year-says-he-was-reassigned-for-3-months-after-too-harshly-stopping-2-male-students-from-attacking-female</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Teacher of the Year says he was reassigned for 3 months after 'too harshly' stopping 2 male students from attacking female</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Kumar Rashad &mdash; who was named the Kentucky Department of Education's Teacher of the Year in September &mdash; told WDRB-TV that in October he was reassigned for three months after "too harshly" stopping two male students from attacking a female student.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">A math teacher in Louisville's Breckinridge Metropolitan High School, Rashad told the station after the incident officials reassigned him to "non-instructional duties" at the Special Needs East Bus Compound.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">WDRB said Jefferson County Public Schools wouldn't say why Rashad was reassigned &mdash; but he gave his side of the story Thursday, one day before he began resuming his teaching duties.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">"I saw two males attack a female, and I went to the female's rescue, and I removed the two students off of that female," Rashad told the station. "The two students said I removed them too harshly."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Rashad noted to WLKY-TV that the two male students complained about him to the powers that be.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">He was not about to apologize, however, telling WLKY: "Please understand, in the community, in school, anywhere I am going, I will never allow a lady to be attacked by a male."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://youtu.be/bJoR4AeYyFc"><span style="font-weight: 400;" data-rich-links="{&quot;fple-t&quot;:&quot;Kentucky's 2024 Teacher of the Year reinstated by JCPS, says he was reassigned for breaking up fight&quot;,&quot;fple-u&quot;:&quot;https://youtu.be/bJoR4AeYyFc&quot;,&quot;fple-mt&quot;:null,&quot;type&quot;:&quot;first-party-link&quot;}">Kentucky's 2024 Teacher of the Year reinstated by JCPS, says he was reassigned for breaking up fight</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;">-Play 0:30-0:49</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Rashad added to WDRB that the investigation is over, and he was cleared to return Friday to the classroom &mdash; which the school district confirmed.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://www.breitbart.com/politics/2024/01/16/here-we-go-wef-hosts-panel-tomorrow-for-disease-x/"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.breitbart.com/politics/2024/01/16/here-we-go-wef-hosts-panel-tomorrow-for-disease-x/</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>WEF Hosts Panel Tomorrow for &lsquo;Disease X&rsquo;</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Klaus Schwab, the World Economic Forum (WEF), and the so-called global elites are gathering for a five-day annual meeting in Davos, Switzerland, from January 15-19. One of the topics on the agenda for January 17 has raised some eyeballs: &ldquo;Preparing for Disease X.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">COVID has been reported to have claimed approximately 7 million lives worldwide, but &ldquo;Disease X,&rdquo; on the other hand, they warn, &ldquo;could result in 20 times more fatalities than the coronavirus pandemic.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Something interesting about people in power is that a not insignificant number of them also happen to believe that the world is overpopulated. If a pandemic 20 times as deadly as COVID did happen, claiming 140 million lives, would global leaders mourn or secretly celebrate that the world&rsquo;s population was curbed?</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Yuval Noah Harari, one of Barack Obama&rsquo;s favorite authors and a frequent speaker at Davos, has said that &ldquo;the big political and economic question of the 21st century will be, &lsquo;What do we need humans for?&rsquo; or at least, &lsquo;What do we need so many humans for?&rsquo;&rdquo;</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Remember, in October 2019 &mdash; just months before COVID-19 was identified in Wuhan &mdash; The Johns Hopkins Center for Health Security in partnership with the WEF and the Bill and Melinda Gates Foundation hosted Event 201, described as &ldquo;a high-level pandemic exercise.&rdquo; Is it out of the question to think another so-called pandemic could be just around the corner?</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Doctors like Peter McCullough and James Thorp stress the importance of being prepared and having life-saving medications on hand for whatever emergency &mdash; pandemic or not &mdash; life throws at you next.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&ldquo;You&rsquo;ve seen all the threats from the establishment suggesting that there&rsquo;s not going to be drug availability in the not-too-distant future,&rdquo; obstetrician-gynecologist and maternal-fetal medicine specialist Dr. James Thorp warns. &ldquo;They tell us &mdash; they&rsquo;re threatening us that there&rsquo;s another pandemic coming. So, look at that and protect yourselves.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">So, what should we be doing?</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&ldquo;Stocking up,&rdquo; urged Dr. Thorp. &ldquo;I&rsquo;ve been doing this since 1995 &mdash; always stocking up I&rsquo;ve been doing that for 20 years, and trust me, even before the pandemic, it saved a lot of my patients and family members because when they need the drugs, they can&rsquo;t get them.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The Wellness Company has put together a Medical Emergency Kit of eight potentially life-saving medications, which includes Ivermectin and Z-Pak, for the treatment of a range of illnesses, including strep throat, pneumonia, COVID-19, nausea and vomiting, and more.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The full list is linked in the article in my show notes.&nbsp;</span></p>]]></description>
   <author><![CDATA[Garrison Hardie]]></author>
   <enclosure url="https://app.dropwave.io/episode/1f43437d-9ebe-432b-9688-8c855bfc0027/daily-news-brief-for-thursday-january-18th-2024.mp3" length="815" type="audio/mp3"/>
   <guid isPermaLink="false"><![CDATA[1f43437d-9ebe-432b-9688-8c855bfc0027]]></guid>
   <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jan 2024 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
   <source url=""><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></source>
   <itunes:author><![CDATA[Garrison Hardie]]></itunes:author>
   <itunes:image href="https://assets-cdn2.dropwave.io/2ab40ac0-e99d-4f25-a6d2-541d2c9b290a/cover-art/mUK8zsnHkCK3vep7E1W6UgYb9dTnLenASAMEFha3.jpg"/>
   <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
   <itunes:duration>815</itunes:duration>
   <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
  
  </item><item>
   <title><![CDATA[Daily News Brief for Wednesday, January 17th, 2024 [Daily News Brief]]]></title>
   <link/>
   <description><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">This is Garrison Hardie with your CrossPolitic Daily News Brief for Wednesday, January 17th, 2024.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>CrossPolitic Email List:</strong></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Are you subscribed to our CrossPolitic email list? If you&rsquo;re not you really should be. Being subscribed to our email list means you won&rsquo;t miss any updates about CrossPolitic or the Fight Laugh Feast Network! You&rsquo;ll hear about what&rsquo;s on the schedule for the week, live events, conference updates, Rowdy Christian Merch, updates from other shows within the Fight Laugh Feast Network, and you&rsquo;ll hear from sponsors on the show, as they seek to take dominion for God&rsquo;s Kingdom in the business world. To subscribe, simply enter your email address at the bottom of the page at fightlaughfeast.com. Again, that&rsquo;s fightlaughfeast.com.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://www.foxnews.com/politics/trump-narrowly-denied-clean-sweep-iowas-99-counties-1-vote"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.foxnews.com/politics/trump-narrowly-denied-clean-sweep-iowas-99-counties-1-vote</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Trump narrowly denied clean sweep of Iowa's 99 counties by 1 vote</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Former President Donald Trump won 98 out of 99 Iowa counties during Monday's dominating victory in the Republican caucuses.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The one county that did not go for Trump was Johnson County, where former South Carolina Gov. Nikki Haley led Trump by one vote with 99% of votes counted. Haley received 1,271 votes, approximately 35.5% of the vote in Johnson County, while Trump received 1,270 votes, according to GOP officials in the state.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Haley finished third statewide behind Florida Gov. Ron DeSantis. Trump pulled in a majority of votes with 51%.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Haley claimed her third-place finish was evidence of momentum when considering polling numbers in upcoming primary states.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">"When you look at how well we&rsquo;re doing in New Hampshire, in South Carolina and beyond, I can safely say tonight Iowa made this Republican primary a two-person race," Haley said.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">DeSantis visited every county and invested significant time and resources in the Hawkeye State, and weeks ago was predicting he would win the caucuses. Recently he had been saying he embraced the underdog role in the state.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">"Because of your support, in spite of all of what they threw at us, we got our ticket punched out of Iowa," DeSantis said in his speech.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">DeSantis outperformed some polling expectations on Monday night, finishing at roughly 21% when the Real Clear Politics average of polls showed him at 15.7% before votes were cast.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">"They threw everything at Ron DeSantis," a senior DeSantis campaign official told Fox News Digital late Monday night. "They couldn&rsquo;t kill him. He is not only still standing, but he&rsquo;s now earned his ticket out of Iowa. This is going to be a long battle ahead, but that is what this campaign is built for. The stakes are too high for this nation and we will not back down."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Trump currently holds large leads in the polls in both New Hampshire and South Carolina. The former president, according to the Real Clear Politics average of polls, holds a 14-point lead in New Hampshire and a 30-point lead in South Carolina.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2024/01/16/nikki-haley-refuses-more-presidential-debates-unless-trump-participates.html"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.cnbc.com/2024/01/16/nikki-haley-refuses-more-presidential-debates-unless-trump-participates.html</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Nikki Haley refuses more presidential debates unless Trump participates</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Nikki Haley said she would not participate in any further primary debates unless front-runner Donald Trump is on stage.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The former president won a landslide victory Monday in the Iowa Caucus, the first contest of the 2024 presidential nomination. Haley placed third in Iowa, with 19.1% of the vote.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Florida Gov. Ron DeSantis accused Haley of not wanting to answer &ldquo;tough questions&rdquo; on topics such as her alleged dealings with aircraft manufacturer Boeing while she was governor of South Carolina.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&ldquo;The reality is that she is not running for the nomination, she&rsquo;s running to be Trump&rsquo;s VP,&rdquo; DeSantis posted to X, formerly known as Twitter, on Tuesday. &ldquo;I won&rsquo;t snub New Hampshire voters like both Nikki Haley and Donald Trump, and plan to honor my commitments. I look forward to debating two empty podiums in the Granite State this week.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The next GOP primary debate is scheduled for Thursday, days before the New Hampshire primary on Jan. 23. Polls have Haley running just behind Trump in the state, some polls by as little as 7 points.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://redstate.com/jenvanlaar/2024/01/15/watch-vivek-ramaswamy-addresses-supporters-in-iowa-n2168776"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://redstate.com/jenvanlaar/2024/01/15/watch-vivek-ramaswamy-addresses-supporters-in-iowa-n2168776</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Vivek Ramaswamy Suspends Presidential Campaign, Endorses Donald Trump</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Presidential candidate Vivek Ramaswamy, fresh off a 4th-place finish in Iowa, addressed his supporters and announced that he is suspending his campaign.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Ramaswamy spoke for just about 10 minutes before taking questions/comments from supporters. He told his supporters that he'd promised them he would tell the truth and be realistic, and that acknowledging hard truths required him to say that there was no path for him to be the nominee. He told his supporters that he is committed to America First principles and that Trump is the candidate who will do things like get rid of the deep state, restore national pride, and eliminate a chunk of federal bureaucracy.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">He ended his comments by assuring supporters that this is just the start of their movement.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://thepostmillennial.com/nypd-stop-man-for-smoking-in-subway-then-arrest-him-on-murder-charges-from-2020?utm_campaign=64487"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://thepostmillennial.com/nypd-stop-man-for-smoking-in-subway-then-arrest-him-on-murder-charges-from-2020?utm_campaign=64487</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>NYPD stop man for smoking in subway&mdash;then arrest him on murder charges from 2020</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">A man was arrested for an alleged murder that took place in Queens in 2020 after he was stopped by the New York Police Department for smoking in the subway.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Brooklyn transit cops stopped the 36-year-old Luis Hernandez after he was seen smoking on the subway on Friday. Under normal circumstances, Hernandez would have been released with a simple court summons, but he was held up after officers scanned his name and found out he was wanted for murder, Daily News reports.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Police took Hernandez to Queens and showed him video and photos showing him at a murder scene on 31st St. near 36th Ave. in Astoria, according to authorities.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Police say Hernandez and three or four others took part in the murder of Richard Hernandez, 21 on Feb. 9, 2020.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&ldquo;Mr. Hernandez has pleaded not guilty and fully intends on fighting the charges against him,&rdquo; his attorney, Mahmoud Rabah, told the Daily News on Monday.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&ldquo;Mr. Hernandez is a committed father of a young child,&rdquo; Rabah claimed. &ldquo;He is a hardworking immigrant who has held a stable job in a meat processing plant for years. He completely maintains his innocence and looks forward to his day in court.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Hernandez has no prior arrests and was arraigned in Queens Criminal Court on Sunday.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The victim, who is not related to Luis, was out with friends when a fight erupted. Witnesses told the Daily News that at least one attacker was armed with a machete, and another a knife. The victim was slain just a few blocks away from where he lived, and ultimately could not be saved after being taken to Mount Sinai Queens. Three other men sustained minor wounds during the brawl, police reported at the time.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Police said on Monday that the attack was linked to gang activity. Authorities remain in pursuit of Hernandez's accomplices.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://notthebee.com/article/coming-soon-someone-made-a-video-showing-what-your-flights-will-look-like-in-our-very-progressive-future"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://notthebee.com/article/coming-soon-someone-made-a-video-showing-what-your-flights-will-look-like-in-our-very-progressive-future</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>"Coming soon": Someone made a parody showing what flights will look like in our progressive future</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Ah, Diversity, Equity, and Inclusion. It's to die for.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://twitter.com/i/status/1747091085736730872"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://twitter.com/i/status/1747091085736730872</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> - Play Video&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Here you thought Final Destination was just a work of fiction! If you want to watch the video rather than just hearing it, you can do so by finding the link in my show notes&hellip;&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://www.breitbart.com/sports/2024/01/14/oh-hes-pssed-the-internet-reacts-to-jerry-jones-visible-anger-after-cowboys-humiliating-loss-to-green-bay/"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.breitbart.com/sports/2024/01/14/oh-hes-pssed-the-internet-reacts-to-jerry-jones-visible-anger-after-cowboys-humiliating-loss-to-green-bay/</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Jerry Jones&rsquo; Visible Anger After Cowboys Humiliating Loss to Green Bay</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">As expected, the Cowboys-Packers game was a blowout. Unexpectedly, it was the Cowboys who got blown out.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The Packers raced to a 27-7 halftime via a fast-paced, deep-ball attacking offense complimented by an explosive running game from Aaron Jones and aided by two interceptions from a defense that seemed determined to make everyone forget about their late-season struggles.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Trailing 48-16 with less than six minutes to go, the Cowboys flurried for two scores to make things look more respectable. But, while things may have looked better on the scoreboard, judging by the expression on Cowboys Owner Jerry Jones&rsquo; face, it didn&rsquo;t really help matters.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Nor did things look any better when Jones walked towards the locker room with his entourage.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Jones&rsquo; words couldn&rsquo;t have been very consoling to head coach Mike McCarthy or QB Dak Prescott, and just a quick warning, there&rsquo;s a little language involved.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://twitter.com/i/status/1746662526643782140"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://twitter.com/i/status/1746662526643782140</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> - Play Video&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Oh I&rsquo;m sorry - what he actually said was:&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&ldquo;I say this to our fans, how much you deserve us not to have this ending,&rdquo; Jones told reporters immediately after the loss. &ldquo;In no way have I spent any of my time over the last three hours asking how and why. And what I&rsquo;m zeroed in on is the fact that I thought we were positioned, everybody in this room thought [we] were in a position, to advance this thing in the playoffs and maybe get as far as our dreams might take us. We didn&rsquo;t do it.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p><br /><br /></p>]]></description>
   <author><![CDATA[Garrison Hardie]]></author>
   <enclosure url="https://app.dropwave.io/episode/8371fe62-0b65-4fca-8e7d-0f1ed63efe6d/daily-news-brief-for-wednesday-january-17th-2024.mp3" length="607" type="audio/mp3"/>
   <guid isPermaLink="false"><![CDATA[8371fe62-0b65-4fca-8e7d-0f1ed63efe6d]]></guid>
   <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jan 2024 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
   <source url=""><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></source>
   <itunes:author><![CDATA[Garrison Hardie]]></itunes:author>
   <itunes:image href="https://assets-cdn2.dropwave.io/2ab40ac0-e99d-4f25-a6d2-541d2c9b290a/cover-art/mUK8zsnHkCK3vep7E1W6UgYb9dTnLenASAMEFha3.jpg"/>
   <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
   <itunes:duration>607</itunes:duration>
   <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
  
  </item><item>
   <title><![CDATA[Daily News Brief for Tuesday, January 16th, 2024 [Daily News Brief]]]></title>
   <link/>
   <description><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">This is Garrison Hardie with your CrossPolitic Daily News Brief for Tuesday, January 16th, 2024.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Page50 ad read concepts:</strong></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Page50 is a distinctly Christian marketing company striving to help Christian-owned businesses grow and succeed in our digital age. They don&rsquo;t want to just make a paycheck, they want to&nbsp;</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">change the world, and that means building it alongside you.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The mission is bigger than just Sunday. Page50 wants to help Christians recapture the work week, economic and political influence, and the public square.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Page50 doesn&rsquo;t work with just anybody, but if you&rsquo;re a believer they want to work with you. Visit pagefifty.com and see what they can do for you. That&rsquo;s pagefifty.com.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://thepostmillennial.com/faa-is-actively-recruiting-people-with-severe-intellectual-and-psychiatric-disabilities-as-part-of-diversity-and-inclusion-plan?utm_campaign=64487"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://thepostmillennial.com/faa-is-actively-recruiting-people-with-severe-intellectual-and-psychiatric-disabilities-as-part-of-diversity-and-inclusion-plan?utm_campaign=64487</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Biden's FAA is actively recruiting people with &lsquo;severe intellectual&rsquo; and &lsquo;psychiatric&rsquo; disabilities as part of 'Diversity and Inclusion' plan</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The Federal Aviation Administration (FAA) places a priority on hiring people with "severe intellectual disability" as part of its diversity and inclusion initiative.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">According to its website, the FAA claims, "Individuals with targeted or 'severe' disabilities are the most under-represented segment of the Federal workforce."&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Under its People with Disabilities Program, the agency says it "actively recruits, hires, promotes, retains, develops and advances people with disabilities." The FAA targets the following disabilities as a matter of policy: "Hearing, vision, missing extremities, partial paralysis, complete paralysis, epilepsy, severe intellectual disability, psychiatric disability and dwarfism."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The FAA told Fox News that it "seeks qualified candidates from as many sources as possible, all of whom must meet rigorous qualifications that of course will vary by position."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Its website reveals that those with disabilities or those who have a veteran status can also be hired via the non-competitive, "on-the-spot" process as long as a manager files the proper paperwork, thus giving them preferential treatment in the hiring process.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The aviation industry has received further scrutiny from the public in the wake of an Alaska Airlines door plug being blown off the side of its two-month-old Boeing 737-9 MAX aircraft causing it to make an emergency landing.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">In a post on X, tech mogul Elon Musk asked, "Do you want to fly in an airplane where they prioritize DEI hiring over your safety?" He added, "That is actually happening."&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">"People will die due to DEI," Musk said.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Musk's comments came in response to a report that revealed in 2022 that Boeing began prioritizing Diversity, Equity, and Inclusion (DEI) as part of its hiring process in 2022.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The Alaskan Airlines situation came on the heels of a shocking report in December, which showed there were 19 instances where planes nearly crashed into each other at airports in the first ten months of 2023.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/news/business/2795955/shark-tank-powerhouse-investor-says-he-wont-invest-in-california-bad-policy/"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/news/business/2795955/shark-tank-powerhouse-investor-says-he-wont-invest-in-california-bad-policy/</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Shark Tank powerhouse investor says he won&rsquo;t invest in California: &lsquo;Bad policy&rsquo;</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Kevin O&rsquo;Leary of Shark Tank revealed he would not make business investments in several Democratic states, including California.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">O&rsquo;Leary explained his reasoning in a yet-to-be-released episode of Sen. Marsha Blackburn&rsquo;s (R-TN) show Unmuted. According to a transcript reviewed by Townhall, the politics of a state help O&rsquo;Leary determine where to invest.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&ldquo;I&rsquo;m not trying to get involved in the partisanship of this statement. Just a fact, I don&rsquo;t invest in New York, I don&rsquo;t invest in Massachusetts, I don&rsquo;t invest in California. In my mind, those are examples of states that are uninvestable because of bad policy,&rdquo; O&rsquo;Leary said. &ldquo;So, I&rsquo;m looking for the path of least resistance. If you make it hard for me to make money, I just take my money and go somewhere else.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">California in particular is ranked in the top ten for sales taxes and corporate taxes, according to the Tax Foundation, while New York is in the top ten only for its sales tax.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">O&rsquo;Leary pointed to Tennessee as an example of a state with &ldquo;fantastic tax policy, reduced regulatory environment, reduced permitting time.&rdquo; Any other state that doesn&rsquo;t implement these business-friendly policies is at risk of &ldquo;killing jobs,&rdquo; according to O&rsquo;Leary.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The Canadian investor started his own venture capital firm O&rsquo;Leary Ventures last year, over 15 years after his first appearance on Shark Tank where he spends episodes deciding in what small businesses he desires to invest.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://www.breitbart.com/politics/2024/01/15/report-white-house-swatted-prank-caller-claiming-residence-on-fire/"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.breitbart.com/politics/2024/01/15/report-white-house-swatted-prank-caller-claiming-residence-on-fire/</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>White House Swatted by &lsquo;Prank Caller&rsquo; Claiming Residence on Fire</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Fire trucks and ambulances reportedly rushed to the White House Monday morning around seven o&rsquo;clock after a &ldquo;prank caller&rdquo; claimed the residence was on fire and someone was trapped inside.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The incident represents the latest swatting event against political officials. Dangerous swatting events appear to have first been instigated by Democrat prank callers against political opponents.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The prank call at the White House forced fire trucks and ambulances to rush to a snow-covered White House, the Daily Mail reported.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">After arriving, the District of Columbia Fire and Emergency Medical Services and the U.S. Secret Service determined the incident was a false alarm.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&ldquo;Fire in the White House, 1600 Pennsylvania Avenue,&rdquo; a Washington, DC, dispatcher said at 7:04 a.m.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Authorities gave an &ldquo;all clear&rdquo; order at 7:15 AM.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">President Joe Biden was located at Camp David on Monday morning, far away from the residence.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Authorities traced the prank call to an apparently spoofed phone number, a source told CNN.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&ldquo;Someone who was reached at the callback number for the 911 report indicated they did not place it, a source told the Associated Press, indicating it was likely spoofed,&rdquo; the Daily Mail reported.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Recent politicians who were swatted include Sen. Rick Scott (R-FL) and Rep. Marjorie Taylor Greene (R-GA), along with celebrities Ashton Kutcher, Justin Bieber, and Kim Kardashian.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://abcnews.go.com/Business/wireStory/yemen-houthi-rebels-fire-missile-us-warship-red-106370679"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://abcnews.go.com/Business/wireStory/yemen-houthi-rebels-fire-missile-us-warship-red-106370679</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Houthi rebels strike a U.S.-owned ship off the coast of Yemen in the Gulf of Aden, raising tensions</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Houthi rebels fired a missile, striking a U.S.-owned ship Monday just off the coast of Yemen in the Gulf of Aden, less than a day after they launched an anti-ship cruise missile toward an American destroyer in the Red Sea.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The attack on the Gibraltar Eagle, later claimed by the Houthis, further escalates tensions gripping the Red Sea after American-led strikes on the rebels. The Houthis' attacks have roiled global shipping, amid Israel's war with Hamas in the Gaza Strip, targeting a crucial corridor linking Asian and Mideast energy and cargo shipments to the Suez Canal onward to Europe.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The United Kingdom Maritime Trade Operations, which oversees Mideast waters, said Monday's attack happened some 110 miles (177 kilometers) miles southeast of Aden. It said the ship&rsquo;s captain reported that the &ldquo;port side of vessel hit from above by a missile.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Private security firms Ambrey and Dryad Global told The Associated Press that the vessel was the Eagle Gibraltar, a Marshall Islands-flagged bulk carrier. The U.S. military's Central Command later acknowledged the strike.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&ldquo;The ship has reported no injuries or significant damage and is continuing its journey,&rdquo; Central Command said.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Houthi military spokesman Brig. Gen. Yahya Saree claimed the attack in a recorded television address that aired Monday night.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&ldquo;The Yemeni armed forces consider all American and British ships and warships participating in the aggression against our country as hostile targets,&rdquo; he said.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The vessel is owned by Eagle Bulk Shipping, a Stamford, Connecticut-based firm traded on the New York Stock Exchange. In a statement to the AP, the company acknowledged the strike and said it caused &ldquo;limited damage to a cargo hold but (the ship) is stable and is heading out of the area.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&ldquo;All seafarers onboard the vessel are confirmed to be uninjured,&rdquo; the firm said. &ldquo;The vessel is carrying a cargo of steel products. Eagle Bulk management is in close contact with all relevant authorities concerning this matter.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Satellite-tracking data analyzed by the AP showed the Eagle Gibraltar had been bound for the Suez Canal, but rapidly turned around at the time of the attack.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Central Command said it detected a separate anti-ship ballistic missile launch toward the southern Red Sea on Monday, though it &rdquo;failed in flight and impacted on land in Yemen."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The U.S. Maritime Administration, under the Transportation Department, also issued a warning Monday saying there continues to be &ldquo;a high degree of risk to commercial vessels&rdquo; traveling near Yemen.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&ldquo;While the decision to transit remains at the discretion of individual vessels and companies, it is recommended that U.S. flag and U.S.-owned commercial vessels&rdquo; stay away from Yemen in the Red Sea and Gulf of Aden &ldquo;until further notice,&rdquo; the advisory said.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Sunday's missile launch toward the American warship also marked the first U.S.-acknowledged fire by the Houthis since America and allied nations began strikes Friday on the rebels following weeks of assaults on shipping in the Red Sea.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The Houthi fire in the direction of the USS Laboon, an Arleigh Burke-class destroyer operating in the southern reaches of the Red Sea, Central Command said.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The missile came from near Hodeida, a Red Sea port city long held by the Houthis, the U.S. said.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&ldquo;An anti-ship cruise missile was fired from Iranian-backed Houthi militant areas of Yemen toward USS Laboon,&rdquo; Central Command said. &ldquo;There were no injuries or damage reported."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The Houthis did not acknowledge that attack.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">It wasn&rsquo;t presently clear whether the U.S. would retaliate for the latest attacks, though President Joe Biden has said he &ldquo;will not hesitate to direct further measures to protect our people and the free flow of international commerce as necessary.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The first day of U.S.-led strikes Friday hit 28 locations and struck more than 60 targets with cruise missiles and bombs launched by fighter jets, warships and a submarine. Sites hit included weapon depots, radars and command centers, including in remote mountain areas, the U.S. has said.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The Houthis have yet to acknowledge how severe the damage was from the strikes, which they said killed five of their troops and wounded six others.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">U.S. forces followed up with a strike Saturday on a Houthi radar site.</span></p>]]></description>
   <author><![CDATA[Garrison Hardie]]></author>
   <enclosure url="https://app.dropwave.io/episode/eac98e01-ec55-42b4-93f1-9af791fa0a0a/daily-news-brief-for-tuesday-january-16th-2024.mp3" length="638" type="audio/mp3"/>
   <guid isPermaLink="false"><![CDATA[eac98e01-ec55-42b4-93f1-9af791fa0a0a]]></guid>
   <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2024 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
   <source url=""><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></source>
   <itunes:author><![CDATA[Garrison Hardie]]></itunes:author>
   <itunes:image href="https://assets-cdn2.dropwave.io/2ab40ac0-e99d-4f25-a6d2-541d2c9b290a/cover-art/mUK8zsnHkCK3vep7E1W6UgYb9dTnLenASAMEFha3.jpg"/>
   <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
   <itunes:duration>638</itunes:duration>
   <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
  
  </item><item>
   <title><![CDATA[Daily News Brief for Thursday, January 11th, 2024 [Daily News Brief]]]></title>
   <link/>
   <description><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">This is Garrison Hardie with your CrossPolitic Daily News Brief for Thursday, January 11th, 2024.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Pub Membership Plug:</strong></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Public Houses, or Pubs, are not just places to drink beer, wine, cider or even something a little stronger. It is also a unique social centre, very often the focus of community life in villages, towns and cities throughout the length and breadth of the world. We here at CrossPolitic hope to emulate that for you and yours. That&rsquo;s why you should grab yourself a pub membership at fightlaughfeast.com&hellip; we need you on this ride with us. So pull up a chair, grab a pint, and join us on this ride at fightlaughfeast.com - that&rsquo;s fightlaughfeast.com.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://thepostmillennial.com/breaking-hunter-biden-shows-up-at-house-while-oversight-considers-contempt-resolution-against-him?utm_campaign=64487"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://thepostmillennial.com/breaking-hunter-biden-shows-up-at-house-while-oversight-considers-contempt-resolution-against-him?utm_campaign=64487</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Hunter Biden makes surprise appearance at Oversight contempt proceeding in congress, then storms out</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">After defying a Congressional subpoena in December, Hunter Biden made a surprise appearance at Wednesday&rsquo;s markup meeting in which lawmakers on the House Oversight Committee are working on a resolution to hold the president&rsquo;s son in contempt of Congress.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">House Oversight member Nancy Mace addressed Biden directly.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://twitter.com/i/status/1745105809439150194"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://twitter.com/i/status/1745105809439150194</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> - Play Video&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">When Rep Marjorie Taylor Greene began speaking Hunter Biden stormed out, with Greene telling him as he left, "Apparently you&rsquo;re afraid of my words."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://twitter.com/i/status/1745108562043437517"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://twitter.com/i/status/1745108562043437517</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> - Play 0:00-0:39</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Then as Hunter Biden was exiting the building, a man asked him on numerous occasions, &ldquo;are you on crack today?&rdquo;&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://twitter.com/i/status/1745107221992632623"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://twitter.com/i/status/1745107221992632623</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> - Play Video&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Hunter Biden attorney Abbe Lowell addressed reporters in the halls of Congress, saying that "Republicans have sought to use [Hunter Biden} as a surrogate to attack his father."</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Lowell said that "we have offered to work with House committees to see what and how relevant information to any legitimate inquiry could be provided."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">"Our first five offers were ignored. And then in November, they issued a subpoena for a behind-closed-doors deposition, a tactic that the Republicans have repeatedly misused in their political crusade to selectively leave and mischaracterize what witnesses have said."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Hunter Biden was subpoenaed to appear for a closed-door deposition on December 13, 2023. He refused to attend this deposition, instead speaking from the Capitol lawn.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Hunter Biden declared that he would only appear in a public session, but Committee on House Administration rules states that depositions of a witness are to take place only in the presence of the "Committee, Committee staff designed by the Chairman or the ranking minority member, an official reporter, the witness, and the witness&rsquo; two designated attorneys." Hunter Biden, however, doesn't think this rule should apply to him.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://www.theblaze.com/news/mexican-president-demands-20-billion-and-work-permits-for-10-million-hispanics-before-offering-immigration-help"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.theblaze.com/news/mexican-president-demands-20-billion-and-work-permits-for-10-million-hispanics-before-offering-immigration-help</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Mexican president demands $20 billion and work permits for 10 million Hispanics before offering immigration help</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Mexican President Andres Manuel Lopez Obrador recently revealed what that U.S. must do in order for the Mexican government to help slow down the flow of migrants crossing the U.S.-Mexico border, and the price is steep.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Fox News Digital reported that Lopez Obrador announced his demands during a press conference on Friday. The development comes just a week after the Mexican president met with Homeland Security Secretary Alejandro Mayorkas and Secretary of State Antony Blinken in Mexico City.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">In order for Mexico to help the U.S., Lopez Obrador demanded that the U.S. provide $20 billion to Latin American and Caribbean countries; provide work visas to 10 million Hispanics who have been working in the U.S. for at least 10 years; end sanctions against Venezuela; and put an end to the blockade of Cuba.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The demands have put pressure on President Joe Biden, who has not polled well on illegal immigration since he took over the presidency in 2021. The report noted that the border experienced a large surge of migrants this fall, with around 240,000 encounters per month toward the end of 2023.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">However, some of the decisions &mdash; if Biden decides to go through with the proposal &mdash; would need to get the approval of Congress.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Lopez Obrador has not been shy about challenging U.S. politicians on the topic of illegal immigration. He recently challenged Texas Governor Greg Abbott on one of the state's new immigration laws just last month.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Blaze News reported last month that Abbott had ratified legislation that would make illegal immigration a state crime. The law, Senate Bill 4, moved forward after the Biden administration seemed unwilling to enforce federal immigration law. The state authorities will now be able to arrest foreign nationals who sneak into the country illegally, and magistrates will be able to order illegal aliens to leave the country.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Lopez Obrador said last month: "The Texas governor acts that way because he wants to be the Republican vice presidential candidate and wants to win popularity with these measures."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">"He&rsquo;s not going to win anything. On the contrary, he is going to lose support because there are a lot of Mexicans in Texas, a lot of migrants."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">However, the law recently ratified in Texas will not punish those who enter the country legally &mdash; only those who attempt to circumvent U.S. law.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://notthebee.com/article/parents-who-refuse-to-go-along-with-their-childs-gender-transition-can-now-face-7-years-in-jail-in-scotland"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://notthebee.com/article/parents-who-refuse-to-go-along-with-their-childs-gender-transition-can-now-face-7-years-in-jail-in-scotland</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Scottish parents could face years in jail for preventing kids from "dressing in a way that reflects their sexual orientation or gender identity"</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Scotland is really making it simple for parents. Let them trans your kids or you go to jail.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">You may think that's overstatement, but that's actually the plan in Scotland.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Parents who do not go along with "affirming" their child's "gender identity" could face jail for SEVEN YEARS!</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Proposals published on Tuesday state that actions designed to "change or suppress" another individual's gender identity, causing them physical or psychological harm, would become illegal under the radical law.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">SNP (Scotland National Party) ministers acknowledged that so-called conversion practices often took place in a "family setting", raising the prospect that parents could be criminalised if they refuse to go along with their child's declaration that they are transgender.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Just so you know the extent of this proposal and how it could apply to families, one of the examples of "conversion therapy" punishable by jail time is preventing a child from wearing clothing of their preferred gender identity.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">So if Billy wants to wear a dress and you stop him you would be guilty of "conversion therapy" and be subject to punishment under the law.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Even if you don't do anything, the state could preemptively take action against you based solely on your beliefs!</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">If they know you're a conservative Christian in Scotland they could issue civil orders against you, warning you not to cross the line of telling your kids what to do.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The Scottish National Party is currently the largest and most represented party in parliament. They hold nearly a majority in the multi-party system. If they're fully on board with this there's not much that can be done to stop them in parliament.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">It's important to note this is in the "public consultation" phase which, in Scotland and the UK, means they have to lay out the plan for public feedback, in this case until April, before moving forward with the proposal.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">So my suggestion, between now and April, is for every freedom and faith-loving Scot to channel his inner Braveheart and publicly oppose this radical anti-family, anti-faith, anti-human proposal from the Scottish liberals.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://youtu.be/S3ubag7dtn4"><span style="font-weight: 400;" data-rich-links="{&quot;fple-t&quot;:&quot;Braveheart - FREEDOM&quot;,&quot;fple-u&quot;:&quot;https://youtu.be/S3ubag7dtn4&quot;,&quot;fple-mt&quot;:null,&quot;type&quot;:&quot;first-party-link&quot;}">Braveheart - FREEDOM</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;">- Play 1:36-1:47</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://mynorthwest.com/3945835/rantz-wa-democrats-deem-ammo-privilege-ammunition-tax-way-end-gun-rights/"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://mynorthwest.com/3945835/rantz-wa-democrats-deem-ammo-privilege-ammunition-tax-way-end-gun-rights/</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Wash. Democrats deem ammo a &lsquo;privilege&rsquo; as way to end gun rights</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Washington Democrats opened the 2024 legislative session with another assault on gun rights. This time they hope to reclassify ammunition as a &ldquo;privilege&rdquo; &mdash; one that should be subject to an onerous tax because the one thing they love more than taking away guns is taking away your money.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">State Representatives My-Linh Thai and Liz Berry, both Democrats, introduced House Bill 2238. Under the auspices of public safety, claiming access to ammunition is the cause of violence and not their soft-on-crime policies that go easy on criminals (including those who use guns in their crimes), the bill imposes an 11% sales and use tax on ammunition statewide. This would be an additional tax on top of the sales tax and any other tax that may levied when purchasing ammunition. The city of Seattle, for example, imposes a per-round tax.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">But the bill also reclassified ammunition, claiming you do not have a right to purchase them as a consumer. Instead, it&rsquo;s labeled a &ldquo;privilege.&rdquo; The legislation creates a new section in pre-existing law that reads, &ldquo;A use tax is levied on every person in this state for the privilege of using ammunition as a consumer at the rate of 11% of the selling price.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Neither Reps. Thai nor Berry responded to inquiries asking the basis for their claim that ammunition is a privilege. But Washington Democrats have set the stage to make this outrageous claim.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Washington Democrats have consistently moved to make gun ownership more onerous for non-criminal Washingtonians. The end goal for Democrats is to ban guns so that we cannot protect ourselves against the criminals they embolden.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Instead of a flat-out ban against guns, they&rsquo;ve hoped to reclassify ammunition as a privilege by severely restricting how much of it a gun owner can use at a time. The Washington Legislature approved a bill to prohibit the sale, distribution, and manufacture of firearm magazines holding more than 10 rounds of ammunition. This is meant to set the precedent claiming Washingtonians do not have a constitutional right to ammunition.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Like most of their clearly unconstitutional bills, they&rsquo;re based on a flimsy and purposefully obtuse understanding of the right to bear arms. The Washington State Constitution, Article I, Section 24, clearly states that &ldquo;the right of the individual citizen to bear arms in defense of himself, or the state, shall not be impaired.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">You cannot bear arms if the firearm has no ammunition in it. This provision, like the Second Amendment of the U.S. Constitution, implicitly includes all necessary components of firearms like ammunition as essential to the protected exercise of the right to bear arms. Without access to ammunition, the right to bear arms would be rendered meaningless, as firearms without ammunition are unable to fulfill their intended purpose in defense of oneself or the state.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">In an ironic twist, Democrats are the best gun salesmen. Their actions are pushing Washingtonians into purchases they might not otherwise make.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Washington Democrats&rsquo; interest in banning guns does not extend to the criminals they support with legislation that keeps them out of prison before the end of their sentences under the claim the criminal justice system is racist. By passing legislation that is clearly tied to the rise in crime, they give every Washingtonian ample reason to purchase firearms for self-defense. We have a rise in violent crime in Seattle, where homicides have hit historic highs. Democrats pretend they hold no blame in this new reality.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">State Reps Tarra Simmons and David Hackney pushed a bill in the 2022 legislative session to lessen charges against drive-by shooters. It would even be applied retroactively to release a drive-by shooter serving time.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">They claimed the change promoted &ldquo;racial equity in the criminal legal system&rdquo; because they implied too many black people commit drive-by shootings and it&rsquo;s unfair for them to be charged more than white people who don&rsquo;t commit as many drive-by shootings. It was as silly an argument as it was racist. Only after considerable public pushback, did the bill die. But it seems reasonable to want a firearm to protect yourself when you have pro-criminal legislators pushing dangerous bills.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">State Rep. Roger Goodman, another anti-gun Democrat, is back this year with HB 1268. It would prevent judges from offering additional years of prison to violent criminals who use guns during their crimes (&ldquo;stacking&rdquo; on gun enhancement charges). It even offers &ldquo;good time credits&rdquo; (or earned release time) to felons serving time on a firearm or deadly weapon enhancement. Any one of these criminals released early is reason enough to own a firearm of your own.</span></p>]]></description>
   <author><![CDATA[Garrison Hardie]]></author>
   <enclosure url="https://app.dropwave.io/episode/8cc7d23c-1574-4d39-a00d-112ac9ae33de/daily-news-brief-for-thursday-january-11th-2024.mp3" length="1056" type="audio/mp3"/>
   <guid isPermaLink="false"><![CDATA[8cc7d23c-1574-4d39-a00d-112ac9ae33de]]></guid>
   <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
   <source url=""><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></source>
   <itunes:author><![CDATA[Garrison Hardie]]></itunes:author>
   <itunes:image href="https://assets-cdn2.dropwave.io/2ab40ac0-e99d-4f25-a6d2-541d2c9b290a/cover-art/mUK8zsnHkCK3vep7E1W6UgYb9dTnLenASAMEFha3.jpg"/>
   <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
   <itunes:duration>1056</itunes:duration>
   <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
  
  </item>
 </channel>
</rss>
