<?xml version="1.0"?>
<?xml-stylesheet href="/storage/feed-stylesheet.xsl" type="text/xsl"?>

<rss xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
 <channel>
  <title>FLF - Daily News Brief</title>
  <link>https://dropwave.io</link>
  <description><![CDATA[FIGHT LAUGH FEAST PRESENTS SHOWS PROCLAIMING THE LORDSHIP OF CHRIST OVER ALL OF LIFE.
]]></description>
  <language>en</language>
  <managingEditor><![CDATA[fightlaughfeast@gmail.com (FLF, LLC)]]></managingEditor>
  <webMaster><![CDATA[support@dropwave.io (DropWave Support)]]></webMaster>
  <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2023 13:25:46 +0000</pubDate>
  <lastBuildDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2023 13:25:46 +0000</lastBuildDate>
  <image>
   <url>https://is4-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Podcasts113/v4/58/56/52/5856525c-2973-cf29-3db9-21faa8595391/mza_1144696925612154085.png/1200x1200bb.jpg</url>
   <link>https://dropwave.io</link>
   <title><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></title>
  </image>
  <itunes:author><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></itunes:author>
  <itunes:image href="https://is4-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Podcasts113/v4/58/56/52/5856525c-2973-cf29-3db9-21faa8595391/mza_1144696925612154085.png/1200x1200bb.jpg"/>
  <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
  <itunes:owner>
   <itunes:name><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></itunes:name>
   <itunes:email>fightlaughfeast@gmail.com</itunes:email>
  </itunes:owner>
  <itunes:category text="News"/>
  <item>
   <title><![CDATA[Daily News Brief for Friday, July 14th, 2023 [Daily News Brief]]]></title>
   <link>https://app.dropwave.io/episode/65fa24ef-b909-4541-8760-9bae78c03604/daily-news-brief-for-friday-july-14th-2023.mp3</link>
   <description><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">This is Garrison Hardie with your CrossPolitic Daily News Brief for Friday, July 14th, 2023.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Redballoon</strong></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Not so long ago, the American dream was alive and well. Employees who worked hard were rewarded, and employers looked for people who could do the job, not for people who had the right political views.&nbsp; RedBalloon.work is a job site designed to get us back to what made American businesses successful: free speech, hard work, and having fun.&nbsp; If you are a free speech employer who wants to hire employees who focus on their work and not identity politics, then post a job on RedBalloon.&nbsp; If you are an employee who is being censored at work or is being forced to comply with the current zeitgeist, post your resume on RedBalloon and look for a new job. redballoon.work, the job site where free speech is still alive!</span></p>
<p><a href="http://www.redballoon.work/"><span style="font-weight: 400;">www.redballoon.work</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/policy/energy-environment/how-farmers-angry-about-green-rules-helped-spur-dutch-governments-collapse"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/policy/energy-environment/how-farmers-angry-about-green-rules-helped-spur-dutch-governments-collapse</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>How farmers angry about green rules helped spur Dutch government's collapse</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Nitrogen emissions reduction targets have divided the Dutch population, ushering in an upstart political party and playing a primary role in the ouster of Prime Minister Mark Rutte just days after the shocking collapse of his coalition government.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Rutte, the longest-serving Dutch prime minister and a sharp tactician who has presided over four different governing coalitions, does not appear to have an immediate successor lined up.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Rutte&rsquo;s looming vacancy and the waning popularity of his People's Party for Freedom and Democracy could also clear the way for him to be replaced by someone on the far Right, as growing controversies over migration, farming, and nitrogen emissions reduction targets continue to sow deep divisions among voters.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The Dutch government agreed last summer to comply with the European Union&rsquo;s nitrate directive, a mandate that requires the country to slash 50% of its nitrogen emissions by 2030 &mdash; and which it plans to do primarily by reducing nitrogen-heavy fertilizer deposits on its many livestock farms.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">That agreement touched off a massive protest by tens of thousands of Dutch farmers, who massed in the streets to protest the decision, which they decried as unrealistic and unfair, given the country's status as a farming and agriculture powerhouse.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Roughly 40,000 people took part in the demonstrations, gathering outside government buildings, setting fire to bales of hay, and using their many tractors to block Dutch highways, canals, and warehouses.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The protests all but forced the country&rsquo;s economy to a standstill &mdash; and may have also played a role in reshaping the country's political tide.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Just months after the summer protests, the Farmers Citizens Movement, a populist, pro-farmer party known by its Dutch acronym of BBB, swept to power in the country&rsquo;s provincial elections, ultimately gaining enough seats in parliament to put it on par with the left-of-center Labor Party and the Green Party in the Senate.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Leaders of BBB, a party formed only three years earlier, made a name for themselves largely by appealing to the anger of farmers and others who work in the Dutch agriculture sector and campaigned on the promise of fighting the EU&rsquo;s mandated nitrogen emissions targets.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">This week's news of Rutte&rsquo;s departure, coupled with the rise of BBB, is widely expected to exacerbate existing deep-seated divisions over the future of agriculture and farming in the Netherlands.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">It also makes it far less likely that the splintered parties will be able to strike a compromise on key politically fraught issues, including nitrate emissions.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">In the near term, the Dutch government will effectively be held at a standstill, since Rutte will remain in his position through November to oversee a so-called &ldquo;caretaker&rdquo; government.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Leading a caretaker government means that Rutte and the holdover group of officials are unable to approve new and important policy decisions until a new government is formed later this year.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Until then, action will be suspended for months on key issues &mdash; including the country's ability to pass important policies on migration or climate, including taking further action on the EU&rsquo;s nitrate directive.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">In May, the European Commission approved the Dutch government&rsquo;s plan to buy out some of its most heavily polluting farms at roughly 120% of their value. The plan, estimated to cost around $1.65 billion, was aimed at helping the government deliver on its nitrogen emissions reduction commitments without sparking the deep unrest seen last summer.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">In announcing the effort, it warned the buyouts could become compulsory if farmers do not comply.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&ldquo;There is no better offer coming,&rdquo; Dutch Nitrogen Minister Christianne van der Wal told members of parliament.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The Netherlands is the EU&rsquo;s largest emitter of nitrogen oxide and ammonia and was ordered by the European Court of Justice in 2018 to address the problem. It also has a nitrogen balance nearly twice the European average &mdash; the majority of which comes from farming.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">And if it hopes to deliver on its 50% nitrogen reduction target by 2030, the Dutch government must act quickly &mdash; it has estimated that to meet its goal, 11,200 farms in the country will have to close. Roughly 17,600 others will have to significantly reduce their livestock numbers.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">But that has not gone over smoothly in the Netherlands, a farming and agriculture powerhouse where disagreements over nitrogen pollution reductions have sparked bitter protest and disagreement.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Despite its size of just 16,158 square miles &mdash; an area only slightly larger than the state of Maryland &mdash; the Netherlands is home to more than 110 million livestock and 54,000 agricultural businesses. It is the most intensively farmed country in all of Europe, and the world&rsquo;s second-largest exporter of agricultural goods, behind only the United States.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Farm and agriculture groups in the Netherlands have slammed the Dutch government&rsquo;s plans as &ldquo;unrealistic," according to the farming group LTO, and argued that the country's farmers have been unfairly targeted compared to other industries, which they argue remain comparably unscathed.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Others point to the massive amount of revenue generated by agriculture exports, which totaled roughly 105 billion euros in 2021 alone.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">"This is not going to work," LTO Netherland Chairman Sjaak van der Tak, whose organization represents 35,000 farmers, said in response to the government targets.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Others fear these divisions in the Netherlands could portend a larger trend in Europe and the Western world as environmental targets grow more ambitious.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://thepostmillennial.com/breaking-secret-service-says-no-suspect-in-white-house-cocaine-scandal?utm_campaign=64487"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://thepostmillennial.com/breaking-secret-service-says-no-suspect-in-white-house-cocaine-scandal?utm_campaign=64487</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Secret Service says 'no suspect' in White House cocaine scandal</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The Secret Service has reportedly concluded its investigation into the bag of cocaine that was discovered in the White House. But no suspect has been identified, according to two sources, per CNN.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The Secret Service looked through visitor logs and surveillance footage of those who came into the West Wing in the days leading up to the discovery, but they came up short.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Investigators weren't even able to identify a specific moment or day when the baggie was left inside the White House. One source said the prevailing theory is that the baggie was left behind by one of the hundreds of visitors who entered the West Wing for tours.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The cubbies where the small bag of cocaine was apparently found were in a blind spot for surveillance cameras, per the report. This has made it difficult to pin down who may have been responsible.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Representative Tim Burchett posted a video on Twitter about the investigation: </span><a href="https://twitter.com/i/status/1679502198374277120"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://twitter.com/i/status/1679502198374277120</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> - Play Video&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">A so-called powdery substance was discovered at the beginning of July, and speculation has since swirled as to who it may have belonged to. By July 5, officials had confirmed that the powdery substance was, in fact, cocaine.</span><span style="font-weight: 400;"><br /><br /></span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">According to Politico, an unidentified source familiar with the case said that it's "gonna be very difficult for us to do that because of where it was," noting that the baggie was discovered in a blind spot that wasn't picked up by the surveillance cameras.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Though the substance was discovered in the heavily trafficked West Wing, White House Press Secretary Karine Jean-Pierre said the Biden family was not at the White House when the substance was discovered on Sunday. Joe, Jill, and Hunter had dashed to Camp David on the previous Friday, and they returned to the White House on Tuesday for Independence Day.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://twitter.com/i/status/1676673509819404301"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://twitter.com/i/status/1676673509819404301</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> - Play Video</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">However, there has been speculation as to whether the cocaine belonged to Hunter Biden, who has openly spoke about his drug problems. Hunter was reportedly at the White House in the days before the cocaine was discovered. But there has been no evidence to directly connect the baggie of cocaine to the president's son.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Jean-Pierre had previously been asked whether the Biden administration would seek out prosecution if the culprit was found, but she evaded the question by saying she was "not going to get into hypotheticals."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Now for my facvorite topic&hellip; sports!</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://sports.yahoo.com/nba-approves-rule-change-to-make-flopping-a-technical-foul-004257997.html?guccounter=1&amp;guce_referrer=aHR0cHM6Ly9ib25naW5vcmVwb3J0LmNvbS8&amp;guce_referrer_sig=AQAAAN0ALfDif8Ng24K_3S2Ldit0ZVhgHi-1UlF8Oc4HwFsLIlnWOVxGDUGyyGt6mRUl9rvX7lOMcziNxuIR2MVOu3p0V1oFnM9cqfB2g67sMCNkkgSbKJDRlV_p41MwrLokuFaZYn3P6LqYZq5qZ8ReSTaWkxnzioOmW0Mb_lpxUeXG"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://sports.yahoo.com/nba-approves-rule-change-to-make-flopping-a-technical-foul-004257997.html?guccounter=1&amp;guce_referrer=aHR0cHM6Ly9ib25naW5vcmVwb3J0LmNvbS8&amp;guce_referrer_sig=AQAAAN0ALfDif8Ng24K_3S2Ldit0ZVhgHi-1UlF8Oc4HwFsLIlnWOVxGDUGyyGt6mRUl9rvX7lOMcziNxuIR2MVOu3p0V1oFnM9cqfB2g67sMCNkkgSbKJDRlV_p41MwrLokuFaZYn3P6LqYZq5qZ8ReSTaWkxnzioOmW0Mb_lpxUeXG</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>NBA approves rule change to make flopping a technical foul</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Look out [insert your least favorite NBA player here], flopping is about to come at a real cost.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The NBA Board of Governors approved a rule change that will make flopping a technical foul for the 2023-24 season, the league announced Tuesday, the result of increasing frustrations from fans and teams toward players who go out of their way to sell contact.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The change will come on a one-year trial basis.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Specifically, when a game official calls a flop, defined by the NBA as "a physical act that reasonably appears to be intended to cause the officials to call a foul on another player," the offending player will be charged with a non-unsportsmanlike technical foul and give the other team one free-throw attempt.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Because of the nature of the technical foul, a player will not be ejected from a game due to flopping violations. Refs will also not have to interrupt play to call a flop, as they can wait until the next stoppage to hit a player with the penalty.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The NBA specifically notes it's possible for the officials to call both a foul and a flop on the same play.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The league also instituted a change that will give coaches a second challenge if their first challenge is successful.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Flopping was previously punished with a warning, then fines escalating from $5,000 to $30,000. Such punishments were rare. The fines will change now that flopping is a tech, as it will be rolled into the existing fines for technical fouls instead.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The NBA was already trying out this system in the Summer League. Lester Quinones of the Golden State Warriors was the first player to feel the effect, getting called for a flop during a break in play.</span></p>
<p><br /><br /><br /><br /></p>]]></description>
   <author><![CDATA[Garrison Hardie]]></author>
   <enclosure url="https://app.dropwave.io/episode/65fa24ef-b909-4541-8760-9bae78c03604/daily-news-brief-for-friday-july-14th-2023.mp3" length="724" type="audio/mp3"/>
   <guid isPermaLink="false"><![CDATA[65fa24ef-b909-4541-8760-9bae78c03604]]></guid>
   <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jul 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
   <source url=""><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></source>
   <itunes:author><![CDATA[Garrison Hardie]]></itunes:author>
   <itunes:image href="https://assets-cdn2.dropwave.io/2ab40ac0-e99d-4f25-a6d2-541d2c9b290a/cover-art/mUK8zsnHkCK3vep7E1W6UgYb9dTnLenASAMEFha3.jpg"/>
   <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
   <itunes:duration>724</itunes:duration>
   <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
  
  </item><item>
   <title><![CDATA[Daily News Brief for Wednesday, July 12th, 2023 [Daily News Brief]]]></title>
   <link>https://app.dropwave.io/episode/07dab912-07c7-452d-b50c-fdbe65f8169d/daily-news-brief-for-wednesday-july-12th-2023.mp3</link>
   <description><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">This is Garrison Hardie with your CrossPolitic Daily News Brief for Wednesday, July 12th, 2023.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Olive Tree Biblical Software:</strong></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Discover why more than a million people use the free Olive Tree Bible App as their go-to for reading, studying, and listening to the God&rsquo;s Word.&nbsp;&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Start by downloading one of many free Bibles and start taking notes, highlighting verses, and bookmarking your favorite passages. You can read at your own pace, or choose from a large selection of Reading Plans, including the Bible Reading Challenge. When you are ready to go deeper into your studies, Olive Tree is right there with a large selection of study Bibles, commentaries, and other helpful study resources available for purchase. There&rsquo;s also an extensive bookstore allows you to build your digital library one book at a time and Olive Tree&rsquo;s sync technology lets you pick up where you left off on your tablet, pc or phone and get right to studying on another supported device.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&nbsp;</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Now here's the best part &ndash; You can start with the Olive Tree Essentials Bundle for FREE. Visit www.olivetree.com/FLF and download it today! </span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">We start things off in China!&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://dailycaller.com/2023/07/10/chinese-military-kindergarteners-war-bootcamps/"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://dailycaller.com/2023/07/10/chinese-military-kindergarteners-war-bootcamps/</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>The Chinese Military Is Training Kindergarteners For War In Bootcamps Across The Country</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The Chinese military is training kindergarteners to handle firearms and fight like soldiers in boot camps across China this summer, according to dozens of school social media accounts.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The boot camps feature combat training for boys and girls with a wide variety of toy weapons including knives, grenades, rifles and shoulder-fired missiles, and require the children to adopt military behavior, such as saluting, the schools&rsquo; social media posts show. The rise in the militarization of China&rsquo;s youth appears to follow a 2019 Chinese Communist Party (CCP) Central Committee push for increased &ldquo;National Defense Education&rdquo; and a related effort directing schools to hold National Defense Education activities in 2022, according to government documents.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Uniformed People&rsquo;s Liberation Army (PLA) soldiers oversaw all of the kindergarten boot camps. The boot camps were located in major Chinese cities, such as Beijing, Nanjing and Shenzhen, and were also run in more than half a dozen provinces.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The programs featured roughly the same sequence of activities, according to a DCNF review of posts from the participating kindergartens.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The boot camps generally began with basic military etiquette and proceeded to teach various military skills ranging from combat to emergency medical training. Additionally, a number of these programs also taught the children about famous PLA heroes and martyrs, according to the schools&rsquo; accounts.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">In May 2023, faculty members and more than 80 children of numerous provinces assembled on the playground for the opening ceremony of their school&rsquo;s week-long National Defense Education camp, all wearing matching camouflage fatigues.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&ldquo;INHERIT THE RED GENE, CARRY FORWARD PATRIOTIC FEELINGS, LOVE CHINA, LITTLE SOLDIER,&rdquo; declared a large PLA banner, which partially hid the kindergarten&rsquo;s playset.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Uniformed PLA soldiers then performed a flag-raising ceremony, with all attendants singing the Chinese national anthem, the social media post stated.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&ldquo;We solemnly swear to love the motherland from now on, to dedicate our hearts to working together to build the dream of a powerful country,&rdquo; the children then pledged, according to the social media post. &ldquo;Even if I fall to the ground I will continue onward!&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">PLA soldiers then taught the kindergarten recruits how to groom themselves and make their beds in accordance with military standards, before drilling them in how to stand at attention, stand at ease and salute.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Experts say recent efforts to militarize China&rsquo;s youth are part of the CCP&rsquo;s ideological goals.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Now compare that to the U.S., where students are regularly pushed into ideologies that despise everything the Founding Father&rsquo;s did.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://notthebee.com/article/just-unfathomable-disney-world-is-just-about-empty-during-summer-vacation-season?fbclid=IwAR2ZgkovaL7WZCwrL8WVQuUm3MNqIpPK8z9WvOLKpsRIph9epbgE0Xknj4E"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://notthebee.com/article/just-unfathomable-disney-world-is-just-about-empty-during-summer-vacation-season?fbclid=IwAR2ZgkovaL7WZCwrL8WVQuUm3MNqIpPK8z9WvOLKpsRIph9epbgE0Xknj4E</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>"Just unfathomable": Disney World is "just about empty" during summer vacation season</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">It takes real skill to drive this many customers away.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The July 4th weekend was a 10-year-low for the massive company's Disney World amusement park in Orlando, but all the parks have been suffering recently.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">According to the Wall Street Journal, Park visitors in recent weeks have had significantly lower wait times to get on rides, according to data from Touring Plans, a company that tracks wait times at major amusement parks, including Disney World and Disneyland in California. Industry analysts say shorter wait times generally correlate with smaller crowds.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The average posted wait time at the Magic Kingdom park in Florida &mdash; which has a special fireworks display on July 4 &mdash; was 27 minutes this year for the holiday, down from 31 minutes in 2022 and 47 minutes in 2019, the Touring Plans analysis shows.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">"It's something that nobody would have predicted &mdash; just unfathomable," says Len Testa, a computer scientist who runs Touring Plans. Testa says wait times rose in the following days.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The Journal offers an assortment of potential reasons for the lull: Cruises and European vacations are back after the pandemic, Disney isn't offering much new, and Disney wants to slim down the crowds for richer guests anyway.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">But unlike the journalist class, most of America understands the two primary reasons:</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Your wallet is hurting</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Disney went woke</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://thehill.com/blogs/blog-briefing-room/4085828-a-record-share-of-americans-are-living-alone/"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://thehill.com/blogs/blog-briefing-room/4085828-a-record-share-of-americans-are-living-alone/</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>A record share of Americans is living alone</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Nearly 30 percent of American households comprise a single person, a record high.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Scholars say living alone is not a trend so much as a transformation: Across much of the world, large numbers of people are living alone for the first time in recorded history.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&ldquo;It&rsquo;s just a stunning social change,&rdquo; said Eric Klinenberg, a sociologist at New York University and author of the book &ldquo;Going Solo.&rdquo; &ldquo;I came to see it as the biggest demographic change in the last century that we failed to recognize and take seriously.&rdquo;&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Homo sapiens is a social animal. Historians tapped ancient census rolls to show that our species has lived in groups for as long as such records have existed, stretching back at least to 1600.&nbsp;&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The U.S. Census shows that &ldquo;solitaries&rdquo; made up 8 percent of all households in 1940. The share of solo households doubled to 18 percent in 1970 and more than tripled, to an estimated 29 percent, by 2022.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The solo-living movement intersects with several other societal trends. Americans are marrying later, if at all. The nation is aging. The national birthrate is falling. People are living longer &mdash; or they were, until the pandemic arrived.&nbsp;&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">More than anything, perhaps, the rise of single-person households is about women entering the workforce and achieving economic self-sufficiency. The share of adult women participating in the labor force reached 50 percent around 1980.&nbsp;&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Historically speaking, &ldquo;you don&rsquo;t really see people living alone until women have control of their own lives and their own bodies,&rdquo; Klinenberg said.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Researchers see a marked downside to living alone, especially for older Americans, for people who live outside thickly settled cities and for pretty much anyone who is not alone by choice.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">A New York Times report on aging solitaries concluded that, &ldquo;while many people in their 50s and 60s thrive living solo, research is unequivocal that people aging alone experience worse physical and mental health outcomes and shorter life spans.&rdquo;&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The nation&rsquo;s declining birth rate and aging population portend a time when America doesn&rsquo;t have enough working-age citizens to sustain the national economy or to support the spiraling health care needs of its oldest citizens. The rise of single-person households can be seen as both a cause and effect of those challenges.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&ldquo;I think it&rsquo;s something we should be worried about,&rdquo; said Wendy Wang, director of research at the Institute for Family Studies, a conservative thinktank. &ldquo;If we have fewer and fewer children, that means we have fewer people to work, to be consumers, to pay taxes.&rdquo;&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Wang notes that low fertility rates are a global problem. Indeed, solo households are far more common across much of Europe than in the United States. According to United Nations data, solitaries make up 39 percent of households in Denmark, 45 percent in Finland, 42 percent in Germany, 38 percent in the Netherlands, 39 percent in Norway and 40 percent in Sweden.&nbsp;&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Even now, living alone is not quite so common in the United States as the data suggest. While nearly 30 percent of households comprise a single person, far fewer than 30 percent of Americans live in them.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Roughly 13 percent of American adults live alone, research shows. Breaking down that figure by age groups, the population of solitaries rises from 4 percent of adults at ages 18-24 to 9 percent at 25-34, dips to 8 percent at 35-44, then rises again, to 12 percent at 45-54, 17 percent at 55-64 and 26 percent at 65 and up.&nbsp;&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Living alone is much more common in large cities. Singles now make up more than 40 percent of households in Atlanta, Seattle, San Francisco, Minneapolis and Denver, according to a paper by the British historian Keith Snell. Half of all Manhattan dwellings are one-person residences. Snell identified a Midtown Census tract where 94 percent of households comprised a single person.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">At younger ages, men outnumber women in one-person households. Young men are far more likely than young women to be single, and they tend to marry later.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The gender gap in solitary living closes with age. In the retirement years, women are more likely than men to live alone.&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">That statistic is partly about women outliving husbands, and partly about &ldquo;grey divorce,&rdquo; the rising rate of marriages that dissolve after age 50. The grey divorce rate has doubled since 1990.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&ldquo;It used to be that if people were married for 30 years and they entered their 60s, basically, they were going to stay married,&rdquo; said Barbara Risman, a distinguished professor of sociology at the University of Illinois Chicago. &ldquo;You would pass the risk of divorce. No one is ever past the risk of divorce anymore.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Through much of the 20th century, marriage was so universal that the very act of living alone carried a stigma.&nbsp;&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The share of Americans who had not married by age 40 hovered below 10 percent from 1950 through 1980, according to a Pew Research analysis. The figure has soared in recent decades, reaching 25 percent in 2021, a record high.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The share of Americans in prime marriage years who are actually married has dwindled from about two-thirds to around half since 1990, Pew data show. Nearly two-fifths of Americans are &ldquo;unpartnered,&rdquo; neither married nor cohabiting.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Researchers consider living alone a risk factor for loneliness and social isolation, conditions associated with a host of physical and mental maladies, from heart disease to obesity to anxiety and depression.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Men tend to fare less well than women in single-person households, said Louise Hawkley, a researcher at the NORC thinktank who studies loneliness and social isolation. - Perhaps because we&rsquo;re meant to be taking dominion &amp; building families&hellip;&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Now for my favorite topic&hellip; sports!</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://www.foxnews.com/sports/us-soccer-star-megan-rapinoe-support-trans-athlete-uswnt-roster-i-see-trans-women-as-real-women"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.foxnews.com/sports/us-soccer-star-megan-rapinoe-support-trans-athlete-uswnt-roster-i-see-trans-women-as-real-women</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>US soccer star Megan Rapinoe would support trans athlete on USWNT roster: 'I see trans women as real women'</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">U.S. women&rsquo;s soccer icon Megan Rapinoe has been a public advocate for the inclusion of transgender athletes in women&rsquo;s sports, and ahead of what will be her final World Cup appearance before retiring, the one-time Golden Boot winner said she would "absolutely" support having a trans woman on the USWNT roster.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Even if that meant replacing a biological female.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">In an interview with Time published Monday, Rapinoe recalled highlights from her lengthy career, including her battles both on and off the pitch. She was asked specifically about her push to defend transgender athletes&rsquo; participation in women&rsquo;s sports.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">"We as a country are trying to legislate away people&rsquo;s full humanity," she told the outlet.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Rapinoe was one of 40 professional athletes to co-sign a letter to House lawmakers in April in opposition of the Protection of Girls and Women in Sports Act, arguing that the bill would exclude women and girls from getting "mental and physical health benefits."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">"It&rsquo;s particularly frustrating when women&rsquo;s sports is weaponized," Rapinoe said in the interview. "Oh, now we care about fairness? Now we care about women&rsquo;s sports? That&rsquo;s total bulls---. And show me all the trans people who are nefariously taking advantage of being trans in sports. It&rsquo;s just not happening."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Rapinoe was asked specifically if she would support a trans woman playing on the United States Women&rsquo;s National Team, even if it meant replacing a biological female. The OL Reign star said she would, but added that she did not view the act as "taking a &lsquo;real&rsquo; woman&rsquo;s place."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">"Absolutely," she told Time. "&lsquo;You&rsquo;re taking a &lsquo;real&rsquo; woman&rsquo;s place,&rsquo; that&rsquo;s the part of the argument that&rsquo;s still extremely transphobic. I see trans women as real women. What you&rsquo;re saying automatically in the argument&mdash;you&rsquo;re sort of telling on yourself already&mdash;is you don&rsquo;t believe these people are women. Therefore, they&rsquo;re taking the other spot. I don&rsquo;t feel that way."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Rapinoe will make her final World Cup appearance this month as the United States Women&rsquo;s National Team heads to Australia and New Zealand with the hopes of making history: becoming the first women&rsquo;s or men&rsquo;s team to win a three-peat.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The 38-year-old soccer star announced over the weekend her plans to retire at the conclusion of the 2023 National Women&rsquo;s Soccer League season.</span></p>]]></description>
   <author><![CDATA[Garrison Hardie]]></author>
   <enclosure url="https://app.dropwave.io/episode/07dab912-07c7-452d-b50c-fdbe65f8169d/daily-news-brief-for-wednesday-july-12th-2023.mp3" length="869" type="audio/mp3"/>
   <guid isPermaLink="false"><![CDATA[07dab912-07c7-452d-b50c-fdbe65f8169d]]></guid>
   <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
   <source url=""><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></source>
   <itunes:author><![CDATA[Garrison Hardie]]></itunes:author>
   <itunes:image href="https://assets-cdn2.dropwave.io/2ab40ac0-e99d-4f25-a6d2-541d2c9b290a/cover-art/mUK8zsnHkCK3vep7E1W6UgYb9dTnLenASAMEFha3.jpg"/>
   <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
   <itunes:duration>869</itunes:duration>
   <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
  
  </item><item>
   <title><![CDATA[Daily News Brief for Tuesday, July 11th, 2023 [Daily News Brief]]]></title>
   <link>https://app.dropwave.io/episode/fc5c04d7-8b7d-4c80-81c4-099bd157ceb1/daily-news-brief-for-tuesday-july-11th-2023.mp3</link>
   <description><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">This is Garrison Hardie with your CrossPolitic Daily News Brief for Tuesday, July 11th, 2023.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Fight Laugh Feast Conference - Ark Encounter</strong></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">This year, our Fight Laugh Feast Conference is at the Ark Encounter in Kentucky on The Politics of Six Day Creation. The politics of six day creation is the difference between a fixed standard of justice and a careening standard of justice, the difference between the corrosive relativism that creates mobs and anarchy and the freedom of objectivity, truth, and due process. The politics of six day creation establishes the authority and sufficiency of God&rsquo;s Word for all of life: from what is a man or a woman, when does human life begin, and how is human society best organized?</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Come hear Ken Ham, Pastor Doug Wilson, Dr. Ben Merkle, Dr. Gordon Wilson, me and more, and of course a live CrossPolitic show! Mark your calendars for October 11th-14th, as we fight, laugh, and feast, with beer &amp; psalms, our amazing lineup of speakers, our Rowdy Christian Merch, and a Sabbath Feast to wrap up the occasion. Maybe an infant baptism while we&rsquo;re at it! Visit fightlaughfeast.com for more information!</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://www.theblaze.com/news/ban-on-transgender-surgery-for-tennessee-children-goes-into-effect"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.theblaze.com/news/ban-on-transgender-surgery-for-tennessee-children-goes-into-effect</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Tennessee's ban on transgender surgery for kids goes into effect immediately, federal appeals court rules</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Tennessee can implement its ban on transgender surgery and related medical interventions for minors as a case challenging the law works its way through the court, a divided federal appeals court panel ruled Saturday.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Tennessee's 44th House District Representative William Lamberth (R) wrote on Twitter Saturday: "I am thankful to the 6th Circuit Court of Appeals for confirming what Tennesseans already know: Children cannot give consent to experimental medical procedures or drugs that destroy their healthy bodies,"&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The Tennessee law now in effect, at least temporarily, prohibits surgical procedures and administration of hormones or puberty blockers for the purpose of gender transition, as Reason explains.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Judge Thapar joined Sutton, concluding that the lower court had wrongly stopped the law's implementation. Judge White delivered a separate opinion concurring in part and dissenting in part.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The ban, originally set to take effect July 1, will now take effect immediately. The ban was held up when a lower court sided with the American Civil Liberties Union of Tennessee. ACLU-TN argued that the law interfered with parental rights and was unconstitutional, as The Hill reported.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">This is the first federal court to allow such a ban, with other courts unanimously blocking similar bans in Arkansas, Alabama, Florida, Indiana, and Kentucky, according to the American Civil Liberties Union of Tennessee.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">ACLU-TN brought the suit on behalf of Samantha and Brian Williams of Nashville and their 15-year-old daughter, as well as two other anonymous families and Dr. Susan N. Lac.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://dailycaller.com/2023/07/09/portland-distribute-foil-straws-snorting-kits-paraphernalia-drug-addicts/"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://dailycaller.com/2023/07/09/portland-distribute-foil-straws-snorting-kits-paraphernalia-drug-addicts/</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>City To Distribute Foil, Straws, Snorting Kits To Drug Addicts</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Health officials in Portland, Oregon announced last week they will begin handing out tin foil, straws and snorting kits to drug addicts throughout the city.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">As part of its &ldquo;Harm Reduction Program,&rdquo; the Multnomah County Health Department announced Friday that drug paraphernalia will be offered to those using fentanyl and other hard drugs, KOIN 6 reported.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The rise of fentanyl has decreased the need for needle-focused &ldquo;harm reduction&rdquo; services, Department spokeswoman Sarah Dean told the Willamette Week. Since fentanyl is smoked rather than injected, clinic visits have dropped 60% since 2019, Dean said.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The program is backed by Multnomah County&rsquo;s Public Health Director, Jessica Guernsey, who says, &ldquo;The new part of the program is that we&rsquo;re adding supplies for people who smoke drugs.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Others are not happy with the move.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&ldquo;This misguided approach also results in greater risk to public safety for those who simply want to enjoy our city without walking through a cloud of toxic smoke,&rdquo; Portland Mayor Ted Wheeler said. &ldquo;Our community would benefit more from the County using its funding to urgently increase treatment and sobering facilities rather than actively enabling this deadly epidemic.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Dean countered the mayor&rsquo;s statement by claiming providing drug paraphernalia does not increase drug use but encourages addicts to visit clinics where they can get access to fentanyl test strips and the overdose antidote, Narcan, KOIN 6 reported.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The Oregon Legislative Assembly recently passed a bill decriminalizing the distribution of &ldquo;drug paraphernalia&rdquo; for harm reduction purposes, according to the Willamette Week. Similar programs have been launched in Washington and California. In New York City, vending machines with smoking kits and bubble pipes have recently been installed, the outlet reported.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The Oregon bill to decriminalize distribution of drug paraphernalia sits on Governor Tina Kotek&rsquo;s desk awaiting signature before going into law, the New York Post reported.</span></p>
<p><a href="https://hotair.com/karen-townsend/2023/07/09/the-winner-of-miss-netherlands-2023-is-a-man-n563401"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://hotair.com/karen-townsend/2023/07/09/the-winner-of-miss-netherlands-2023-is-a-man-n563401</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>The winner of Miss Netherlands 2023 is a man</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Transgender activism marches on. The newly crowned Miss Universe Netherlands is a man. The runner-up is a woman.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Rikkie Valerie Koll&eacute; was crowned Miss Universe Netherlands 2023 on Saturday. Rikkie is 22 years old, a Dutch-Moluccan model and actress in Leusden. He will represent the Netherlands at the 2023 Miss Universe pageant in El Salvador. The first runner-up is Nathalie Mogbelzada, 26, from Amsterdam.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The reigning Miss Universe, R&rsquo;Bonney Gabriel of Houston, Texas, was a special guest at the pageant.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">He makes history as the first transgender woman to win the national title. In 2018, Angele Ponce, Miss Universe Spain, was the first transgender to participate in the Miss Universe pageant.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The question of having a transgender competitor in the Miss Universe pageant goes back to 2012. That is when Trump owned it and he overturned a decision by the Miss Universe organization to disqualify a Canadian model. Jenna Talackova was not being allowed to compete because &ldquo;she was not a naturally born female.&rdquo; Trump bowed to the laws of Canada and allowed Jenna to compete. The LGBTQ community applauded Trump. Now he&rsquo;s running against a very socially conservative Republican, Ron DeSantis, among others, and Trump has flipped on the issue.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The Miss America pageant is also having its share of problems. Ever since former Fox anchor Gretchen Carlson came out as super woke and joined the organization, internal battles have leaked into the press. One big issue is that when Carlson joined the organization in 2018, she made the decision to ban the swimsuit segment. Now a former Miss America, Caressa Cameron, says that the pageant feels like a Ted Talk. There is a new docuseries on A&amp;E that exposes scandals, misogyny, and racism in the Miss America competitions.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Now in world news:&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://www.foxnews.com/us/us-centcom-says-killed-isis-leader-syria-airstrike-no-civilian-casualties"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.foxnews.com/us/us-centcom-says-killed-isis-leader-syria-airstrike-no-civilian-casualties</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>US CENTCOM says it killed ISIS leader in Syria airstrike, no civilian casualties</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">U.S. forces killed ISIS leader Usamah al-Muhajir in an airstrike in eastern Syria on Friday, U.S. Central Command (CENTCOM) announced in a Sunday statement.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Al-Muhajir was killed by the same MQ-9 reaper drones that had been harassed by Russian aircraft in the region. The two incidents occurred the same day, the U.S. says, with the drones carrying out the strike after the interaction with Russian craft.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">"We have made it clear that we remain committed to the defeat of ISIS throughout the region," said CENTCOM commander Gen. Michael Kurilla. "ISIS remains a threat, not only to the region but well beyond."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">CENTCOM clarified that there were no indications that any civilians were killed in the strike, but the U.S. and allies were assessing reports of a civilian injury.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The U.S. and allied forces in the region have carried out a consistent campaign against remaining ISIS leaders operating in Syria. The U.S. killed the head of the organization, Abu Bakr al-Baghdadi, in a 2019 raid. Since then, ISIS forces have operated as cells.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The MQ-9 drones used in the attack had earlier interactions with Russian SU-35 fighter jets throughout last week. The Russian craft have repeatedly flown into the path of the drones, forcing them to take evasive action to avoid a collision.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">"Russian military aircraft engaged in unsafe and unprofessional behavior Thursday, 9:30 a.m. local time, while interacting with U.S. MQ-9 drones carrying out our D-ISIS mission in Syria," said Lt. Gen. Alexus Grynkewich, commander, 9th AF and CFACC for CENTCOM. "Russian aircraft dropped flares in front of the drones and flew dangerously close, endangering the safety of all aircraft involved."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">"This is the second instance of dangerous behaviors by Russian pilots within the past 24 hours, with the first happening Wednesday at approximately 10:40 a.m. local time," he added.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The U.S. military has also urged Russian forces in Syria to "cease this reckless behavior and adhere to the standards of behavior expected of a professional air force, so we can resume our focus on the enduring defeat of ISIS," he said.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The U.S. maintains a force of about 900 troops deployed in Syria. They primarily work with the Kurdish-led Syrian Democratic Forces in their struggle against Islamic State militants.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Now in entertainment&hellip;&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://thepostmillennial.com/cnn-discourages-viewers-from-watching-anti-pedophile-movie-sound-of-freedom?utm_campaign=64487"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://thepostmillennial.com/cnn-discourages-viewers-from-watching-anti-pedophile-movie-sound-of-freedom?utm_campaign=64487</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>CNN discourages viewers from watching anti-pedophile movie, Sound of Freedom</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">In a clip from CNN, network host Abby Phillip brought on an author named Mike Rothschild to talk about the new and popular anti-child sex trafficking film, Sound of Freedom. Rothschild charged the film is created out of a "moral panic" and "QAnon concepts."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Sound of Freedom is based on the adventures of Tim Ballard, who started an organization known as Operation Underground Railroad (OUR). OUR's mission is to save children from human trafficking.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Rothschild wrote a book titled, "The Storm is Upon Us," which details many QAnon conspiracy theories such as the idea that the Democratic Party elites are part of a cabal of Satanic worshippers that drink the blood of children.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Rothschild targeted said the film is "being marketed to either specific QAnon believers or to people who believe all of the same tenets as QAnon, but claim they don't know what it is."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://rumble.com/v2yw470-cnn-encourages-viewers-not-to-see-anti-pedophile-movie-sound-of-freedom.html"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://rumble.com/v2yw470-cnn-encourages-viewers-not-to-see-anti-pedophile-movie-sound-of-freedom.html</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> - Play Video&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">CNN has had its own problems with employees being involved in child sex crimes. One former producer at the network, John Griffin, was sentenced to 19 years in prison. Griffin coerced a woman online to bring her nine-year-old daughter to Vermont to engage in illicit acts.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The story depicted in the film is of Ballard, played by Caviezel, rescuing children. After much strife with working in the US government, he bumps up against bureaucracy in his position as an agent. He had to quit his job to rescue the kids in the film and did so in reality as well.&nbsp;&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">This was the beginning of OUR as a non-government organization. The movie focuses on Ballard's mission to save the two children and reunite a family torn apart by child sex trafficking.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">At the end of the movie, Caviezel appears on screen with a special message to share and urges people to "pay it forward" and donate to allow others to see the film.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Caviezel says, "Steve Jobs once said, 'The most powerful person in the world is the storyteller.' Abraham Lincoln credited Harriet Stowe when she wrote Uncle Tom's Cabin. This powerful story inspired millions to rise up and fight against slavery. I think we can make Sound of Freedom the Uncle Tom's Cabin of modern-day slavery."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">"Sound of Freedom is a hero's tale, but I'm not talking about the character I play. It's the heroic brother and sister in this film that work to save each other."&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Caviezel added, "Together, we have a chance to make these two kids, and the countless children that they represent, the most powerful people in the world by telling their story in a way only the cinema can do."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Before we wrap up today&rsquo;s show, let&rsquo;s talk about on this day in history!&nbsp;</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">On this day in history, July 11th:</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">138 Antoninus Pius succeeds Hadrian as Emperor of Rome</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">1302 Battle of the Golden Spurs (Guldensporenslag in Dutch) near Kortrijk (cor-tray), Belgium: Flemish coalition defeat the French army of Philip IV</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">1405 Chinese fleet commander Zheng He sets sail on his first major expedition, to the Spice Islands, leading 208 vessels, including 62 treasure ships with 27,800 sailors</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">1533 Pope Clement VII excommunicates England's King Henry VIII</span></li>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="2"><span style="font-weight: 400;">On 11th July 1533, the Pope declared that Henry VIII&rsquo;s marriage to Anne Boleyn was null and void, as was the annulment declared by Archbishop Thomas Cranmer in May 1533, and he restored Catherine of Aragon to her &ldquo;royal state&rdquo;. He ordered the wayward king to abandon the newly crowned and pregnant Anne Boleyn and return to Catherine of Aragon. If the king refused then the Pope would issue the bull of excommunication that he had drawn up. He&rsquo;d give Henry until September to sort himself out, but if he didn&rsquo;t heed the Pope&rsquo;s warning then he&rsquo;d be excommunicated, the most severe punishment that the Church could inflict.</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="2"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Of course, Henry took absolutely no notice of the Pope, but he escaped excommunication until 17th December 1538 when Pope Paul III excommunicated him following his break with Rome, his persecution of those who did not accept his supremacy, the dissolution of the monasteries and Henry&rsquo;s desecration of religious shrines including that of Thomas Becket.</span></li>
</ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">1576 English explorer Martin Frobisher sights Greenland</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">1740 Jews are expelled from Little Russia by order of Tsarina Anne</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">1781 Thomas Hutchins designated Geographer of US</span></li>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="2"><span style="font-weight: 400;">By the age of 30, the remarkable Thomas Hutchins (1730?-1789) was an experienced frontiersman, a veteran of the French and Indian War, and a skilled Indian agent. He was best known, however, as a formidable surveyor, cartographer, and geographer. A native of New Jersey, the particular combination of skills made Hutchins the perfect candidate for surveying the vast western regions of the British North American empire. In 1766, he was officially assigned to duty as an engineer in the British army, gradually becoming the most respected surveyor and map maker in the colonies. From 1764 through 1768, he took part in expeditions spanning the west from the northern reaches of the Mississippi Valley to New Orleans, and in 1770, was transferred from the Illinois territory to Pensacola, where he was charged with reorganizing the provincial defenses and mapping.</span></li>
</ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">1798 US Marine Corps established by an act of Congress</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">1801 French astronomer Jean-Louis Pons discovers his 1st comet</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">1882 British fleet bombards Alexandria, Egypt</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">1906 The Gillette-Brown murder inspires Theodore Dreiser's "An American Tragedy"</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">1960 "To Kill a Mockingbird" by Harper Lee is first published by J. B. Lippincott &amp; Co.</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">1984 Government orders air bags or seat belts would be required in cars by 1989</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">1988 Mike Tyson hires Donald Trump as an advisor</span></li>
</ul>]]></description>
   <author><![CDATA[Garrison Hardie]]></author>
   <enclosure url="https://app.dropwave.io/episode/fc5c04d7-8b7d-4c80-81c4-099bd157ceb1/daily-news-brief-for-tuesday-july-11th-2023.mp3" length="1092" type="audio/mp3"/>
   <guid isPermaLink="false"><![CDATA[fc5c04d7-8b7d-4c80-81c4-099bd157ceb1]]></guid>
   <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
   <source url=""><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></source>
   <itunes:author><![CDATA[Garrison Hardie]]></itunes:author>
   <itunes:image href="https://assets-cdn2.dropwave.io/2ab40ac0-e99d-4f25-a6d2-541d2c9b290a/cover-art/mUK8zsnHkCK3vep7E1W6UgYb9dTnLenASAMEFha3.jpg"/>
   <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
   <itunes:duration>1092</itunes:duration>
   <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
  
  </item><item>
   <title><![CDATA[Daily News Brief for Friday, July 7th, 2023 [Daily News Brief]]]></title>
   <link>https://app.dropwave.io/episode/8ea4dd68-6b6d-4ec1-a163-8164a4c598d1/daily-news-brief-for-friday-july-7th-2023.mp3</link>
   <description><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">This is Garrison Hardie with your CrossPolitic Daily News Brief for Friday, July 7th, 2023.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>Samaritan Ministries</strong></span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">How are you paying for your health care, and how&rsquo;s it working out? If it&rsquo;s working perfectly,</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">great! If not, then listen closely, because I have a solution for you. A Biblical solution.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Samaritan Ministries is a community of Christians who pay one another&rsquo;s medical bills. Here&rsquo;s</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">how it works. When a medical need arises, you choose the provider that&rsquo;s right for you, and</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">have a say in the treatment you receive, even if it&rsquo;s a non-conventional approach. Your medical</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">bills are shared with fellow members, and your need is covered in prayer.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">It&rsquo;s affordable, and you can join anytime, even today. Learn more at samaritan ministries dot</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">org slash cross politic.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">We start today off with world news as Ukraine and Russia are playing a game of he did it - he did it.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://www.foxnews.com/world/ukraine-russia-accuse-each-other-planning-imminent-attack-europes-largest-nuclear-plant"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.foxnews.com/world/ukraine-russia-accuse-each-other-planning-imminent-attack-europes-largest-nuclear-plant</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>Ukraine, Russia accuse each other of planning imminent attack against Europe's largest nuclear plant</strong></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Ukraine and Russia have accused each other of planning an imminent attack against one of the world's largest nuclear plants.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">In a video address Tuesday night, Ukrainian President Volodymyr Zelenskyy alleged that information from Ukrainian intelligence officials shows the "Russian military has placed objects resembling explosives on the roof of several power units" of the Za-po-ree-zia Nuclear Power Plant &ndash; located in southeastern Ukraine and occupied by Russian troops.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The "foreign objects" were placed on the roof of the plant's third and fourth power units, according to a statement from the General Staff of Ukraine&rsquo;s armed forces. "Their detonation should not damage power units but may create a picture of shelling from Ukraine," the statement said.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">In Russia, Kremlin spokesman Dmitry Peskov raised the specter of a potentially "catastrophic" provocation by the Ukrainian army at the nuclear plant, which is Europe&rsquo;s largest but has its six reactors shut down. It still needs power and qualified staff to operate crucial cooling systems and other safety features.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Over the last year, the U.N.'s atomic watchdog repeatedly expressed alarm over the possibility of a radiation catastrophe like the one at Chernobyl, where a reactor exploded in 1986.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">While Russia and Ukraine regularly traded blame over shelling near the plant that caused power outages, Ukraine has alleged more recently that Moscow might try to cause a deliberate leak in an attempt to derail Kyiv&rsquo;s ongoing counteroffensive in the surrounding Za-po-ree-zia region.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Moscow, meanwhile, had accused the Ukrainians of "deliberate sabotage" of the Ka-hove-ka hydroelectric power plant, claiming Kyiv was "pursuing the goal of depriving Crimea of water."&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The International Atomic Energy Agency has officials stationed at the Russian-held plant, which is still run by its Ukrainian staff. IAEA Director General Rafael Mariano Grossi said his agency's most recent inspection of the plant found no mining activities, "but we remain extremely alert."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">We now go to California.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://www.dailywire.com/news/california-bills-keep-pride-marching-long-past-june"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.dailywire.com/news/california-bills-keep-pride-marching-long-past-june</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>California Bills Keep Pride Marching Long Past June</strong></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The infernal provocation that is Pride Month might be over, but the marches continue through the legislature in California. They are here, they are queer, and they are coming for your children &mdash; legally.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Multiple bills at various stages in the California legislative process proclaim who ultimately has authority of your kids, and it&rsquo;s not you. Some have understandably garnered much media attention, but SB 407 is working its way through the Assembly without much fanfare or discussion.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">SB 407 would require all potential foster families to demonstrate their capacity and willingness to facilitate pharmaceutical and surgical interventions for &ldquo;gender-expansive&rdquo; children. Even if the child seems to give no indication of such inclinations at the time, the resource family must be assessed with the understanding that need for such care could arise at any stage of development.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Sen. Scott Weiner (D-San Francisco) in introducing the bill, claimed it would protect children from being placed in &ldquo;hostile foster homes.&rdquo; Hostile homes are the homes of any foster families who are unwilling to commit to actively supporting gender transition interventions for minors. SB 407 effectively institutionalizes a prohibition against orthodox Christians as well as other religious believers.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">It effectively prohibits foster parents who think it unwise to allow the mutilation of perfectly healthy body parts on minors.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Current and historic data give us insight into the demographics of those most prone to foster non-related babies and minors. Barna Group&rsquo;s research shows that Christians engage in adoption, foster care, and other ways of aiding vulnerable children more than the average. &ldquo;Practicing Christians (5%) are more than twice as likely to adopt than the general population (2%). Catholics are three times as likely. And evangelicals are five times as likely to adopt as the average adult.&rdquo; Practicing Christians are also nearly three times more likely to have seriously considered foster care, and 65% of non-kin foster parents attend religious services weekly &mdash; compared to 39%for the general population.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">In any just world such families willing to stretch themselves to help kids would be sought after, not precluded from the foster system. However, the only families fit to foster, according to the supporters of this bill, are those who give full assent to the most radical tenets of gender theory. What is obvious to most everyone (except the bill&rsquo;s authors) is that such ideological assent signals a willingness to reject sexual boundaries. It is that rejection that makes sexual chaos far more likely in the home, not less. Is that the goal? If minors can consent to invasive transitioning interventions, what can they not consent to?</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">There is also the reality that SB407 is hardly the only bill in California attacking parental rights.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">SB 107, passed and was signed into law in September of last year, allowing minors to be brought to the Golden State against the will of a parent if it is for the sake of seeking gender transitioning.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">In-state parents are not really calling any shots either, according to AB 957&nbsp; which puts parental custody in jeopardy absent the guardian&rsquo;s support of their child&rsquo;s &ldquo;gender identity.&rdquo; Absent full support, which is not defined in the bill, a parent can be charged by a court with child abuse. The age at which the child&rsquo;s desires to begin transitioning must be accommodated is not mentioned, but the bill&rsquo;s author, Assemblywoman Lori Wilson (D-Suisun City) used an example of a seven-year old in arguing the merits of this bill.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>Now this is the author of the article talking here:</strong><span style="font-weight: 400;"> At a recent speaking event I attended for the Awake Americans launch, some protestors carried a sign that read, &ldquo;We don&rsquo;t co-parent with hate groups.&rdquo; Bemused, a few of us commented that obviously we don&rsquo;t want them to co-parent with us either, so&hellip;no problem. But their meaning was more sinister. It was not that they would not co-parent our kids with us, it was that we are unfit to co-parent our own kids with them. They see our kids as theirs to parent and ours to lose.</span></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Biden said as much out loud recently, &ldquo;There&rsquo;s no such things as someone else&rsquo;s child. Our nation&rsquo;s children are all our children.&rdquo; There&rsquo;s no such thing as someone else&rsquo;s child. In no situation do normal people act as though that were true. I do not decide when to speak to other people&rsquo;s children about sex, nor take them home with me at will. I don&rsquo;t even know their food allergies much less make pivotal decisions for them. Someone could dismiss Biden&rsquo;s words as an empty platitude or incoherent ramblings except that they reflect a real perspective that is incrementally creeping into policy.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://www.dailywire.com/news/governor-vetoes-bipartisan-bill-protecting-womens-sports"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.dailywire.com/news/governor-vetoes-bipartisan-bill-protecting-womens-sports</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>Governor Vetoes Bipartisan Bill Protecting Women&rsquo;s Sports</strong></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">North Carolina Governor Roy Cooper vetoed a bipartisan bill that would protect women&rsquo;s sports on Wednesday.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">HB 574, which is titled the &ldquo;Fairness in Women&rsquo;s Sports Act&rdquo; and passed with bipartisan supermajorities, would prohibit men from playing in women&rsquo;s sports in middle schools, high schools, and universities.</span><span style="font-weight: 400;"><br /><br /></span></span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">&ldquo;We don&rsquo;t need politicians inflaming their political culture wars by making broad, uninformed decisions about an extremely small number of vulnerable children that are already handled by a robust system that relies on parents, schools and sports organizations,&rdquo; the Democratic governor stated. &ldquo;Republican governors in other states have vetoed similar bills because they hurt their states&rsquo; reputation and economy and because they are neither fair nor needed.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The Fairness in Women&rsquo;s Sports Act was passed with the support of two Democrats in the state legislature &mdash; Rep. Michael Wray in the House, and Sen. Val Applewhite in the Senate. If Cooper&rsquo;s veto is overridden, the bill would apply to all public schools and any private school that competes against public schools.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Applewhite said that her vote was &ldquo;a tough decision to make&rdquo; and was based on conversations with coaches and other constituents in her district. One umpire told the Democrat that changes in strength levels between boys and girls can start as soon as seven years old.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">According to the Fayetteville Observer, Applewhite received &ldquo;bad threats&rdquo; after her vote. When approached by The News &amp; Observer, Wray declined to comment on why he supported the bill.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Cooper also vetoed SB 49, named the &ldquo;Parents&rsquo; Bill of Rights,&rdquo; and HB 808, which would ban sex change treatments for minors. Unlike the women&rsquo;s sports bill, these two bills passed with no Democratic support.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Cooper&rsquo;s vetoes of HB 574 and HB 808 are likely to be overridden by the North Carolina General Assembly, since the GOP holds supermajorities in both houses, thanks in part to Rep. Tricia Cotham, who switched parties from Democrat to Republican in April and voted for all three bills.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">However, the path forward for the Parents&rsquo; Bill of Rights is less certain, since one Republican, Rep. Hugh Blackwell, voted against the bill, leaving Republicans one vote short of overriding the governor&rsquo;s veto on that bill.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Cooper is not the only Democratic governor to veto bipartisan bills surrounding protecting womens&rsquo; sports, banning sex change treatments for minors, and strengthening parental rights in education.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Governor John Bel Edwards of Louisiana vetoed three similar bills Friday, all of which saw multiple Democrats join Republicans to support them in the state legislature. In a press conference, Edwards compared the bills&rsquo; supporters to segregationists during the Civil Rights Movement.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">We now go to Phoenix&hellip;&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://thepostmillennial.com/phoenix-city-council-votes-to-send-unclaimed-firearms-to-national-police-of-ukraine?utm_campaign=64487"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://thepostmillennial.com/phoenix-city-council-votes-to-send-unclaimed-firearms-to-national-police-of-ukraine?utm_campaign=64487</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>Phoenix City Council votes to send 'unclaimed' firearms to National Police of Ukraine</strong></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The Phoenix City Council passed a vote last week that allows up to 600 unclaimed guns from Phoenix to be donated to the National Police of Ukraine.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The plan is going through a contract with a company, DT Gruelle, that is specially approved for overseas arms trading. Around $200,000 worth of firearms will be handed over to the company for shipment, according to the Arizona Daily Independent.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Under Arizona City law, unclaimed arms need to be resold within one year after they have been obtained by the city. The arms are disposed of or sold "to any business that is authorized to receive and dispose of the article under federal and state law."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">In the June 28 City Council report, the city "selected approximately 500-600 unclaimed firearms to transfer through Gruelle, a private company which provides export and import services." The plan passed with unanimous support.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The report stated that "firearms are unclaimed when there has been no owner contact after a thirty day notice, in which case the City can dispose of them." The Phoenix Police Department states that the firearms are "lost, unclaimed, or found in possession of the Phoenix Police Department." KJZZ said of unclaimed firearms, "essentially they end up in the police department&rsquo;s lost and found"</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">"Only 9mm, 45mm, 39mm and 12 gauge firearms will be sent," according to the notes.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The council promoted the "two year" contract with the private company and, according to the meeting notes, no taxpayer money will be "expended by the City."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">However, questions about the transfer of arms have been raised. The law in Arizona states that firearms that are authorized to be sold by the city need to be sold "to the public" by the business.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The company's website says, "We have a breadth of experience due to 40 years of continuous support to the United States and over 150 other countries, including Iraq, Afghanistan, and Ukraine."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">"We comply with all required procedures which permeate through our ongoing operations," it goes on.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The company has a history of working in Ukraine. In April of 2022 last year, a report showed that a township in Pennsylvania worked with DT Gruelle to raise funds for the Ukrainian war effort, according to the Tribune-Democrat.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Now this! Is it time to boycott Ben &amp; Jerry&rsquo;s?</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://www.newsweek.com/ben-jerry-boycott-calls-july-4th-message-1810991"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.newsweek.com/ben-jerry-boycott-calls-july-4th-message-1810991</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;">&nbsp;</span></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>Ben &amp; Jerry's Faces Boycott Calls Over 4th of July Message</strong></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Ben &amp; Jerry's is facing a boycott after calling on the United States to "commit to returning" stolen Indigenous land in its 4th of July message.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">On Independence Day, the iconic American ice cream brand sparked outrage on social media by publishing a Twitter post with an image reading: "The United States was founded on stolen Indigenous land. This Fourth of July, let's commit to returning it."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">In the caption, the company added: "It's high time we recognize that the US exists on stolen Indigenous land and commit to returning it."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Ben &amp; Jerry's message generated a flood of negative responses on social media, with some calling it the company's "Bud Light moment," referring to controversy and subsequent boycott after the beer brand partnered with a transgender activist in April.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Other Twitter users called on the company to be the first to give up its profits and properties, including factories, buildings and stores. Others said that the company should be returning its factory land to the Abenaki people.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">"Ok you start. Relinquish your headquarters," one Twitter user wrote. "This should be easy then," wrote another. "Shut down and donate all of your land, facilities, and assets to indigenous people."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Others accused the company of virtue-signaling&mdash;the practice of expressing opinions or sentiments intended to demonstrate one's good character, social conscience and awareness of a certain issue, just for the sake of appearing good in people's eyes.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Scrutiny has continued to escalate over the company's support of the LGBTQ+ community and the Black Lives Matter movement, among other polarizing issues.</span></p>]]></description>
   <author><![CDATA[Garrison Hardie]]></author>
   <enclosure url="https://app.dropwave.io/episode/8ea4dd68-6b6d-4ec1-a163-8164a4c598d1/daily-news-brief-for-friday-july-7th-2023.mp3" length="878" type="audio/mp3"/>
   <guid isPermaLink="false"><![CDATA[8ea4dd68-6b6d-4ec1-a163-8164a4c598d1]]></guid>
   <pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
   <source url=""><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></source>
   <itunes:author><![CDATA[Garrison Hardie]]></itunes:author>
   <itunes:image href="https://assets-cdn2.dropwave.io/2ab40ac0-e99d-4f25-a6d2-541d2c9b290a/cover-art/mUK8zsnHkCK3vep7E1W6UgYb9dTnLenASAMEFha3.jpg"/>
   <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
   <itunes:duration>878</itunes:duration>
   <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
  
  </item><item>
   <title><![CDATA[Daily News Brief for Thursday, July 6th, 2023 [Daily News Brief]]]></title>
   <link>https://app.dropwave.io/episode/25b29238-5b56-4c4c-83ca-23fe1d5e6eaa/daily-news-brief-for-thursday-july-6th-2023.mp3</link>
   <description><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">This is Garrison Hardie with your CrossPolitic Daily News Brief for Thursday, July 6th, 2023.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Story Real Estate:</strong></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Home. It&rsquo;s where you build your legacy. Where traditions are started, seeds are planted, meals are shared, and stories are told. Home is where you prepare to go out into the world. Finding the home that&rsquo;s perfect for your family is a big job.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&nbsp;</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Story Real Estate is Moscow&rsquo;s top real estate team. They give people real estate advice all over the country. Family homes, investments, land, new construction, or commercial&mdash; they know real estate.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&nbsp;</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">If you&rsquo;ve thought about a move to Moscow or anywhere in the country, reach out to get connected with a Story Real Estate agent. Wherever you&rsquo;re going, they can help guide you Home. Visit storyrealestate.com.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://thepostmillennial.com/potential-prisoner-swap-deal-in-the-works-for-wall-street-journal-writer-detained-in-russia-report?utm_campaign=64487"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://thepostmillennial.com/potential-prisoner-swap-deal-in-the-works-for-wall-street-journal-writer-detained-in-russia-report?utm_campaign=64487</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Potential prisoner swap deal in the works for Wall Street Journal writer detained in Russia</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Russian and American officials are reportedly discussing a prisoner swap that could include detained Wall Street Journal reporter Evan Gershkovich, however, no further details have been released by either side.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Gershkovich has been held in Moscow&rsquo;s Lefortovo pre-trial detention centre for months after being arrested and charged with "espionage." Previous attempts to free him via the Russian legal system have come up fruitless.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">According to the Washington Post, Kremlin spokesperson Dmitry Peskov explained on Tuesday that officials "don't want [the details] discussed in public," adding that prisoner swap negotiations "must be carried out and continue in complete silence."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The Russian government has appeared willing to swap US-held prisoners for Gershkovich, however, Deputy Foreign Minister said earlier this year that talks would only begin after the journalist's trial had ended.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Gershkovich and the US have tried to hasten proceedings, but it has been to no avail. Last week, a Russian court determined that he had to remain in pre-trial detention at Lefortovo until August 30.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">On Monday, US Ambassador to Russia, Lynne Tracy, met with Gershkovich and noted that he "is in good health and remains resilient despite the circumstances." She expressed hope that the Russian government would "provide regular consular access."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">As the Wall Street Journal reports, White House officials stated on Tuesday, "While we unfortunately do not have a breakthrough to share, we continue to pursue every avenue to secure the release of Evan Gershkovich."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The US government, including Ambassador Tracy, has maintained Gershkovich's innocence and slammed the Russian government over his treatment.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">"The accusations against Gershkovich are unfounded," she said, "and we call on the Russian authorities to release the journalist immediately."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The Wall Street Journal also stood with Gershkovich, stating,"Evan is a member of the free press who right up until he was arrested was engaged in news-gathering. Any suggestions otherwise are false."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The first US journalist to be detained in Russia on charges of spying since the Cold War, Gershkovich could face up to 20 years in prison if found guilty.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Now this! Another whoopsie from the government!</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://justthenews.com/accountability/waste-fraud-and-abuse/usda-says-it-overpaid-10-food-stamp-benefits-2022-program"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://justthenews.com/accountability/waste-fraud-and-abuse/usda-says-it-overpaid-10-food-stamp-benefits-2022-program</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>USDA says it overpaid 10% of food stamp benefits in 2022 as program doubled from 2019</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Largely due to unintentional mistakes" by the government or households, the U.S. Department of Agriculture said it overpaid Supplemental Nutrition Assistance Program benefits in 10% of cases, The Washington Times reports.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The government either wrongly determined households were eligible for the program better known as food stamps or overestimated how much they were due, while 2% were deemed underpayments. The total rate of under- and overpayments was lower before the COVID-19 pandemic: 7.4% in 2019 and 6.8% in 2018.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">States varied widely in how accurate their payments were, with Alaska the worst at overpayment with 57% and South Dakota the best at under 3%.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The program has also doubled since 2019, reaching $113.9 billion from $55.6 billion. It now covers 41 million Americans with an average payment of $230 per month.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The Government Accountability Office also released figures Friday of overpayment across the federal government in fiscal 2022, $247 billion, while cautioning the figure is an estimate because the government cannot "determine the full extent to which improper payments occur."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Now to Los Angeles we go&hellip;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://thepostmillennial.com/los-angeles-homeless-population-spikes-to-more-than-46000?utm_campaign=64487"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://thepostmillennial.com/los-angeles-homeless-population-spikes-to-more-than-46000?utm_campaign=64487</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Los Angeles County homeless population spikes to over 75,000</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Homelessness has increased by ten percent in the city of Los Angeles, and it has increased in Los Angeles County by nine percent.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">According to the 2023 Greater Los Angeles homeless count results conducted by the Los Angeles Homeless Services Authority (LAHSA), Los Angeles County&rsquo;s homeless population increased to approximately 75,518, an increase from 69,144 in 2022. In the City of Angels, the number of homeless people increased to approximately 46,260 people, an increase from 41,980 people in 2022.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Earlier this year, it was revealed that California holds half of all &ldquo;unsheltered people&rdquo; in the US.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Dr. Va Lecia Adams Kellum, chief executive officer of the Los Angeles Homeless Services Authority, said, &ldquo;The homeless count results tell us what we already know, that we have a crisis on our streets, and it&rsquo;s getting worse.&rdquo;&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Los Angeles County Board of Supervisors Chair Janice Hahn called the results &ldquo;disappointing,&rdquo; writing in a statement, &ldquo;It is frustrating to have more people fall into homelessness even as we are investing hundreds of millions of taxpayer dollars and resources into efforts to bring people inside. I appreciate the cities that have stepped up and supported solutions, but these numbers prove that solutions-oriented cities are too few and far between.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Los Angeles officials challenged the accuracy of the 2022 LAHSA count that reported finding zero homeless people in Venice Beach, an area known for its massive homeless problem. As a result, the county used a new counting app and hired a demographer and two data scientists.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Though Democratic Mayor Karen Bass has claimed at least 14,000 homeless people have been moved into interim or permanent housing under her administration, it was revealed earlier this year that the city was spending over $800,000 per housing unit.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The Los Angeles Homeless Services Authority made a point of emphasizing that Los Angeles is not the only major US city to see an increase in its homeless population, noting that Chicago saw a 57 percent increase and Portland saw a 20 percent hike. According to the agency, in California, Kern County saw a 22 percent increase, San Bernardino County a 26 percent increase, San Diego County a 22 percent increase, and Riverside County a 12 percent increase.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Earlier this month, San Diego and Portland approved homeless camping bans.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Moving on&hellip; Do you guys remember that Children&rsquo;s hospital in Boston that was exposed for performing gender mutilation &amp; sterilazation on kids?&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://townhall.com/tipsheet/miacathell/2023/07/04/boston-childrens-hospital-dethroned-n2624870"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://townhall.com/tipsheet/miacathell/2023/07/04/boston-childrens-hospital-dethroned-n2624870</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Children's Hospital Caught Trans-ing Kids No Longer No. 1 for Pediatric Care</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">For the first time in a decade, Boston's Children's Hospital&mdash;which was exposed last year for its experimental genital mutilation, sterilization, and chemical castration of minors identifying&nbsp; &nbsp; as "transgender"&mdash;is no longer the no. 1 pediatric medical center in America.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Since 2014, Boston Children&rsquo;s Hospital has claimed the top spot on U.S. News and World Report's honor roll rating the best pediatric-care facilities in the nation. But, the consumer-ranking giant's 2023 - 2024 list published on June 21 has dethroned the Beantown-based institution, the leading recipient of pediatric-research funding from the National Institutes of Health (NIH).&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">In the latest rankings, Cincinnati Children's Hospital Medical Center took the crown, with Boston Children's Hospital bumped to second place.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">U.S. News and World Report collected data from almost 200 medical centers through an annual survey that examines a myriad of criteria, such as patient safety, clinical outcomes, and surgical success. Each hospital's score was derived from a nationwide polling of 15,000-plus pediatric specialists, who were asked "where they would send the sickest children in their specialty."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Among its LGBTQ-centered departments, Boston Children's Hospital is home to the Gender Multispecialty Service (GeMS) clinic, the "first pediatric and adolescent transgender health program" in the U.S. Serving more than 1,000 families to date, GeMS has expanded to "treat" patients as young as three-years-old. The hospital's Center for Gender Surgery offers surgical mutilation to gender-dysphoric teenagers, including vaginoplasties for 17-year-old boys (Boston Children's Hospital has since quietly changed the age minimum); metoidioplasties and phalloplasties; and chest reconstruction and breast augmentation for 15-year-old kids.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Now, the age range has been raised to 18-years-old in the hospital's official guidance. Removal of the testicles is often performed at the same time as a vaginoplasty, which requires a lifetime of dilation,, and can leave the patient sterile.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Boston Children's Hospital, whose tagline is: "Until every child is well," was caught promoting "gender-affirming hysterectomies" for "trans youth" in a now-scrubbed video, which was part of a 90-part series that positively frames the medical butchery without addressing the irreversible damage that it does to the human body. Other topics highlighted in the series include "Why is hair removal necessary before phalloplasty?" and "Fertility preservation: What transgender patients should know."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Salvaged by Libs of TikTok, an archived version of the 33-second hysterectomy footage shows a smiling Dr. Frances Grimstad of Boston Children's Hospital Division of Gynecology happily describing, as upbeat background music played, the medically unnecessary operation that can render (otherwise) physically healthy patients infertile by removing female reproductive organs.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Another since-deleted video posted to the hospital's YouTube channel showed a psychologist claiming that "a good portion" of children she sees at Boston Children's Hospital GeMS clinic know they're transgender "from the womb.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://twitter.com/i/status/1649007304774123521"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://twitter.com/i/status/1649007304774123521</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> - Play Video&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">In a Journal of the American Medical Association article that Boston Children's Hospital GeMS co-director Dr. Oren Ganor authored on "Streamlining Interstate Access to Gender-Affirming Surgeries," the plastic and reconstructive surgeon called for a drastic increase in "clinician capacity" for children to be subjected to "sex-change" surgeries. Ganor also urged a ramping up of "training efforts" at medical school residency programs to instruct future physicians on performing "transgender" procedures.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The local NPR news station WBUR reported in 2018 that Ganor wrote in an email that Boston Children's Hospital is "slightly flexible" when it comes to the age acceptance of biological males seeking genital surgery "because of the difficulty young women can experience accessing gendered spaces&mdash;like dorms and bathrooms&mdash;if they still have male genitalia." The hospital's policy had not yet been finalized, Ganor said, "because of the issue around consent for sterilization (which is part of the procedure)."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Now, in entertainment news&hellip;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://boundingintocomics.com/2023/07/03/after-the-walt-disney-company-canned-chief-diversity-officer-latondra-newton-warner-bros-discovery-and-netflix-lose-their-diversity-heads/"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://boundingintocomics.com/2023/07/03/after-the-walt-disney-company-canned-chief-diversity-officer-latondra-newton-warner-bros-discovery-and-netflix-lose-their-diversity-heads/</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>After The Walt Disney Company Canned Chief Diversity Officer Latondra Newton, Warner Bros. Discovery And Netflix Lose Their Diversity Heads</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">At the end of June it was revealed that The Walt Disney Company&rsquo;s Chief Diversity Officer Latondra Newton was no longer with the company. Now Warner Bros. Discovery and Netflix&rsquo;s have also seen their diversity heads leave their respective companies.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Variety announced Newton had left The Walt Disney Company after they obtained an internal company memo on June 20th from the company&rsquo;s HR chief Sonia Coleman.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Coleman wrote in the memo, &ldquo;I&rsquo;m writing to share the news that Latondra Newton has decided to leave The Walt Disney Company to pursue other endeavors.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Coleman went on to reveal that Julie Merges would take on Newton&rsquo;s role on an interim basis as the company looked for a new DEI leader, &ldquo;Latondra&rsquo;s direct reports will report to Julie Merges on an interim basis until a new DEI leader is identified. I want to thank Julie for leading this team along with her Talent Acquisition organization.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&ldquo;Additionally, Shelby Curry and the DEI Internal Communications team will continue reporting to Carrie Brown in her role leading internal communications &amp; engagement for the company,&rdquo; Coleman wrote.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Following Newton&rsquo;s exit, TheWrap reported that Netflix&rsquo;s head of inclusion strategy Vernā Myers was stepping down from her position at the company in September. While she is exiting the company as head of inclusion strategy she will still advise the company albeit the report notes she will be focusing primarily on her consulting company, The Vernā Myers Company.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Unlike The Walt Disney Company, Netflix appears to have a replacement for Myers already lined up in Wade Davis. Davis is currently the Vice President of Inclusion Strategy and worked under Myers for four years.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">In a statement Myers said, &ldquo;It&rsquo;s hard to step away from the company and this role because of how much I love Netflix and the people here. I&rsquo;m so excited for the talented Wade Davis who will be taking the lead of the I-and-D work along with our incredible inclusion strategy team and I can&rsquo;t wait to see the continued progress we all will make together.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">At the end of June, Los Angeles Times reported that Warner Bros. Discovery axed its diversity leader Karen Horne, who was the company&rsquo;s Vice President for Diversity, Equity, and Inclusion in North America.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">According to the outlet&rsquo;s sources her departure from the company was announced on June 28th and the company&rsquo;s spokeswoman Megan Klein informed the outlet she was not let go due to Warner Bros. Discovery&rsquo;s &ldquo;cost-cutting but rather a rethinking and reorganization of the company&rsquo;s diversity organization.&rdquo;</span></p>]]></description>
   <author><![CDATA[Garrison Hardie]]></author>
   <enclosure url="https://app.dropwave.io/episode/25b29238-5b56-4c4c-83ca-23fe1d5e6eaa/daily-news-brief-for-thursday-july-6th-2023.mp3" length="866" type="audio/mp3"/>
   <guid isPermaLink="false"><![CDATA[25b29238-5b56-4c4c-83ca-23fe1d5e6eaa]]></guid>
   <pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
   <source url=""><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></source>
   <itunes:author><![CDATA[Garrison Hardie]]></itunes:author>
   <itunes:image href="https://assets-cdn2.dropwave.io/2ab40ac0-e99d-4f25-a6d2-541d2c9b290a/cover-art/mUK8zsnHkCK3vep7E1W6UgYb9dTnLenASAMEFha3.jpg"/>
   <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
   <itunes:duration>866</itunes:duration>
   <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
  
  </item>
 </channel>
</rss>
