<?xml version="1.0"?>
<?xml-stylesheet href="/storage/feed-stylesheet.xsl" type="text/xsl"?>

<rss xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
 <channel>
  <title>FLF - Daily News Brief</title>
  <link>https://dropwave.io</link>
  <description><![CDATA[FIGHT LAUGH FEAST PRESENTS SHOWS PROCLAIMING THE LORDSHIP OF CHRIST OVER ALL OF LIFE.
]]></description>
  <language>en</language>
  <managingEditor><![CDATA[fightlaughfeast@gmail.com (FLF, LLC)]]></managingEditor>
  <webMaster><![CDATA[support@dropwave.io (DropWave Support)]]></webMaster>
  <pubDate>Wed, 29 Mar 2023 13:25:49 +0000</pubDate>
  <lastBuildDate>Wed, 29 Mar 2023 13:25:49 +0000</lastBuildDate>
  <image>
   <url>https://is4-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Podcasts113/v4/58/56/52/5856525c-2973-cf29-3db9-21faa8595391/mza_1144696925612154085.png/1200x1200bb.jpg</url>
   <link>https://dropwave.io</link>
   <title><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></title>
  </image>
  <itunes:author><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></itunes:author>
  <itunes:image href="https://is4-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Podcasts113/v4/58/56/52/5856525c-2973-cf29-3db9-21faa8595391/mza_1144696925612154085.png/1200x1200bb.jpg"/>
  <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
  <itunes:owner>
   <itunes:name><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></itunes:name>
   <itunes:email>fightlaughfeast@gmail.com</itunes:email>
  </itunes:owner>
  <itunes:category text="News"/>
  <item>
   <title><![CDATA[Daily News Brief for Wednesday, March 29th, 2023 [Daily News Brief]]]></title>
   <link>https://app.dropwave.io/episode/02bac00b-821c-48a0-90bb-4a46a3115dfa/daily-news-brief-for-wednesday-march-29th-2023.mp3</link>
   <description><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">&nbsp;This is Garrison Hardie with your CrossPolitic Daily News Brief for Wednesday, March 29th, 2023.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Let&rsquo;s get right into the news&hellip;&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://thepostmillennial.com/breaking-nashville-police-release-body-cam-footage-showing-officers-neutralizing-school-shooter?utm_campaign=64487" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" data-callout-id="edit_links_in_description">https://thepostmillennial.com/breaking-nashville-police-release-body-cam-footage-showing-officers-neutralizing-school-shooter?utm_campaign=64487</a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Nashville police release body cam footage showing officers 'neutralizing' school shooter</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The Nashville Police have released bodycam footage of the school shooting that took place at Covenant Christian school in Nashville, Tennessee on Monday.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The attack resulted in the deaths of six individuals, including three nine-year-old children.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=muz2EDhqEhs&amp;t=8s" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">GRAPHIC WARNING: Officials Release Bodycam Footage From Nashville Elementary School Shooting</a>-Play 5:00-6:00</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The footage showed the heroism of police officers who quickly responded to the situation and took down the shooter Audrey Hale.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Hale had gained entry by shooting through the glass panes of the front door, which was seen on surveillance footage that was released on Monday night by the Nashville police. Hale would go on to shoot and kill three students and three teachers.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Surveillance footage released last night shows Hale's car driving through the school's parking lot.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Hale can be seen walking through a hallway as the alarm goes off, gun drawn.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">"Hale fired a number of rounds inside the Covenant Church/School building. She was armed with these 3 guns and significant ammunition," Nashville PD said in a report.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Hale, a transgender shooter, identified as male using the name 'Aiden' and 'he/him' pronouns. Hale killed head teacher Katherine Koonce, church custodian Mike Hill, and substitute teacher Cynthia Peak in an "assassination" style shooting.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Hale was a former student of Covenant Christian school and was found with multiple firearms. A search of the family home in Nashville uncovered maps and a manifesto detailing the attack, according to police at a Monday press conference.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Armored Republic</span></p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The Mission of Armored Republic is to Honor Christ by equipping Free Men with Tools of Liberty necessary to preserve God-given rights. In the Armored Republic there is no King but Christ. We are Free Craftsmen. Body Armor is a Tool of Liberty. We create Tools of Liberty. Free men must remain ever vigilant against tyranny wherever it appears. God has given us the tools of liberty needed to defend the rights He bestowed to us. Armored Republic is honored to offer you those Tools. Visit them, at <a href="http://ar500armor.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" data-callout-id="edit_links_in_description">ar500armor.com</a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://thepostmillennial.com/biden-to-issue-new-mandates-to-reduce-emissions-by-50-on-cars-trucks-by-2030-climate-czar?utm_campaign=64487" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" data-callout-id="edit_links_in_description">https://thepostmillennial.com/biden-to-issue-new-mandates-to-reduce-emissions-by-50-on-cars-trucks-by-2030-climate-czar?utm_campaign=64487</a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Biden to issue new mandates to reduce emissions by 50% on cars, trucks by 2030</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Biden's climate czar, John Kerry, told Yahoo News that Joe Biden plans on pushing more mandates, especially on cars and trucks in the US, to help attain the goal of cutting US greenhouse gas emissions by up to 50 percent by 2030 and for transportation vehicles to produce zero carbon emissions by 2050.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Kerry was asked about Biden's $739 billion Inflation Reduction Act, which allocated $369 billion on climate change goals and promised a 40 percent reduction in carbon emissions by decade's end and Kerry said, "Well, we're doing a lot more than just the IRA. The IRA is a package that in and of itself can get the 40%. But in addition to that, the president is issuing executive orders."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://rumble.com/v25zusw-john-kerry-praises-select-group-of-human-beings-at-wef-coming-together-to-s.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" data-callout-id="edit_links_in_description">https://rumble.com/v25zusw-john-kerry-praises-select-group-of-human-beings-at-wef-coming-together-to-s.html</a> - Play Video&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The Biden white house has pushed for consumers to move to electric vehicles and have offered tax credits for those who purchase expensive vehicles.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">During the Trump administration, Kerry said, 70 percent of new energy came from renewables but he only speaks of Trump "reluctantly."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Kerry addressed what would happen if a new, Republican, administration took office in 2024 and undid Biden's dictates.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Kerry said people will have to change their lifestyles to accommodate Biden's climate goals, especially when it comes to the use of gas for a utility.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://www.cnsnews.com/blog/craig-bannister/aoc-warns-what-predatory-cisgender-and-often-straight-men-do-when-left" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">https://</a><a href="http://www.cnsnews.com/blog/craig-bannister/aoc-warns-what-predatory-cisgender-and-often-straight-men-do-when-left" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" data-callout-id="edit_links_in_description">www.cnsnews.com/blog/craig-bannister/aoc-warns-what-predatory-cisgender-and-often-straight-men-do-when-left</a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">AOC Warns of What &lsquo;Predatory Cisgender and Often Straight Men Do When Left in the Presence&rsquo; of Women and Children</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Conservatives, straight men, and &ldquo;predatory cisgender&rdquo; people are attacking transgender and LGBT people, in an effort to turn Americans against &ldquo;gender expressiveness,&rdquo; Rep. Alexandria Ocasio-Cortez (D-NY) says.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Ocasio-Cortez introduces one of her recent Instagram video commentaries by vilifying heterosexual men as sexual abuses and praising the LGBT+ community for standing up to them:</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Ocasio-Cortez begins her video by claiming that conservatives are using &ldquo;culture wars&rdquo; to turn Americans against LGBT people who are &ldquo;challenging the institutions of power&rdquo;:</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://twitter.com/therecount/status/1640768226136039424?s=20" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" data-callout-id="edit_links_in_description">https://twitter.com/therecount/status/1640768226136039424?s=20</a> - Play Video&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">That darn patriarchy&hellip;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://www.cnn.com/2023/03/28/politics/mike-pence-grand-jury-testimony/index.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" data-callout-id="edit_links_in_description">https://www.cnn.com/2023/03/28/politics/mike-pence-grand-jury-testimony/index.html</a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Mike Pence must testify about conversations he had with Donald Trump leading up to January 6, judge rules</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">A federal judge has decided that former Vice President Mike Pence must testify to a grand jury about conversations he had with Donald Trump leading up to January 6, 2021, according to multiple sources familiar with a recent federal court ruling.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">But the judge said &ndash; in a ruling that remains under seal &ndash; that Pence can still decline to answer questions related to his actions on January 6 itself, when he was serving as president of the Senate for the certification of the 2020 presidential election, according to one of the sources.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The ruling from chief judge James Boasberg of the US District Court in Washington, DC, is a major win for special counsel Jack Smith, who is spearheading the Justice Department investigation. Pence still has the ability to appeal.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">In the lead-up to the congressional certification vote, Pence faced enormous pressure from Trump and his allies to disrupt lawmakers&rsquo; plans to validate Joe Biden&rsquo;s win. As president of the Senate, Pence was tasked with presiding over the certification proceedings.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Trump&rsquo;s conversations with Pence in the days surrounding the insurrection have been of keen interest to investigators probing the attack. Though Pence declined to testify before the House January 6 committee that investigated the insurrection, people in Trump&rsquo;s orbit told the committee about a heated phone call he had with Pence the day of the attack in which he lobbed insults at his vice president.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Pence and Trump did not speak during the attack on the Capitol itself, in which many of Trump&rsquo;s supporters angrily sought him out, and Pence narrowly escaped the mob heading to the Senate floor.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Nicholas Luna, a former special assistant to Trump, told the committee he remembered Trump calling Pence a &ldquo;wimp.&rdquo; Luna said he recalled something to the effect of Trump saying, &ldquo;I made the wrong decision four or five years ago.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">And Julie Radford, Ivanka Trump&rsquo;s former chief of staff, said she recalled Ivanka Trump telling her that &ldquo;her dad had just had an upsetting conversation with the vice president.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Radford said she was told that Trump had called Pence &ldquo;the P-word,&rdquo; referencing a derogatory term.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">For Pence&rsquo;s part, many of his public comments about his conversations with Trump in the days before and after the insurrection have come in a memoir he published last year.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">In the book, Pence wrote that Trump told him in the days before the attack that he would inspire the hatred of hundreds of thousands of people because he was &ldquo;too honest&rdquo; to attempt to overturn the results of the election.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Over lunch on December 21, Pence wrote, he tried to steer Trump to listen to the White House counsel&rsquo;s team&rsquo;s advice, rather than outside lawyers, a suggestion the then-president shot down.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Hi Contrast Hymn Books</span></p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">If you don&rsquo;t teach your kids the Lord&rsquo;s songs, the world will teach them its songs.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The brand-new Hi-Contrast Hymn Book is designed to help you teach your children the most beloved songs of the Christian faith.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Its captivating illustrations will create special moments of truth, goodness, and beauty in your home every day.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">To get a copy for your family, go to<a href="http://www.hicontrasthymnbooks.com/FLF" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"> </a><a href="http://www.hicontrasthymnbooks.com/FLF" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" data-callout-id="edit_links_in_description">www.hicontrasthymnbooks.com/FLF</a>.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">That&rsquo;s www. &ldquo;H&rdquo; &ldquo;I&rdquo;<a href="http://contrasthymnbooks.com/FLF" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"> </a><a href="http://contrasthymnbooks.com/FLF" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" data-callout-id="edit_links_in_description">contrasthymnbooks.com/FLF</a>.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://www.cnn.com/2023/03/28/politics/joe-biden-social-security-gop-kfile/index.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" data-callout-id="edit_links_in_description">https://www.cnn.com/2023/03/28/politics/joe-biden-social-security-gop-kfile/index.html</a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Joe Biden attacks Republicans for positions he once held about Social Security</span></p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">President Joe Biden and the White House have attacked Republicans in recent months for positions the president himself once held on Social Security and entitlement programs including sunset bills and raising the retirement age, a CNN KFile review of Biden&rsquo;s record shows.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">In his State of the Union address earlier this year, and in the months since, Biden has hammered Republicans over entitlements, saying they want to cut Social Security and Medicare. The president zeroed in on Florida Sen. Rick Scott&rsquo;s sunset plan &ndash; though Biden himself introduced a similar proposal in 1975 &ndash; which would have sunset all legislation without exemptions for the two entitlement programs. Once Biden started attacking Scott for the lack of exemptions for the entitlement programs, Scott added that his sunset provisions would not apply to Social Security or Medicare.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Biden first introduced a proposal in 1975 that would have ceased funding all federal programs &ndash; including Social Security and Medicare &ndash; unless they were reauthorized by Congress. In fact, Biden&rsquo;s bill was the first so-called federal sunset bill, something the president later boasted about in his 1978 Senate reelection campaign.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Biden has also attacked Republicans, saying congressional Republicans want to cut the two entitlement programs and raise the retirement age to 70. The White House vowed to not support any increase in the retirement age in any future negotiations with Republicans even though Biden himself once proposed raising the retirement age as life expectancy went up.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Biden, in one exchange pushing back against plans by then-President George W. Bush to partially privatize Social Security in 2005, said he was open to discussing benefit cuts to guarantee the solvency of the program.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=cIKeu4SkgjU" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Joe Biden in 1987: 'Change' retirement age for Social Security</a>- Play 0:00-1:08</span></p>]]></description>
   <author><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></author>
   <enclosure url="https://app.dropwave.io/episode/02bac00b-821c-48a0-90bb-4a46a3115dfa/daily-news-brief-for-wednesday-march-29th-2023.mp3" length="843" type="audio/mp3"/>
   <guid isPermaLink="false"><![CDATA[02bac00b-821c-48a0-90bb-4a46a3115dfa]]></guid>
   <pubDate>Wed, 29 Mar 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
   <source url=""><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></source>
   <itunes:author><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></itunes:author>
   <itunes:image href="https://assets-cdn2.dropwave.io/2ab40ac0-e99d-4f25-a6d2-541d2c9b290a/cover-art/hUZu1H9lrRY0wXg66WHC8eLwYBA3hbRNTAHQmHt2.png"/>
   <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
   <itunes:duration>843</itunes:duration>
   <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
  
  </item><item>
   <title><![CDATA[Daily News Brief for Tuesday, March 28th, 2023 [Daily News Brief]]]></title>
   <link>https://app.dropwave.io/episode/6c689941-0482-4109-b65b-e86920ce5974/daily-news-brief-for-tuesday-march-28th-2023.mp3</link>
   <description><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">This is Garrison Hardie with your CrossPolitic Daily News Brief for Tuesday, March 28th, 2023.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">We start today with the heartbreaking situation that unfolded in Nashville TN, Three children and three staff members were gunned down at a private Christian school in Nashville on Monday before the shooter, a heavily armed 28-year-old woman, was killed by police, authorities said.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The shooting unfolded at The Covenant School on Burton Hills Boulevard where officers "engaged" the attacker, described by Metropolitan Nashville Police Chief John Drake as a woman who appears to be a former student at the school.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://youtu.be/vTtNVEejhJ0"><span style="font-weight: 400;" data-rich-links="{&quot;fple-t&quot;:&quot;Nashville School Shooting: Police chief provides update&quot;,&quot;fple-u&quot;:&quot;https://youtu.be/vTtNVEejhJ0&quot;,&quot;fple-mt&quot;:null,&quot;type&quot;:&quot;first-party-link&quot;}">Nashville School Shooting: Police chief provides update</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;">- Play 0:05-2:42</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://www.nbcnews.com/news/us-news/school-shooting-tennessee-leaves-multiple-injured-shooter-dead-officia-rcna76841"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.nbcnews.com/news/us-news/school-shooting-tennessee-leaves-multiple-injured-shooter-dead-officia-rcna76841</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;">&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Shooting at Nashville Christian school leaves at least 3 children and 3 adults dead, officials say</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The shooter was identified as Audrey Hale, a Nashville resident, three law enforcement officials briefed on the matter told NBC News.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The shooter was killed on the school's second floor, a police spokesperson said. She had two "assault-type rifles and a handgun," according to the official.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Students of the school, which serves preschool students through sixth graders, were being bused to Woodmont Baptist Church, two miles away, to be reunited with their parents.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Police said they first got calls about the shooter at 10:13 a.m. CT and Nashville firefighters first reported their personnel were responding to an &ldquo;active aggressor&rdquo; at 10:39 a.m. CT.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">"The police department response was swift," police spokesperson Don Aaron told reporters.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Five police officers came upon the shooter and two opened fire on her, Aaron said. The shooter entered the school through a "side entrance" on the first floor, he added.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">It was not clear how the shooter gained access to the school.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">One officer was hurt by shattered glass, officials said.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The names and ages of the victims have not been released. The chief said the families of all six victims had been notified.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Please lift that school, and those affected families in your prayers.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/policy/education/republicans-introduce-resolution-scrap-student-forgiveness"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/policy/education/republicans-introduce-resolution-scrap-student-forgiveness</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Republicans announce resolution to scrap Biden student loan forgiveness plan</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Rep. Bob Good (R-VA) and Sen. Bill Cassidy (R-LA) announced legislation Monday to scrap President Joe Biden's student loan forgiveness program.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Under the resolution, Congress will express disapproval of the student loan cancellation plan to overturn the program, which is stuck in limbo amid a court battle. The resolution will need a simple majority to clear the Senate and is expected to draw a veto from Biden.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">On the Senate side, Sens. John Cornyn (R-TX) and Joni Ernst (R-IA) are backing the Congressional Review Act resolution alongside Cassidy, the ranking member of the Senate Health, Education, Labor, and Pensions Committee.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Biden unveiled the student loan forgiveness plan last August to much fanfare from progressives. Under the initiative, borrowers with an annual income of $125,000 or less can have up to $10,000 in federal student loans canceled, while those who received Pell Grants during their schooling can have up to $20,000 wiped out.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The program stems from the 2003 HEROES Act, which grants the executive power to relieve student loan debt in times of national emergency or war. Critics have pointed out that Biden deemed the COVID-19 pandemic was "over" in a 60 Minutes interview last year. The pandemic was used as justification for using the HEROES Act.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Last November, a lower court in Texas halted the program amid pending legal challenges. The Supreme Court is expected to rule on the program's legality by June or July.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The White House says it has amassed roughly 26 million applications and approved 16 million for relief, but cancellation has not yet taken place amid the legal wrangling.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Biden used his veto power for the first time last week to reject a resolution that would've nixed a Labor Department rule permitting retirement plans to take into account environmental, social, and governance considerations in investment decisions.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://www.foxbusiness.com/markets/fdic-first-citizens-bank-reached-deal-purchase-silicon-valley-bank"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.foxbusiness.com/markets/fdic-first-citizens-bank-reached-deal-purchase-silicon-valley-bank</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>FDIC says First Citizens Bank has reached deal to purchase Silicon Valley Bank</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The Silicon Valley Bank finally has a buyer.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">On Sunday, the Federal Deposit Insurance Corporation (FDIC) announced First-Citizens Bank &amp; Trust Company of Raleigh, North Carolina entered a purchase agreement for all deposits and loans of Silicon Valley Bridge Bank, National Association.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">"The 17 former branches of Silicon Valley Bridge Bank, National Association, will open as First&ndash;Citizens Bank &amp; Trust Company on Monday, March 27, 2023," the FDIC said in a statement.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">"Customers of Silicon Valley Bridge Bank, National Association, should continue to use their current branch until they receive notice from First&ndash;Citizens Bank &amp; Trust Company that systems conversions have been completed to allow full&ndash;service banking at all of its other branch locations," the statement continued.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Depositors of the Santa Clara, California-located bank will automatically become depositors of First&ndash;Citizens Bank &amp; Trust Company, according to the statement, and all deposits will be assumed and insured by First&ndash;Citizens Bank &amp; Trust Company, up to the insurance limit.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The FDIC said: "As of March 10, 2023, Silicon Valley Bridge Bank, National Association, had approximately $167 billion in total assets and about $119 billion in total deposits. Today's transaction included the purchase of about $72 billion of Silicon Valley Bridge Bank, National Association's assets at a discount of $16.5 billion."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">In addition, approximately $90 billion in securities and other assets will remain in the receivership for disposition by the FDIC.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">According to the statement, the FDIC and First&ndash;Citizens Bank &amp; Trust Company entered into a "loss&ndash;share transaction" on all commercial loans it purchased from Silicon Valley Bank (SVB).&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The FDIC estimated SVB's failure cost approximately $20 billion, although a cost will be more accurately determined when the FDIC terminates the receivership, it said.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The FDIC created Silicon Valley Bridge Bank after the California Department of Financial Protection &amp; Innovation closed Silicon Valley Bank on Friday, March 10. All of the deposits&mdash;both insured and uninsured&mdash;were transferred to the bridge bank.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Alps Precious Metals Group</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">THE PAST WEEK HAS BROUGHT SOME &ldquo;EXCITEMENT&rdquo; TO THE MARKETS.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">BANK RUNS.&nbsp; STOCK COLLAPSES.&nbsp; WHAT WAS THOUGHT TO BE STABLE SUDDENLY APPEARS UNSTABLE.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">AND YET, GOLD&rsquo;S PRICE *WENT UP* AS THE HEADLINES BECAME MORE OMINOUS.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">ALPS PRECIOUS METALS WAS ESTABLISHED BECAUSE WE BELIEVE THE BEST WAY TO PROTECT ONE&rsquo;S HARD-EARNED WEALTH FROM THE SERIOUS FINANCIAL PROBLEMS THAT ARE UPON US IS BY OWNING PHYSICAL GOLD AND SILVER.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">CALL JAMES HUNTER OF ALPS AT 251-377-2197, AND VISIT OUR WEBSITE AT WWW.ALPSPMG.COM TO DISCOVER HOW YOU CAN BUY PHYSICAL PRECIOUS METALS FOR YOUR INVESTMENT AND IRA PORTFOLIOS.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">OWN THE ASSET GOD SPECIFICALLY MENTIONED AS &ldquo;GOOD&rdquo; IN THE 2ND CHAPTER OF GENESIS, AND OBTAIN A PEACE OF MIND THAT CAN BE HAD WITH FEW OTHER INVESTMENTS.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">AGAIN, CALL JAMES HUNTER OF ALPS PRECIOUS METALS AT 251-377-2197, AND VISIT WWW.ALPSPMG.COM TO LEARN HOW TO OWN THE BEDROCK ASSET OF THE AGES. </span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://thepostmillennial.com/portland-area-school-administrator-arrested-in-sex-sting?utm_campaign=64487"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://thepostmillennial.com/portland-area-school-administrator-arrested-in-sex-sting?utm_campaign=64487</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Progressive Portland area school administrator arrested in human sex trafficking sting</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Eight men, including a Portland-area high school administrator, were arrested and charged in relation to their alleged participation in a sex trafficking sting conducted by local law enforcement.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">As announced by the city of Lake Oswego's police department, they "conducted a human sex trafficking mission with the assistance of the Clackamas County Sheriff's Office, Oregon City Police, Milwaukie Police, and Sandy Police," on Thursday, March 23, 2023.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">"During the operation, decoys (law enforcement officers) were contacted by men who offered to pay money in exchange for the decoys to perform requested sexual acts," the department stated, going on to describe how the eight suspects allegedly agreed to meet with the supposed trafficking victims, and were subsequently "arrested and charged with the relevant crimes."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Suspects Stephen R. Berry, Maximilien Aquitaine, Austin L. Olson, Vincent S. Namauleg, German D. Pascual, Jake R. Walt, and Erik J. Bjorman were all cited and released for Commercial Sexual Solicitation, officials said. However, according to the Lake Oswego Police Department, the assistant principal of Centennial High School in Gresham, Oregon was hit with additional charges.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">"Terrance A. Schloth (1/11/71) of Gresham, OR initially gave a false name and refused to identify himself," police stated. "As a result, he was lodged at the Clackamas County Jail in order to get a positive identification. He was charged for Commercial Sexual Solicitation (ORS 167.008) and the additional charge of Giving False Information to a Peace Officer in Connection with a Citation (ORS 162.385)."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">According to 52-year-old Schloth's LinkedIn page, he had been working in education for over 27 years, going from a Reynolds High School physical education teacher, to educational leader, to dean of students, and eventually serving as the assistant principal in 2014 before moving to the Centennial School District.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Schloth was a progressive. His LinkedIn boasts of anti-bullying and restorative justice initiatives.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">According to his school profile, two of the accused administrator's children attend Centennial as well. The school district placed Schloth on administrative leave following his arrest, Conan Daily reported.</span></p>]]></description>
   <author><![CDATA[Garrison Hardie]]></author>
   <enclosure url="https://app.dropwave.io/episode/6c689941-0482-4109-b65b-e86920ce5974/daily-news-brief-for-tuesday-march-28th-2023.mp3" length="777" type="audio/mp3"/>
   <guid isPermaLink="false"><![CDATA[6c689941-0482-4109-b65b-e86920ce5974]]></guid>
   <pubDate>Tue, 28 Mar 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
   <source url=""><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></source>
   <itunes:author><![CDATA[Garrison Hardie]]></itunes:author>
   <itunes:image href="https://assets-cdn2.dropwave.io/2ab40ac0-e99d-4f25-a6d2-541d2c9b290a/cover-art/hUZu1H9lrRY0wXg66WHC8eLwYBA3hbRNTAHQmHt2.png"/>
   <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
   <itunes:duration>777</itunes:duration>
   <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
  
  </item><item>
   <title><![CDATA[Daily News Brief for Friday, March 24th, 2023 [Daily News Brief]]]></title>
   <link>https://app.dropwave.io/episode/a5983cc1-b3f5-4ced-88d4-c8cf1462f207/daily-news-brief-for-friday-march-24th-2023.mp3</link>
   <description><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">&nbsp;This is Garrison Hardie with your CrossPolitic Daily News Brief for Friday, March 24th, 2023.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>Hi Contrast Hymn Books</strong></span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">If you don&rsquo;t teach your kids the Lord&rsquo;s songs, the world will teach them its songs.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The brand-new Hi-Contrast Hymn Book is designed to help you teach your children the most beloved songs of the Christian faith.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Its captivating illustrations will create special moments of truth, goodness, and beauty in your home every day.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">To get a copy for your family, go to</span><a href="http://www.hicontrasthymnbooks.com/FLF"><span style="font-weight: 400;"> </span><span style="font-weight: 400;">www.hicontrasthymnbooks.com/FLF</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;">.&nbsp;</span></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">That&rsquo;s www. &ldquo;H&rdquo; &ldquo;I&rdquo;</span><a href="http://contrasthymnbooks.com/FLF"><span style="font-weight: 400;"> </span><span style="font-weight: 400;">contrasthymnbooks.com/FLF</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;">.&nbsp;</span></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://www.foxnews.com/politics/blinken-says-several-americans-remain-detained-taliban-afghanistan"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.foxnews.com/politics/blinken-says-several-americans-remain-detained-taliban-afghanistan</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>Blinken says 'several Americans' remain detained by Taliban in Afghanistan</strong></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Secretary of State Antony Blinken confirmed that "several Americans" remain detained by the Taliban in Afghanistan after the Biden administration's withdrawal from the country in the summer of 2021.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Blinken's comments came during an exchange with Rep. Joe Wilson, R-S.C., during a House Foreign Affairs Committee hearing on Thursday to examine the "State of American Diplomacy in 2023: Growing Conflicts, Budget Challenges, and Great Power Competition."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">"There are several Americans who are being detained by the Taliban. We are working to secure their freedom. The families have asked that we protect their identities and don't speak publicly to their cases," Blinken responded when asked by Wilson how many Americans remain in the war-torn country.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Blinken's comments come as Republicans continue to push for accountability from the Biden administration over its rocky withdrawal from Afghanistan in 2021, which resulted in the deaths of 13 U.S. service members who were killed in a suicide bombing while protecting the evacuation at the Kabul airport.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Republicans in the House of Representatives have begun an investigation into Biden's handling of the withdrawal. Lawmakers seek to examine what they called a "stunning failure" of leadership in their first hearing on the topic earlier this month.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The Taliban quickly took over Afghanistan's capital of Kabul in August 2021 as U.S. troops prepared to withdraw on Biden's orders, timed for the 20th anniversary of the 9/11 attacks. In addition to the thirteen U.S. service members who were killed, 170 others also lost their lives during the withdrawal and thousands of U.S. citizens and allies were left behind in the country overrun by the terrorist group.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Earlier this week, House Foreign Affairs Committee Chairman Michael McCaul, R-Texas, sent a letter &mdash; one of many in recent months &mdash; to Blinken demanding that he provide the committee with "documents and information concerning the Biden Administration&rsquo;s disastrous withdrawal from Afghanistan."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Specifically, McCaul is demanding information from Blinken regarding a "Dissent Channel cable reportedly sent on July 13, 2021, by 23 State Department officials and the Department&rsquo;s response to it," as well as an after-action report and two versions of U.S. Embassy Kabul&rsquo;s Emergency Action Plan (EAP) prior to the embassy's closure.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">In the letter, McCaul warned Blinken that his "failure to produce" those documents would "result in the Committee issuing a subpoena to compel their production."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://www.dailywire.com/news/your-platform-should-be-banned-congresswoman-rips-into-tiktok-ceo-for-targeting-kids"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.dailywire.com/news/your-platform-should-be-banned-congresswoman-rips-into-tiktok-ceo-for-targeting-kids</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>&lsquo;Your Platform Should Be Banned&rsquo;: Congresswoman Rips Into TikTok CEO For Targeting Kids</strong></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Rep. Cathy McMorris Rodgers (R-WA) tore into TikTok CEO Shou Zi Chew during a Thursday morning hearing, accusing him and his company of targeting American children and feeding data to the Chinese Communist Party.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Rodgers, who chairs the House Committee on Energy and Commerce, held nothing back in a blistering opening statement, saying that the platform specifically and intentionally targets children outside of communist China while protecting their own children from the platform&rsquo;s harmful content.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://youtu.be/e-DZTFwyzfY"><span style="font-weight: 400;" data-rich-links="{&quot;fple-t&quot;:&quot;Chair Rodgers to TikTok CEO: &ldquo;Your Platform Should be Banned&rdquo;&quot;,&quot;fple-u&quot;:&quot;https://youtu.be/e-DZTFwyzfY&quot;,&quot;fple-mt&quot;:null,&quot;type&quot;:&quot;first-party-link&quot;}">Chair Rodgers to TikTok CEO: &ldquo;Your Platform Should be Banned&rdquo;</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;" data-rich-links="{&quot;fple-t&quot;:&quot;Chair Rodgers to TikTok CEO: &ldquo;Your Platform Should be Banned&rdquo;&quot;,&quot;fple-u&quot;:&quot;https://youtu.be/e-DZTFwyzfY&quot;,&quot;fple-mt&quot;:null,&quot;type&quot;:&quot;first-party-link&quot;}"> </span><span style="font-weight: 400;">Play 3:00-6:01</span></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Now we go to Michigan&hellip;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://www.foxnews.com/media/michigan-university-hosting-separate-graduation-celebrations-based-on-race-sexuality"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.foxnews.com/media/michigan-university-hosting-separate-graduation-celebrations-based-on-race-sexuality</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>Michigan university hosting separate graduation celebrations based on race, sexuality</strong></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">A Michigan college is coming under fire for hosting five graduation celebrations separated by race, sexuality and gender identity, in addition to the university's larger commencement ceremony.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Grand Valley State University's Multicultural Affairs Office lists graduation ceremonies or celebrations for Black students, Asian students, "Latinx" students, Native American students, and "LGBTQIA+" students next month. The university will also have a general commencement ceremony for all students.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The college describes the graduation celebration for "Latino/a/x students" as "an opportunity to come together and acknowledge Latin accomplishments in the spirit and traditions of culture."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Similarly, the Black Graduation Celebration encourages students to celebrate all "that is representative of Black/African American and African tradition, heritage, culture, and legacy." The ceremony appears to go back to at least 2016.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">An annual "Native American Graduation Feast" has also been held by the school's Native American Advisory Council (NAAC) for the past several years.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">A celebration just for Asian graduates will also take place.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The only celebration hosted by the center not focused on race appears to be the "Lavender Graduation." The rainbow-decorated GVSU webpage will celebrate "the personal and academic achievements of LGBTQIA+ and allied students."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Students are also eligible for an "Outstanding LGBTQIA+ Graduate Award," which is given "to an exceptional student graduating in the Fall or Winter semester of 2023&hellip;who self-identifies as a member of the LGBTQIA+ community," the GVSU site says.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Several other liberal universities have followed similar practices for graduations in recent years.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">New York's Columbia University host graduation celebrations for affinity groups on campus, including "Lavender (LGBTQIA+), Asian, First-Generation and/or Low-Income, Black, Latinx, and Native communities," its website says.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Harvard University also hosts graduation celebrations for Black students, Asian students, Latino students and LGBTQ students.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Grand Valley State University told Fox News Digital that there are unified graduation ceremonies for all students:&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">"Grand Valley State University holds unified Commencement ceremonies for all of its graduates. GVSU is not 'segregating graduation ceremonies by race,' as some people and outlets have said.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">"Grand Valley also welcomes student organizations and faculty leaders to hold smaller scale celebrations designed to honor graduates. These more intimate celebrations are a complement to GVSU&rsquo;s Commencement and are open to all students and their supporters."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">"The vast majority of graduating students who participate in these celebrations also choose to participate in our larger Commencement ceremony where degrees are conferred," a representative said.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://townhall.com/tipsheet/leahbarkoukis/2023/03/22/dead-dolphins-nj-n2620984"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://townhall.com/tipsheet/leahbarkoukis/2023/03/22/dead-dolphins-nj-n2620984</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>NJ Lawmakers Demand Pause on Offshore Wind Projects After Latest Mass-Death Incident at Beach</strong></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Eight dolphins have died in New Jersey after washing ashore a Sea Isle City beach on Tuesday.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">According to the Marine Mammal Stranding Center, two dolphins died shortly after they were spotted on the beach while the six others were euthanized after a veterinarian determined their conditions were deteriorating so rapidly that returning them to the water would have prolonged their suffering in what would have resulted in an &ldquo;inevitable death.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The mass stranding on Tuesday follows a dead dolphin washing up at a New Jersey marina last week, the sixth one to be found along the state&rsquo;s shoreline in under a month.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">In addition to dolphin deaths, nearly a dozen dead whales have washed up along the New Jersey-New York coast since December.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The spate of deaths has prompted lawmakers to call for a suspension of offshore wind projects until it can be determined why the animals are dying.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The eight dolphins that died on Tuesday will be sent to a state lab to determine the cause of death.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Let&rsquo;s take a look at the job market:&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>Jobless Claims Fall to 191,000</strong></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">New claims for unemployment benefits fell last week to 191,000, the Labor Department said Thursday.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Economists had forecast a rise in claims to 197,000. The prior week was unrevised at 192,000.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The Federal Reserve has been attempting to soften demand for labor in order to sap inflationary pressures from the economy. Despite many headlines about layoffs at companies like Amazon and Facebook, unemployment remains extraordinarily low.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The 4-week moving average of initial claims fell by 250 to 196,250.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Continuing claims, which are reported with a one week delay, rise by 14,000 to 1,694,000.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://www.theblaze.com/news/chicago-blackhawks-opt-out-pride23"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.theblaze.com/news/chicago-blackhawks-opt-out-pride23</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>Chicago Blackhawks opt out of 'Pride Night' jerseys, citing safety concerns for Russian players</strong></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The Chicago Blackhawks are yet another NHL team to decline wearing "pride"-themed jerseys for the 2023 season, citing safety concerns for their Russian players, according to the New York Post.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The Blackhawks are the fourth team to decline wearing such jerseys, behind the New York Rangers, New York Islanders, and Minnesota Wild. multiple sports outlets are citing anonymous sources that state the team is doing so to protect Russian players.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The Athletic says that the move was made by &ldquo;team management and security officials&rdquo; and not the players.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Russia has laws against the spread of certain views, which make it illegal to "spread &lsquo;propaganda&rsquo; about &lsquo;nontraditional sexual relations&rsquo; in all media, including social, advertising and movies," according to the New York Times.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The Blackhawks have several players on their roster who could potentially run into problems, including Moscow-born defenseman Nikita Zaitsev.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Goalie Anton Khudobin is a Kazakhstani-born Russian, and forward Philipp Kurashev was born in Davos, Switzerland, but holds Russian citizenship and is the son of a former professional hockey player.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">As well, Canadian-born Boris Katchouk holds Canadian and Russian citizenship, and his mother was an Olympian for the Soviet Union.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">However, other Russian NHL players have worn similar jerseys in the same season, including San Jose Sharks players Alexander Barabanov and Nikolai Knyzhov and Pittsburgh Penguins star Evgeni Malkin.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Just two months prior to the Blackhawks' decision, Ivan Provorov, Russian-born player for the Philadelphia Flyers, cited his Russian Orthodox beliefs as the reason why he didn't want to wear a "pride" warm-up jersey, with San Jose Sharks goalie James Reimer following suit in March 2023 because of his Christian faith.</span></p>
<p><br /><br /></p>]]></description>
   <author><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></author>
   <enclosure url="https://app.dropwave.io/episode/a5983cc1-b3f5-4ced-88d4-c8cf1462f207/daily-news-brief-for-friday-march-24th-2023.mp3" length="890" type="audio/mp3"/>
   <guid isPermaLink="false"><![CDATA[a5983cc1-b3f5-4ced-88d4-c8cf1462f207]]></guid>
   <pubDate>Fri, 24 Mar 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
   <source url=""><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></source>
   <itunes:author><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></itunes:author>
   <itunes:image href="https://assets-cdn2.dropwave.io/2ab40ac0-e99d-4f25-a6d2-541d2c9b290a/cover-art/hUZu1H9lrRY0wXg66WHC8eLwYBA3hbRNTAHQmHt2.png"/>
   <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
   <itunes:duration>890</itunes:duration>
   <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
  
  </item><item>
   <title><![CDATA[Daily News Brief for Thursday, March 23rd, 2023 [Daily News Brief]]]></title>
   <link>https://app.dropwave.io/episode/a4c4c32c-75f7-4ef2-a99e-4ef2f4e421d0/daily-news-brief-for-thursday-march-23rd-2023.mp3</link>
   <description><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">This is Garrison Hardie with your CrossPolitic Daily News Brief for Thursday, March 23rd, 2023.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Alps Precious Metals Group</strong></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">THE PAST WEEK HAS BROUGHT SOME &ldquo;EXCITEMENT&rdquo; TO THE MARKETS.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">BANK RUNS.&nbsp; STOCK COLLAPSES.&nbsp; WHAT WAS THOUGHT TO BE STABLE SUDDENLY APPEARS UNSTABLE.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">AND YET, GOLD&rsquo;S PRICE *WENT UP* AS THE HEADLINES BECAME MORE OMINOUS.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">ALPS PRECIOUS METALS WAS ESTABLISHED BECAUSE WE BELIEVE THE BEST WAY TO PROTECT ONE&rsquo;S HARD-EARNED WEALTH FROM THE SERIOUS FINANCIAL PROBLEMS THAT ARE UPON US IS BY OWNING PHYSICAL GOLD AND SILVER.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">CALL JAMES HUNTER OF ALPS AT 251-377-2197, AND VISIT OUR WEBSITE AT WWW.ALPSPMG.COM TO DISCOVER HOW YOU CAN BUY PHYSICAL PRECIOUS METALS FOR YOUR INVESTMENT AND IRA PORTFOLIOS.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">OWN THE ASSET GOD SPECIFICALLY MENTIONED AS &ldquo;GOOD&rdquo; IN THE 2ND CHAPTER OF GENESIS, AND OBTAIN A PEACE OF MIND THAT CAN BE HAD WITH FEW OTHER INVESTMENTS.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">AGAIN, CALL JAMES HUNTER OF ALPS PRECIOUS METALS AT 251-377-2197, AND VISIT WWW.ALPSPMG.COM TO LEARN HOW TO OWN THE BEDROCK ASSET OF THE AGES.  </span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://thepostmillennial.com/breaking-grand-jury-investigating-trump-over-hush-money-called-off-for-wednesday-delaying-possible-indictment-vote?utm_campaign=64487"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://thepostmillennial.com/breaking-grand-jury-investigating-trump-over-hush-money-called-off-for-wednesday-delaying-possible-indictment-vote?utm_campaign=64487</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Grand jury investigating Trump over 'hush money' called off for Wednesday, delaying possible indictment vote</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">According to two law enforcement officers, the grand jury investigating former President Donald Trump for his alleged involvement in a $130,000 payment to adult film actress Stormy Daniels on the eve of the 2016 election has been canceled for Wednesday.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The grand jury has been meeting on Mondays, Wednesdays, and Thursdays to hear evidence related to the payments made to Daniels. It is unlikely the grand jury will meet for the rest of the week, delaying the process into next week, one source said to Business Insider.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The grand jury's deliberations are secret, and prosecutors are prohibited from discussing what happens during them.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The pause in the grand jury's activity follows the unexpected testimony on Monday of Robert Costello, who was allowed to address the grand jurors at the defense's request.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Business Insider reports: "Star prosecution witness Michael Cohen had told reporters as recently as last week that he had expected to be the grand jury's final witness. Had that remained the plan, Cohen's testimony, which concluded last Wednesday, would have been quickly followed by deliberation and a vote."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Costello, who previously served as Cohen's legal advisor, said he attacked his former client's credibility during his testimony. It is not known why Alvin Bragg, the District Attorney, temporarily halted the grand jury's proceedings.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Trump commented on the grand jury's proceedings on Truth Social, claiming that Bragg is having a hard time with the grand jury. Prosecutors are prohibited from disclosing grand jury details.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Bragg's office has not yet commented on the matter.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://www.dailywire.com/news/deadly-drug-resistant-fungus-spreading-in-hospitals-across-u-s?fbclid=IwAR0ou0XGKdkBSFMurCwvw59_oBlcsNrLTuKNvt1GkEw4_luK0NsSgBLc2I4"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.dailywire.com/news/deadly-drug-resistant-fungus-spreading-in-hospitals-across-u-s?fbclid=IwAR0ou0XGKdkBSFMurCwvw59_oBlcsNrLTuKNvt1GkEw4_luK0NsSgBLc2I4</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Deadly Drug-Resistant Fungus Spreading In Hospitals Across U.S.</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">A new report warns of a potentially deadly fungus &mdash; that resists drugs &mdash; spreading in hospitals around the country.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Candida auris, or C. auris, can be fatal for people who already have weakened immune systems; roughly one-third of people who contract the fungus die, as the fungus attacks through infections in the bloodstream, brain, and heart. Healthy people are not at risk of dying from the disease.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&ldquo;Unfortunately, multi-drug resistant organisms such as C. auris have become more prevalent among our highest risk individuals, such as residents in long-term care facilities,&rdquo; Tammy Yates, spokesperson for Mississippi State Department of Health, stated.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Since November, four people have suffered &ldquo;potentially associated deaths,&rdquo; due to the fungus in Mississippi, Yates noted.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&ldquo;If [the fungi] get into a hospital, they are very difficult to control and get out,&rdquo; William Schaffner of Vanderbilt University Medical Center said. &ldquo;They can persist, smoldering, causing infections for a considerable period of time despite the best efforts of the infection control team and everyone else in the hospital.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The fungus&rsquo; existence in the U.S. was first widely reported in 2016; four people reportedly died from the disease.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The report released by the CDC contends that clinical cases in the United States soared from 476 in 2019 to 1,471 in 2021.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&ldquo;We&rsquo;ve seen increases not just in areas of ongoing transmission, but also in new areas,&rdquo; Dr. Meghan Lyman, who led the study, asserted,</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Acknowledging the findings are &ldquo;worrisome,&rdquo; infectious disease expert Dr. Waleed Javaid cautioned, &ldquo;But we don&rsquo;t want people who watched &lsquo;The Last of Us&rsquo; to think we&rsquo;re all going to die. This is an infection that occurs in extremely ill individuals who are usually sick with a lot of other issues.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The fungus can be spread not only through people but also through contact with patient rooms.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&ldquo;By its nature it has an extreme ability to survive on surfaces,&rdquo; Javaid explained. &ldquo;It can colonize walls, cables, bedding, chairs. We clean everything with bleach and UV light.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Dr. Graham Snyder, medical director of infection prevention at University of Pittsburgh Medical Center, warned that stopping the spread of the fungus was imperative, recalling how the bacteria MRSA, also drug-resistant, spread.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://www.dailyfetched.com/biden-admin-spending-50-million-a-year-just-to-store-trumps-border-wall-materials/"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.dailyfetched.com/biden-admin-spending-50-million-a-year-just-to-store-trumps-border-wall-materials/</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Biden Admin Spending $50 Million a Year Just to Store Trump&rsquo;s Border Wall Materials</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The administration pays private landowners to store 20,000 unused border wall sections at 20 project sites.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Other costs associated with storing the border wall materials included security cameras, electrical and stormwater materials, and overhead lights, Fox News reported.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Republican Senate Armed Forces Committee members sent a letter to assistant secretary of defense for homeland Defense and hemispheric affairs Melissa Dalton detailing the situation.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&ldquo;Every day, the Department of Defense pays $130,000 to store, maintain, and secure these materials,&rdquo; the senators wrote.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&ldquo;Since you were sworn in as the Assistant Secretary of Defense for Homeland Defense and Hemispheric Affairs a year ago, you have allowed the Department to pay over $47 million to store these panels,&rdquo; they said.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Dalton was asked why the Defense Department did not dispose of the unused materials.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The Defence department is required to remove such materials in coordination with the Defense Logistics Agency to reutilize, resell, or demilitarize military property.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&ldquo;We assume you are well aware of this capability since the Department used the program to transfer 1,700 border wall panels to the state of Texas early in your tenure,&rdquo; the senators wrote.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The USACE confirmed President Biden&rsquo;s administration&rsquo;s cancelation of the border wall contracts in 2021 &ldquo;left a variety of excess materials,&rdquo; and the &ldquo;total costs to store, maintain, and secure all the materials across all sites is estimated to be approximately $130,000 per day.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&ldquo;Some of these materials, including security cameras, overhead lights, and electrical and stormwater materials, are being disposed of in accordance with federal excess material disposal laws and regulations,&rdquo; the USACE stated.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&ldquo;Overall, 61% of non-bollard panel materials and 4% of bollard panel materials have been transferred to other government agencies or disposed of through the DLA disposition process. The total value of these materials is estimated at approximately $300 million. However, the cost to the government cannot be finalized until audits are completed and negotiations with contractors are concluded.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">As The Epoch Times noted:</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">U.S. Customs and Border Protection (CBP) has so far apprehended 2,999 Chinese nationals who illegally attempted to cross the southern border in the fiscal year 2023, a 719 percent increase over 2022.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Most of the illegal fentanyl in the United States is manufactured in Mexico by cartels and then trafficked into the United States with the support of the Chinese Communist government in Beijing.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">According to a report issued by Senate Republicans in 2021, Biden&rsquo;s attempt to suspend or end border wall construction cost American taxpayers $3 million per day.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">On March 9, Sen. Jim Risch (R-Idaho) and several Republican senators introduced a bill that would allow the Biden administration to resume construction of Trump&rsquo;s border wall to stop the massive influx of illegal immigrants</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Secretary of Homeland Security Alejandro Mayorkas, who is largely to blame for the mess at the border, is facing impeachment charges in the Republican-controlled House over his handling of the crisis.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Rep. Andy Biggs (R-Ariz.) filed his second article of impeachment against Mayorkas in February, accusing him of exacerbating the crisis.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/policy/energy-environment/biden-to-create-two-new-national-monuments"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/policy/energy-environment/biden-to-create-two-new-national-monuments</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Biden to limit development on 500,000 acres in Texas and Nevada with new monuments</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The White House announced plans to establish two new national monuments as part of President Joe Biden's land conservation agenda, which it said would protect and conserve 514,000 acres of public land in the West.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Biden will sign a proclamation Tuesday at the White House Conservation in Action Summit establishing the Avi Kwa Ame National Monument in Nevada and the Castner Range National Monument in El Paso, Texas. The designations will restrict development in the areas, including drilling and mining and possibly the construction of renewable energy facilities.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The Avi Kwa Ame designation honors tribal nations that consider the area sacred, the White House said. Avi Kwa Ame is home to one of the world&rsquo;s largest Joshua tree forests.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The monument at Castner Range covers the site of a former training and testing site used by the U.S. Army during World War II and the Korean and Vietnam wars. It also contains cultural sites significant to tribal</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Biden set a goal of conserving at least 30% of U.S. lands and waters by 2030 and, in October, established a new national monument encompassing Camp Hale, another former U.S. Army base, and the site of the Continental Divide in north-central Colorado.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">In a separate action Tuesday, Biden will direct Commerce Secretary Gina Raimondo to consider initiating a new National Marine Sanctuary designation to protect all U.S. waters around the Pacific Remote Islands.</span></p>
<p><br style="font-weight: 400;" /><br style="font-weight: 400;" /></p>]]></description>
   <author><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></author>
   <enclosure url="https://app.dropwave.io/episode/a4c4c32c-75f7-4ef2-a99e-4ef2f4e421d0/daily-news-brief-for-thursday-march-23rd-2023.mp3" length="667" type="audio/mp3"/>
   <guid isPermaLink="false"><![CDATA[a4c4c32c-75f7-4ef2-a99e-4ef2f4e421d0]]></guid>
   <pubDate>Thu, 23 Mar 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
   <source url=""><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></source>
   <itunes:author><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></itunes:author>
   <itunes:image href="https://assets-cdn2.dropwave.io/2ab40ac0-e99d-4f25-a6d2-541d2c9b290a/cover-art/hUZu1H9lrRY0wXg66WHC8eLwYBA3hbRNTAHQmHt2.png"/>
   <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
   <itunes:duration>667</itunes:duration>
   <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
  
  </item><item>
   <title><![CDATA[Daily News Brief for Wednesday, March 22nd, 2023 [Daily News Brief]]]></title>
   <link>https://app.dropwave.io/episode/a7085f44-768f-4196-91a5-bce3a83578b7/daily-news-brief-for-wednesday-march-22nd-2023.mp3</link>
   <description><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">This is Garrison Hardie with your CrossPolitic Daily News Brief for Wednesday, March 22nd, 2023.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>Hi Contrast Hymn Books</strong></span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">If you don&rsquo;t teach your kids the Lord&rsquo;s songs, the world will teach them its songs.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The brand-new Hi-Contrast Hymn Book is designed to help you teach your children the most beloved songs of the Christian faith.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Its captivating illustrations will create special moments of truth, goodness, and beauty in your home every day.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">To get a copy for your family, go to</span><a href="http://www.hicontrasthymnbooks.com/FLF"><span style="font-weight: 400;"> </span><span style="font-weight: 400;">www.hicontrasthymnbooks.com/FLF</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;">.&nbsp;</span></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">That&rsquo;s www. &ldquo;H&rdquo; &ldquo;I&rdquo;</span><a href="http://contrasthymnbooks.com/FLF"><span style="font-weight: 400;"> </span><span style="font-weight: 400;">contrasthymnbooks.com/FLF</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;">.&nbsp;</span></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Now to the news&hellip; First in world news&hellip;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://www.foxnews.com/world/vladimir-putin-xi-jinping-sign-economic-deal-latest-demonstration-friendship-limits"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.foxnews.com/world/vladimir-putin-xi-jinping-sign-economic-deal-latest-demonstration-friendship-limits</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>Vladimir Putin, Xi Jinping sign economic deal in latest demonstration of 'friendship without limits'</strong></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Chinese President Xi Jinping and Russian President Vladimir Putin signed an agreement to expand their economic ties during a bilateral meeting in Moscow on Tuesday.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Xi is in Moscow for a multiday series of meetings with his Russian counterpart, aimed at demonstrating the two countries' new "friendship without limits." Xi and Putin emphasized the importance of jointly safeguarding their countries' energy security.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Putin touted plans for a gas pipeline from Siberia to China ahead of the meeting, saying the agreement was all-but finalized.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">"We were just discussing a good project, the new Power of Siberia 2 pipeline via Mongolia. Practically all the parameters of that agreement have been finalized," Putin told Xi at the beginning of the meeting, according to the Financial Times.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Beijing has grown increasingly friendly with Moscow over the past year as Putin's invasion of Ukraine left the country largely ostracized on the world stage.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Xi's visit comes just days after the International Criminal Court issued a warrant for Putin's arrest for war crimes committed in Ukraine. Nevertheless, the pair called each other "dear friend" when they first shook hands on Monday.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Putin alleged during Monday's meeting that the Western world is conspiring to stifle Russia and China by "persistently working to split the common Eurasian space into a network of &lsquo;exclusive clubs&rsquo; and military blocs that would serve to contain our countries&rsquo; development."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The exact details of Russia and China's Tuesday economic agreement have yet to be released.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Over to Paris&hellip;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://nationalpost.com/pmn/news-pmn/crime-pmn/macrons-government-faces-moment-of-truth-over-pension-reform"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://nationalpost.com/pmn/news-pmn/crime-pmn/macrons-government-faces-moment-of-truth-over-pension-reform</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>Protesters set rubbish on fire as French govt barely survives no-confidence vote</strong></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Protesters set piles of rubbish on fire in central Paris on Monday after President Emmanuel Macron&rsquo;s government narrowly survived a no-confidence motion in parliament on Monday over a deeply unpopular pension reform.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The failure of the no-confidence vote will be a relief to Macron. Had it succeeded, it would have sunk his government and killed the legislation, which is set to raise the retirement age by two years to 64.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">But the relief proved short-lived.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">In some of Paris&rsquo; most prestigious avenues, firefighters scrambled to put out burning rubbish piles left uncollected for days due to strikes as protesters played cat-and-mouse with police.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Earlier on Thursday, a Reuters reporter saw police fire tear gas and briefly charge at protesters after the no-confidence vote barely fell short of enough votes to pass.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Unions and opposition parties said they would step up protests to try and force a u-turn.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The vote on the tripartisan, no-confidence motion was closer than expected. Some 278 MPs backed it, just nine short of the 287 needed for it to succeed.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">As soon as the failure of the no-confidence vote was announced, lawmakers from the hard left&nbsp; (LFI, France Unbowed) shouted &ldquo;Resign!&rdquo; at Prime Minister Elisabeth Borne and brandished placards that read: &ldquo;We&rsquo;ll meet in the streets.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">In the southwestern city of Bordeaux, about 200-300 people, mostly youngsters, gathered against the reform and chanted: &ldquo;Macron, resign!&rdquo; A couple of trash bins were lit on fire as the crowd chanted: &ldquo;This will blow up.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Over the past three nights, clashes over the pension reform, in Paris and throughout the country, have been reminiscent of the Yellow Vest protests that erupted in late 2018 over high fuel prices.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">A ninth nationwide day of strikes and protests is scheduled on Thursday.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">&ldquo;Nothing undermines the mobilization of workers,&rdquo; the hardline CGT union said after the vote, calling on workers to step up industrial action and &ldquo;participate massively in rolling strikes and demonstrations.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Opposition parties will also challenge the bill in the Constitutional Council, which could decide to strike down some or all of it &ndash; if it considers it breaches the constitution.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">A second motion of no confidence, tabled by the far-right National Rally (RN), also failed, after it gathered only 94 votes. Other opposition parties said they would not vote for it.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Far-right leader Marine Le Pen said Borne should go. She said Macron should call a referendum on the reform but was unlikely to do so. &ldquo;He&rsquo;s deaf to what the French people want,&rdquo; she told reporters.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://townhall.com/tipsheet/katiepavlich/2023/03/20/this-is-insane-mexican-government-seizes-assets-of-american-company-n2620887"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://townhall.com/tipsheet/katiepavlich/2023/03/20/this-is-insane-mexican-government-seizes-assets-of-american-company-n2620887</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>'This Is Insane': Mexican Military Just Seized Assets of an American Company</strong></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Over the weekend, the Mexican military seized a number of assets belonging to American company Vulcan Materials.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">"The seizure of a US company's marine terminal in Mexico has drawn criticism from a US senator and risks sparking more tension between the two nations amid spats over energy and security," Bloomberg reports. "US construction firm Vulcan Materials alleges that armed forces, including from the Mexican government, launched a takeover of its facility in the country's southeast on Tuesday. The company says a federal judge in Mexico has ordered a stay on any government effort to confiscate the property."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The move prompted national security experts to sound the alarm, calling the situation "insane."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Former Director of National Intelligence John Ratcliffe is also weighing in, noting President Joe Biden's continued weakness on the world stage.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Last week, Mexican President Andr&eacute;s Manuel L&oacute;pez Obrador lashed out after Republicans called for additional tools to use military force against Mexican cartels.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2023/03/21/february-home-sales-spike.html"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.cnbc.com/2023/03/21/february-home-sales-spike.html</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>Home sales spike 14.5% in February as the median price drops for the first time in over a decade</strong></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Sales of previously owned homes rose 14.5% in February compared with January, according to a seasonally adjusted count by the National Association of Realtors. That put sales at an annualized rate of 4.58 million units.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">It was the first monthly gain in 12 months and the largest increase since July 2020, just after the start of the Covid-19 pandemic. Sales were, however, 22.6% lower than they were in February of last year.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">These sales counts are based on closings, so the contracts were likely signed at the end of December and throughout January, when mortgage rates had fallen sharply. The average rate on the popular 30-year fixed loan hovered in the low 6% range throughout January after reaching a high of 7% last fall.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The relative drop caused a jump in sales of newly built homes, before rates jumped back toward 7% in February. They now stand at 6.67%, according to Mortgage News Daily.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">&ldquo;Conscious of changing mortgage rates, home buyers are taking advantage of any rate declines,&rdquo; said Lawrence Yun, chief economist for the Realtors, in a release. &ldquo;Moreover, we&rsquo;re seeing stronger sales gains in areas where home prices are decreasing and the local economies are adding jobs.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Higher mortgage rates have been cooling home prices since last summer, and for the first time in a record 131 consecutive months &mdash; nearly 11 years &mdash; prices were lower on a year-over-year comparison. The median price of an existing home sold in February was $363,000, a 0.2% decline from February 2022.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">That lower median price could be a sign that homes on the more affordable end of the market are selling.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Sales might have been even higher were it not for what is still very low supply. There were just 980,000 homes for sale at the end of February, according to the Realtors, flat compared with January. At the current sales pace, that represents a 2.6-month supply. A balanced market between buyer and seller is considered a 4- to 6-month supply.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">&ldquo;Inventory levels are still at historic lows,&rdquo; Yun added. &ldquo;Consequently, multiple offers are returning on a good number of properties.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">This could start to heat prices again, but with mortgage rates now higher than they were in January it will be harder for some buyers to compete.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">All-cash sales accounted for 28% of transactions in February, down from 29% in January but up from 25% in February 2022. Individual investors returned, making up 18% of buyers, up from 16% in January but down from 19% in February 2022.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">When looking at sales at different price points, they were all down in the range of 20% from February last year, with sales down the most in the top, million-dollar-plus segment.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://www.cnn.com/2023/03/21/politics/idaho-firing-squad-bill/index.html"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.cnn.com/2023/03/21/politics/idaho-firing-squad-bill/index.html</span></a></span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Idaho lawmakers approve bill that would allow execution by firing squad</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Idaho lawmakers approved a bill Monday that would allow execution by firing squad, according to the legislature&rsquo;s website.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">State Rep. Bruce D. Skaug confirmed the move in a statement to CNN.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">&ldquo;H186 has now passed the Idaho Senate and House with a veto proof majority,&rdquo; Skaug wrote in an email to CNN. &ldquo;Upon signature of the Governor, the state may now more likely carry out justice, as determined by our judicial system, against those who have committed first degree murder.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">A total of 24 officials voted for the bill, while 11 voted against it.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">House Bill 186 will move to Republican Gov. Brad Little&rsquo;s desk next.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The bill stipulates that firing squads will be used only if the state cannot obtain the drugs needed for lethal injections. Several states have struggled to source the drugs required for lethal injection, causing them to pause executions and triggering lawsuits from inmates who argue the injections are inhumane.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Additionally, the bill permits Idaho to use firing squads if lethal injections are deemed unconstitutional by a court.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">A fiscal note tied to the bill explains that refurbishing the Department of Correction to meet &ldquo;safety and execution requirements for the firing squad&rdquo; will cost around $750,000.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">If the bill is signed into law, Idaho will follow South Carolina, which approved the usage of firing squads in March 2022. Three other states permit firing squads, according to the Death Penalty Information Center: Mississippi, Utah and Oklahoma.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">A firing squad was last used in the US in 2010 to execute convicted murderer Ronnie Lee Gardner in Utah.</span></p>]]></description>
   <author><![CDATA[Garrison Hardie]]></author>
   <enclosure url="https://app.dropwave.io/episode/a7085f44-768f-4196-91a5-bce3a83578b7/daily-news-brief-for-wednesday-march-22nd-2023.mp3" length="706" type="audio/mp3"/>
   <guid isPermaLink="false"><![CDATA[a7085f44-768f-4196-91a5-bce3a83578b7]]></guid>
   <pubDate>Wed, 22 Mar 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
   <source url=""><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></source>
   <itunes:author><![CDATA[Garrison Hardie]]></itunes:author>
   <itunes:image href="https://assets-cdn2.dropwave.io/2ab40ac0-e99d-4f25-a6d2-541d2c9b290a/cover-art/hUZu1H9lrRY0wXg66WHC8eLwYBA3hbRNTAHQmHt2.png"/>
   <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
   <itunes:duration>706</itunes:duration>
   <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
  
  </item><item>
   <title><![CDATA[Daily News Brief for Tuesday, March 21st, 2023 [Daily News Brief]]]></title>
   <link>https://app.dropwave.io/episode/d6af41df-33c2-40eb-9791-f638ceec870a/daily-news-brief-for-tuesday-march-21st-2023.mp3</link>
   <description><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">This is Garrison Hardie with your CrossPolitic Daily News Brief for Tuesday, March 21st, 2023. Happy Tuesday everyone! I hope you all had a fantastic weekend with you and yours! Before we get to the news&hellip;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">THE PAST WEEK HAS BROUGHT SOME &ldquo;EXCITEMENT&rdquo; TO THE MARKETS.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">BANK RUNS.&nbsp; STOCK COLLAPSES.&nbsp; WHAT WAS THOUGHT TO BE STABLE SUDDENLY APPEARS UNSTABLE.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">AND YET, GOLD&rsquo;S PRICE *WENT UP* AS THE HEADLINES BECAME MORE OMINOUS.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">ALPS PRECIOUS METALS WAS ESTABLISHED BECAUSE WE BELIEVE THE BEST WAY TO PROTECT ONE&rsquo;S HARD-EARNED WEALTH FROM THE SERIOUS FINANCIAL PROBLEMS THAT ARE UPON US IS BY OWNING PHYSICAL GOLD AND SILVER.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">CALL JAMES HUNTER OF ALPS AT 251-377-2197, AND VISIT OUR WEBSITE AT WWW.ALPSPMG.COM TO DISCOVER HOW YOU CAN BUY PHYSICAL PRECIOUS METALS FOR YOUR INVESTMENT AND IRA PORTFOLIOS.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">OWN THE ASSET GOD SPECIFICALLY MENTIONED AS &ldquo;GOOD&rdquo; IN THE 2ND CHAPTER OF GENESIS, AND OBTAIN A PEACE OF MIND THAT CAN BE HAD WITH FEW OTHER INVESTMENTS.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">AGAIN, CALL JAMES HUNTER OF ALPS PRECIOUS METALS AT 251-377-2197, AND VISIT WWW.ALPSPMG.COM TO LEARN HOW TO OWN THE BEDROCK ASSET OF THE AGES.  </span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://www.politico.com/news/2023/03/20/law-enforcement-donald-trump-indictment-plan-00087836"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.politico.com/news/2023/03/20/law-enforcement-donald-trump-indictment-plan-00087836</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Trump indictment could land as early as Monday, sending law enforcement scrambling</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Law enforcement officials are meeting at NYPD headquarters in lower Manhattan on Monday afternoon to plan for a possible indictment of former President Donald Trump on charges stemming from payments to a porn star, a person involved in the planning told POLITICO.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">An indictment by a grand jury is expected late Monday or Wednesday, according to three people involved in the deliberations.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">A court spokesperson said there&rsquo;s nothing to report since no charges have been filed. Spokespeople for the Secret Service and District Attorney&rsquo;s Office did not immediately respond to requests for comment.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&ldquo;The NYPD&rsquo;s state of readiness remains a constant at all times, for all contingencies,&rdquo; an NYPD spokesperson said. &ldquo;Our communications and coordination with our partners in government and in law enforcement are fundamental tenets of our commitment to public safety.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Attorney Robert J. Costello, who once advised former Trump lawyer Michael D. Cohen, is scheduled to testify before the grand jury Monday afternoon. Cohen has said he will be a rebuttal witness to Costello, who may question Cohen&rsquo;s credibility.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Once the sealed indictment is delivered to the judge, the DA&rsquo;s office would discuss Trump&rsquo;s surrender with his counsel, according to a court official who, like the others, was granted anonymity to discuss internal planning procedures. If Trump were to not surrender, a warrant would be issued for his arrest.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Whether Trump would be handcuffed is a decision that would be made by the district attorney, the court official said. He would be finger printed and a mug shot would be taken, though he is not expected to be &ldquo;perp-walked&rdquo; or paraded before the public in handcuffs, the official said.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The Manhattan Criminal Courthouse, a 17-story Art Deco building that sits just northwest of the Brooklyn Bridge, was surrounded by over a dozen news vans Monday morning. Security was heightened as police officers and court officers set up barricades outside the courthouse. There was no sign of protesters.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">New York City Mayor Eric Adams said Monday he has not met with Bragg on the situation, but is prepared for any contingencies.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">While the New York Young Republicans planned for peaceful protests, more sinister messages were posted on conservative chat sites. On the site patriots.win, once TheDonald.win &mdash; a site which lawmakers said played a significant role in organizing January 6th &mdash; users called for a &ldquo;nationwide strike&rdquo; and for &ldquo;all patriots&rdquo; to &ldquo;bring society to a halt.&rdquo; The arrest of Donald Trump and calls to protest was the top post section in the chat site on Monday.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">A leading Republican elected official in the state said he did not expect large, pro-Trump protests.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&ldquo;You&rsquo;ll get the same crazy couple dozen people and that&rsquo;s it,&rdquo; said the Republican official, who was granted anonymity to speak frankly about internal party dynamics.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&ldquo;There&rsquo;ll probably more counter protestors than protestors,&rdquo; he said.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://thepostmillennial.com/breaking-biden-vetoes-bill-banning-woke-funds-for-americans-retirement-accounts?utm_campaign=64487"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://thepostmillennial.com/breaking-biden-vetoes-bill-banning-woke-funds-for-americans-retirement-accounts?utm_campaign=64487</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Biden vetoes bill banning woke funds for Americans' retirement accounts</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Joe Biden issued his first veto as president on Monday in a sign of what's to be expected with the Republican-majority Congress. Biden is seeking to kill a GOP measure that would ban the federal government from considering the environmental impacts or lawsuits when making investment decisions for retirement plans.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The measure, which was vetoed by Biden, ended a Biden administration rule allowing federal managers of retirement plans to consider factors such as climate change, social impacts, or pending lawsuits when making investment choices, a move that undid a Trump-era ban on the practice, The Hill reported</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Critics of environmental, social and governance (ESG) investments believe that money is allocated based on leftist causes rather than returns for retirees. Author James Lindsay, a vocal critic of ESG, told The Post Millennial, "ESG is a scam against America and a first-rate national security threat, and Biden is in on it. ESG uses your retirement money to do Woke and Sustainability activism that hurts America and everyday Americans."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Now this!</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://www.conservativereview.com/fauci-gets-reamed-after-trying-to-push-vaccine-on-black-man-2659623988.html"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.conservativereview.com/fauci-gets-reamed-after-trying-to-push-vaccine-on-black-man-2659623988.html</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Fauci Gets Reamed After Trying To Push Vaccine On DC Resident</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">A Washington, D.C., resident stunned Dr. Anthony Fauci and Mayor Muriel Bowser after he refused to take the vaccine and alleged the government was running a fear campaign.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Fauci and Boswer visited Anacostia residents to combat vaccine hesitancy when they knocked on the door of one resident who was having none of their vaccine talk.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://twitter.com/i/status/1637790253258866688"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://twitter.com/i/status/1637790253258866688</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> - Play Video 0:00-1:58</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Moving on&hellip;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://hotair.com/david-strom/2023/03/20/minnesotas-woman-of-the-year-is-a-man-n537969"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://hotair.com/david-strom/2023/03/20/minnesotas-woman-of-the-year-is-a-man-n537969</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Minnesota's "woman of the year" is a man</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Because of course &ldquo;she&rdquo; is.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">At the risk of being accused of &ldquo;stochastic terrorism,&rdquo; I am compelled to state the obvious: it is not the case that every woman in the State of Minnesota is less worthy than the natal male Leigh Finke.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">USA Today begs to differ. Every woman in my state is less worthy of national recognition for excellence in womanhood than Finke.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&ldquo;She&rdquo; looks like a dude in a dress, and that is because &ldquo;she&rdquo; is a dude in a dress.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Yet we are to believe that a man cosplaying as a woman is the most praiseworthy woman in the state.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Finke must be one impressive &ldquo;woman,&rdquo; since &ldquo;she&rdquo; rose from being just a guy to the most impactful woman in my state is less than 6 years. It&rsquo;s the same path that transgender athletes take so often: a mediocre man becomes an exceptional woman, not through hard work, diligence, accomplishment, or anything similar. They do it by pretending to be a woman, and the rest of society applauds them and plays along.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Before we end today&hellip; how are your brackets doing? This is easily one of the most insane March Madness Tournaments that I can remember: </span><a href="https://youtu.be/cOA8zCg2kcQ"><span style="font-weight: 400;" data-rich-links="{&quot;fple-t&quot;:&quot;These are the best moments from Saturday's second round&quot;,&quot;fple-u&quot;:&quot;https://youtu.be/cOA8zCg2kcQ&quot;,&quot;fple-mt&quot;:null,&quot;type&quot;:&quot;first-party-link&quot;}">These are the best moments from Saturday's second round</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;">- Play Video&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Thus far, here are the best brackets in our Fight Laugh Feasters Group:&nbsp;</span></p>
<ol>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Choul1784 - Houston - 99.8%</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Lenwood Smith - Kansas - 99.6%</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">JoshuaOC - Alabama - 99.2%</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Matt Sarr - 98.3% - Houston</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Mike Gore - 98.3% - Houston</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">TravisBuys - 98.3% - Houston</span></li>
</ol>]]></description>
   <author><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></author>
   <enclosure url="https://app.dropwave.io/episode/d6af41df-33c2-40eb-9791-f638ceec870a/daily-news-brief-for-tuesday-march-21st-2023.mp3" length="946" type="audio/mp3"/>
   <guid isPermaLink="false"><![CDATA[d6af41df-33c2-40eb-9791-f638ceec870a]]></guid>
   <pubDate>Tue, 21 Mar 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
   <source url=""><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></source>
   <itunes:author><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></itunes:author>
   <itunes:image href="https://assets-cdn2.dropwave.io/2ab40ac0-e99d-4f25-a6d2-541d2c9b290a/cover-art/hUZu1H9lrRY0wXg66WHC8eLwYBA3hbRNTAHQmHt2.png"/>
   <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
   <itunes:duration>946</itunes:duration>
   <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
  
  </item><item>
   <title><![CDATA[Daily News Brief for Friday, March 17th, 2023 [Daily News Brief]]]></title>
   <link>https://app.dropwave.io/episode/243e7611-272d-4aea-9796-7187e8b791b2/daily-news-brief-for-friday-march-17th-2023.mp3</link>
   <description><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">This is Garrison Hardie with your CrossPolitic Daily News Brief for Friday, March 17th, 2023. Happy Friday everyone!&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>New Saint Andrews:</strong></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Today&rsquo;s culture shifts like sand, but New Saint Andrews College is established on Christ, the immovable rock. The college is a premier institution that forges evangelical leaders who don&rsquo;t fear or hate the world. Guided by God&rsquo;s word, equipped with the genius of classical liberal arts and God-honoring wisdom, with a faculty dedicated to academic rigor and to God&rsquo;s kingdom, New Saint Andrews College offers an education that frees people.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Logic and language, hard work and joyful courage, old books and godly professors &mdash; New Saint Andrews Colleges provides time-tested resources that can equip your student for any vocation. To find out more, visit: nsa.edu</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://www.theepochtimes.com/health/american-children-are-dying-at-highest-rate-in-50-years_5124568.html?utm_source=partner&amp;utm_campaign=BonginoReport"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.theepochtimes.com/health/american-children-are-dying-at-highest-rate-in-50-years_5124568.html?utm_source=partner&amp;utm_campaign=BonginoReport</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>American Children Are Dying at Highest Rate in 50 Years</strong><strong><br /><br /></strong></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Mortality rates among American children and adolescents rose by almost 20 percent in just two years, with non-COVID injuries being a top reason for increased deaths.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Between 2019 and 2020, all-cause mortality rates for Americans in the age group of 1 to 19 years jumped by 10.7 percent, according to data collected and published by JAMA Network from the American Medical Association. This was followed by an 8.3 percent spike between 2020 and 2021. The total mortality rate in the two years between 2019 and 2021 was 19 percent&mdash;the biggest increase in at least 50 years. &ldquo;These increases, the largest in decades, followed a period of great progress in reducing pediatric mortality rates,&rdquo; the editorial stated.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&ldquo;This reversal in the pediatric mortality trajectory was caused not by COVID-19, but by injuries,&rdquo; the editorial stated. &ldquo;In 2020, the COVID-19 mortality rate at ages 1 to 19 years was 0.24 deaths per 100 000, but the absolute increase in injury deaths alone was nearly 12 times higher (2.80 deaths per 100 000).&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Between 2019 and 2020, injury mortality rose by 22.6 percent among those between the ages of 10 and 19, with homicides rising by 39.1 percent and drug overdose deaths jumping by 113.5 percent. Among children aged 1 to 9 years, injuries accounted for 63.7 percent of the increase in all-cause mortality in 2021.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&ldquo;We&rsquo;ve now reached a tipping point where the number of injury-related deaths is so high that it is offsetting many of the gains we&rsquo;ve made in treating other diseases,&rdquo; said Elizabeth Wolf, an author of the editorial and an assistant professor in the department of pediatrics at the Virginia Commonwealth University&rsquo;s School of Medicine.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The editorial points out that the increase in injury deaths predates the pandemic. For instance, suicides among individuals between 10 and 19 years of age began to rise in 2007, with homicide rates starting to increase in 2013.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Between 2007 and 2019, mortality rates for suicide rose by 69.5 percent. Between 2013 and 2019, homicide rates increased by 32.7 percent. The editorial blamed the increase in suicide and homicide rates on a &ldquo;deepening&rdquo; mental health crisis and access to firearms.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Despite the fear created by the pandemic, the share of COVID-19 in deaths among children and young people (CYP) was lower when compared to other causes, according to a Jan. 30 study published in JAMA Network.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The study identified 821 deaths among CYP aged 0 to 19 years between August 1, 2021, and July 31, 2022, in the United States and compared it with other causes of death in 2019 prior to the pandemic. COVID-19 was ranked eighth among all causes of death within this demographic, accounting for 2 percent of all causes of death.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">According to data from the National Center for Health Statistics, unintentional injuries were the leading cause of death among children in 2020, accounting for 12.5 percent of deaths below the age of 12 and 31.4 percent of deaths among adolescents aged 12-17.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">COVID-19 accounted for 0.3 percent of deaths in children under the age of 12 and 0.8 percent of deaths among those aged 12-17.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Mental health among children and adolescents worsened during the pandemic per a paper published in The Lancet Psychiatry that analyzed emergency department visits. The analysis found a 22 percent jump in youth visits for suicide attempts when comparing the period prior to the pandemic to the pandemic period until July 2021.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">This surge in suicide visits happened even though there was a 32 percent reduction in pediatric emergency department visits for health-related reasons during the pandemic. In addition, there was also an 8 percent increase in visits for suicidal ideation&mdash;referring to individuals who entertain suicidal thoughts.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">A study on the National Poison Data System found that suspected suicide attempts through self-poisoning among children rose by 26.7 percent between 2015 and 2020.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Speaking of children&hellip;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://hotair.com/david-strom/2023/03/15/fda-pushing-vaccine-boosters-for-infants-based-upon-trials-in-just-24-children-n537177"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://hotair.com/david-strom/2023/03/15/fda-pushing-vaccine-boosters-for-infants-based-upon-trials-in-just-24-children-n537177</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>FDA pushing vaccine boosters for infants based upon trials in just 24 children</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The FDA has approved the use of a new bivalent COVID-19 booster for children 6 months old to 4 years old based upon trials that included almost no children.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">24 participants for the 6-month-23-month cohort, and 36 for the 2 years through 4 years old cohort. 60 children in all.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">There are tens of millions of children in these age cohorts, and while this sort of trial is better than one where only 9 mice are given the jab, it strikes me as bizarre that the FDA is pushing this out the door and recommending that all children in America be vaccinated with a jab that has barely been tested.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Particularly given that the COVID virus presents almost no threat to any children those ages.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">European countries have pulled back from recommending or even giving COVID vaccines to people under 50, except in cases where the patient is in a high-risk category. It beggars belief that the United States FDA is still going full steam ahead recommending vaccines that are not actually approved&ndash;they are being given under an Emergency Use Authorization, not full approval&ndash;to millions of children at little risk for serious disease.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Even the FDA admits that there are side effects, because of course there are. There are with everything. Side effects can be justified if the benefits outweigh the downsides, but there really is no evidence that the benefits are there.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Alps Precious Metals Group</strong></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The Word of God in Genesis 2:10-12b teaches this:</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&ldquo;&hellip;And a river went out of Eden to water the garden; and from thence it was parted, and became into four heads.&nbsp; The name of the first is Pison: that is it which compasseth the whole land of Havilah, where there is gold;&nbsp; And the gold of that land is good&hellip;&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Gold maintains God&rsquo;s stamp of approval if used with the wisdom He gives us by His Grace.&nbsp;&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Since the creation of the Federal Reserve and all of the other Central Planning Banks around the world, tumultuous modern financial markets have been the natural consequence.&nbsp; In the midst of these tempests, such as the one that is upon us now, Gold has maintained an impeccable record of preserving the labor and wealth of individuals, families and institutions.&nbsp;&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Alps Precious Metals is a U.S.-based company formed for the purpose of re-establishing the essential role of Physical Precious Metals within investment portfolios.&nbsp; Whether as a compliment or replacement for bank/brokerage accounts and/or Retirement accounts, Physical Precious Metals allow the investor to own *the* bedrock asset that has weathered all financial storms.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Call James Hunter of Alps at 251-377-2197, and visit our website at www.alpspmg.com to begin the discussion of the trading and Vaulting of Physical Precious Metals.&nbsp;&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://townhall.com/tipsheet/spencerbrown/2023/03/16/biden-administration-pursuing-a-taxpayer-funded-bailout-for-moderna-n2620646"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://townhall.com/tipsheet/spencerbrown/2023/03/16/biden-administration-pursuing-a-taxpayer-funded-bailout-for-moderna-n2620646</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>The Biden Administration Is Trying to Bail Out Moderna</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">While Americans' eyes and justified outrage are aimed at the Biden administration's "not a bailout" bailout of failed banks, there's an even larger bailout &mdash; and potentially a new scandal for Biden &mdash; his administration is pursuing.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Specifically, the Biden Department of Justice has inserted the federal government &mdash; and with it hardworking American taxpayers &mdash; into a patent infringement dispute alleging that Moderna stole intellectual property from smaller biotech companies and used it to create and produce its COVID-19 mRNA vaccine that's since been administered more than 250 million times in the U.S. and sent the company's revenue soaring.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">According to the two small biotech companies alleging patent infringement &mdash; called Arbutus and Genevant &mdash; Moderna stole their vaccine delivery method that uses lipid nanoparticles (LNPs) to protect vaccine-introduced mRNA in the bloodstream and help ensure it reaches the intended target to become effective.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Moderna's response to Arbutus and Genevant has not focused on the companies' claims, but sought to have the case dismissed entirely. Moderna says that, under a World War I-era law found in Section 1498 of U.S. Code, its vaccine development and production is shielded from patent claims because it was under contract to provide the vaccine to the federal government. Moderna maintains its COVID vaccine did not infringe on intellectual property, but said that "dispute is for later."&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Rather than allowing the case to play out on its own, the Biden administration &mdash; via Delaware U.S. Attorney David Weiss &mdash; filed a statement of interest in the dispute last month "to relieve Moderna of any liability for patent infringement resulting in performance of the &rsquo;-0100 Contract and to transfer to the United States any liability for the manufacture or use of the inventions claimed in the Patents-in-Suit resulting from the authorized and consented acts."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The "-0100 Contract" mentioned by the U.S. attorney in its statement of interest is an $8.2 billion contract between Moderna and the Department of Defense coded as "pharmaceutical preparation manufacturing."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">So, the Biden administration appears to be stepping in and seeking to put hardworking American taxpayers on the hook for what could be potentially billions of dollars worth of liability claims caused by Moderna's alleged theft of intellectual property to make its COVID vaccine.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Why would the Biden administration, after the federal government has already poured billions of dollars into Moderna for its COVID vaccine, now seek to bail them out for, potentially, billions more? And why did the Biden DOJ wait until February of 2023 to file a statement of interest when the case against Moderna has been in motion since early 2022?</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">And that's where another twist complicates the Biden DOJ's intervention and raises more questions about how the decision to intervene was made.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The U.S. attorney filed the statement of interest on behalf of the Biden DOJ on February 14 and, one day later on February 15, Moderna announced its "commitment to patient access in the United States." The company's announcement states that "Moderna remains committed to ensuring that people in the United States will have access to our COVID-19 vaccines regardless of ability to pay" and Americans who are uninsured or underinsured will still be able to get Moderna's COVID vaccines at pharmacies and doctors' offices at "no cost" to them.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">In 2019, the company's revenue was $60 million. It increased to $803 million in 2020, then surged to more than $18 billion in 2021. It seems as though the federal government has done enough to help Moderna by now, and yet the U.S. government intervened on Moderna's behalf in the patent infringement case to say American taxpayers should assume liability for claims stemming from the company's alleged intellectual property theft.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">So far, the judge hearing claims against Moderna has not sided with the company's &mdash; or the Biden DOJ's &mdash; claims that the federal government (again, read: taxpayers) should be held liable instead, and has ruled against motions to dismiss the case outright.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Next week, Moderna's CEO St&eacute;phane Bancel will testify before the Senate Health, Education, Labor and Pensions (HELP) Committee. That hearing, led by HELP Chairman Bernie Sanders (I-VT), is titled "Taxpayers Paid Billions For It: So Why Would Moderna Consider Quadrupling the Price of the COVID Vaccine?"</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">And finally&hellip;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/restoring-america/community-family/california-pushes-360k-person-reparations-despite-major-deficit"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/restoring-america/community-family/california-pushes-360k-person-reparations-despite-major-deficit</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>California pushes for $360,000 per person in reparations despite major deficit</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The state-endorsed California Reparations Task Force is pushing to give every black resident $360,000 in reparations despite a major budget deficit.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">In 2020, the United States Census Bureau recorded approximately 2.251 million black people residing in California, of whom 1.8 million had at least one ancestor who was a slave, Fox News reported , making the total reparations cost around $640 billion. It is unknown where the state will come up with the funds, however, as Gov. Gavin Newsom (D-CA) reported that California is facing a budget deficit of $22.5 billion for this coming fiscal year.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Chas Alamo, the state's Legislative Analyst's Office's principal fiscal and policy analyst, appeared at the Reparation Task Force's second in-person meeting, in which he proposed further steps that could be taken to fulfill the reparations plan. He proposed several different paths the task force could take to make reparations state law, including the creation of a new agency that would oversee the dispensation of reparations.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">"The creation of a new agency would be initiated through the governor's executive branch and reorganization process, but other options exist," Alamo said, California Black Media reported. "Regardless of the path, to initiate a new agency or enact any other recommendation that makes changes to state law, fundamentally both houses from the state legislature would have to approve the action and the governor will have to sign it."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The task force is due to submit a final report and its accompanying recommendations by July 1. The state legislature, which created the commission amid the fallout from George Floyd's death in 2020, will then vote on the proposal, at which point it will be sent to Newsom to sign.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">So far, neither the panel nor any government agency has suggested how the reparations will be paid for.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Meanwhile, a separate, city-appointed reparations task force in San Francisco recommended giving $5 million in reparations to every black resident, which would total nearly $225 billion.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><br /><br style="font-weight: 400;" /></p>]]></description>
   <author><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></author>
   <enclosure url="https://app.dropwave.io/episode/243e7611-272d-4aea-9796-7187e8b791b2/daily-news-brief-for-friday-march-17th-2023.mp3" length="908" type="audio/mp3"/>
   <guid isPermaLink="false"><![CDATA[243e7611-272d-4aea-9796-7187e8b791b2]]></guid>
   <pubDate>Fri, 17 Mar 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
   <source url=""><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></source>
   <itunes:author><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></itunes:author>
   <itunes:image href="https://assets-cdn2.dropwave.io/2ab40ac0-e99d-4f25-a6d2-541d2c9b290a/cover-art/hUZu1H9lrRY0wXg66WHC8eLwYBA3hbRNTAHQmHt2.png"/>
   <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
   <itunes:duration>908</itunes:duration>
   <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
  
  </item>
 </channel>
</rss>
