<?xml version="1.0"?>
<?xml-stylesheet href="/storage/feed-stylesheet.xsl" type="text/xsl"?>

<rss xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
 <channel>
  <title>FLF - Daily News Brief</title>
  <link>https://dropwave.io</link>
  <description><![CDATA[FIGHT LAUGH FEAST PRESENTS SHOWS PROCLAIMING THE LORDSHIP OF CHRIST OVER ALL OF LIFE.
]]></description>
  <language>en</language>
  <managingEditor><![CDATA[fightlaughfeast@gmail.com (FLF, LLC)]]></managingEditor>
  <webMaster><![CDATA[support@dropwave.io (DropWave Support)]]></webMaster>
  <pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2024 19:25:44 +0000</pubDate>
  <lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2024 19:25:44 +0000</lastBuildDate>
  <image>
   <url>https://is4-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Podcasts113/v4/58/56/52/5856525c-2973-cf29-3db9-21faa8595391/mza_1144696925612154085.png/1200x1200bb.jpg</url>
   <link>https://dropwave.io</link>
   <title><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></title>
  </image>
  <itunes:author><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></itunes:author>
  <itunes:image href="https://is4-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Podcasts113/v4/58/56/52/5856525c-2973-cf29-3db9-21faa8595391/mza_1144696925612154085.png/1200x1200bb.jpg"/>
  <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
  <itunes:owner>
   <itunes:name><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></itunes:name>
   <itunes:email>fightlaughfeast@gmail.com</itunes:email>
  </itunes:owner>
  <itunes:category text="News"/>
  <item>
   <title><![CDATA[Daily News Brief for Wednesday, January 31st, 2024 [Daily News Brief]]]></title>
   <link/>
   <description><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">This is Garrison Hardie with your CrossPolitic Daily News Brief for Wednesday, January 31st, 2024.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>Fight Laugh Feast Magazine</strong></span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Our Fight Laugh Feast Magazine is a quarterly issue that packs a punch like a 21 year Balvenie, no ice. We don&rsquo;t water down our scotch, why would we water down our theology? Order a yearly subscription for yourself and then send a couple yearly subscriptions to your friends who have been drinking luke-warm evangelical cool-aid. Every quarter we promise quality food for the soul, wine for the heart, and some Red Bull for turning over tables. Our magazine will include cultural commentary, a Psalm of the quarter, recipes for feasting, laughter sprinkled through out the glossy pages, and more. Sign up today, at fightlaughfeast.com.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://www.dailywire.com/news/pro-life-demonstrators-found-guilty-face-up-to-11-years-in-federal-prison"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.dailywire.com/news/pro-life-demonstrators-found-guilty-face-up-to-11-years-in-federal-prison</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>Pro-Life Demonstrators Found Guilty, Face Up To 11 Years In Federal Prison</strong></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Six pro-lifers were found guilty on Tuesday after the Biden administration charged them over a peaceful protest at a Tennessee abortion facility in 2021. They face up to 11 years in prison.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The pro-life activists were accused by the Department of Justice of violating the FACE Act and civil rights conspiracy for a protest that took place in a hallway outside of a Mount Juliet abortion provider on March 5, 2021. On that day, a group of demonstrators gathered on the second floor of an office building in the hallway outside the Carafem Health Center Clinic. The group prayed, sang hymns, and urged women showing up to the clinic to not get abortions.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Those on trial included Chet Gallagher of Tennessee, Coleman Boyd of Mississippi, Heather Idoni of Michigan, Cal Zastrow of Michigan, Paul Vaughn of Tennessee, and Dennis Green of Virginia.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">All six defendants were found guilty of both counts. They are expected to be sentenced in July.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The conspiracy charge can be punished with up to 11 years in prison, three years of supervised release, and fines of up to $350,000 while the FACE Act charge can lead to one year in prison and a $10,000 fine.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The verdict was delivered on the fifth day of the trial, which took place at the Fred D. Thompson courthouse in Nashville. The case was overseen by Judge Aleta Trauger, appointed to the court in 1998 by then-President Bill Clinton.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">One of the government&rsquo;s key witnesses was Caroline Davis, a woman who was arrested with the group at Carafem. During her testimony, Davis claimed that she had a change of heart about attending the protest and that her &ldquo;rational side&rdquo; was &ldquo;in the toilet&rdquo; at the time of her participation. She said that she changed her mind &ldquo;over time&rdquo; and that being indicted by the federal government &ldquo;terrified&rdquo; her.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Video of the demonstration showed the group singing songs like &ldquo;Holy, Holy, Holy,&rdquo; and &ldquo;Onward Christian Soldiers,&rdquo; while others showed members of the group talking to police. Another video showed one participant telling another to speak &ldquo;in love&rdquo; to a man with his girlfriend who had shown up at Carafem and that someone&rsquo;s &ldquo;baby is a gift from God.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://www.foxnews.com/politics/texas-governor-abbott-stark-message-sanctuary-cities-migrant-crisis"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.foxnews.com/politics/texas-governor-abbott-stark-message-sanctuary-cities-migrant-crisis</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>Texas Gov. Abbott sends stark message to sanctuary cities as migrant crisis continues</strong></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Republican Texas Gov. Greg Abbott sent a stark message to sanctuary cities on Monday, vowing his state's transportation of migrants to their areas would continue until the federal government takes action on the worsening border crisis.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">"Texas has transported over 102,000 migrants to sanctuary cities. Overwhelmed Texas border towns should not bear the brunt of Biden&rsquo;s open border policies. Our transportation mission will continue until Biden secures the border," Abbott wrote in a post on X.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Abbott's promise comes amid his feud with the Biden administration over enforcement of the border, and whether Texas has the authority to defend itself from the waves of migrants overwhelming law enforcement and immigration officials.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The two sides have been feuding since 2021 when the migrant crisis escalated and Texas launched Operation Lone Star to surge resources to the border.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The administration recently sued over an anti-illegal immigration law that allows state and local law enforcement to arrest illegal immigrants. It has also sued over the state&rsquo;s setting up of buoys in the Rio Grande. The administration says immigration enforcement is up to the federal government and Texas is interfering.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Last week, the Supreme Court ruled in a 5-4 decision on an emergency appeal to temporarily overturn a lower court&rsquo;s injunction that banned the federal government from cutting razor fencing Texas had installed along the border near Eagle Pass while litigation continues.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Following the ruling, Abbott declared his constitutional authority to reserve the right of his state to self-defense against an invasion, adding that the executive branch had broken its constitutional pact with the states by failing to enforce federal immigration laws.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Former President Donald Trump on Thursday gave his backing to Abbott amid the latter&rsquo;s feud with the Biden administration &mdash; urging states to send their National Guards to the border and promising to work "hand in hand" with the state to combat the "invasion" if he is inaugurated again in January 2025.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Abbott has also picked up the support of more than two dozen Republican states who have publicly expressed their support for the state. Meanwhile, some Democrats have urged the Biden administration to seize control of the National Guard.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://www.dailywire.com/news/exclusive-disneyland-posts-woke-wheel-of-privilege-in-employee-kitchen-removes-it-after-daily-wire-inquiry"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.dailywire.com/news/exclusive-disneyland-posts-woke-wheel-of-privilege-in-employee-kitchen-removes-it-after-daily-wire-inquiry</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>Disneyland Posts Woke &lsquo;Wheel Of Privilege&rsquo; In Employee Kitchen, Removes It After Daily Wire Inquiry</strong></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Posters featuring a &ldquo;wheel of power/privilege&rdquo; were hung in employee spaces in Disneyland, instructing employees that being white, &ldquo;cisgender male,&rdquo; and even speaking English means you have &ldquo;unearned&rdquo; privilege that your &ldquo;marginalized&rdquo; coworkers do not, according to images obtained by The Daily Wire.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The wheel featured for all employees to see has the word &ldquo;power&rdquo; in the middle, and is sectioned like a dart board, with certain traits fanning outward that are labeled &ldquo;marginalized.&rdquo; For example, being white, a &ldquo;cisgender male,&rdquo; owning property, and speaking English are all considered privileged, while being dark-skinned, transgender, homeless, and not speaking English are considered marginalized. In between the inner and outer circle &ndash; which would be considered not completely marginalized but not totally privileged either &ndash; are &ldquo;cisgender women,&rdquo; gay men, people with a high school education, and who learned English.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Included with the wheel is a definition of &ldquo;privilege,&rdquo; stating that it is &ldquo;unearned access or advantage granted to specific groups of people because of their membership in a social group.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">&ldquo;Privilege can be based off a variety of different social identities such as race, gender, religion, socioeconomic status, ability status, sexuality, age, education level, and more,&rdquo; it continues. &ldquo;Within the US, members of social groups that hold privileges (white, male, wealthy, able-bodied, etc) have historically held dominance and power over targeted groups.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The poster also asks, &ldquo;why should we accept that we have privileges?&rdquo; It provides the following answer: &ldquo;By accepting that we have privileges, we can see that not everyone sees the world from our perspective and that we have privileges in our life that have hindered our awareness of the world.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The image was provided by source who works for the Walt Disney Company, who wished to remain anonymous for fear of retribution from the company. The employee said the materials were posted in the production kitchen on Main Street USA in Disneyland in Anaheim, California. This production kitchen services Carnation Cafe, The Tropical Hideaway, Jolly Holiday Bakery and Cafe, and Refreshment Corner sponsored by Coca Cola.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The employee said divisive materials like this are &ldquo;destroying the magic&rdquo; of the park.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">&ldquo;So many cast members, myself included, are tired of the division being pushed by companies with a lack of regard for the founder&rsquo;s vision,&rdquo; the source told The Daily Wire. &ldquo;This isn&rsquo;t what Walt would have wanted for his company. He once said, &lsquo;To ALL who come to this happy place, Welcome.&rsquo; Things like this make people feel unwelcome, destroying the magic.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The Daily Wire reached out to the Walt Disney Company to ask about the poster and why they are posted. Within hours of reaching out, our source said a manager removed the poster, and sent a photo of the now-empty display cabinet, which still features another poster about the lunar new year and 2024 being the year of the dragon. Disney did not ultimately respond to the request for comment.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Disney has come under fire in recent years for its turn toward &ldquo;wokeness,&rdquo; with numerous box-office blunders for films deemed to be pushing Leftist political agendas. Top-ranking employees at Disney have also admitted to pushing a &ldquo;not-at-all-secret gay agenda,&rdquo; The Daily Wire previously reported. In 2023, the company lost nearly $1 billion on movies like Elemental and The Little Mermaid.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Company CEO Bob Iger admitted last year that Disney lost sight of entertainment as it put more political messaging into its content.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://www.dailyfetched.com/serbia-to-introduce-a-mandatory-military-draft-amid-ww3-tensions/"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.dailyfetched.com/serbia-to-introduce-a-mandatory-military-draft-amid-ww3-tensions/</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>Serbia to Introduce a Mandatory Military Draft amid WW3 Tensions</strong></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Serbia is reportedly considering reintroducing compulsory military service as tensions in the Balkans and elsewhere in Europe begin increasing amid WW3 fears.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">President Aleksandar Vucic said army commanders gave him &ldquo;a strong argumentation&rdquo; in favor of mandatory draft.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Compulsory drafts here were suspended in 2011 in a push to professionalize the armed forces.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">However, the Serbian president did not specify when the draft would return but said the national parliament would vote on the proposal.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">&ldquo;We are not threatening anyone,&rdquo; Vucic said.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">&ldquo;Today, if you don&rsquo;t have (a strong) army, you don&rsquo;t have a country.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">&ldquo;We will see if it (military service) will last 90 or 100 days, or maybe 110 days,&rdquo; Vucic told reporters.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">&ldquo;As well as when it will be introduced and how the financial and logistical assumptions will be fulfilled.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The Washington Post reported:</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">&ldquo;Opposition politicians and other critics of a draft have questioned the logic of a military buildup when Serbia is almost completely surrounded by NATO member countries which have superior firepower in case of a conflict. There are also concerns that the government may struggle to foot the bill for a larger military.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Tensions have been high in the Balkans, which went through the bloody breakup of the former Yugoslavia in the 1990s. Although formally neutral, the Serbian Army has maintained close ties to Russia, from which it purchases most of its arms, including fighter jets and tanks.&ldquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Serbia was one of the few countries to refuse sanctions against Russia over its invasion of Ukraine.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Tensions revolved around Serbia&rsquo;s former province of Kosovo, which declared independence in 2008, which Serbia and allies Russia and China have not recognized.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Over the last few months, Serbia has raised the combat readiness on the border with Kosovo several times.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The country also maintained cordial relations with NATO, whose troops have been stationed in Kosovo since 1999.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Earlier this week, top military officials warned that conscription could happen in the UK if NATO goes to war with Russia.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">General Sir Patrick Sanders, the outgoing head of the British Army, said such a conflict would need to be a &ldquo;whole-of-nation undertaking.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">&ldquo;Within the next three years, it must be credible to talk of a British Army of 120,000, folding in our reserve and strategic reserve. But this is not enough,&rdquo; he said.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">&ldquo;We will not be immune and as the pre-war generation we must similarly prepare &ndash; and that is a whole-of-nation undertaking,&rdquo; Sanders added.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">&ldquo;Ukraine brutally illustrates that regular armies start wars; citizen armies win them.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">&ldquo;But we&rsquo;ve been here before, and workforce alone does not create capability.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The BBC reports that &ldquo;other senior NATO military commanders have also recently been calling on the alliance to ready itself for a potential conflict.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">According to the outlet:</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">In response to Gen Sir Patrick speech the UK prime minister&rsquo;s spokesman said hypothetical scenarios of a future potential conflict were not helpful and ruled out any move towards a conscription model for the Army.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">One senior Conservative MP told the BBC he did not think Rishi Sunak had fully appreciated the threat posed by Russia.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The MP said that might be because the prime minister when growing up had not experienced the existential threat posed by the old Soviet Union during the Cold War era.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Gen Sir Patrick said the nation could not afford to make the same mistakes of 1914, when it failed to perceive the escalations that led to World War One.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">And that is your news for today&hellip;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Now folks, normally this is the part where I&rsquo;d ask you to send me a news story to my email, or if you have questions about the upcoming FLF conference shoot me an email, etc. But alas, not this time. I&rsquo;ve thoroughly enjoyed bringing you the news over the last year and a half or so. I&rsquo;ve enjoyed giving you a look at what&rsquo;s happening around the world on your morning commute to work&hellip; but I&rsquo;ve received a job offer out of state - down in Huntsville AL, that I just couldn&rsquo;t pass up. If you&rsquo;re down that way, friend me up on Facebook by the way and we&rsquo;ll meet up!&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">With that being said, I wanted to tell you, the listener, how thankful I am for you giving my news show a listen. For saying hello at our FLF Conferences when I was out and about, for sending me news stories to my email, for the encouragement, or constructive criticism I&rsquo;d receive when I couldn&rsquo;t pronounce something&hellip; which believe me, I&rsquo;m aware of those things&hellip; All of that to say. I&rsquo;m thankful for the FLF community</span></p>]]></description>
   <author><![CDATA[Garrison Hardie]]></author>
   <enclosure url="https://app.dropwave.io/episode/21f876d9-0036-4c8d-b3a2-c05120c53681/daily-news-brief-for-wednesday-january-31st-2024.mp3" length="792" type="audio/mp3"/>
   <guid isPermaLink="false"><![CDATA[21f876d9-0036-4c8d-b3a2-c05120c53681]]></guid>
   <pubDate>Wed, 31 Jan 2024 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
   <source url=""><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></source>
   <itunes:author><![CDATA[Garrison Hardie]]></itunes:author>
   <itunes:image href="https://assets-cdn2.dropwave.io/2ab40ac0-e99d-4f25-a6d2-541d2c9b290a/cover-art/mUK8zsnHkCK3vep7E1W6UgYb9dTnLenASAMEFha3.jpg"/>
   <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
   <itunes:duration>792</itunes:duration>
   <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
  
  </item><item>
   <title><![CDATA[Daily News Brief for Friday, January 26th, 2024 [Daily News Brief]]]></title>
   <link/>
   <description><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">This is Garrison Hardie with your CrossPolitic Daily News Brief for Friday, January 26th, 2024.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Dropwave</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Do you have a podcast, or thinking about starting one? Does your church have a podcast feed for sermons? Then Dropwave.io is for you. Cancel culture is like walking on a thin glass bridge over the Grand Canyon. Every step you take could get you killed, I mean canceled. Since the beginning CrossPolitic has been working on being antifragile, so no matter what happens, our content can still be delivered to your tv and to your podcast. The Waterboy and his friend Jeremi, have been working on building a podcast hosting solution for rowdy platforms like CrossPolitic, so that you can be confident your podcast will never fall through that glass bridge. Dropwave offers seamless onboarding for shows that have been around for years to easy to use solutions for starting your own podcast. Dropwave will track all your show&rsquo;s downloads by city, state, and country, and it offers network and enterprise packages for solutions like the Fight Laugh Feast Network. Free to speak, Free to podcast, free to start your journey now at www.Dropwave.io.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://thehill.com/homenews/state-watch/4428905-gop-governors-abbott-border-security-immigration/"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://thehill.com/homenews/state-watch/4428905-gop-governors-abbott-border-security-immigration/</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>GOP governors back Abbott in border standoff</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Republican governors are backing Texas Gov. Greg Abbott (R) in his standoff against the federal government over border authority.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">On Tuesday, the Texas National Guard appeared to ignore a Supreme Court decision and continued building razor wire barriers on the U.S.-Mexico border, preventing the federal Border Patrol from doing their jobs.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">In a statement Wednesday, Abbott justified the actions by claiming his authority to combat an &ldquo;invasion&rdquo; of the state &ldquo;supersedes&rdquo; federal law.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">GOP Govs. Kevin Stitt of Oklahoma, Kristi Noem of South Dakota, Ron DeSantis of Florida, Glenn Youngkin of Virginia and Brian Kemp of Georgia have all said they support Abbott&rsquo;s actions.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&ldquo;If the Constitution really made states powerless to defend themselves against an invasion, it wouldn&rsquo;t have been ratified in the first place and Texas would have never joined the union when it did,&rdquo; DeSantis said on X, formerly Twitter. &ldquo;TX is upholding the law while Biden is flouting it.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Youngkin added that the Biden administration &ldquo;has turned every state into a border state,&rdquo; and that Abbott is doing what the border officials &ldquo;refuse to do to secure our border.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Stitt, Noem and Kemp also said their states &ldquo;stand with&rdquo; Texas.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The federal government has claimed in court filings that the Texas National Guard has physically prevented the Border Patrol from doing its job on certain parts of the Rio Grande, as well as blocked off portions of the border previously used to process migrants.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The claim that Texas officials can supersede federal authority has sparked calls from Democrats for President Biden to nationalize the Texas National Guard and force them to follow the court&rsquo;s decision and federal law.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Democratic Texas Reps. Joaquin Castro and Greg Casar have advocated for nationalizing the state guard.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Abbott&rsquo;s statement Wednesday specifically claims the federal government has &ldquo;broken the compact&rdquo; with the states, justifying ignoring federal law and the Supreme Court.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The so-called &ldquo;compact theory&rdquo; is a rejected idea of state supremacy used to justify the secession of Confederate states during the Civil War. The Supreme Court repeatedly shot down the legal theory in the early years of the U.S., when it was first proposed to nullify federal legislation during former President John Adams&rsquo;s time in office.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://www.foxnews.com/politics/gop-ags-battle-blue-state-push-to-shutter-largest-ammo-manufacturer-to-punish-second-amendment-rights"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.foxnews.com/politics/gop-ags-battle-blue-state-push-to-shutter-largest-ammo-manufacturer-to-punish-second-amendment-rights</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>GOP AGs take aim at Dem plea for Biden to shut down critical ammo manufacturer</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Every republican attorney general in the country blasted their Democrat counterparts for attempting to shutter an ammunition factory in Missouri, a letter sent to the White House Wednesday revealed.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">In a letter obtained exclusively by Fox News Digital, all 28 GOP attorneys general asked President Biden and White House Office of Gun Violence Prevention director Stefanie Feldman to disregard their Democrat colleagues' request to end commercial sales from Lake City Army Ammunition Plant, one of the country&rsquo;s largest ammo manufacturers.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Democrats had previously asked the administration to investigate the contracting and manufacturing practices of the plant after a New York Times report alleged that "military-grade rounds" were sold commercially and were connected to mass shootings.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">But the Republicans say the Democrats&rsquo; letter contained a "litany of errors." "Perhaps those States should focus more on prosecuting crime to stop mass shootings&mdash;rather than trying to stop lawful Americans&rsquo; use of guns and ammunition. Their tactic is an overt attempt to punish Americans&rsquo; exercise of their Second Amendment rights,</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Among the list of "errors" the GOP AGs point out that their Democrat colleages allege that ammunition manufactured for "military use" does not belong in communities.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">"First, the ammunition manufactured at Lake City and sold into the commercial market is not the primary rifle cartridge used by the United States military. The primary cartridge is proprietary to the Army and may not be sold commercially," the AGs note.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">"Second, while the United States military purchases and uses a particular type of ammunition, that is not determinative as to whether it is "military ammunition" that should be banned for public use," they write.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">"If the United States military using ammunition precluded that ammunition&rsquo;s use by civilians, then other widely and commonly available ammunition, including 9mm and 12-gauge shotshells, would also be prohibited for public use," they argued, adding that Supreme Court precedent "does not support such an openly artificial distinction."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">According to the state&rsquo;s top prosecutors, Lake City only sells ammunition to commercial customers that is legal to manufacture, and it complies with all the Bureau of Alcohol, Tobacco, Firearms and Explosives&rsquo; (ATF) requirements.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The AGs argued that the Democrats&rsquo; efforts would undermine national security. "Gun control advocates are firing blanks when they contend that taxpayers are subsidizing mass shooters. They get causality backward. The law-abiding target shooters and gun owners who buy Lake City ammunition are subsidizing national defense and military readiness," they argue.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">They note that the Defense Department "sought to avoid a situation when the military needs surge due to a real-world conflict, ammunition is not readily available," adding that ammunition availability requires facilities, production equipment, a skilled workforce, and supply chains to remain in constant operation.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">"Machines and production cannot be turned on like the flip of a switch. It takes time to hire and train the highly skilled workers needed to operate production lines to manufacture the highest quality ammunition for U.S. warfighters. Commercial production has allowed Lake City, and its suppliers, to maintain steady labor, maximize equipment run time, ensure a stable supply base, and provide a level of readiness to the U.S. military that would not otherwise be available," they added.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The attorneys general also said that Lake City cannot halt commercial use without a "detrimental loss" to their communities and economy. If it stopped, the AGs allege it would result in an estimated loss of 500&ndash;700 jobs or 30%&ndash;45% of the skilled workforce now employed at Lake City and "countless more" throughout the supply chain.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Montana Attorney General Austen Knudsen in a statement to Fox News Digital called the investigation by the New York Times "highly questionable" and, their latest effort to shut down the Lake City Army Ammunition Plant is based on a highly questionable &lsquo;investigation' by the New York Times."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Iowa Attorney General Brenna Bird charged that "if the Biden Administration and anti-gun activists were serious about saving lives, they would start by enforcing the laws on the books to combat violent criminals."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Missouri Attorney General Andrew Bailey echoed those sentiments, adding that "Lake City Ammunition did nothing wrong."&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">"We should be focused on the free flow of illegal weapons coming across our border &ndash; not taking aim at law-abiding patriots," Indiana Attorney General Todd Rokita said, adding that the border crisis "is exactly why law-abiding citizens need the liberty to defend themselves."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://thefederalist.com/2024/01/24/canadian-court-rules-trudeaus-unreasonable-crackdown-on-trucker-convoy-violated-federal-law/"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://thefederalist.com/2024/01/24/canadian-court-rules-trudeaus-unreasonable-crackdown-on-trucker-convoy-violated-federal-law/</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Canadian Court Rules Trudeau&rsquo;s &lsquo;Unreasonable&rsquo; Crackdown On Trucker Convoy Violated Federal Law</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">A Canadian court ruled Tuesday that Prime Minister Justin Trudeau&rsquo;s use of a controversial federal law in early 2022 to target truckers protesting their industry&rsquo;s Covid vaccine mandate was &ldquo;unreasonable&rdquo; and illegal.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The use of the Emergencies Act &ldquo;does not bear the hallmarks of reasonableness &mdash; justification, transparency and intelligibility,&rdquo; Federal Court Justice Richard Mosley wrote. &ldquo;I conclude that there was no national emergency justifying the invocation of the Emergencies Act and the decision to do so was therefore unreasonable and ultra vires.&rdquo; As the Canadian Broadcasting Corporation (CBC) explained, &ldquo;ultra vires&rdquo; is a term courts use &ldquo;to refer to actions beyond the scope of the law.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">In early 2022, Trudeau&rsquo;s government implemented a series of Covid shot mandates for various sectors of Canadian society, including a requirement for truckers crossing the U.S.-Canada border. The tyrannical mandate ultimately prompted Canadian truckers to launch the &ldquo;Freedom Convoy,&rdquo; a massive protest comprised of vehicles that ended outside Parliament Hill in the nation&rsquo;s capital.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">While peaceful, the protests evoked the ire of Trudeau, who used the Emergencies Act to mobilize the Canadian military and state intel agencies to forcibly remove the demonstrators gridlocking Ottawa. In addition to backing GoFundMe&rsquo;s attempts to deplatform fundraising efforts for the convoy, Trudeau&rsquo;s administration also expanded &ldquo;its terrorist financing rules to target crowdfunding sites like the convoy&rsquo;s new platform GiveSendGo,&rdquo; The Federalist&rsquo;s Jordan Boyd wrote, with Deputy Prime Minister and Finance Minister Chrystia Freeland baselessly claiming the platforms were &ldquo;being used to support illegal blockades and illegal activity which is damaging the Canadian economy.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">As if his abuse of the Emergencies Act weren&rsquo;t despicable enough, Trudeau &mdash; who went into hiding upon the convoy&rsquo;s arrival in Ottawa &mdash; also grossly smeared the protesters with the typical diatribe of leftist slanders, including accusations of &ldquo;antisemitism, Islamophobia, anti-Black racism, homophobia, and transphobia.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Despite his best attempt to play the role of a dictator, Trudeau&rsquo;s use of the Emergencies Act went beyond the scope of what is permitted by Canadian law. While the Emergencies Act can be employed to manage a national emergency that &ldquo;cannot be effectively dealt with under any other law of Canada,&rdquo; Mosley determined that Trudeau&rsquo;s actions far exceeded that threshold.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&ldquo;The potential for serious violence, or being unable to say that there was no potential for serious violence was, of course, a valid reason for concern,&rdquo; Mosley wrote. &ldquo;But in my view, it did not satisfy the test required to invoke the Act, particularly as there was no evidence of a similar &lsquo;hardened cell&rsquo; elsewhere in the country, only speculation, and the situation at Cou[r]ts had been resolved without violence.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Mosley further ruled that the government&rsquo;s financial crackdown violated demonstrators&rsquo; Charter rights &ldquo;by permitting unreasonable search and seizure of the financial information of designated persons and the freezing of their bank and credit card accounts.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Unsurprisingly, the Canadian government plans to appeal the ruling, with Freeland laughably claiming on Tuesday that the administration&rsquo;s unlawful actions were &ldquo;necessary&rdquo; and &ldquo;legal&rdquo; because Canadian &ldquo;national security was under real threat.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://justthenews.com/politics-policy/energy/taxpayers-could-get-stuck-cost-removing-offshore-wind-farm-after-biden-admin"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://justthenews.com/politics-policy/energy/taxpayers-could-get-stuck-cost-removing-offshore-wind-farm-after-biden-admin</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Taxpayers may get stuck with cost of removing an offshore wind farm after Biden admin waives fees</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The Biden administration reportedly waived fees for an offshore wind project that are in place to ensure that the infrastructure is removed and the site reclaimed at the end of the project&rsquo;s life.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">President Joe Biden, as part of his climate agenda, is pushing an aggressive buildout of offshore wind projects along the East Coast. With the offshore wind industry struggling financially, the waiving of these fees raises concerns about what would happen if these companies go bankrupt and leave behind wind farms they can&rsquo;t afford to remove.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Protect The Public Trust (PPT), a government watchdog group, obtained documents showing that the Bureau of Ocean Energy Management (BOEM) informed Vineyard Wind had approved the company&rsquo;s request to waive fees for financial assurances that goes toward decommissioning costs.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The bureau&rsquo;s reasoning for granting the deferral, according to PPT, was that the financial assurance was &ldquo;unnecessarily burdensome for lessees because, at that point, they have not begun receiving project income.&rdquo; Since the project is using &ldquo;proven wind turbine technology&rdquo; and its contracts guaranteed electricity sale prices, BOEM reasoned, the project had a predictable income over the life of the project.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The Department of Interior requires these bonds from oil and gas producers, as taxpayers have been stuck decommissioning the projects of companies that go bankrupt or were operating prior to bonding requirements.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">California, for example, is trying to decommission 23 federal offshore platforms at a cost of $1.7 billion, and the liability for those costs remain unresolved. There are also thousands of onshore orphaned wells across the country that the federal government is trying to plug. In some cases, these wells were drilled a century or more ago before bonding requirements, and there&rsquo;s no solvent owner of record to hold accountable for the costs.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">In Wyoming, an industry sprang up a decade ago hoping to tap coal beds for natural gas, but after natural gas prices collapsed, the entire industry collapsed with it. The state was left with a lot of wells to plug and no companies to hold accountable.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">While the Biden administration is granting waivers for these protections to offshore wind projects, it&rsquo;s proposing steep increases in bonding requirements for oil and gas operations. While that proposal is met with support from environmentalists, industry groups have criticized the measure.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Kathleen Sgamma, president of the Western Energy Alliance, told Reuters in July that rather than trying to ensure funding for reclamation efforts, the administration was raising the costs so high as a means to reduce the number of operations.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Elmer Peter Danenberger III, a petroleum engineer with decades of experience in the oil and gas industry, explained on his &ldquo;Bud&rsquo;s Offshore Energy&rdquo; blog that BOEM&rsquo;s decision to waive Vineyard Wind&rsquo;s obligations significantly increases the public&rsquo;s risk exposure. Danenberger wrote that BOEM, in granting the waiver, cited a general departure authority, which was intended for special situations and not for waivers that could be applied broadly.</span></p>]]></description>
   <author><![CDATA[Garrison Hardie]]></author>
   <enclosure url="https://app.dropwave.io/episode/fac42fd9-aa67-4a71-b75d-72cc7051b4e3/daily-news-brief-for-friday-january-26th-2024.mp3" length="854" type="audio/mp3"/>
   <guid isPermaLink="false"><![CDATA[fac42fd9-aa67-4a71-b75d-72cc7051b4e3]]></guid>
   <pubDate>Fri, 26 Jan 2024 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
   <source url=""><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></source>
   <itunes:author><![CDATA[Garrison Hardie]]></itunes:author>
   <itunes:image href="https://assets-cdn2.dropwave.io/2ab40ac0-e99d-4f25-a6d2-541d2c9b290a/cover-art/mUK8zsnHkCK3vep7E1W6UgYb9dTnLenASAMEFha3.jpg"/>
   <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
   <itunes:duration>854</itunes:duration>
   <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
  
  </item><item>
   <title><![CDATA[Daily News Brief for Thursday, January 25th, 2024 [Daily News Brief]]]></title>
   <link/>
   <description><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">This is Garrison Hardie with your CrossPolitic Daily News Brief for Thursday, January 25th, 2024.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Fight Laugh Feast Magazine</strong></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Our Fight Laugh Feast Magazine is a quarterly issue that packs a punch like a 21 year Balvenie, no ice. We don&rsquo;t water down our scotch, why would we water down our theology? Order a yearly subscription for yourself and then send a couple yearly subscriptions to your friends who have been drinking luke-warm evangelical cool-aid. Every quarter we promise quality food for the soul, wine for the heart, and some Red Bull for turning over tables. Our magazine will include cultural commentary, a Psalm of the quarter, recipes for feasting, laughter sprinkled through out the glossy pages, and more. Sign up today, at fightlaughfeast.com.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://www.breitbart.com/2024-election/2024/01/24/calls-grow-louder-for-haley-to-drop-out-of-gop-primary/"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.breitbart.com/2024-election/2024/01/24/calls-grow-louder-for-haley-to-drop-out-of-gop-primary/</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Calls Grow Louder for Haley to Drop Out of GOP Primary</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Demands grew louder for former Gov. Nikki Haley to drop out of the GOP primary race on Tuesday after placing second in New Hampshire to former President Donald Trump.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Many Republicans believe Haley should leave the race so all available GOP resources can be allocated towards defeating President Joe Biden. Republicans spent over $167 million in losing efforts to defeat Trump in New Hampshire and Iowa, with plans to release millions more in future primaries.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://twitter.com/i/status/1750015374639390818"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://twitter.com/i/status/1750015374639390818</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> - Play Video</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">After Gov. Ron DeSantis (R) exited the race Sunday, Haley&rsquo;s path to the nomination did not appear to improve. In fact, Gov. Ron DeSantis&rsquo; endorsement of Trump further consolidated support behind the former president, placing pressure on Haley to also end her fledgling campaign. In all states besides New Hampshire, Trump leads by no less than 30 points.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Sen. Tom Cotton (R-AR) said Trump is the de facto GOP nominee moving forward. &ldquo;Congratulations to President Trump on another decisive win in New Hampshire and becoming the presumptive nominee of our party,&rdquo; he said.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Gov. Kristi Noem (R-SD) congratulated Trump on his big win Tuesday evening: &ldquo;To no one&rsquo;s surprise, @realDonaldTrump won BIG tonight in New Hampshire. President Trump&rsquo;s message is resonating with voters. It&rsquo;s only a matter of time until 45 becomes 47. Congratulations, Mr. President!&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">CEO of the Federalist Sean Davis urged Haley to drop out, noting that if she did not, she would be &ldquo;fully owned by the left-wing Democrats.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&ldquo;If Nikki Haley&rsquo;s primary goal is to defeat Joe Biden in November, she will drop out tonight and endorse Trump. If she continues to stay in a race she cannot win just to attack Trump, then we&rsquo;ll know she&rsquo;s fully owned by the left-wing Democrats who are funding her campaign,&rdquo; he said.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&nbsp;Social media influencer Ryan Fournier demanded Haley just give up and drop out. &ldquo;Nikki Haley is refusing to drop out, claiming &ldquo;this race is far from over.&rdquo; It&rsquo;s been over from the start. You all betted on the worst happening to Trump to secure victory. It&rsquo;s time to give it up.,&rdquo; he said.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&nbsp;Nate Cohn, the New York Times&rsquo; chief political analyst, wrote on Monday the polling undoubtedly shows Haley&rsquo;s inevitable resignation from the race, so Trump can turn his focus to defeating President Joe Biden. &ldquo;So, without a monumental shift in the race, he will secure the nomination in short order,&rdquo; he said.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&ldquo;Too little, too late,&rdquo; Haley backer and a former chairman of the New Hampshire Republican Party, Fergus Cullen, told the New York Times about Haley&rsquo;s prospects. &ldquo;She had to inspire and engage unaffiliated voters, and I just haven&rsquo;t seen her doing what she needs to do to reach that audience and turn them out in the numbers that she needs.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/policy/immigration/2814985/biden-administration-demands-texas-grant-dhs-access-border/"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/policy/immigration/2814985/biden-administration-demands-texas-grant-dhs-access-border/</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Biden administration demands Texas grant border access following Supreme Court decision</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The Biden administration has demanded the state of Texas relinquish control of a 2.5-mile strip of land on the border and grant federal agents access following a Supreme Court decision that gave Border Patrol agents to slash state-installed razor wire.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The Department of Homeland Security sent Attorney General Ken Paxton (R-TX) a letter Tuesday obtained first by the Washington Examiner in which General Counsel Jonathan Meyer called out the state for its inaction after the highest court rescinded an appeal court injunction and allowed federal police to cut down razor wire fencing in Eagle Pass in order to rescue and apprehend illegal immigrants as they cross the Rio Grande.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&ldquo;The state has alleged that Shelby Park is open to the public, but we do not believe this statement is accurate,&rdquo; Meyer said. &ldquo;To our knowledge, Texas has only permitted access to Shelby Park by allowing public entry for a memorial, the media, and use of the golf course adjacent to Shelby Park, all while continuing to restrict U.S. Border Patrol&rsquo;s access to the park.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Meyer said the Supreme Court decision allowed federal law enforcement not only to cut wire at the border but to be present on the border, the latter of which has not been possible since the Texas National Guard commandeered the 2.5-mile strip of city land and locked out all federal employees on Jan. 10.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&ldquo;As you are aware, yesterday, the Supreme Court vacated the injunction prohibiting the Department from cutting or moving the concertina wire that Texas had placed along the border except in case of emergency, and restored the Department&rsquo;s right to cut and move the concertina wire placed by Texas in order to perform their statutory duties,&rdquo; Meyer wrote. &ldquo;The Department must also have the ability to access the border in the Shelby Park area that is currently obstructed by Texas.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">But despite the court&rsquo;s decision, Texas National Guard soldiers reaffirmed the state&rsquo;s position Tuesday. Soldiers in Eagle Pass installed more razor wire at the river and laid out more fencing and concertina wire despite the rain that swept through the region Tuesday, according to video.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The DHS maintained in its letter that it had the upper ground in terms of legal ground that allowed its personnel to be on city land along the border. It cited the U.S. Code, in which the department acquired permanent real estate interests in and around Eagle Pass in 2008 to build border wall barriers in the vicinity.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&ldquo;Because the Department owns property rights to the areas depicted on the attached map, we demand that you immediately remove any and all obstructions on it,&rdquo; Meyer said.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Border Patrol still has limited access to a boat ramp within Shelby Park despite the state&rsquo;s initial concession earlier in the land seizure to let agents load and unload a boat into the river. Meyer called for full access to the boat ramp and river.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The Biden administration had threatened Gov. Greg Abbott (R-TX) with legal action on Jan. 14 if Texas did not relinquish control of land, but has not followed up with a lawsuit.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&ldquo;We demand that Texas cease and desist its efforts to block Border Patrol&rsquo;s access in and around the Shelby Park area and remove all barriers to access in the Shelby Park area,&rdquo; Meyer told Paxton in the letter.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The showdown between state and federal leaders comes 12 days after three immigrants drowned attempting to wade across the river from Mexico on Jan. 12. Border Patrol officials in Eagle Pass were alerted to immigrants who had drowned and two others in distress and attempted to respond but were denied access at a gate into the state-seized land.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The state has taken issue with Border Patrol cutting its wire on the basis that the wire would deter and prevent more illegal immigration. Federal law enforcement agents are required to arrest anyone who has illegally entered the country or is illegally present, including those who cross the river and are blocked from continuing up the riverbank by the razor wire.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://www.newsmax.com/world/globaltalk/holocaust-survivors-numbers-report-claims-conference/2024/01/23/id/1150570/"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.newsmax.com/world/globaltalk/holocaust-survivors-numbers-report-claims-conference/2024/01/23/id/1150570/</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Almost 80 Years after the Holocaust, 245,000 Jewish Survivors Are Still Alive</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Almost 80 years after the Holocaust, about 245,000 Jewish survivors are still living across more than 90 countries, a new report revealed Tuesday.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Nearly half of them, or 49%, are living in Israel; 18% are in Western Europe, 16% in the United States, and 12% in countries of the former Soviet Union, according to a study by the New York-based Conference on Jewish Material Claims Against Germany, also referred to as the Claims Conference.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Before the publication of the demographic report, there were only vague estimates about how many Holocaust survivors are still alive.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Their numbers are quickly dwindling, as most are very old and often of frail health, with a median age of 86. Twenty percent of survivors are older than 90, and more women (61%) than men (39%) are still alive.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The vast majority, or 96% of survivors, are &ldquo;child survivors&rdquo; who were born after 1928, says the report &ldquo;Holocaust Survivors Worldwide. A Demographic Overview'&rdquo; which is based on figures that were collected up until August.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&ldquo;The numbers in this report are interesting, but it is also important to look past the numbers to see the individuals they represent,&rdquo; said Greg Schneider, the Claims Conference&rsquo;s executive vice president.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&ldquo;These are Jews who were born into a world that wanted to see them murdered. They endured the atrocities of the Holocaust in their youth and were forced to rebuild an entire life out of the ashes of the camps and ghettos that ended their families and communities."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Six million European Jews and people from other minorities were killed by the Nazis and their collaborators during the Holocaust.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">It is not clear exactly how many Jews survived the death camps, the ghettos or somewhere in hiding across Nazi-occupied Europe, but their numbers were a far cry from the pre-war Jewish population in Europe.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">In Poland, of the 3.3 million Jews living there in 1939, only about 300,000 survived.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Around 560,000 Jews lived in Germany in 1933, the year Adolf Hitler came to power. At the end of World War II in 1945, their numbers had diminished to about 15,000 &mdash; through emigration and extermination.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Germany's Jewish community grew again after 1990, when more than 215,000 Jewish migrants and their families came from countries of the former Soviet Union, some of them also survivors.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Nowadays, only 14,200 survivors still live in Germany, the demographic report concluded.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">For its new report, the Claims Conference said it defined Holocaust survivors "based on agreements with the German government in assessing eligibility for compensation programs.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">For Germany, that definition includes all Jews who lived in the country from Jan. 30, 1933, when Hitler came to power, to May 1945, when Germany surrendered unconditionally in World War II.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The group handles claims on behalf of Jews who suffered under the Nazis and negotiates compensation with Germany's finance ministry every year. In June, the Claims Conference said that Germany has agreed to extend another $1.4 billion, (1.29 billion euros), overall for Holocaust survivors around the globe for 2024.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Since 1952, the German government has paid more than $90 billion to individuals for suffering and losses resulting from persecution by the Nazis.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://www.foxbusiness.com/politics/nyc-mayor-eric-adams-announces-2-billion-medical-debt-bailout-500000-residents"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.foxbusiness.com/politics/nyc-mayor-eric-adams-announces-2-billion-medical-debt-bailout-500000-residents</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>NYC Mayor Eric Adams announces $2B medical debt bailout for up to 500K residents</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">New York City Mayor Eric Adams announced on Monday a plan to buy up millions of dollars in medical debt owed by hundreds of thousands of New Yorkers.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">In what the mayor said would be a "one-time" deal, the city will spend $18 million in taxpayer funds over the next three years to pay off medical debt owed by up to 500,000 residents. Officials estimate that the program will wipe out over $2 billion of medical debt owed in what they call the "largest municipal initiative of its kind in the country."&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">"Getting health care shouldn't be a burden that weighs on New Yorkers and their families," Adams said in a statement. "Since day one, our administration has been driven by the clear mission of supporting working-class New Yorkers and today's investment that will provide $2 billion in medical debt relief is another major step in delivering on that vision. Up to half a million New Yorkers will see their medical debt wiped thanks to this life changing program &mdash; the largest municipal initiative of its kind in the country."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Medical debt is among the top causes of bankruptcy in the United States, especially for those who lack health insurance. Nearly 1 in 10 U.S. adults (9%), or roughly 23 million people, owe medical debt, according to the Kaiser Family Foundation. The collective medical debt owed by Americans nationwide is estimated by the group to be as much as $195 billion.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">New York City will partner with RIP Medical Debt, a New York-based nonprofit, to acquire debt portfolios and retiree debt from health care providers and hospitals and erase it, officials said.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">"No one chooses to go into medical debt &mdash; if you're sick or injured, you need to seek care. But no New Yorker should have to choose between paying rent or for other essentials and paying off their medical debt, which is why we are proud to bring this relief to families across the five boroughs, as we continue to fight on behalf of working-class New Yorkers," Adams said.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Founded in 2014, RIP Medical Debt uses donations to buy debt from health care providers in bundles at a steep discount. The group uses data analytics to identify debtors who are most in need &mdash; households that earn less than four times the federal poverty level or whose debts are 5% or more of annual income &mdash; and buys their debt. Those who benefit from the organization's work receive letters in the mail announcing that their debt has been erased, tax and penalty-free.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The group has partnered with local governments before, including with Cook County in Illinois to abolish more than $280 million in medical debt owed by residents, but never at the scale of its partnership with New York City.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">To supplement the city's spending on the program, RIP Medical Debt and the Mayor's Fund to Advance New York City are soliciting private donations to raise additional funding over the next three years.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://www.worldofreel.com/blog/2024/1/22/ngsegtq5k078chahr8s3etgus3983p"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.worldofreel.com/blog/2024/1/22/ngsegtq5k078chahr8s3etgus3983p</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>New &lsquo;Jurassic World&rsquo; Movie in the Works, 2025 Release Being Eyed</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">A new &ldquo;Jurassic World&rdquo; movie is in the works. In fact, it&rsquo;s so deep in development that Universal is eyeing a 2025 release date for this one. If that&rsquo;s the case then it wouldn&rsquo;t come as much of a surprise if it goes into production this year.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The good news is that &ldquo;Jurassic Park&rdquo; screenwriter David Koepp is back, his last script for the series was 1997&rsquo;s &ldquo;The Lost World.&rdquo; Koepp is set write the script to introduce a &ldquo;new Jurassic era,&rdquo; which likely means Chris Pratt won&rsquo;t be returning as the lead.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">It&rsquo;s only been two years since the last one, 2022&rsquo;s &ldquo;Jurassic World Dominion&rdquo;, but Universal&rsquo;s clearly looking to make more of these films. No director is attached for now, but, the way things are speeding up, one will surely be hired soon.</span></p>]]></description>
   <author><![CDATA[Garrison Hardie]]></author>
   <enclosure url="https://app.dropwave.io/episode/e4937212-1cd5-4cee-b1e4-8ad4f32d9ee3/daily-news-brief-for-thursday-january-25th-2024.mp3" length="927" type="audio/mp3"/>
   <guid isPermaLink="false"><![CDATA[e4937212-1cd5-4cee-b1e4-8ad4f32d9ee3]]></guid>
   <pubDate>Thu, 25 Jan 2024 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
   <source url=""><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></source>
   <itunes:author><![CDATA[Garrison Hardie]]></itunes:author>
   <itunes:image href="https://assets-cdn2.dropwave.io/2ab40ac0-e99d-4f25-a6d2-541d2c9b290a/cover-art/mUK8zsnHkCK3vep7E1W6UgYb9dTnLenASAMEFha3.jpg"/>
   <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
   <itunes:duration>927</itunes:duration>
   <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
  
  </item>
 </channel>
</rss>
