<?xml version="1.0"?>
<?xml-stylesheet href="/storage/feed-stylesheet.xsl" type="text/xsl"?>

<rss xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
 <channel>
  <title>FLF - Daily News Brief</title>
  <link>https://dropwave.io</link>
  <description><![CDATA[FIGHT LAUGH FEAST PRESENTS SHOWS PROCLAIMING THE LORDSHIP OF CHRIST OVER ALL OF LIFE.
]]></description>
  <language>en</language>
  <managingEditor><![CDATA[fightlaughfeast@gmail.com (FLF, LLC)]]></managingEditor>
  <webMaster><![CDATA[support@dropwave.io (DropWave Support)]]></webMaster>
  <pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 01:25:44 +0000</pubDate>
  <lastBuildDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 01:25:44 +0000</lastBuildDate>
  <image>
   <url>https://is4-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Podcasts113/v4/58/56/52/5856525c-2973-cf29-3db9-21faa8595391/mza_1144696925612154085.png/1200x1200bb.jpg</url>
   <link>https://dropwave.io</link>
   <title><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></title>
  </image>
  <itunes:author><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></itunes:author>
  <itunes:image href="https://is4-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Podcasts113/v4/58/56/52/5856525c-2973-cf29-3db9-21faa8595391/mza_1144696925612154085.png/1200x1200bb.jpg"/>
  <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
  <itunes:owner>
   <itunes:name><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></itunes:name>
   <itunes:email>fightlaughfeast@gmail.com</itunes:email>
  </itunes:owner>
  <itunes:category text="News"/>
  <item>
   <title><![CDATA[Daily News Brief for Wednesday, November 1st, 2023 [Daily News Brief]]]></title>
   <link/>
   <description><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">This is Garrison Hardie with your CrossPolitic Daily News Brief for Wednesday, November 1st, 2023.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Samaritan Ministries:</strong></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">How are you planning to pay your medical bills in 2024? Before answering that question, here</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">are three reasons you should look into health care sharing with Samaritan Ministries.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">One, there are no networks which means you choose the doctors and hospitals you go to, and</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">have a say in the treatments you receive. Two, you&rsquo;re part of a Christian community. When you have a medical need, fellow members send money directly to you to help you pay your shareable medical bills. And you&rsquo;ll do the same for them, all while praying for and encouraging one another. Three, it could be more affordable than what you&rsquo;re paying now. For more reasons to join the Samaritan community, visit samaritan ministries dot org slash cross politic.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://justthenews.com/accountability/political-ethics/step-aside-hillary-joe-biden-may-become-king-email-scandals-new"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://justthenews.com/accountability/political-ethics/step-aside-hillary-joe-biden-may-become-king-email-scandals-new</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Step aside Hillary, Joe Biden may become king of email scandals as new stash alarms investigators</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The National Archives&rsquo; stunning admission that it has located 82,000 pages of potentially government-related emails from Joe Biden&rsquo;s private accounts not only threatens to supplant Hillary Clinton in the annals of email scandals, it could also provide a boon to the ongoing federal and congressional investigations into the Biden family.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The admission came out Monday as part of a Freedom of Information Act (FOIA) lawsuit brought by the non-profit Southeastern Legal Foundation.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&ldquo;We're duty bound to make sure that everybody's following the law here. And it sure looks like that's questionable at this moment,&rdquo; Rep. Scott Perry, R-Pa., a member of the House Oversight Committee that is conducting the Biden impeachment inquiry right now, said hours after the revelation.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Perry told the John Solomon Reports podcast that lawmakers in Congress must take action to ensure all the emails are preserved given the history of Hillary Clinton&rsquo;s team trying to delete her private emails or to destroy the devices they were stored on.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Sen. Ron Johnson, R-Wis., who first raised questions about President Biden&rsquo;s use of private email years ago, said the discovery of the emails should be combed for potential evidence by every investigator from Congress to the Justice Department.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Under legal pressure, the National Archives has confirmed to a court that it has located 82,000 pages of emails that Biden sent or received during his vice presidential tenure on three private pseudonym accounts. It&rsquo;s a total that potentially dwarfs the amount that landed Hillary Clinton in hot water a decade ago.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The total of Biden private email exchanges was disclosed Monday in a little-noticed status report filed in a Freedom of Information Act lawsuit brought against the National Archives and Records Administration by the nonprofit public interest law firm the Southeastern Legal Foundation.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The foundation brought the lawsuit seeking access to the emails after Just the News revealed a year ago that Joe Biden had used three pseudonym email accounts &ndash; during the time he served as President Barack Obama&rsquo;s vice president.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The status report filed Monday in a federal court in Atlanta was the first to provide an estimate of the size and scope of possible government business conducted through Joe Biden&rsquo;s private email accounts.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">To date, there is no indication from the National Archives in the court case that any of Biden&rsquo;s email contain classified information. However, the president is under criminal investigation by Special Counsel Robert Hur for taking classified documents from his time as vice president and as a senator and storing them in insecure locations in the garage of his Delaware home and a think tank office he kept in Washington D.C.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Hur recently spent two days interview Biden in that investigation. President Donald Trump has already been indicted by Special Counsel Jack Smith for mishandling classified documents the FBI recovered from his Mar-a-Lago estate in Florida or that Trump returned to the Archives belatedly.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Perry said he will be inquiring whether the FBI or DOJ has ever reviewed the Biden email stash located by the National Archives for relevant criminal investigations involving Hunter Biden or Biden&rsquo;s handling of classified information and whether prosecutors ever considered charges for possible violations of the Federal Records Act.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">You can read the full letter here in my show notes&hellip;&nbsp;</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">File</span></p>
<p><a href="https://justthenews.com/sites/default/files/2023-08/NARA%20-%20special%20access%20request%20%281%29.pdf"><span style="font-weight: 400;">NARA - special access request (1).pdf</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://www.theepochtimes.com/us/federal-agency-makes-new-student-loan-proposal-months-after-supreme-court-order-5520324?utm_source=partner&amp;utm_campaign=BonginoReport"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.theepochtimes.com/us/federal-agency-makes-new-student-loan-proposal-months-after-supreme-court-order-5520324?utm_source=partner&amp;utm_campaign=BonginoReport</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Federal Agency Makes New Student Loan Proposal Months After Supreme Court Order</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The Biden administration appeared to make major changes to its new student loan relief plan after the initial plan was struck down by the U.S. Supreme Court earlier this year.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">On Monday, the Department of Education (DOE) released a draft text that showed that the narrower plan would allow student debt forgiveness to apply only to specific groups of students rather than being a blanket rule that would cancel debt for some 45 million borrowers under the original plan.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The first student loan proposal, announced by President Joe Biden, would have promised up to $20,000 in debt relief for low- and middle-income individuals. The Supreme Court struck that down in June.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The DOE has yet to release the full details of the plan, saying that it wants to cancel some or all student debt for borrowers whose balances exceed what they originally owed; those who have loans that entered repayment 25 or more years ago; those who used loans to attend career-training programs that led to &ldquo;unreasonable&rdquo; debt loads or insufficient earnings; or those who are eligible for other loan forgiveness programs but did not apply.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">A fifth group is also being discussed, or &ldquo;those who are experiencing financial hardship that the current student loan system does not currently adequately address,&rdquo; the DOE said.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The draft does not include details about how many borrowers would be impacted by the federal government's latest plan. It also did not include details about how much it may cost.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The DOE stated it will continue to refine the proposal as it goes through a federal rulemaking process. The public will be able to provide written feedback next year. The draft proposal would give the department authority to wipe away federal student loans entirely for borrowers in some categories.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The Biden administration has canceled more than $120 billion in federal student loan debt via existing student loan forgiveness programs for specific individuals.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Previously, the president called for a plan to help &ldquo;as many borrowers as possible,&rdquo; but his administration seems to be moving away from the type of mass cancellation that he promised in August 2022. That plan was estimated to cost $400 billion. It&rsquo;s unclear how much the second proposal will cost.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://www.dailyfetched.com/experts-claim-not-reading-mainstream-media-can-cause-heart-attacks/"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.dailyfetched.com/experts-claim-not-reading-mainstream-media-can-cause-heart-attacks/</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>&lsquo;Experts&rsquo; Claim Not Reading Mainstream Media Can Cause Heart Attacks</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Not Reading mainstream media and opting for alternative sources can cause heart attacks, according to new research reported by the mainstream media.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Yes, really.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">According to a pilot study led by Manchester Metropolitan University, those who do not read legacy mainstream media and opt for alternative sources of information demonstrate unhealthy symptoms of physical and mental stress, which can lead to heart attacks.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The research study used so-called &ldquo;sophisticated techniques&rdquo; to monitor how people use media websites to measure their reactions to online information.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The researchers claimed people with a low ID have a flawed &lsquo;threat&rsquo; response when presented with misleading information in a stressful situation, which they say brings on cardiac responses and erratic reading behavior.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The study also found that participants with low IDs also lacked self-confidence.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">It also claimed that reading alternative media from &ldquo;unverified&rdquo; sources (i.e., not reading CNN, MSNBC, BBC, ect) could negatively affect a person&rsquo;s health and well-being.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Senior Lecturer in Information and Communications at Manchester Metropolitan University and principal investigator on the study, Dr Geoff Walton, said:</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&ldquo;Those who aren&rsquo;t very good at making judgments about information they read or see in newspapers, TV, or social media, especially misinformation such as fake news, experience a negative physical response to it. This means that misinformation is actually bad for their physical health.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&ldquo;On the other hand, those people that are very good at making judgments about information tend to have a much healthier physical response when they encounter misinformation,&rdquo; he said.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://youtu.be/wDYNVH0U3cs"><span style="font-weight: 400;" data-rich-links="{&quot;fple-t&quot;:&quot;Woman screams as Donald Trump is sworn in as President&quot;,&quot;fple-u&quot;:&quot;https://youtu.be/wDYNVH0U3cs&quot;,&quot;fple-mt&quot;:null,&quot;type&quot;:&quot;first-party-link&quot;}">Woman screams as Donald Trump is sworn in as President</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;">- Play 0:00-0:10 - That was an example of the healthy response they may exhibit.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&ldquo;Given the constant barrage of fake news that we come across every day of our lives, it clearly shows there is a worrying public health issue emerging.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&ldquo;However, our previous research has shown that we can change this through teaching and training so that people get better at making judgments about misinformation such as fake news.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&ldquo;By doing so, they will have a much better physical response, which will positively affect their well-being.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&ldquo;This shows it is now time for school teachers and lecturers to be given the right tools, devised in our previous research, to develop ID in their learners.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The results will be presented at the European Conference on Information Literacy (ECIL) later this year. A peer-reviewed journal article is in preparation, and a larger study is planned.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Similarly, a WHO study from 2022 claimed reading so-called &ldquo;misinformation&rdquo; can have a negative effect on health.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The official website of the WHO reported:</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Incorrect interpretations of health information, which increase during outbreaks and disasters, often negatively impact people&rsquo;s mental health and increase vaccine hesitancy, and can delay the provision of health care, a new WHO review shows.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The authors conclude that the effects of infodemics and health misinformation online can be countered by &ldquo;developing legal policies, creating and promoting awareness campaigns, improving health-related content in mass media and increasing people&rsquo;s digital and health literacy&rdquo;.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The systematic review of published studies found 31 reviews that analysed fake news, misinformation, disinformation and infodemics related to health.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Misinformation was defined as false or inaccurate information deliberately intended to deceive, while disinformation also included misleading or biased information, manipulated narratives or facts, and propaganda.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The authors gathered, compared, and summarized this evidence in order to identify ways to address the negative effects of false health information on public health.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&ldquo;Twitter, Facebook, YouTube, and Instagram are critical in disseminating the rapid and far-reaching spread of information,&rdquo; the systematic review explains.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The repercussions of misinformation on social media include such negative effects as &ldquo;an increase in erroneous interpretation of scientific knowledge, opinion polarization, escalating fear and panic or decreased access to health care&rdquo;.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The increased spread of health-related misinformation in a health emergency is accelerated by easy access to online content, especially on smartphones.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&ldquo;During crises such as infectious disease outbreaks and disasters, the overproduction of data from multiple sources, the quality of the information and the speed at which new information is disseminated create social and health-related impacts.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The authors found that social media have been propagating poor-quality health-related information during pandemics, humanitarian crises, and health emergencies at an increasing rate. They note, &ldquo;Such spreading of unreliable evidence on health topics amplifies vaccine hesitancy and promotes unproven treatments.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">All the more reason not to read mainstream media.</span></p>]]></description>
   <author><![CDATA[Garrison Hardie]]></author>
   <enclosure url="https://app.dropwave.io/episode/85b5c869-26ec-4795-ad1a-36d8e2071fdc/daily-news-brief-for-wednesday-november-1st-2023-1.mp3" length="722" type="audio/mp3"/>
   <guid isPermaLink="false"><![CDATA[85b5c869-26ec-4795-ad1a-36d8e2071fdc]]></guid>
   <pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
   <source url=""><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></source>
   <itunes:author><![CDATA[Garrison Hardie]]></itunes:author>
   <itunes:image href="https://assets-cdn2.dropwave.io/2ab40ac0-e99d-4f25-a6d2-541d2c9b290a/cover-art/mUK8zsnHkCK3vep7E1W6UgYb9dTnLenASAMEFha3.jpg"/>
   <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
   <itunes:duration>722</itunes:duration>
   <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
  
  </item><item>
   <title><![CDATA[Daily News Brief for Tuesday, October 31st, 2023 [Daily News Brief]]]></title>
   <link/>
   <description><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">This is Garrison Hardie with your CrossPolitic Daily News Brief for Tuesday, October 31st, 2023.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Happy reformation day everyone!&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Pub Membership Plug</strong></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Elevate your cultural and political conversations with CrossPolitic's Pub Memberships! Join our passionate community of thinkers, debaters, and action-takers. Gain exclusive access to premium content, live events, and engaging discussions on faith, politics, and culture. Become a CrossPolitic Pub Member today! For more information, head on over to fightlaughfeast.com to join our rowdy pub - that&rsquo;s fightlaughfeast.com</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">We start off with world news today&hellip;&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/policy/defense-national-security/iran-proxies-strikes-against-us-troops-middle-east-israel"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/policy/defense-national-security/iran-proxies-strikes-against-us-troops-middle-east-israel</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Iranian proxies continue attacks against US troops in Middle East following US strikes</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Iranian proxy forces have continued conducting attacks against U.S. troops in Syria and Iraq following last week's U.S. strikes against two facilities linked to Iranian forces in Syria.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">From Oct. 17 to Oct. 30, U.S. and coalition forces have been attacked at least 14 times at al Asad Air Base in Iraq and nine times at al Tanf garrison in Syria via a mix of one-way attack drones and rockets for a total of 23 attacks to date, a senior defense official told reporters on Monday. The total demonstrated an increase from late last week.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">"Many of these attacks were successfully disrupted by our military," the official said. "Most failed to reach their targets thanks to our robust defenses."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The U.S. military in eastern Syria targeted two facilities used by Iran&rsquo;s Islamic Revolutionary Guard Corps last Thursday.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&ldquo;The President has no higher priority than the safety of U.S. personnel, and he directed today&rsquo;s action to make clear that the United States will not tolerate such attacks and will defend itself, its personnel, and its interests,&rdquo; Secretary of Defense Lloyd Austin said in a statement.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">One of the facilities the U.S. targeted was a "weapons storage area," while the other was "an ammunition storage area," according to a senior military official.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Twenty-one U.S. service members were injured, albeit not severely, at the two air bases between Oct. 17 and Oct. 18. A U.S. contractor died after suffering cardiac arrest when an early warning system detected another possible threat, leading to people scrambling for shelter.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">U.S. leaders, President Joe Biden included, have urged Iran not to escalate or involve itself with Israel's war with Hamas. Hamas, which is a U.S.-designated Iran-supported terrorist organization based in Gaza, carried out an unprecedented terrorist attack on Oct. 7 that killed roughly 1,400 people, the vast majority of whom were civilians. The carnage included families being butchered, civilians burned alive, torture, sexual violence, and more.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Iran has forcefully spoken out against Israel's military response in Gaza, threatening to get involved in the conflict.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The Iranian Foreign Minister spoke in New York at the United Nations last week, where he warned the U.S. of "uncontrollable consequences" regarding its support for Israel.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Biden has reinforced the country's presence in the Middle East to attempt to deter Iranian aggression, though the continued attacks indicate that their bolstered presence may not be having the impact the president had hoped.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://redstate.com/nick-arama/2023/10/29/lynch-mob-storms-airport-in-russia-searching-for-jews-reportedly-arriving-from-tel-aviv-n2165671"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://redstate.com/nick-arama/2023/10/29/lynch-mob-storms-airport-in-russia-searching-for-jews-reportedly-arriving-from-tel-aviv-n2165671</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>'Lynch Mob' Storms Airport in Russia Searching for Jews Arriving From Tel Aviv</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">There is some scary news coming out of Dagestan, Russia, right now.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">There was what reports have described as a "lynch mob" storming the airport in Dagestan and chanting "Allahu Akbar," waving Palestinian flags and looking for Jews who they believed had arrived on a plane from Tel Aviv, Israel. Dagestan is a Muslim area.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">There were also reports that the mob stopped police cars in front searching for Jews, as well as a bus full of children that they assumed were Israeli children. In videos shared on X, you can see them storm the terminal, and even make their way out onto the Tar-Mac, and demanded to know if any Jews were on planes on the Tar-Mac.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The airport employee in the vest and green hat says there are no passengers on that plane.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The mob started grilling people as to whether they were Jews and asking for passports. A&nbsp; poor gentleman in one of the videos insisted he wasn't Jewish&mdash;that he was Uzbek&mdash;but they didn't believe him and demanded that he show his passport.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">They were also allegedly looking for Jews in the cars around the airport and this footage allegedly shows them trying to flip a police car that dared to get in their way:</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">According to Ria Novosti, the Ministry of Internal Affairs is warning the mob they are on video, that order will be established and they will be identified and "face criminal liability."&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The Jerusalem Post said that the plane they were looking for was diverted to another airport, but the rioters went there as well.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">According to N12, the pilots were warned of the mob and rerouted the plane to land at a nearby airport. The rioters reached that one as well. The flight staff ordered the locking of all aircraft exits, while security forces closed the area off. Russian aviation authority said all aircraft were diverted to other airports. A security source said that a small number of Israelis and Jews were secured in the airport, and were set to be evacuated to Moscow "at the earliest convenience."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">This is happening as antisemitism is on the rise in Russia, as evidenced by a Jewish cultural center that was set on fire in the neighboring republic of Nalchik and graffitied with the inscription "Death to the Jews."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://www.breitbart.com/europe/2023/10/29/czech-defence-minister-calls-for-country-to-leave-u-n-for-cheering-hamas-terrorists/"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.breitbart.com/europe/2023/10/29/czech-defence-minister-calls-for-country-to-leave-u-n-for-cheering-hamas-terrorists/</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Czech Defence Minister Calls for Country to Leave U.N. for &lsquo;Cheering&rsquo; Hamas Terrorists</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Czech Defence Minister Jana Černochov&aacute; has called for her country to leave the United Nations in response to the international body&rsquo;s failure to condemn Hamas terrorists for the slaughter of civilians in Israel on the October 7th attacks.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">This week, the United Nations General Assembly overwhelmingly voted to demand a &ldquo;ceasefire&rdquo; between Israel and Hamas as Jerusalem was preparing for its invasion of Gaza to root out the Islamist terror organisation.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Just 14 nations opposed the measure, including Austria, Croatia, the Czech Republic, Fiji, Guatemala, Hungary, Israel, the Marshall Islands, Micronesia, Nauru, Papua New Guinea, Paraguay, Tonga and the United States.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Meanwhile, multiple attempts from the United States and others to pass a resolution to condemn the Hamas attacks were thwarted at the U.N. by China and Russia, who used their veto power as permanent members of the Security Council to block the condemnation of the terrorist group.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Responding to the apparent anti-Israel bias at the U.N. on Saturday, Czech Defence Minister Jana Černochov&aacute; said: &ldquo;In my opinion, the Czech Republic has no place in an organisation that cheers on terrorists and does not respect the fundamental right to self-defence,&rdquo; declaring: &ldquo;Let&rsquo;s get out.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&ldquo;Exactly three weeks ago, Hamas murdered over 1,400 Israelis, more victims for their population than the militant Islamist organisation al-Qaeda murdered in the US on 9/11. And only 14 countries, including ours, have spoken out clearly and understandably against this unprecedented terrorist attack perpetrated by Hamas terrorists! I am ashamed of the U.N.,&rdquo; Černochov&aacute; continued.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The Czech Defence Minister doubled down on her condemnations of the United Nations on Sunday, writing that the presence of hostile nations such as Iran and Russia, as well as states which violate human rights such as Afghanistan, North Korea and Syria, undermines the U.N. charter and therefore the very purpose of the institution itself. With China and Russia having a veto over expelling any nation from the international body, the process is meaningless, Černochov&aacute; argued.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&ldquo;What is the use of an organisation that cannot use even the few principles and possibilities it has and cannot apply them without the consent of the dictators?&rdquo; she questioned.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The conservative politician said that if the U.N. is incapable of making reforms to be able to condemn terrorists or expel rogue nations &ldquo;it has lost its role as a peacemaker&rdquo;. Therefore, she said, the world needs &ldquo;a new international organisation&rdquo; based upon on &ldquo;modern principles&rdquo; such as the elimination of veto powers granted to dictatorships and the end of &ldquo;sponsoring terrorists.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The Czech defence chief concluded by saying that she had &ldquo;often wondered&rdquo; about how the world refused to believe the horrors committed in concentration camps by Nazi Germany during World War II but said that perhaps &ldquo;it wasn&rsquo;t the case at all,&rdquo; saying that rather than refusing to believe the atrocities &ldquo;a part of society apparently wanted to get rid of the Jews.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&ldquo;Anti-Semitism has spread deeply throughout the world, including the United Nations. They trust terrorists, but they don&rsquo;t trust the country that has been protecting our Western civilisation&rsquo;s ass for many years in the Middle East. Absurd world,&rdquo; Černochov&aacute; said.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&ldquo;It is completely incomprehensible to me that no one is calling for a fundamental reform of the organisation, which long ago turned from a peacemaker into a hammer against Israel.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://www.theepochtimes.com/us/californias-gun-ban-allowed-to-continue-by-appeals-court-5518977?utm_source=partner&amp;utm_campaign=BonginoReport"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.theepochtimes.com/us/californias-gun-ban-allowed-to-continue-by-appeals-court-5518977?utm_source=partner&amp;utm_campaign=BonginoReport</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>California&rsquo;s Gun Ban Allowed to Continue by Appeals Court</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">A U.S. appeals court has allowed California&rsquo;s ban on certain types of semi-automatic rifles, so-called assault weapons, to remain in effect, reversing an earlier lower court decision to stay the law.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Semi-automatic rifles have been restricted in the state since 1989, with the law updated multiple times to keep the ban in effect. On Oct. 19, U.S. District Judge Roger Benitez in San Diego ruled that the ban was a violation of Second Amendment rights and issued an injunction that blocked its enforcement in the state.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">An appeal against the ruling was filed by California Attorney General Rob Bonta.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">On Oct. 28, a panel of three judges from the 9th U.S. Circuit Court of Appeals blocked the injunction issued by Judge Benitez, thereby allowing the weapon ban to take effect in the state.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">By a 2&ndash;1 majority, the 9th Circuit panel stayed the judge's order, citing the full appeals court's finding in a similar case that the attorney general was likely to succeed on the merits and had shown that &ldquo;California would be irreparably harmed absent a stay.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Mr. Bonta, a Democrat who called Judge Benitez's decision &ldquo;dangerous and misguided,&rdquo; welcomed the Oct. 28 9th Circuit order.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&ldquo;Weapons of war do not belong on our streets,&rdquo; Mr. Bonta said, pointing to the mass shooting on Oct. 25&nbsp; in Lewiston, Maine, that claimed 18 lives and left 13 people wounded.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">In 1989, California became the first U.S. state to ban semi-automatic rifles, acting in the wake of a school shooting that killed five children, then toughened the law the following year.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Since then, California has restricted the manufacture, distribution, transportation, importation, sale, or possession of firearms that qualify under the law as &ldquo;assault weapons.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Judge Benitez declared the same law unconstitutional in 2021. But the San Francisco-based 9th U.S. Circuit last year vacated his order and directed him to review the matter further.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Judge Benitez, in September, also ruled California's ban on high-capacity ammunition magazines unconstitutional. But the 9th Circuit subsequently allowed that statute to remain in effect while the state appeals.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">In a post on Facebook, nonprofit civil rights advocate Firearms Policy Coalition (FPC) stated that even though the 9th Circuit has &ldquo;temporarily blocked our District Court victory, [the] good news is that the State&rsquo;s appeal has been expedited and it is likely that the merits panel, which hears the appeal, will be made up of different judges.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&ldquo;Once all briefs are filed, it is possible that the merits panel may order additional oral arguments,&rdquo; the group stated in the post.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">In the Oct. 19 ruling, Judge Benitez wrote that the U.S. Constitution made it clear that Americans have the right to decide what firearms they use for self-defense.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">He pointed out that the banned rifles use the same ammunition, perform the same functions, and fire at the same rate as rifles that haven't been prohibited. The legislators selected which firearms to ban based on how the guns looked, he wrote.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&ldquo;Falling back on an old, recycled justification, the State says that its ban should stand because a person can have as many other rifles, shotguns, and pistols as one wants,&rdquo; Judge Benitez wrote in the ruling. "[However,] this is not the way American Constitutional rights work. It is not permissible for a state to ban some books simply because there are other books to read.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&ldquo;In their normal configurations, the so-called &lsquo;assault weapons&rsquo; ... are modern firearms commonly owned by law-abiding citizens for lawful purposes across the nation.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">California Gov. Gavin Newsom, a Democrat, had criticized Judge Benitez&rsquo;s ruling, insisting that the judge is &ldquo;hellbent on making it more dangerous for our kids to go to school, for families to go to the mall, or to attend a place of worship,&rdquo; according to an Oct. 19 statement.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The 9th Circuit&rsquo;s ruling to allow California&rsquo;s weapon ban to remain in effect comes as the Biden administration is pushing for stronger gun control regulations.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Following the mass shooting in Maine that killed 18 people, President Biden said in an Oct. 26 statement that while his administration has &ldquo;made progress on gun safety,&rdquo; such measures are &ldquo;simply not enough.&rdquo;</span></p>]]></description>
   <author><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></author>
   <enclosure url="https://app.dropwave.io/episode/9305416d-34f4-4171-bce6-d5b89b379d20/daily-news-brief-for-tuesday-october-31st-2023.mp3" length="803" type="audio/mp3"/>
   <guid isPermaLink="false"><![CDATA[9305416d-34f4-4171-bce6-d5b89b379d20]]></guid>
   <pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
   <source url=""><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></source>
   <itunes:author><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></itunes:author>
   <itunes:image href="https://assets-cdn2.dropwave.io/2ab40ac0-e99d-4f25-a6d2-541d2c9b290a/cover-art/mUK8zsnHkCK3vep7E1W6UgYb9dTnLenASAMEFha3.jpg"/>
   <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
   <itunes:duration>803</itunes:duration>
   <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
  
  </item><item>
   <title><![CDATA[Daily News Brief for Friday, October 27th, 2023 [Daily News Brief]]]></title>
   <link/>
   <description><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">This is Garrison Hardie with your CrossPolitic Daily News Brief for Friday, October 27th, 2023.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Classical Conversations</strong></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Classical Conversations supports homeschooling parents by cultivating the love of learning through a Christian worldview in fellowship with other families. They provide a classical Christ-centered curriculum, local like-minded communities across the United States and in several countries, and they train parents who are striving to be great classical&nbsp; educators in the home. For more information and to get connected, please visit their website at ClassicalConversations.com. </span><span style="font-weight: 400;">Again that&rsquo;s </span><span style="font-weight: 400;">ClassicalConversations.com.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">We start today&rsquo;s show with tragic news coming out of Lewiston Maine, as a gun man shot and killed at least 18 people, and wounded 13 more&hellip;&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://www.foxnews.com/live-news/lewiston-maine-mass-shooting-october-26"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.foxnews.com/live-news/lewiston-maine-mass-shooting-october-26</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Maine State Police have released a detailed timeline of the mass shooting in Lewiston that killed at least 18 people and injured 13 more at two separate locations Wednesday night as the manhunt for suspect Robert Card intensified across the state.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">At 6:56 p.m., the Auburn Communications Center was alerted that an unidentified man walked into Just-In-Time Bowling, which was recently renamed from Sparetime Recreation, on Mollison Street in Lewiston and began shooting. Police said multiple 911 calls that followed confirmed the shooting.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">At 7:08 p.m., the Auburn Communications Center received multiple calls that a man had entered a Bar and Grille Restaurant on Lincoln Street and opened fire.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Police said multiple law enforcement agencies and emergency medical personnel were immediately dispatched to the locations, which are about 4 miles apart.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">At 8:06 pm, police released a photo of the alleged shooter to the media. The surveillance photo showed a man wearing a brown sweatshirt and holding a rifle while walking through doors decorated with bowling pins and a bowling ball.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">At 9:26 p.m., the Lewiston Police Department received a call identifying the man in the distributed photos as Robert Card, 40, of Bowdoin, Maine.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">At 9:56 p.m., the Lisbon Police Department notified Lewiston Police that it had located a white Subaru at the at a Boat Launch in Lisbon. The vehicle was confirmed to belong to Card.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Card remains at large as more than 350 law enforcement personnel from federal, state and local agencies continue to search for him. Authorities stress that Card should be considered armed and dangerous.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Card is a "trained firearms instructor" who recently reported mental health issues,including "hearing voices and threats to shoot up the National Guard Base in Saco, ME," according to a Maine law enforcement bulletin shared with Fox News Digital.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Card is also a Petroleum Supply Specialist in the Army Reserve, having enlisted in December 2002, an Army spokesperson told Fox News, adding that Card has had no combat deployments.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Officials have yet to publicly name any of the 18 victims, and police said Thursday morning 10 of the victims killed have yet to be identified.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Police have confirmed that seven people &mdash; one female and six males &mdash; were killed at the bowling alley, which was holding a youth league at the time of the shooting. Eight males were killed at the Bar and Grille. Three additional people died after first responders rushed them to Central Maine Medical Hospital in Lewiston.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">An additional 13 people were injured in the shootings.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">At least 80 FBI agents are involved in the search for Robert Card, in addition to agents from the Bureau of Alcohol, Tobacco, Firearms and Explosives, Drug Enforcement Administration, and Coast Guard, according to Sen. Susan Collins, R-Maine.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Collins made the comments during a press conference on Thursday evening.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">"I had a call from the deputy director of the FBI who told me that there were 80 FBI agents on site participating in the search for the killer," Collins said.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">State and local law enforcement agencies are also searching for Card.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Before we move on, I want to ask that you be praying for the community of Lewiston Maine today&hellip; pray that the Lord would be near the broken hearted as is promised in His word&hellip; that He would bind up their wounds, and grant comfort and peace to those who are grieving the loss of loved ones. Be praying that the Lord would be with local leaders in Maine, both political and law enforcement&hellip; and that justice would be served on the one responsible for this heinous crime, and tragic loss of life.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://justthenews.com/government/congress/johnson-begins-house-speakership-focus-debt-inflation-and-border-catastrophe"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://justthenews.com/government/congress/johnson-begins-house-speakership-focus-debt-inflation-and-border-catastrophe</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Johnson begins House speakership with focus on debt, inflation, &lsquo;border catastrophe&rsquo; as top issues</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Rep. Mike Johnson, R-La., the newly elected Speaker of the House of Representatives kicked off his leadership role on Wednesday with a commitment to establish a fiscal commission dedicated to rolling back excessive government spending as a way to reduce inflation. He also called on the Senate and White House to stop ignoring the &ldquo;catastrophe&rdquo; at the southern border.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Johnson described the nation&rsquo;s rising $33 trillion national debt as the greatest threat to national security and connected it to the level of inflation that America&rsquo;s families have been grappling with the last few years.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://youtu.be/qKrtMtZFeP0"><span style="font-weight: 400;" data-rich-links="{&quot;fple-t&quot;:&quot;JUST IN: Mike Johnson Delivers First Remarks As Speaker Of The House&quot;,&quot;fple-u&quot;:&quot;https://youtu.be/qKrtMtZFeP0&quot;,&quot;fple-mt&quot;:null,&quot;type&quot;:&quot;first-party-link&quot;}">JUST IN: Mike Johnson Delivers First Remarks As Speaker Of The House</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"><br /><br /></span></p>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Play 11:36-16:09</span></li>
</ul>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Just a note, not a lot of clapping from democrats on that last part.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://www.19fortyfive.com/2023/10/u-s-aircraft-carriers-and-marines-are-on-the-move-towards-irans-military-backyard/"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.19fortyfive.com/2023/10/u-s-aircraft-carriers-and-marines-are-on-the-move-towards-irans-military-backyard/</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>U.S. Aircraft Carriers And Marines Are On The Move Towards Iran&rsquo;s &lsquo;Military Backyard&rsquo;</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The situation in Israel continues to be tense as the Israeli Defense Forces are on standby to launch a large-scale ground invasion of Gaza. As of now, Tel Aviv has agreed to hold off invading until the U.S. military puts more forces in the area.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The Israeli Air Force is pounding hundreds of targets within Gaza, killing and wounding hundreds of Hamas terrorists and Palestinian civilians.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">On the other end, Hamas continues to be defiant, launching missiles and small-scale attacks against Israel. The terrorist group also holds scores of hostages and is threatening to execute them if Israel invades.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">According to the German newspaper Bild, the Israelis won&rsquo;t hold back a possible ground invasion of Gaza over the issue of the hostages. Hamas is currently holding over 200 hostages and has been using them as deterrence against an Israeli ground invasion.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">But with more than 1,400 Israelis killed and thousands more wounded, the Israeli government might very likely choose to go in and destroy Hamas despite what might happen to the hostages.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The Israeli Army is likely waiting for the air force to take out the most important targets before it rolls in with tanks and armored personnel carriers.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Meanwhile, two more hostages were released this week as two elderly women, were released on Wednesday.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">One of the women said, &ldquo;When we arrived in Gaza, they first told us that they believed in the Quran and would not harm us, they fed us well, were kind, a doctor and paramedic visited us regularly, everything was provided for us.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">But their experience leading up to their captivity in Gaza was traumatic. Hostages were beaten and humiliated as they were snatched from their homes in Israel to Gaza&rsquo;s underground tunnel complex.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Meanwhile, the international military presence around Israel continues to grow.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">European countries are getting ready for forceful evacuations of their citizens from Israel and Lebanon. German and French special operations forces have set up camp in Cyprus and are on standby for contingencies.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The U.S. military has already sent two aircraft carrier strike groups in the region and the 26th Marine Expeditionary Unit (MEU), which is special operations capable. The Pentagon has also relocated a number of C-130 tactical transport aircraft and support personnel to Greece to be on standby for potential evacuation operations.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Thus far, Israel has been adamant that it doesn&rsquo;t want any direct military assistance or foreign boots on the ground. However, Tel Aviv was allowed a number of U.S. military advisors to support the Israeli Defense Forces. According to Axios, U.S. Marine Corps Lt. Gen. James Glynn, a former commander of the Marine Forces Special Operations Command and with experience against the Islamic State, is leading the advisory group.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The increased presence of U.S. forces in the region is also in response to credible threats about U.S. citizens and facilities in the region.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">According to U.S. defense officials, the Pentagon assesses that state and non-state actors in the region&mdash;mainly Iran&mdash;are considering escalating the ongoing hostilities between Israel and Hamas into a wider regional conflict.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The U.S. military is ready to counter any hostile actions in the area. Whether Iran understands the danger is another thing.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Now in entertainment news&hellip;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://www.hollywoodintoto.com/jenna-fischer-angela-kinsey-office-reboot-update/"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.hollywoodintoto.com/jenna-fischer-angela-kinsey-office-reboot-update/</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>&lsquo;Office&rsquo; Alums Jenna Fischer, Angela Kinsey: No News on a Reboot (Yet)</strong></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&ldquo;The Office&rdquo; is one of the most streamed sitcoms around.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The show, spun from the British version created by Ricky Gervais and Stephen Merchant, aired on NBC for nine seasons. The workplace comedy nearly got canceled after its first year, but it found its creative footing and became a modern TV classic.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The show said goodbye in 2013, with cast members like Steve Carell and John Krasinski drawing raves for follow-up projects like &ldquo;Foxcatcher&rdquo; and &ldquo;A Quiet Place,&rdquo; respectively.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Now, Puck News reports show runner Greg Daniels is prepping an &ldquo;Office&rdquo; reboot. That&rsquo;s news to show alums Jenna Fischer and Angela Kinsey, AKA the hosts of the popular &ldquo;Office Ladies&rdquo; podcast.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The two discussed a possible show return via their podcast, throwing some cold water on the possibility.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&ldquo;We get asked all the time, there are always these rumors of another American version [of &lsquo;The Office&rsquo;],&rdquo; Fischer said in the latest episode of &ldquo;Office Ladies.&rdquo; &ldquo;Like a reboot or a remake or a spinoff.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&ldquo;No one has ever in all of these years &hellip; contacted me about being on another version of &lsquo;The Office.&rsquo; Or any cast member,&rdquo; said Fischer, who played receptionist Pam Beesly on the series. &ldquo;Whenever I talk to the cast members., &lsquo;never heard of anything. Not a word.'&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&ldquo;Do we need a 50-year-old Pam sitting at a desk at Dunder Mifflin?&rdquo;&nbsp; referring to turning that age next year. One cast member should definitely be invited back, she suggested.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&ldquo;I like the idea that Creed still works there .. he comes down from the ceiling at night,&rdquo; Fischer said of the mercurial character played by ex-rocker Creed Bratton.</span></p>]]></description>
   <author><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></author>
   <enclosure url="https://app.dropwave.io/episode/602eceff-321b-4410-89a6-8c88fb59ab52/daily-news-brief-for-friday-october-27th-2023.mp3" length="867" type="audio/mp3"/>
   <guid isPermaLink="false"><![CDATA[602eceff-321b-4410-89a6-8c88fb59ab52]]></guid>
   <pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
   <source url=""><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></source>
   <itunes:author><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></itunes:author>
   <itunes:image href="https://assets-cdn2.dropwave.io/2ab40ac0-e99d-4f25-a6d2-541d2c9b290a/cover-art/mUK8zsnHkCK3vep7E1W6UgYb9dTnLenASAMEFha3.jpg"/>
   <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
   <itunes:duration>867</itunes:duration>
   <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
  
  </item><item>
   <title><![CDATA[Daily News Brief for Thursday, October 26th, 2023 [Daily News Brief]]]></title>
   <link/>
   <description><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">This is Garrison Hardie with your CrossPolitic Daily News Brief for Thursday, October 26th, 2023.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Alps Precious Metals:</strong></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">IN GENESIS CHAPTER 2, VERSES 10 THROUGH 12, GOD TELLS OF THE GOLD IN THE LAND OF HAVILAH, AND THAT THE GOLD OF THAT LAND IS GOOD.&nbsp; EVER SINCE THE DAWN OF OUR FATHER&rsquo;S WORLD, GOLD HAS BEEN UNIVERSALLY RECOGNIZED AS TRUE MONEY AND, THEREFORE, THE MOST RELIABLE STORE OF SAVINGS.&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">CROSS POLITIC&rsquo;S CORPORATE PARTNER, ALPS PRECIOUS METALS, ENABLES THEIR CLIENTS TO PROTECT THEIR GOD-GIVEN, HARD-EARNED WEALTH FROM THE SERIOUS FINANCIAL PROBLEMS THAT ARE UPON US.&nbsp; ALPS PROVIDES THE CROSSPOLITIC FAMILY WITH THE BEST STRATEGIES AND SOLUTIONS FOR INVESTING IN PHYSICAL PRECIOUS METALS.&nbsp; AS A RESULT, YOU CAN ENJOY A PEACE OF MIND THAT CAN BE HAD WITH FEW OTHER INVESTMENTS.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">CALL JAMES HUNTER OF ALPS AT 251-377-2197, AND VISIT OUR WEBSITE AT WWW.ALPSPMG.COM&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://www.foxnews.com/live-news/speaker-of-the-house-race-october-25"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.foxnews.com/live-news/speaker-of-the-house-race-october-25</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Johnson secures speaker's gavel as Republicans rally behind nominee</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Rep. Mike Johnson was elected by the House to become the next speaker as Republicans rallied behind their fourth nominee to replace former Speaker Kevin McCarthy.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Johnson could afford only a handful of defections from his fellow Republicans in the chamber-wide vote, but unlike prior candidates, there were no defections to his candidacy from his party.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">He won 220 votes, needing around 217 to become speaker.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Democrats meanwhile continued to vote for Minority Leader Hakeem Jeffries. He picked up 209 votes from his fellow Democrats.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Johnson scored his party's nomination late Tuesday, with several members absent and three voting present. In just the hours from Tuesday, though, Johnson has shored up support from the three Republicans who voted present in Tuesday's late nomination vote.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Johnson also got support from President Trump, who gave his support for the GOP nominee, urging Republicans to "get it done, fast" ahead of a potential House speaker vote.</span></p>
<p><strong>DNC says House GOP will 'have to answer' for electing 'MAGA' Mike Johnson as speaker</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The Democratic National Committee (DNC) took aim at newly-elected House Speaker Mike Johnson, R-La., Wednesday just before he won a House-wide vote to replace former Speaker Kevin McCarthy, R-Calif., saying Republicans would "have to answer" to voters in 2024 for supporting him.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&ldquo;Many Americans are waking up this morning wondering &mdash; who is Mike Johnson? We&rsquo;re here to help: MAGA Republicans&rsquo; new speaker-designate supports extreme nationwide abortion bans," DNC National Press Secretary Sarafina Chitika said in a statement.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">"He led the charge for Donald Trump denying President Biden&rsquo;s legitimate election win and tried to overthrow the votes of 81 million Americans. He&rsquo;s a leading proponent of slashing Social Security and Medicare," she said.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Chitika called Johnson a "carbon-copy" of "MAGA extremism," and predicted House Republicans would have to answer for supporting him when voters head to the polls in 2024.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">"Make no mistake: The American people will hold them accountable for this choice," she added.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Republicans celebrate newly minted House Speaker Mike Johnson's gavel ascension</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Republicans celebrated the election of House Speaker Mike Johnson, R-La., after he ascended to the gavel on Wednesday.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Johnson was elected speaker via a vote of 220-209, taking over the gavel from Speaker pro-tempore Patrick McHenry, R-N.C.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Republicans were ecstatic about the election of Johnson, with House Majority Whip Tom Emmer &mdash; who secured the GOP's speaker nomination on Tuesday before bowing out &mdash; writing his congratulations to the new speaker.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">"Congratulations to my friend and colleague, [Johnson], on being elected Speaker of the House!" Emmer posted.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">"His strong convictions and commitment to conservatism will serve this body and the American people well," Emmer added.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Rep. Byron Donalds, R-Fla., who also ran for House speaker, wrote "servant leadership," with a picture of the new speaker's nameplate</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">"God bless America," Donalds wrote.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://www.foxnews.com/politics/new-report-unmasks-true-costs-electric-vehicle-mandates-remain-expensive"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.foxnews.com/politics/new-report-unmasks-true-costs-electric-vehicle-mandates-remain-expensive</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>New report unmasks true costs of electric vehicle mandates: 'Remain more expensive'</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">A sweeping first-of-its-kind analysis published by think tank Texas Public Policy Foundation (TPPF) concludes that electric vehicles (EV) would cost tens of thousands of dollars more if not for generous taxpayer-funded incentives.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">According to the TPPF report &mdash; authored by energy experts Jason Isaac and Brent Bennett &mdash; the average model year 2021 EV would cost approximately $48,698 more to own over a 10-year period without the staggering $22 billion in taxpayer-funded handouts that the government provides to electric car manufacturers and owners. The analysis factors in federal fuel efficiency programs, electric grid strain, and direct state and federal subsidies.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">"It is not an overstatement to say that the federal government is subsidizing EVs to a greater degree than even wind and solar electricity generation and embarking on an unprecedented endeavor to remake the entire American auto industry," the report states. "Despite these massive incentives, EVs are receiving a tepid response from the majority of Americans who cannot shoulder their higher cost."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">"It&rsquo;s time for federal and state governments to stop driving the American auto industry off an economic cliff and allow markets to drive further improvements in cost and efficiency," it continues.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The report determined that, thanks to a special multiplier that has existed for more than two decades, EVs receive roughly seven times more credits under federal fuel efficiency programs than they provide in actual fuel economy benefits. That figure, the total regulatory credits from federal and state fuel efficiency and greenhouse gas emissions standards, amounts to an average of $27,881 per vehicle for EV makers.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Further, the analysis calculated the socialized cost of EV charging stations' strain on the U.S. electric grid amounts to an average of $11,833 per EV over 10 years. Such costs are shouldered by utility ratepayers and taxpayers, many of whom may not own an EV.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">And, finally, state governments and the federal government provide an average of $8,984 per EV over 10 years in direct taxpayer-funded subsidies.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">"The stark reality for proponents of EVs and for the dreamers in the federal government, who are using fuel economy regulations to force manufacturers to produce ever more EVs, is that the true cost of an EV is in no way close to a comparable [internal combustion engine vehicle (ICEV)]," the report concludes.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">"Without increased and sustained government favors, EVs will remain more expensive than ICEVs for many years to come," it states. "Hence why, even with these subsidies, EVs have been challenging for dealers to sell and why basic economic realities indicate that the Biden administration&rsquo;s dream of achieving 100% EVs by 2040 will never become a reality."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The TPPF report, meanwhile, comes as lawmakers at the federal and state level continue to take aim at traditional gas-powered vehicles while boosting EVs. President Biden has set a goal of ensuring 50% of all car sales are zero-emissions by 2030 and his administration has pursued rigorous restrictions on gas-powered vehicles.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">In December 2022, the Environmental Protection Agency (EPA) finalized rules, which targeted heavy-duty trucks, that it said at the time were the "strongest-ever national clean air standards to cut smog- and soot-forming emissions" from such vehicles. The new standards went into effect on March 27 and will be implemented for new trucks sold after 2027.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Then, in April, the EPA proposed the most aggressive federal tailpipe emissions rules on light- and medium-duty emissions ever crafted. If finalized and implemented, 67% of new sedan, crossover, SUV and light truck purchases, up to 50% of bus and garbage truck purchases, 35% of short-haul freight tractor purchases, and 25% of long-haul freight tractor purchases could be electric by 2032, the White House projected.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Months later, in July, the Department of Transportation's National Highway Traffic Safety Administration issued its most aggressive fuel economy standards ever, an action critics say would increase consumer costs.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">And last year, the EPA also reinstated California&rsquo;s authority under the Clean Air Act to implement its own emission standards and electric vehicle sales mandates, allowing other states to also adopt California's rules. The state then approved regulations that mandated all car purchases in the state &mdash; which leads the country in annual car sales &mdash; be electric by 2035.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://redstate.com/wardclark/2023/10/24/chinese-scientists-discover-8-new-viruses-on-tropical-island-what-could-possibly-go-wrong-n2165509"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://redstate.com/wardclark/2023/10/24/chinese-scientists-discover-8-new-viruses-on-tropical-island-what-could-possibly-go-wrong-n2165509</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Chinese Scientists Discover 8 New Viruses on Tropical Island - What Could Possibly Go Wrong?</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Chinese scientists working on tropical Hainan Island off China's southern coast have discovered eight new viruses in that island's rodent population, and have not ruled out the capability of those viruses to species-jump to humans. One of the viruses has been confirmed to have been a coronavirus; the COVID-19 virus was also a coronavirus, as are several of the viruses that can cause the syndrome we call "the common cold," although rhinoviruses are more common in those cases.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Researchers tasked with preparing the world for future pandemic took almost 700 samples from rodents living in Hainan, just off China's southern coast.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Eight novel viruses &mdash; including one belonging to the same family as Covid &mdash; were uncovered in the project, funded by the Chinese Government.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Experts said the discovered pathogens had a 'high probability' of infecting humans should they ever cross the species barrier.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">As a result, they called for further experiments on the viruses to determine exactly what their effects on humans could be.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Lots of people from lots of governments as well as academic institutions and private-sector organizations do these kinds of surveys, of course. That's how we learn about viruses, or about anything else in the natural world &mdash; by going out, taking samples, and examining things. But there's a different wrinkle in this case.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The findings were shared in the journal Virologica Sinica, the publishing arm of the Chinese Society for Microbiology (CSM).</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">CSM is linked to the state-affiliated China Association of Science and Technology, which 'accepts administrative supervision' from the Chinese Government's 'Ministry of Civil Affairs'.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Virologica Sinica is also edited by Dr Shi Zhengli, an influential scientist described as China's 'bat woman' who works inside the Wuhan Institute of Virology &ndash; considered to be the source of the Covid pandemic in some corners.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The journal's editorial board also features over a dozen other academics linked to the WIV.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The last sentence of that article's conclusion might raise some concerns:</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The pathogenicity and associated impact of these novel viruses on humans and animals should be evaluated in further studies.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">This is, yes, the same Wuhan virology lab that set off alarms about their safety practices at the outbreak of the COVID-19 panic. (There, the Wuhan lab isn't alone.) This is also the same Wuhan virology lab where $2 million in U.S. taxpayer funds were used to conduct research, including gain-of-function research.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">If that doesn't set some alarm bells ringing, it's not at all clear what would.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Coming as it does, hot on the heels of the impeccably coiffed Governor Newsom flying to the Middle Kingdom to stump for Chinese electric cars, and at a time when the American public is growing good and tired of the whole COVID scare, the timing of the discovery is interesting as well. Granted, these kinds of expeditions go on all the time, and granted as well that China doesn't have an unlimited pool of virologists out there looking for work.</span></p>]]></description>
   <author><![CDATA[Garrison Hardie]]></author>
   <enclosure url="https://app.dropwave.io/episode/db7c1589-f8b1-4045-b21b-62fd97fd0ed6/daily-news-brief-for-thursday-october-26th-2023.mp3" length="728" type="audio/mp3"/>
   <guid isPermaLink="false"><![CDATA[db7c1589-f8b1-4045-b21b-62fd97fd0ed6]]></guid>
   <pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
   <source url=""><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></source>
   <itunes:author><![CDATA[Garrison Hardie]]></itunes:author>
   <itunes:image href="https://assets-cdn2.dropwave.io/2ab40ac0-e99d-4f25-a6d2-541d2c9b290a/cover-art/mUK8zsnHkCK3vep7E1W6UgYb9dTnLenASAMEFha3.jpg"/>
   <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
   <itunes:duration>728</itunes:duration>
   <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
  
  </item><item>
   <title><![CDATA[Daily News Brief for Wednesday, October 25th, 2023 [Daily News Brief]]]></title>
   <link/>
   <description><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">This is Garrison Hardie with your CrossPolitic Daily News Brief for Wednesday, October 25th, 2023.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Page50 ad read concepts:</strong></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Page50 is a distinctly Christian marketing company striving to help Christian-owned businesses grow and succeed in our digital age. They don&rsquo;t want to just make a paycheck, they want to&nbsp;</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">change the world, and that means building it alongside you.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The mission is bigger than just Sunday. Page50 wants to help Christians recapture the work week, economic and political influence, and the public square.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Page50 doesn&rsquo;t work with just anybody, but if you&rsquo;re a believer they want to work with you. Visit pagefifty.com (ya gotta spell it out) and see what they can do for you. That&rsquo;s pagefifty.com.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://dailycaller.com/2023/10/24/tom-emmer-wins-gop-nomination-speaker/"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://dailycaller.com/2023/10/24/tom-emmer-wins-gop-nomination-speaker/</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Tom Emmer Wins GOP Nomination For Speaker Of The House On Secret Ballot</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">House Majority Whip Tom Emmer won the nomination for Speaker of the House on Tuesday after five rounds of votes.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Republicans were voting by secret ballot until they were able to get to a candidate who received a simple majority of the conference votes. After each round of votes, the member who received the lowest numbers was eliminated.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Candidates running had the option to drop out before each round of votes if they felt that they did not have enough support. 109 votes were needed to win.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Before the first round, there were seven GOP Republicans running for Speaker. Reps Tom Emmer, Mike Johnson, Byron Donald&rsquo;s, Kevin Hern, Austin Scott, Jack Bergman and Pete Sessions. Sessions received the lowest amount of votes during the first round of votes and dropped out.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Bergman dropped out after the second round of votes, as he received the least amount of votes.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">After the third round, Scott received the least amount of votes and dropped out of the race.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">After the fourth vote, Hern dropped out of the race after receiving the least amount of votes. Donalds then voluntarily dropped out of the race.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Emmer secured the majority of votes during the fifth vote.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">House Judiciary Chairman Jim Jordan was voted out of the race for speaker of the House on Friday after failing to receive the necessary votes on three separate ballots. Jordan lost in a secret ballot vote 86-112.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://justthenews.com/nation/states/center-square/nearly-1-million-residents-left-california-2022-fueled-cost-living"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://justthenews.com/nation/states/center-square/nearly-1-million-residents-left-california-2022-fueled-cost-living</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Nearly 1 million residents left California in 2022 fueled by cost of living</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The exodus from California accelerated in 2022, with 817,000 residents leaving the state in 2022 for an annual net loss of over three hundred thousand residents to other states, according to new U.S. Census data. Should outmigration continue, California could lose more than the five, already projected, congressional seats it&rsquo;s expected to shed after the 2030 census.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">During the COVID-19 pandemic and switch to remote work, California lost population for the first time in its existence as a state, leading to the loss of a single congressional seat in 2021 during the nation&rsquo;s reapportionment of census-based distribution of the nation&rsquo;s 435 congressional representatives. With a smaller congressional delegation, the state would have less power to shape federal spending.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">While California Governor Gavin Newsom has not addressed the new numbers directly, when challenged by Fox News host Sean Hannity on California&rsquo;s population decline in a June 2023 interview, he said, &ldquo;.3% [population loss] during COVID. My gosh.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Just before the interview, Newsom&rsquo;s Department of Finance estimated the state&rsquo;s population had declined by 138,443 during 2022, making for a .36% population loss in a single year. Also using Department of Finance Data, the Public Policy Institute of California estimated a decline of 211,000 residents in 2022. Meanwhile, the latest Census data cited above, once accounting for a sharp rebound in immigration and decrease in deaths that offset the increase in outward immigration, estimates a population decrease of 113,000 for 2022. While the reason for the differences is not clear &mdash; the finance department notes that the discrepancy between its numbers and the Census reporting is due to different time frames being measured &mdash; the general trend of data demonstrating the state&rsquo;s general population decline is consistent.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">According to PPIC polling, 45% of Californians are considering leaving the state due to the high cost of housing. Will Swaim, founder of the California Policy Center, acknowledges that housing is a major factor but that other costs, the lack of opportunity, and even the poor state of public education are leaving many Californians, especially parents, looking to move elsewhere.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&ldquo;There&rsquo;s no question that housing costs are huge, but that really ignores the myriad other ways that California has simply destroyed business opportunity, especially for the working class,&rdquo; said Swaim to The Center Square. &ldquo;It is a very expensive state to live in and the poorer you are the more that housing cost number hurts. But how about gasoline? Every week people are putting almost double what our fellow Americans in other states are putting in their cars.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Those leaving the state are disproportionately younger and lower income. For many families, buying property and raising children in the state is no longer a viable option.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&ldquo;We are losing younger folks, and I think we will see people continuing to migrate where housing costs are lower,&rdquo; Manuel Pastor, a professor of sociology and American Studies &amp; Ethnicity at the University of Southern California, said in an interview with the Associated Press. &ldquo;There are good jobs in California, but housing is incredibly expensive. It hurts young families, and it hurts immigrant families.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Swaim, who raised his children in California, noted that his now-adult children are left looking elsewhere for alternatives. Sharing his children&rsquo;s thoughts, he said, &ldquo;We don&rsquo;t want our children to be educated in California's public schools, but we want them to be educated in private schools that we can&rsquo;t afford.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The majority of students in California public schools do not meet the state&rsquo;s moderate standards for math, science, and English. When combining all sources of funding, California public schools spend approximately $27,000 per student. The Education Data Initiative estimates the average K-12 private school tuition in California is $16,337.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://townhall.com/tipsheet/spencerbrown/2023/10/23/us-border-agents-warned-to-look-out-for-hamas-fighters-n2630232"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://townhall.com/tipsheet/spencerbrown/2023/10/23/us-border-agents-warned-to-look-out-for-hamas-fighters-n2630232</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>CBP Agents Receive New Warning in Light of Israel-Hamas Conflict</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Authorities along the U.S.-Mexico border are being warned by the San Diego Field Office of U.S. Customs and Border Protection (CBP) to keep an eye out for "foreign fighters" connected to the terrorist groups waging war against Israel for the last two-plus weeks, another sign that the border crisis has wide-ranging national security implications.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">First reported by the Daily Caller News Foundation's Jennie Taer, the "Situational Awareness" bulletin sent Friday is titled "Foreign Fighters of Israel-Hamas Conflict May Potentially be Encountered at Southwest Border" and is marked "unclassified/law enforcement sensitive."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The bulletin explains:</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">San Diego Field Office Intelligence Unit (SDFO-FITU) assesses that individuals inspired by, or reacting to, the current Israel-Hamas conflict may attempt to travel to or from the area of hostilities in the Middle East via transit across the Southwest border.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Foreign fighters motivated by ideology or mercenary soldiers of fortune may attempt to travel to or from the US to or from countries in the Middle East through Mexico.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Among the items border agents are advised to watch for are military patches for Hamas, Palestinian Islamic Jihad (PIJ), and Hezbollah terrorist organizations &mdash; all funded by the regime in Iran.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Other possible indicators are military age males, military gear including weapons, camouflage, and the previously mentioned terror group patches, single travelers, and those with undetermined return plans or associations to Israel, the Palestinian territories or regional affiliations.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Agents are also given "questions of interest" to ask potential suspects with ties to the terrorist organizations to probe whether individuals have any "association with military or security services or government civilian agencies?" or "personal or familial association with Hamas, Hezbollah, Palestinian Islamic Jihad (PIJ), Popular Front for the Liberation of Palestine (PLFP) or any other similar groups?"</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">It's unsurprising that there's growing fear that terror-linked individuals may be seeking to take advantage of the border crisis after a record-setting number of apprehensions and "gotaways" have been recorded on the Biden administration's watch, including an alarming number of individuals whose names matched with people listed in U.S. terror watch lists.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://www.foxnews.com/world/iceland-pm-goes-strike-womens-equal-pay-gender-based-violence"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.foxnews.com/world/iceland-pm-goes-strike-womens-equal-pay-gender-based-violence</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Iceland PM goes on strike over women's equal pay, gender-based violence</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The prime minister of Iceland went on strike Tuesday in protest of gender discrimination.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Prime Minister Katrin yaker-stoder joined women across the country in a national demonstration against pay discrimination and gendered violence.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">"We have not yet reached our goals of full gender equality and we are still tackling the gender-based wage gap, which is unacceptable in 2023," Jakobsd&oacute;ttir told news outlet mbl.is.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The nationwide protest, referred to as a "women's strike," is the first full day of widespread female absence from the workforce since 1975.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">"I will not work this day, as I expect all the women [in cabinet] will do as well," Jakobsd&oacute;ttir said.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The original protest aimed to emphasize the importance of women in the workforce and urge an end to disparate wages between female and male workers.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Women in Iceland earn approximately 10% less on average compared to their male counterparts, according to the World Economic Forum.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">As Icelandic women's rights movements have made greater headway in their campaigns, the scope and meaning of the protests have expanded to include other issues.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">"We are still tackling gender-based violence, which has been a priority for my government to tackle," yakob-stoder said.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Iceland consistently ranks among the most gender-equal countries in the world in terms of education, employment and health care.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Jakobsd&oacute;ttir's cabinet maintains an equal number of men and women and Iceland's national parliament hovers just under 50% female.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Past Icelandic women's strikes have sparked similar protests in other European countries.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://thepostmillennial.com/coca-cola-quietly-deletes-mentions-of-hamas-supporting-blm-from-company-website?utm_campaign=64487"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://thepostmillennial.com/coca-cola-quietly-deletes-mentions-of-hamas-supporting-blm-from-company-website?utm_campaign=64487</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Coca-Cola quietly deletes mentions of BLM from company website</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Coca-Cola has been a financial sponsor of Black Lives Matter for years, however, references to its support of the organization appeared to have vanished from its website in light of recent posts shared by the group siding with Hamas.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">BLM Chicago and an organizer from Los Angeles are among those associated with the purported civil rights group to have publicly voiced support for the Iranian-backed Palestinian terrorist group following its latest wave of violence.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">On Friday, Texas Sen. Ted Cruz (R) revealed that he had caught the beverage giant "red-handed," posting two screenshots of its website, one of which included references to BLM, and an updated version that does not.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Coca-Cola had originally stated on its website that Sprite, which it owns, had donated $500,000 to the Black Lives Matter Global Network to "support the group's voting education efforts and their February 2021 Black Future Month program."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">"We're in this for the long haul," brand lead Aaliyah Shafiq noted. "Lasting change will not happen overnight, so we're committed to continuing to amplofy the voices and efforts of our community, to listen and learn, and to actively help create a better shared future for America."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">In the updated version of their website, Shafiq's quote is still there, however, the entire sentence highlighting the $500,000 contribution has been deleted.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">"Editing your website is not enough," Cruz said. "Americans DEMAND an apology."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The posts in question were shared in the days following Hamas' brutal massacre of civilians in Israel.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">BLM Chicago featured an image of a paraglider with a Palestinian flag attached to his parachute. "That is all that it is!" was the caption.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Before long, users utilized X's Community Notes feature to point out important context.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">"The Palestinian terrorist group Hamas used armed gun men on Paragliders to enter a rave in Israel to kill over 260 innocent people partying," the note read, adding that, "previous to this incident, Palestinians were not know[n] for paragliding."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">It was later deleted, though the group did remain steadfast in its support for the Palestinians over Israel.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">"For every corporate donor who sent millions to BLM&mdash;including Amazon, Apple, BlackRock &amp; Bank of America&mdash;do you regret supporting such an antisemitic organization?" Cruz asked on his podcast Wednesday, according to Fox News.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The organizer from Los Angeles, Dr. Melina Abdullah, said in her post that "we must stand unwaveringly on the side of the oppressed," adding, "when a people have been subject to decades of unimaginable violence, their resistance must not be condemned, but understood as a desperate act of self-defense."</span></p>]]></description>
   <author><![CDATA[Garrison Hardie]]></author>
   <enclosure url="https://app.dropwave.io/episode/0d620e19-e9a3-4104-9190-09012f42b348/daily-news-brief-for-wednesday-october-25th-2023.mp3" length="790" type="audio/mp3"/>
   <guid isPermaLink="false"><![CDATA[0d620e19-e9a3-4104-9190-09012f42b348]]></guid>
   <pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
   <source url=""><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></source>
   <itunes:author><![CDATA[Garrison Hardie]]></itunes:author>
   <itunes:image href="https://assets-cdn2.dropwave.io/2ab40ac0-e99d-4f25-a6d2-541d2c9b290a/cover-art/mUK8zsnHkCK3vep7E1W6UgYb9dTnLenASAMEFha3.jpg"/>
   <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
   <itunes:duration>790</itunes:duration>
   <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
  
  </item><item>
   <title><![CDATA[Daily News Brief for Tuesday, October 24th, 2023 [Daily News Brief]]]></title>
   <link/>
   <description><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">This is Garrison Hardie with your CrossPolitic Daily News Brief for Tuesday, October 24th, 2023.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>PUB MEMBERSHIP PLUG:</strong></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Summer has been great here at CrossPolitic, and we want you to join us on this ride&hellip; First, we&rsquo;re no longer calling it the Fight Laugh Feast club&hellip; it&rsquo;s now called the Pub! Second, we&rsquo;ve launched a new line of content, focused on family entertainment. We have our new show &ldquo;This America&rdquo; already in the Pub and our exciting new &ldquo;Rowdy Christian Guides&rdquo; highlighting the practical guides to fun and godly life! Additionally, we will have the live streaming of our conferences, and our past conference talks, all bundled within our new polished Fight Laugh Feast App. Sign up today! Head on over to fightlaughfeast.com, and join the Pub! that&rsquo;s fightlaughfeast.com.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://www.dailyfetched.com/over-12000-us-troops-head-toward-middle-east-on-10-warships/"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.dailyfetched.com/over-12000-us-troops-head-toward-middle-east-on-10-warships/</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Over 12,000 US Troops Head toward Middle East on 10 Warships</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">As tensions equate to World War Three levels in the Middle East, over 12,000 US Navy and Marine Corps personnel aboard ten warships are heading towards the Middle East, according to reports.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Over the weekend, Defense Secretary Lloyd J. Austin III announced a series of actions to bolster the US military presence in the Middle East.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The USS Dwight D. Eisenhower Carrier Strike Group has been redirected to the Central Command area of responsibility in addition to the Navy&rsquo;s most advanced nuclear aircraft carrier, USS Gerald R. Ford Carrier Strike Group, which is currently positioned in the Eastern Mediterranean Sea.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The USS Dwight D. Eisenhower Carrier Strike Group now joins the USS Gerald R. Ford group, bringing the number of American warships in the region to 10.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">There are 4,500 sailors on board the US aircraft carrier Gerald R. Ford, accompanied by five other ships carrying over 1,600 US troops.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Onboard the USS Dwight D. Eisenhower aircraft carrier is 5,000 service members, with further ships carrying another 1,000 troops.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Last week, Secretary of Defense Lloyd Austin placed 2,000 forces on standby to &ldquo;be ready to deploy.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The forces will now be ready to be deployed to the Eastern Mediterranean within 24 hours, Fox News reported.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The order came just days after a special operations Marine Corps unit participating in exercises departed early &ldquo;as a result of emerging events.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Over the weekend, Austin placed an unspecified number of US troops under &ldquo;prepare to deploy&rdquo; orders.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Austin said in a statement:</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&ldquo;I have placed an additional number of forces on prepare to deploy orders as part of prudent contingency planning, to increase their readiness and ability to quickly respond as required.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Meanwhile, up to six Chinese Warships have been spotted in waters near the Middle East.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">IDF spokesman Daniel Hagari said in a statement:</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&ldquo;We need to enter under the best possible conditions, and this is what we are doing now, as the next stage of war approaches.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&ldquo;From today, we are increasing the strikes and minimizing the danger.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&ldquo;We will narrow the risks to our forces over the next stages. This is why we have once again urged residents of Gaza to keep moving south,&rdquo; he added.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">As The Daily Fetched reported:</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Many media outlets have taken Hagari&rsquo;s words as meaning they are preparing for an imminent ground assault.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://www.newsmax.com/world/globaltalk/israel-mideast-assets/2023/10/22/id/1139191/"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.newsmax.com/world/globaltalk/israel-mideast-assets/2023/10/22/id/1139191/</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>US Rushes Advanced THAAD Missile Defense to Mideast</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Fears that the Israel-Hamas war could mushroom into a wider Middle East conflict rose on Sunday with Washington warning of a significant risk to U.S. interests in the region as ally Israel pounded Gaza and clashes on its border with Lebanon intensified.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Gaza's Health Ministry said 266 Palestinians, including 117 children, had been killed by Israeli air strikes in the past 24 hours in the enclave, to which Israel laid "total siege" after a deadly mass infiltration into Israel by Hamas gunmen on Oct. 7.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">In neighboring Syria, where Hamas' main regional backer Iran has a military presence, Israeli missiles hit Damascus and Aleppo international airports early on Sunday, putting both out of service and killing two workers, Syrian state media said.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Along Israel's northern border with Lebanon, the Iran-backed Hezbollah group has clashed with Israeli forces in support of Hamas in the deadliest escalation of frontier violence since an Israel-Hezbollah war in 2006.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">With violence around its heavily guarded borders increasing, Israel on Sunday added 14 communities close to Lebanon and Syria to its evacuation contingency plan in the north of the country.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Palestinian Prime Minister Mohammad Shtayyeh called on the international community to create "a united front" to stop Israel's attacks against Gaza and allow in desperately needed aid which has only begun to trickle in.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">"We place at the top of our priorities stopping the Israeli aggression (...) and bringing in medical and relief aid to prevent a major humanitarian catastrophe," Shtayyeh said during a meeting with 25 ambassadors, representatives and consuls.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">U.S. Defense Secretary Lloyd Austin said on Saturday that Washington would send more military assets to the Middle East in support of Israel and strengthen the U.S. defense posture in the region after "recent escalations by Iran and its proxy forces" - a reference to Hezbollah, Palestinian and other militants.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Austin told ABC's "This Week" program on Sunday: "We're concerned about potential escalation. In fact, what we're seeing ... is the prospect of a significant escalation of attacks on our troops and our people throughout the region.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">"If any group or any country is looking to widen this conflict and take advantage of this very unfortunate situation ... our advice is: don&rsquo;t," he added.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Austin said a Terminal High Altitude Area Defense (THAAD) system and extra Patriot air defense missile system battalions will be sent to the region and more troops put on standby.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Iranian security officials told Reuters Iran's strategy was for Middle East proxies like Hezbollah to pursue limited strikes on Israeli and U.S. targets but to avoid a major escalation that would draw in Tehran, a high-wire act for the Islamic Republic.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Israel unleashed an aerial blitz on Gaza to its southwest after Hamas militants breached the border on Oct. 7 and killed 1,400 people, mainly civilians, and took 212 hostages back to Gaza.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Gaza's Health Ministry said on Sunday that Israel's air and missile strikes in retaliation had killed at least 4,741 and wounded 15,898, with over a million of the densely populated enclave's 2.3 million people displaced.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Israel has amassed tanks and troops near the fenced border around Gaza for a planned ground invasion aiming to annihilate Hamas, after several inconclusive wars dating to its seizure of power there in 2007, after Israel ended a 38-year occupation.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Several Egyptian guards on the border with Gaza suffered minor injuries on Sunday after being accidentally hit by fragments of a shell from an Israeli tank, the Egyptian army said. Israel's defense force expressed "sorrow regarding the incident," which it said was being investigated.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Hamas's armed wing said it had fired more rockets at Tel Aviv on Sunday. There was no immediate word of damage or casualties.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">With Israel keeping up daily bombings, Palestinians said they received renewed Israeli military warnings to move from Gaza's north to the south to avoid the deadliest theater of the war.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">They said military leaflets dropped on the territory, just 45 km (28 miles) long, contained the added warning that they could be identified as sympathizers with a "terrorist organization" if they stayed put.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Gaza's Health Ministry said most of the dead from air strikes over the past 24 hours were in Gaza's south. Israel says it is only targeting militants and that they often use residential buildings as cover.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The first humanitarian aid convoy allowed into Gaza since war erupted arrived in southern Gaza from Egypt on Saturday after days of negotiations. The U.N. said the 20-truck convoy brought life-saving medical supplies and some food.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">A second convoy of around 19 trucks loaded with medical and food supplies entered the Egyptian side of the Rafah crossing on Sunday and was being inspected before proceeding into Gaza, sources said.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">An explosion and ambulance sirens were heard on Sunday afternoon, shortly after the second convoy had entered the crossing, witnesses said. The cause and exact location were not immediately clear.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The U.N. humanitarian office said the volume of aid entering so far was just 4% of the daily average before the hostilities and a fraction of what was needed with food, water, medicines and fuel stocks running out.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Deprived of electricity and water, Gazans in the southern town of Khan Younis said they were struggling to feed their children.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&ldquo;We are suffering extremely, waiting since dawn to get bread. If this continues for two more days it will be catastrophic,&rdquo; said Saleh Skafi, a father of four from north Gaza now sheltering in Khan Younis.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Now, on this note - let&rsquo;s take a look at the overall situation across the globe&hellip;&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://www.axios.com/2023/10/20/biden-government-war-fears-israel-hamas"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.axios.com/2023/10/20/biden-government-war-fears-israel-hamas</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Behind the Curtain: Rattled U.S. government fears wars could spread</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Never before have we talked to so many top government officials who, in private, are so worried about so many overseas conflicts at once.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&nbsp;We don't like to sound dire. But to sound a siren of clinical, clear-eyed realism: U.S. officials say this confluence of crises poses epic concern and historic danger.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Behind the scenes: Officials tell us that inside the White House, this was the heaviest, most chilling week since President Biden took office just over 1,000 days ago.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Former Defense Secretary Bob Gates &mdash; who ran the Pentagon under presidents of both parties, George W. Bush and Barack Obama &mdash; tells us America is facing the most crises since World War II ended 78 years ago.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">He explains the White House's system overload like this: "There's this gigantic funnel that sits over the table in the Situation Room. And all the problems in the world end up coming through that funnel to the same eight or 10 people. There's a limit to the bandwidth those eight or 10 people can have."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<ol>
<li><span style="font-weight: 400;"> Israel's response to the Hamas terrorist attack, and growing fear of a spreading war that reaches to Iran and beyond. Officials point to the protests, threats and deadly, anti-American warnings of Arab nations after they thought &mdash; incorrectly &mdash; Israel struck a hospital in Gaza, killing hundreds. This is a preview of what they fully expect will be a worldwide response to the expected Israeli invasion of Gaza.</span></li>
</ol>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The U.S. is deploying two aircraft carriers to the region. A U.S. Navy destroyer on Thursday shot down missiles from Yemen that appeared headed toward Israel. U.S. troops were fired on this week by drones in Syria and Iraq.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<ol start="2">
<li><span style="font-weight: 400;"> Vladimir Putin meeting in China this week with Xi Jinping to further strengthen their anti-America alliance. In a new Foreign Affairs article that top officials are sharing, Gates argues that both leaders believe America and other big democracies "are past their prime and have entered an irreversible decline." Putin and Xi sniff weakness and are activating on many fronts&hellip;</span></li>
</ol>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">This Reuters headline says it all: "Russia says it is coordinating Middle East policy with China."</span></p>
<ol start="3">
<li><span style="font-weight: 400;"> A malicious Iran. It's unclear how involved Iran was in orchestrating or assisting the Hamas terrorist attack &mdash; but officials seem certain there are ties. More worrisome: U.S. officials fear Hezbollah &mdash; a much bigger terrorist group than Hamas, funded by Iran &mdash; will strike the moment Israel gets stuck in Gaza.</span></li>
</ol>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Biden said Thursday night in his Oval Office address: "Iran is supporting Russia in Ukraine, and it's supporting Hamas and other terrorist groups in the region."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Then there's the unhinged leader of North Korea, Kim Jong Un, and his frequent testing of long-range, nuclear-capable missiles. As Gates points out, the combined nuclear arsenal of Russia, China, Iran and North Korea "could within a few years be nearly double the size of" America's.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<ol start="5">
<li><span style="font-weight: 400;"> A new weapon is being deployed in all these conflicts: a massive spread of doctored or wholly fake videos to manipulate what people see and think in real time. The architects of these new technologies, in background conversations after demonstrating new capabilities soon to be released, say even the sharpest eyes looking for fake videos will have an impossible time detecting what's real. (We'll have a column coming soon to Go Deeper on this topic).</span></li>
</ol>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Fake video, on top of bots (fake people) and fake written content, is being used aggressively by all anti-American actors, intelligence officials say. Some experts estimate that more than 90% of content on the internet will soon be fake or manipulated.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">What scares officials is how all five threats could fuse into one.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The State Department on Thursday issued a rare "Worldwide Caution," warning U.S. travelers abroad of "increased tensions in various locations around the world" that raise "the potential for terrorist attacks, demonstrations or violent actions against U.S. citizens and interests."</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">These simultaneous threats are hitting at the very moment the American political system seems &mdash; and sometimes is &mdash; literally broken.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">It's not just that Republicans don't have a House speaker and can't seem to elect one, or that we might shut down the government in the middle of this mess, or that we're hurtling toward another toxic presidential election in which big chunks of both parties want different candidates.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Former top intelligence officials tell us domestic unrest is one of their biggest fears &mdash; whether it's triggered by court rulings against President Trump or protests over war in the Middle East. Biden allies frame these flare-ups as a reminder that global chaos requires calm and experience. "With age comes wisdom," Ron Klain, Biden's first chief of staff, told us.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">But there has been a total collapse of people's trust in the opposing party, the media, what they see or share on social platforms, and even the top-secret intelligence the government relies on to measure these threats.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">This, as much as the five individual threats above, is what worries officials. They know things could get worse &mdash; fast &mdash; and require tough actions &mdash; fast. And no one knows whether Congress or the public could unite in an emergency.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://www.breitbart.com/europe/2023/10/22/londons-met-police-declare-calling-for-jihad-is-lawful-as-word-has-number-of-meanings/"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.breitbart.com/europe/2023/10/22/londons-met-police-declare-calling-for-jihad-is-lawful-as-word-has-number-of-meanings/</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>London Police Declare Calling for Jihad Is Lawful as Word has &lsquo;Number of Meanings&rsquo;</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">London&rsquo;s Metropolitan Police have come under criticism for their seemingly lax approach towards pro-Palestine demonstrations and for giving excuses for those calling for &ldquo;jihad&rdquo; against Israel on the streets of the British capital.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">An estimated 100,000 anti-Israel protesters took to the streets of London on Saturday. Ahead of the demonstration, the Met police warned activists that they may face arrest if they were seen to be supporting proscribed terror groups like Hamas.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">However, while several people were arrested and some investigations continue, the police force drew considerable backlash for appearing to excuse calls for jihad.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Responding to footage of a speaker calling for jihad while standing in front of a placard calling on the &ldquo;Muslim armies&rdquo; of the world to attack Israel, the Met said on X: &ldquo;The word jihad has a number of meanings but we know the public will most commonly associate it with terrorism.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&ldquo;We have specialist counter-terrorism officers here in the operations room who have particular knowledge in this area. They have assessed this video, filmed at the protest in central London today, and have not identified any offences arising from the specific clip.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">However, recognising the way language like this will be interpreted by the public and the divisive impact it will have, officers have identified the man involved and will be speaking to him shortly to discourage any repeat of similar chanting.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Yet users on social media noted that the Metropolitan Police&rsquo;s own hate crime guide states: &ldquo;The offence of incitement to hatred occurs when someone acts in a way that is threatening and intended to stir up hatred&hellip; Hate content may include: messages calling for violence against a specific person or group.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://twitter.com/i/status/1715732342604505530"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://twitter.com/i/status/1715732342604505530</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> - Play Video&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">While the Arabic word literally translates to &ldquo;struggle&rdquo; and has been used in other, more peaceful contexts, observers noted that the context of the call for jihad on Saturday in London was a literal war cry against Israel.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Journalist Andy Ngo, who covered the London rally on Saturday, said: &ldquo;I was there and the speaker was specifically talking about getting military leaders and countries to mobilize armies of Muslims to go to Palestinian territories to assist the (those who do jihad) against Israel in a holy battle for Islam.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The post has received widespread derision, with author Douglas Murray writing: &ldquo;Yes, oh Imam of the Met Police. Those guys definitely looked like they were calling for an intense inner spiritual struggle. Got it in one.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Political commentator Darren Grimes added: &ldquo;Shouting &lsquo;Jihad! Jihad! Jihad!&rsquo; won&rsquo;t get you arrested in Britain, but telling a copper that they look like your lesbian nan as a teenager will see six officers pound your door down.&rdquo;</span><span style="font-weight: 400;"><br /></span></p>]]></description>
   <author><![CDATA[Garrison Hardie]]></author>
   <enclosure url="https://app.dropwave.io/episode/ce8ee047-1736-4e02-b9ad-865fad84ef94/daily-news-brief-for-tuesday-october-24th-2023.mp3" length="1020" type="audio/mp3"/>
   <guid isPermaLink="false"><![CDATA[ce8ee047-1736-4e02-b9ad-865fad84ef94]]></guid>
   <pubDate>Tue, 24 Oct 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
   <source url=""><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></source>
   <itunes:author><![CDATA[Garrison Hardie]]></itunes:author>
   <itunes:image href="https://assets-cdn2.dropwave.io/2ab40ac0-e99d-4f25-a6d2-541d2c9b290a/cover-art/mUK8zsnHkCK3vep7E1W6UgYb9dTnLenASAMEFha3.jpg"/>
   <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
   <itunes:duration>1020</itunes:duration>
   <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
  
  </item>
 </channel>
</rss>
