<?xml version="1.0"?>
<?xml-stylesheet href="/storage/feed-stylesheet.xsl" type="text/xsl"?>

<rss xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
 <channel>
  <title>FLF - Daily News Brief</title>
  <link>https://dropwave.io</link>
  <description><![CDATA[FIGHT LAUGH FEAST PRESENTS SHOWS PROCLAIMING THE LORDSHIP OF CHRIST OVER ALL OF LIFE.
]]></description>
  <language>en</language>
  <managingEditor><![CDATA[fightlaughfeast@gmail.com (FLF, LLC)]]></managingEditor>
  <webMaster><![CDATA[support@dropwave.io (DropWave Support)]]></webMaster>
  <pubDate>Sun, 30 Apr 2023 13:25:44 +0000</pubDate>
  <lastBuildDate>Sun, 30 Apr 2023 13:25:44 +0000</lastBuildDate>
  <image>
   <url>https://is4-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Podcasts113/v4/58/56/52/5856525c-2973-cf29-3db9-21faa8595391/mza_1144696925612154085.png/1200x1200bb.jpg</url>
   <link>https://dropwave.io</link>
   <title><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></title>
  </image>
  <itunes:author><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></itunes:author>
  <itunes:image href="https://is4-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Podcasts113/v4/58/56/52/5856525c-2973-cf29-3db9-21faa8595391/mza_1144696925612154085.png/1200x1200bb.jpg"/>
  <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
  <itunes:owner>
   <itunes:name><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></itunes:name>
   <itunes:email>fightlaughfeast@gmail.com</itunes:email>
  </itunes:owner>
  <itunes:category text="News"/>
  <item>
   <title><![CDATA[Daily News Brief for Friday, April 28th, 2023 [Daily News Brief]]]></title>
   <link>https://app.dropwave.io/episode/4dbee7a4-0428-4cf2-aeb0-40bf35f52577/daily-news-brief-for-friday-april-28th-2023.mp3</link>
   <description><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">This is Garrison Hardie with your CrossPolitic Daily News Brief for Friday, April 28th, 2023.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://www.breitbart.com/politics/2023/04/27/argentina-shuns-u-s-dollar-will-pay-for-china-imports-in-yuan/"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.breitbart.com/politics/2023/04/27/argentina-shuns-u-s-dollar-will-pay-for-china-imports-in-yuan/</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>Argentina Shuns U.S. Dollar: Will Pay for China Imports in Yuan</strong></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Argentina struck a deal with Beijing on Wednesday to stop using U.S. dollars to pay for Chinese imports and embrace the yuan instead.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The measure, driven by Argentina&rsquo;s leftist President Alberto Fern&aacute;ndez, is designed to relieve the South American country&rsquo;s dwindling dollar reserves, AP reports.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The deal further enhances China&rsquo;s rise on the world stage and the diminished role of the U.S. on a host of fronts under President Joe Biden.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">After reaching the agreement with various companies, Argentina will use the yuan for imports from China worth about U.S.$1.04 billion from next month, accelerating trade with China as Beijing seeks to gain a further foothold in South America.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">In November last year Argentina expanded a currency swap with China by $5 billion in an effort to increase its yuan reserves.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">That agreement allowed Argentina &ldquo;to work on the possibility&rdquo; of advancing the rate of imports with yuan-denominated import orders being authorized in 90 days rather than the standard 180 days.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The decision comes as Argentina battles critical levels in its dollar reserves amid a sharp drop in agricultural exports caused by a historic drought, as well as political uncertainty ahead of elections this year.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">It has also been working hard to build a relationship with Beijing after having officially joined China&rsquo;s infrastructure-building Belt and Road Initiative (BRI) last year.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Argentina&rsquo;s government finalized a deal with Beijing soon after to construct a nuclear plant based on Chinese technology near Buenos Aires, Argentina&rsquo;s national capital, in the near future.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The Chinese Communist Party will reportedly provide $8 billion in financing toward the project&rsquo;s $12 billion total budget.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">As Breitbart News reported, Argentina currently owes the International Monetary Fund (IMF) $44 billion.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The international organization is in talks with Argentine authorities to finalize a fourth review of its program that includes a flexibilization of the proposed foreign exchange reserve accumulation as Argentina, whose foreign reserves are now at a $5 billion deficit, cannot comply with the current goals.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://www.foxnews.com/world/singapore-executes-man-conspired-traffic-2-pounds-cannabis"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.foxnews.com/world/singapore-executes-man-conspired-traffic-2-pounds-cannabis</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>Singapore executes man who allegedly conspired to traffic 2 pounds of cannabis</strong></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Singapore on Wednesday executed a man accused of coordinating a cannabis delivery, despite pleas for clemency from his family and protests from activists that he was convicted on weak evidence.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Tangaraju Suppiah, 46, was sentenced to death in 2018 for abetting the trafficking of 2.2 pounds of cannabis. Under Singapore laws, trafficking more than 500 grams of cannabis may result in the death penalty.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Tangaraju was hanged Wednesday morning and his family was given the death certificate, according to a tweet from activist Kirsten Han of the Transformative Justice Collective, which advocates for abolishing the death penalty in Singapore.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Although Tangaraju was not caught with the cannabis, prosecutors said phone numbers traced him as the person responsible for coordinating the delivery of the drugs. Tangaraju had maintained that he was not the one communicating with the others connected to the case.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">At a United Nations Human Rights briefing Tuesday, a spokesperson called on the Singapore government to adopt a "formal moratorium" on executions for drug-related offenses.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">"Imposing the death penalty for drug offences is incompatible with international norms and standards," said the spokesperson, who added that increasing evidence shows the death penalty is ineffective as a deterrent.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Singapore authorities say there is a deterrent effect, citing studies that traffickers carry amounts below the threshold that would bring a death penalty.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The island-state's imposition of the death penalty for drugs is in contrast with its neighbors. In Thailand, cannabis has essentially been legalized, and Malaysia has ended the mandatory death penalty for serious crimes.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Singapore executed 11 people last year for drug offenses. One case that spurred international concern involved a Malaysian man whose lawyers said he was mentally disabled.</span></p>
<p><br /><br /></p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://dailycaller.com/2023/04/26/red-state-bill-religious-institutions-state-funding/"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://dailycaller.com/2023/04/26/red-state-bill-religious-institutions-state-funding/</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>Red State Passes Bill Allowing Religious Institutions Access To State Funding</strong></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The Oklahoma House of Representatives passed a bill Tuesday protecting religious institutions from being denied access to state funding.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The Oklahoma Religious Freedom Act was introduced by Republican state Sen. Shane Jett and Republican state Sen. Julie Daniels to further reinforce the First Amendment by preventing the state from denying faith-based groups access to taxpayer dollars, according to the bill. The legislature passed the act Tuesday by a 64 to 27 vote, officially sending the act to Republican Gov. Kevin Stitt&rsquo;s desk to be signed into law.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The bill makes way for religious institutions to access state funding by barring the state from denying applications for funding &ldquo;based solely on the religious character or affiliation of the person or entity.&rdquo; The act adds to religious protections the state passed in 2021 preventing the government from declaring church activities non-essential, as was often the case during the COVID-19 pandemic.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">However, some Democrats argued that the bill was an unnecessary addition to the First Amendment, according to KFOR.com, a local media outlet. One Democratic state representative warned that the bill could lead to government funding of religious activities at religious schools.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Republican state Rep. John Echols, who co-authored the bill, disagreed with his colleague&rsquo;s assessment, according to KFOR.com.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Oklahoma has been at the center of this discussion for some time. Earlier this month, Gov. Stitt and state Attorney General Gentner Drummond clashed over a Catholic charter school application that would have created the first state-funded religious charter school in the nation. The application was temporarily denied by the state&rsquo;s virtual charter board but will be voted on again in the coming weeks. Stitt told the Daily Caller News Foundation that he was disappointed by the the attorney general&rsquo;s response to the charter and continued to hope that Oklahoma would host the nation&rsquo;s first state-funded religious charter school, providing more options for parents.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Stitt, Jett, Daniels and Echols did not immediately respond to the Daily Caller News Foundation&rsquo;s request for comment.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://thepostmillennial.com/breaking-ex-producer-suing-tucker-carlson-has-never-even-met-him?utm_campaign=64487"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://thepostmillennial.com/breaking-ex-producer-suing-tucker-carlson-has-never-even-met-him?utm_campaign=64487</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>Ex-producer suing Tucker Carlson has never even met him</strong></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Tucker Carlson Tonight producer Abby Grossberg is suing Carlson and the Fox Network over sexual behavior in the workplace, despite never having met Carlson in person.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The Spectator reports that lawyers for Grossberg have confirmed that she never actually met Carlson. "Like many on the [Tucker Carlson Tonight] staff, Abby never met Tucker Carlson in person because he taped the show from his personal studios in Maine and Florida, and he did not visit Fox's NY HQ during her time there," said one of Grossberg's attorneys Kimberly A. Catala.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Grossberg was the head of booking from July 2022 until she was recently placed on leave in March. She "alleges that Carlson encouraged a hostile and sexist workplace environment among his employees. Grossberg says she was subjected to bullying, antisemitic comments and sexism by staff while working out of Fox&rsquo;s Manhattan office," Spectator reports.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Despite never having met Carlson, Grossberg told rival network MSNBC that "Tucker and his executive producer Justin Wells, who was also fired, really were responsible for breaking me and making my life a living hell."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">"Since Tucker did not come to the Fox office, he relied on Justin Wells, his executive producer, and others like Alexander McCaskill, senior producer, who were present in the office every day to be his eyes, ears and mouthpiece, and to convey his &lsquo;tone,&rsquo; as they threateningly reminded Ms. Grossberg," Catala said.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The allegation per Grossberg's attorneys is that Carlson directed the "sexist" environment from afar. Apparently, the attorneys posited that Carlson had staff work as his "eyes" and "ears" in the New York office while he worked away in Maine.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Carlson and Fox parted ways on Monday morning, though promos for the evening's show were already airing as the press release from Fox went out. It is unclear as to why Fox dismissed the insanely popular news anchor, though speculation abounds, including that Fox owner Rupert Murdoch took issue with Carlson's Christian beliefs.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Carlson has been seen in Florida enjoying time with his wife, and laughing about finally being able to dine together on weeknights. His show has been on the air for 7 years, and in that time he amassed a loyal following. In the hours following his departure from the network, "RIP Fox News" was trending on Twitter as many viewers found they had no reason to tune in once Carlson was no longer on the air.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The end of the Tucker Carlson Tonight era was celebrated by AOC, who had called for federal regulation of Fox and Carlson, which routinely took aim at her and her shenanigans.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2023/04/26/us/colorado-rock-throwing-arrests.html"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.nytimes.com/2023/04/26/us/colorado-rock-throwing-arrests.html</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>3 Teens Charged With Murder in Rock-Throwing Spree That Killed Colorado Driver</strong></span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Three teenagers have been charged with first-degree murder in connection with a rock-throwing spree on Colorado roads last week that led to the death of one driver, the authorities said.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The three suspects, all 18 and identified as Joseph Koenig, Nicholas Karol-Chik and Zachary Kwak, were arrested on Tuesday evening at their homes in Arvada, Colo., for taking part in a series of rock-throwing episodes on April 19 that fatally wounded Alexa Bartell, 20, who was killed when one of the rocks smashed through her windshield and struck her, the Jefferson County Sheriff&rsquo;s Office announced on Wednesday.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">In addition to murder, the three men are charged with extreme indifference; other charges to be determined by the First Judicial District Attorney&rsquo;s Office are expected.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">It was not immediately clear if the three, who are seniors from different high schools, had lawyers on Wednesday.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The rock-throwing spree began shortly after 10 p.m. on April 19 in Westminster, Colo., which is a city of about 114,000 residents north of Denver, the authorities said.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">During that hour, the authorities said, the three drove a pickup truck around the county and threw large landscaping rocks at six vehicles, including a minivan and an S.U.V., hitting their windshields and driver&rsquo;s side windows. Those drivers had minor or no injuries.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Around 10:45 p.m., Ms. Bartell was driving north on Indiana Street when her Chevrolet Spark, a subcompact, became the last vehicle struck during the spree, the authorities said.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Moments before she was killed, Ms. Bartell was on her phone talking to a friend &ldquo;when the phone went silent,&rdquo; according to the sheriff&rsquo;s office.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Her friend tracked her phone and drove to the location on Indiana Street where she found Ms. Bartell &ldquo;fatally wounded inside her car, which was off the roadway in a field.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">It was unclear which of the men were driving but &ldquo;all three are suspected of throwing rocks,&rdquo; the sheriff&rsquo;s office said. They were believed to be in a black 2016 Chevrolet Silverado pickup truck.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">&ldquo;Ultimately, mobile device forensics and supporting information from the public helped lead to the identification and arrest of the suspects,&rdquo; according to the sheriff&rsquo;s office, which did not release additional details.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The men, who were booked into the jail at the Jefferson County Sheriff&rsquo;s Office, are scheduled to appear in court on Thursday.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Before we end today&hellip; how about some good news?!</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://www.goodnewsnetwork.org/mom-wins-lottery-with-ticket-she-bought-celebrating-daughters-victory-over-cancer/"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.goodnewsnetwork.org/mom-wins-lottery-with-ticket-she-bought-celebrating-daughters-victory-over-cancer/</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>Mom Wins Lottery with Ticket She Bought Celebrating Daughter&rsquo;s Victory Over Cancer</strong></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">After shelling out her life savings to pay for her daughter&rsquo;s breast cancer treatment, a Florida grandmother got a nod from the universe.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Buying the last available scratch-off from her preferred lottery game at the store, she landed a $2 million jackpot.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Geraldine Gimblet of Lakeland was celebrating the moment that her daughter, Lawrencia Jackson, rang a bell at the local hospital signifying she had finished her breast cancer treatment.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">A long-time lottery player, Gimblet, 74, spent $10 on the last scratch-off card at the store, and it happened to be a winner.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">&ldquo;I just didn&rsquo;t know,&rdquo; Gimblet told Good Morning America regarding her reaction,, &lsquo;Are you sure, would you check this on your phone?&rsquo; And, I won!&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Daughter Jackson, who accompanied Gimblet to the Tallahassee lottery offices to accept a lump sum of $1.6 million, described it as a &ldquo;blessing.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Gimblet didn&rsquo;t hesitate to finance the cancer treatment, saying she just &ldquo;did what I had to do,&rdquo; with Jackson adding that she would &ldquo;just have to keep loving her,&rdquo; as a means to try and repay the kindness.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">+-</span></p>]]></description>
   <author><![CDATA[Garrison Hardie]]></author>
   <enclosure url="https://app.dropwave.io/episode/4dbee7a4-0428-4cf2-aeb0-40bf35f52577/daily-news-brief-for-friday-april-28th-2023.mp3" length="760" type="audio/mp3"/>
   <guid isPermaLink="false"><![CDATA[4dbee7a4-0428-4cf2-aeb0-40bf35f52577]]></guid>
   <pubDate>Fri, 28 Apr 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
   <source url=""><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></source>
   <itunes:author><![CDATA[Garrison Hardie]]></itunes:author>
   <itunes:image href="https://assets-cdn2.dropwave.io/2ab40ac0-e99d-4f25-a6d2-541d2c9b290a/cover-art/hUZu1H9lrRY0wXg66WHC8eLwYBA3hbRNTAHQmHt2.png"/>
   <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
   <itunes:duration>760</itunes:duration>
   <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
  
  </item><item>
   <title><![CDATA[Daily News Brief for Thursday, April 27th, 2023 [Daily News Brief]]]></title>
   <link>https://app.dropwave.io/episode/b0ae4f18-e5ad-48c5-8f38-9355608404b3/daily-news-brief-for-thursday-april-27th-2023.mp3</link>
   <description><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">This is Garrison Hardie with your CrossPolitic Daily News Brief for Thursday, April 27th, 2023.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://theconversation.com/ukraine-war-pentagon-leaks-paint-gloomy-picture-of-long-war-that-cant-be-won-but-must-not-be-lost-203698"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://theconversation.com/ukraine-war-pentagon-leaks-paint-gloomy-picture-of-long-war-that-cant-be-won-but-must-not-be-lost-203698</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Ukraine war: Pentagon leaks paint gloomy picture of long war that can&rsquo;t be won but must not be lost</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Classified Pentagon documents leaked last week paint a grim picture of the trajectory of the war in Ukraine. While it may well be the most significant national security breach since the Snowden leaks of US National Security Agency material a decade ago, the fact that the leak occurred is almost certainly more significant than what was revealed about Ukraine.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The leak reveals how apparently easy it was for a low-level employee on a US military base to obtain and then share highly sensitive US government information. By comparison, the contents of the documents on Ukraine leaked are far less explosive in nature &ndash; they mostly confirm existing battlefield assessments that cast doubt, in the eyes of US intelligence officials, on any major breakthroughs in a widely expected Ukrainian spring offensive.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The key shortfalls on the Ukrainian side &ndash; artillery pieces and munitions, as well as air defences &ndash; have been well known for some time. What has also been obvious for some time, and was reconfirmed in some of the leaked documents, is that Ukraine has been mostly relying on Soviet-era artillery equipment and stocks of ammunition have begun to run dry.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">At the same time, western equipment has been slow to be delivered and training of Ukrainian forces has taken time. And the western capacity to produce shells in excess of current Ukrainian consumption has yet to be built.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Add to that delays in training and equipping the troops needed for a counter-offensive and the likelihood of well-entrenched Russian defences. The low expectations of at best modest territorial gains in a Ukrainian spring offensive do not come as a surprise.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The equally limited gains that Russia has made over the past several months of its offensive, including around the still contested city of Bakhmut should serve as an indication of what is and is not possible after more than a year of war. Similarly, the protracted battle over Soledar back in January this year already gave a glimpse at how costly even minimal and strategically insignificant gains in this war have become.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The flipside of the US assessment that any Ukrainian counter-offensive is unlikely to constitute a turning point in the war is that the fighting is likely to continue beyond this year. In some estimates it could last well beyond that.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">There are no signs that either side is willing to give up. US estimates of casualties &ndash; among the leaks from the Pentagon &ndash; indicate more than 40,000 Russian soldiers killed in action over the past year and an additional 180,000 wounded. On the Ukrainian side, the figures are lower &ndash; with 17,500 likely dead and 113,500 wounded troops &ndash; but still significant. Both countries now have tightened conscription rules and procedures in another sign that they are readying themselves for intensifying battles.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Equally important from a Ukrainian perspective is continuing support from its western partners. Despite the logistical difficulties of ramping up defence industry outputs and deliveries to Ukraine, there is no indication that supplies will fall critically short and expose Ukraine to the risk of major battlefield defeats. This is partly because Moscow also cannot muster the superior military capabilities that would be needed for inflicting such defeats on Kyiv.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Ultimately, both sides are likely to match each other&rsquo;s increases in capability over time and the current stalemate will continue, albeit at a higher level of mutual attrition. And each increase in capability, however slight, will boost the conviction that this war remains winnable.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The Pentagon leaks have cast doubt on such assumptions, but also confirmed that neither Washington nor Kyiv are contemplating losing the war on the battlefield or the negotiation table. Time will tell whether this is a sustainable objective &ndash; and at what cost.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/policy/courts/disney-sues-desantis-alleged-campaign-weaponize-government-power-against-company"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/policy/courts/disney-sues-desantis-alleged-campaign-weaponize-government-power-against-company</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Disney sues DeSantis over alleged 'campaign to weaponize government power' against company</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Disney has filed a lawsuit against Gov. Ron DeSantis (R-FL) and members of the new Central Florida Tourism Oversight District alleging government power has been weaponized against them.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">In the lawsuit filed in the U.S. District Court for the Northern District of Florida, the company alleges a "relentless campaign to weaponize government power against Disney in retaliation for expressing a political viewpoint unpopular with certain State officials."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Disney argues the state and DeSantis have violated its First Amendment right to speech by working to strip control of the special taxing district encompassing the Walt Disney World Resort from the company after Disney spoke out against Florida's Parental Rights in Education bill.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The lawsuit was filed shortly after the Central Florida Tourism Oversight District unanimously approved a resolution to declare an agreement designed to undercut the new board's power as void. Disney cites the action as the "latest strike" in the state's string of "retaliatory" and "unconstitutional" actions.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The lawsuit also argues the state violated the contract clause in the U.S. Constitution by working to void an agreement Disney made with the previous board, which undercut the power of the new DeSantis-appointed district board. Lawyers for Disney also say the state violated the takings clause in the U.S. Constitution by allegedly taking property rights from the company "without payment of just compensation."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The fifth cause of action Disney makes in the lawsuit accuses the state of violating the due process clause of the 14th Amendment by arbitrating "the Contracts without any rational basis and for only impermissible reasons."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The board had cited violations of necessary procedures outlined in the state's sunshine laws as reason to declare the agreement as void.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Disney is seeking to have the two laws restructuring the former Reedy Creek Improvement District declared as "unlawful and unenforceable," along with legally upholding the agreement between Disney and the former district made on Feb. 8, which stripped the new district of most of its power.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The entertainment giant had maintained full autonomy over the district since its creation in 1967, but legislation signed into law in February gave the state power over the district.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://justthenews.com/politics-policy/nebraska-becomes-27th-state-pass-constitutional-carry"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://justthenews.com/politics-policy/nebraska-becomes-27th-state-pass-constitutional-carry</span></a></p>
<p><strong>Nebraska becomes 27th state to pass constitutional carry</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Nebraska Gov. Jim Pillen signed constitutional carry into law on Tuesday, making it the 27th state to add to the constitutional carry majority.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The law allows law-abiding Nebraskans who are 21 and up to be able to carry a concealed handgun without a permit.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">It will go into effect 90 days after the end of the legislative session, which is scheduled for June 9.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The bill is backed by the NRA.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">"Today, Nebraska joined 26 other states whose constituents and leaders recognize that law-abiding Americans should not have to ask for special government permission and pay additional fees in order to exercise their rights outside of the home,"&nbsp; Randy Kozuch, executive director of the NRA's legislative lobby arm told Fox News in a statement.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://www.dailyfetched.com/satanic-church-founder-sentenced-to-18-months-in-prison-for-operating-unlicensed-money-transmitting-business/"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.dailyfetched.com/satanic-church-founder-sentenced-to-18-months-in-prison-for-operating-unlicensed-money-transmitting-business/</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Satanic Church Founder Sentenced to 18 Months in Prison for Operating Unlicensed Money-Transmitting Business</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Self-described satanist Aria DiMezzo, 35, was also ordered to pay a fine of $5,000 and to forfeit more than $14,000 along with 1.93 bitcoins.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">According to investigators, between June 2020 and January 2021, DiMezzo charged a fee to exchange mostly U.S. dollars for Bitcoin, recruiting customers on websites.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Customers sent DiMezzo money through bank accounts to the Reformed Satanic Church.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">DiMezzo sold more than $3 million worth of virtual currency but did not register the operation as a money-transmitting business, failing to comply with mandatory regulations.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">According to investigators, DiMezzo failed to file currency transaction reports for exchanges of over $10,000 or suspicious activity reports for transactions over $2,000.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Prosecutors said DiMezzo worked with a man named Ian Freeman to sell virtual currency to customers, paying Freeman a percentage of the profits.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Freeman was found guilty of operating an unlicensed money-transmitting business, laundering over $10 million in proceeds of romance scams, and tax evasion.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">In 2020, Republicans in one New Hampshire county nominated DiMezzo for sheriff, whose campaign slogan disparaged the police.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">At the time, DiMezzo said, as law enforcement, any of his deputies &ldquo;would be fired on the spot, and perhaps charged with crimes, for any brutality or misconduct.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">DiMezzo serves as the high priest and founder of the Reformed Satanic Church.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The church doesn&rsquo;t believe Satan exists, DiMezzo claimed, but instead &ldquo;stands for individualism and voluntarism, and opposes the god of the day,&rdquo; which he described as the state.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://www.theblaze.com/news/let-s-go-lawsuit-students-sue-after-school-forces-them-to-remove-let-s-go-brandon-sweatshirts"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.theblaze.com/news/let-s-go-lawsuit-students-sue-after-school-forces-them-to-remove-let-s-go-brandon-sweatshirts</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>'Let's go, lawsuit':&nbsp; Students sue after school forces them to remove 'Let's Go Brandon' sweatshirts</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Two students are suing a Michigan school district for viewpoint discrimination after school employees forbade them wearing sweatshirts opposing President Biden, the students' legal team announced in a statement Tuesday.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">"These students should not only be allowed to express their political beliefs, but should be encouraged to do so," FIRE attorney Harrison Rosenthal said in the statement.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">"America&rsquo;s students must be free to exercise their constitutional rights, not just learn about them."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The case stems from multiple incidents in February 2022 and May 2022 at Tri County Middle School in Howard City, Michigan. School employees ordered two students to "remove 'Let's Go Brandon' sweatshirts despite allowing students to wear apparel with other political and social messages," the complaint alleges.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">FIRE attorneys representing the students say the incidents are "part of a pattern of political favoritism by the school district." They add that during a field day, an administrator ordered a student to stop wearing a Trump flag as a cape, but permitted students to wear gay pride flags in the same manner.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Though the phrase originated as a means for mimicking a "f*** Joe Biden" chant, the phrase "let's go Brandon" contains no profane language. Therefore, FIRE attorneys reason, the school's dress code barring profane clothing does not apply.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Howard City is in west central Michigan about 35 miles from Grand Rapids. It has a population of approximately 1,967.</span></p>]]></description>
   <author><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></author>
   <enclosure url="https://app.dropwave.io/episode/b0ae4f18-e5ad-48c5-8f38-9355608404b3/daily-news-brief-for-thursday-april-27th-2023.mp3" length="619" type="audio/mp3"/>
   <guid isPermaLink="false"><![CDATA[b0ae4f18-e5ad-48c5-8f38-9355608404b3]]></guid>
   <pubDate>Thu, 27 Apr 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
   <source url=""><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></source>
   <itunes:author><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></itunes:author>
   <itunes:image href="https://assets-cdn2.dropwave.io/2ab40ac0-e99d-4f25-a6d2-541d2c9b290a/cover-art/hUZu1H9lrRY0wXg66WHC8eLwYBA3hbRNTAHQmHt2.png"/>
   <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
   <itunes:duration>619</itunes:duration>
   <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
  
  </item><item>
   <title><![CDATA[Daily News Brief for Wednesday, April 26th, 2023 [Daily News Brief]]]></title>
   <link>https://app.dropwave.io/episode/e312eefe-8699-408e-8a15-1c6dca1221f8/daily-news-brief-for-wednesday-april-26th-2023.mp3</link>
   <description><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">This is Garrison Hardie with your CrossPolitic Daily News Brief for Wednesday, April 26th, 2023.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p><br /><br /></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Before we get to the news today&hellip; how about a little on this day in history?</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">On this day in history&hellip; April 26th.</span></p>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">1514 Copernicus makes his 1st observations of Saturn</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">1564 William Shakespeare is baptized in Stratford-upon-Avon, Warwickshire, England</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">1607 Jamestown expedition makes first landing in America at a place named Cape Henry, in what would become Virginia, but they quickly depart for a better site</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">1654 Jews are expelled from Brazil - this was known as the &ldquo;Capitulation Protocol&rdquo; -According to the terms of the capitulation protocol of January 26, 1654, Portugal decreed that Jewish and Dutch settlers had three months to leave Brazil. Approximately 150 Jewish families of Portuguese descent fled the Brazilian city of Recife, in the state of Pernambuco. By September, twenty-three of these refugees had established the first community of Jews in New Amsterdam.</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">1755 1st Russian university opens in Moscow</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">1859 Dan Sickles is acquitted of murder on grounds of temporary insanity - 1st time this defense used successfully in the US</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">1865 Confederate General J E Johnston surrenders remaining forces to Union General William Sherman at Bennett Place in Durham, North Carolina, ending the US Civil War</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">1904 General Kuroko leads the Japanese Army against the large Russian force at the Yalu river during the Russo-Japanese War</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">1968 Students seize administration building at Ohio State - In 1968, two months before Martin Luther King's assassination, students seized the administration building in a dispute over the right of the campus newspaper to criticize the policies of the university president.</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">1982 Argentina surrenders to Great Britain on South Georgia Island, near the Falkland Islands - The Falklands War was a ten-week undeclared war between Argentina and the United Kingdom in 1982 over two British dependent territories in the South Atlantic: the Falkland Islands and its territorial dependency, South Georgia and the South Sandwich Islands. The conflict began on 2 April, when Argentina invaded and occupied the Falkland Islands, followed by the invasion of South Georgia the next day. On 5 April, the British government dispatched a naval task force to engage the Argentine Navy and Air Force before making an amphibious assault on the islands. The conflict lasted 74 days and ended with an Argentine surrender on 14 June, returning the islands to British control. In total, 649 Argentine military personnel, 255 British military personnel, and three Falkland Islanders were killed during the hostilities. The conflict lasted 74 days and ended with an Argentine surrender on 14 June, returning the islands to British control.</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">1982 Rod Stewart is mugged, gunman steals his $50,000 Porsche on Hollywood Boulevard, Los Angeles, California</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">1986 World's worst nuclear disaster: 4th reactor at Chernobyl nuclear power station in USSR explodes, 31 die, radioactive contamination reaches much of Western Europe</span></li>
</ul>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">And that&hellip; was on this day in history.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://www.theblaze.com/news/city-of-chicago-forced-to-rehire-pay-lost-wages-to-workers-fired-for-refusing-covid-vaccine-mandate"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.theblaze.com/news/city-of-chicago-forced-to-rehire-pay-lost-wages-to-workers-fired-for-refusing-covid-vaccine-mandate</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>City of Chicago forced to rehire, pay lost wages to workers fired for refusing COVID vaccine mandate</strong></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">A Chicago judge recently ordered the city to rehire and pay lost wages to workers who were fired for refusing to comply with Democratic Mayor Lori Lightfoot's 2021 COVID vaccination mandate.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">On April 19, administrative law Judge Anna Hamburg-Gal ruled that Chicago violated the Illinois Public Labor Relations Act by failing and refusing to bargain in good faith over COVID vaccine requirements for city workers.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The city was ordered to "make whole" unionized workers who refused the mandate and lost pay and benefits. The affected employees will also receive 7% annual interest on lost wages.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The order applies to city workers, including carpenters, bricklayers, plumbers, electricians, machinists, and operating engineers, represented by trade unions or by the American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The judge's ruling does not affect police officers. However, the Fraternal Order of Police has its own pending case before the state board.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Lightfoot stated in 2022 that 16 police officers were placed on no-pay status after failing to abide by the vaccine mandate.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">In response to the judge's recent ruling, AFSCME spokesperson Anders Lindall told the Chicago Sun-Times, "We think it's a strong decision and favorable for worker rights generally."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">A Chicago Federation of Labor spokesperson stated that the judge's order "defends the rights of workers to have a say in their workplace through collective bargaining."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Lightfoot announced in 2021 that all city employees must be fully vaccinated by October and warned that those who refused would face "consequences."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">According to Hamburg-Gal's ruling, "multiple" city employees were placed on non-paid leave for missing the October deadline, and some were terminated.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">In a statement to Fox News Digital, a spokesperson for the mayor's office said, "The record before the Administrative Law Judge tells a completely different story. Yesterday's ruling was an erroneous decision that does not follow the law, facts nor importantly the science. We are currently reviewing the ruling and evaluating next steps."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Lightfoot, the first Chicago mayor to lose a re-election bid in 40 years, will be replaced by Democrat Brandon Johnson on May 15.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://www.theepochtimes.com/fbi-faces-growing-pressure-to-release-nashville-school-shooters-manifesto_5216890.html?utm_source=partner&amp;utm_campaign=BonginoReport"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.theepochtimes.com/fbi-faces-growing-pressure-to-release-nashville-school-shooters-manifesto_5216890.html?utm_source=partner&amp;utm_campaign=BonginoReport</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>Officials Face Growing Pressure to Release Nashville School Shooter&rsquo;s Manifesto</strong></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Law enforcement officials are facing increasing pressure to release the manifesto of Nashville, Tennessee, school shooter Audrey Hale, with a U.S. lawmaker accusing the federal government of delaying its release.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Local officials said that Hale, a female who used transgender pronouns, left behind a suicide note, journals, and other materials. However, none of that has been released to the public, and a motive hasn&rsquo;t been publicly identified in the case.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">MNPD &ldquo;is leading this investigation &hellip; any and all information that may or may not be released will be at the direction of MNPD,&rdquo; an FBI spokesperson told The Epoch Times on April 24.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">MNPD officials didn&rsquo;t respond by press time to a request by The Epoch Times for comment.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Rep. Tim Burchett (R-Tenn.) and several other Republicans have also called for the document to be released to the public.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The shooter&rsquo;s notes &ldquo;could maybe tell us a little bit about what&rsquo;s going on inside of her head,&rdquo; Burchett told the New York Post. &ldquo;I think that would answer a lot of questions.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Meanwhile, Rep. Andy Ogles (R-Tenn.) told the paper that if the documents don&rsquo;t make it to the public, &ldquo;then we need to investigate why.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Hale, 28, was a former student at The Covenant School, where she fatally shot three children and three adults on March 27.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Hale was killed by police within minutes of the first call of an active shooter.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Since the shooting, a range of conservative commentators have publicly called for Hale&rsquo;s manifesto to be made public and have accused the federal government of delaying its release as part of a coverup to keep the public from knowing about the dangers of transgenderism. About a week after the Nashville mass shooting, a 19-year-old male who reportedly identified as female was arrested in Colorado with detailed plans for several school shootings.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Days after the shooting, Nashville Police Chief John Drake said that Hale was suffering from mental health issues and was under a doctor&rsquo;s care for an unspecified emotional disorder. Her parents didn&rsquo;t know that she had multiple weapons hidden in the house, Drake added.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The Metro Nashville Police Department said in a statement earlier this month that Hale&rsquo;s writings would be &ldquo;under careful review by the MNPD and the FBI&rsquo;s Behavioral Analysis Unit based in Quantico, Virginia,&rdquo; while the &ldquo;motive for Hale&rsquo;s actions has not been established and remains under investigation by the Homicide Unit in consultation with the FBI&rsquo;s Behavioral Analysis Unit.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">From that statement, it isn&rsquo;t clear when&mdash;or if&mdash;Hale&rsquo;s writings will be released. But the department said that Hale &ldquo;considered the actions of other mass murderers,&rdquo; without elaborating.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">FBI officials didn&rsquo;t respond by press time to a request by The Epoch Times for comment.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://thepostmillennial.com/antifa-members-arrested-after-allegedly-attacking-protestors-outside-of-fort-worth-family-friendly-drag-show?utm_campaign=64487"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://thepostmillennial.com/antifa-members-arrested-after-allegedly-attacking-protestors-outside-of-fort-worth-family-friendly-drag-show?utm_campaign=64487</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>Antifa members arrested after allegedly attacking protestors, police outside of Fort Worth &lsquo;family-friendly&rsquo; drag show</strong></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">On Sunday, three members of Antifa were arrested outside of a Fort Worth, Texas family-friendly drag show after allegedly attacking protestors of the event.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Samuel Fowlkes was arrested on charges of resisting arrest, search, or transport, assaulting a peace officer, evading arrest or detention, and four counts of assault causing bodily injury, according to booking documents.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://twitter.com/i/status/1650261782542315520"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://twitter.com/i/status/1650261782542315520</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> - Play Video 0:00-0:25</span></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">What you just heard in that audio clip, was another antifa member being arrested after they attempted to &ldquo;de-arrest&rdquo; a fellow antifa member from the back of a police cruiser.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Fowlkes, who is being held on $22,500 bail, has been revealed to identify as nonbinary.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Meghan Grant was arrested on charges of resisting arrest, search, or transport, and interfering with public duties.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Christopher Guillott was arrested on charges of assaulting a peace officer and interfering with public duties.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The incident occurred outside Fort Brewery and Pizza, which held the drag brunch on Sunday. In an event description, the brewery stated, "This is the perfect event to celebrate a special occasion with your friends, family, or coworkers, or to simply indulge in a fun-filled day out with your loved ones."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The three arrested are reportedly part of the Elm Fork John Brown Gun Club, members of which are frequently armed at protests and riots. The group is currently advertising its CashApp account on Twitter to raise bail for the arrested members.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">A CashApp spokesperson told The Post Millennial, "Customer security is our number one priority. Our team takes all security concerns seriously and will take action when appropriate."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The group claimed that the arrested members were "trying to aid an injured drag defender."&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Protect Texas Kids, one of the groups protesting the event, said that Antifa members "were outside assaulting police officers and macing members of [the New Columbia Movement] who were peacefully praying.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">On to politics&hellip;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/news/white-house/biden-will-veto-mccarthys-debt-limit-package"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/news/white-house/biden-will-veto-mccarthys-debt-limit-package</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>Biden will veto McCarthy's debt limit package, White House announces</strong></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">President Joe Biden will veto House Speaker Kevin McCarthy's (R-CA) debt limit bill, should it pass both chambers of Congress.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Biden's Office of Management and Budget released a Statement of Administration Policy Tuesday morning indicating that the administration "strongly opposes the Limit, Save, Grow Act of 2023, which is a reckless attempt to extract extreme concessions as a condition for the United States simply paying the bills it has already incurred."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">"The President has been clear that he will not accept such attempts at hostage-taking. House Republicans must take default off the table and address the debt limit without demands and conditions, just as the Congress did three times during the prior Administration," the statement continued. "The bill stands in stark contrast to the President&rsquo;s vision for the economy. The President&rsquo;s Budget invests in America, lowers costs for families, grows the economy, and reduces the deficit by nearly $3 trillion by asking the wealthy and large corporations to pay their fair share. Therefore, if the President were presented with the Limit, Save, Grow Act of 2023, he would veto it."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://thepostmillennial.com/tucker-carlsons-executive-producer-follows-him-in-exit-from-fox-report?utm_campaign=64487"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://thepostmillennial.com/tucker-carlsons-executive-producer-follows-him-in-exit-from-fox-report?utm_campaign=64487</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>Tucker Carlson&rsquo;s executive producer follows him in exit from Fox</strong></span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Tucker Carlson's executive producer Justin Wells is also leaving Fox News, according to Jack Posobiec.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The announcement of Carlson's leaving was made on Monday, after his last show was on Friday, April 21. Fox News Tonight will now feature rotating personalities as an interim show until a new host is named.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Carlson's departure comes just weeks after a former booker, Abby Grossberg, sued Fox, citing "vile sexist stereotypes" working for Carlson. Grossberg claims that she was fired after filing a lawsuit that claimed Fox lawyers coerced her into giving misleading testimony in the Dominion case.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Fox maintains that she was fired for divulging privileged information.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The decision to part ways with Carlson came less than a week after the broadcaster and Dominion Voting Systems reached a $787 million settlement, although his show was not a main focus of Dominion's lawsuit.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Carlson's show was frequently the top-rated show on cable news, often surpassing 4.5 million viewers per episode.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The show premiered in November 2016 and took over the coveted 8 pm EST time slot in 2017. Fox News Media is currently the number one network in all of cable and reaches nearly 200 million people each month.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p><br /><br /><br /><br /><br /><br /><br /></p>]]></description>
   <author><![CDATA[Garrison Hardie]]></author>
   <enclosure url="https://app.dropwave.io/episode/e312eefe-8699-408e-8a15-1c6dca1221f8/daily-news-brief-for-wednesday-april-26th-2023.mp3" length="891" type="audio/mp3"/>
   <guid isPermaLink="false"><![CDATA[e312eefe-8699-408e-8a15-1c6dca1221f8]]></guid>
   <pubDate>Wed, 26 Apr 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
   <source url=""><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></source>
   <itunes:author><![CDATA[Garrison Hardie]]></itunes:author>
   <itunes:image href="https://assets-cdn2.dropwave.io/2ab40ac0-e99d-4f25-a6d2-541d2c9b290a/cover-art/hUZu1H9lrRY0wXg66WHC8eLwYBA3hbRNTAHQmHt2.png"/>
   <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
   <itunes:duration>891</itunes:duration>
   <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
  
  </item><item>
   <title><![CDATA[Daily News Brief for Tuesday, April 25th, 2023 [Daily News Brief]]]></title>
   <link>https://app.dropwave.io/episode/280988c9-bb85-4503-84b7-452622bdf242/daily-news-brief-for-tuesday-april-25th-2023.mp3</link>
   <description><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">This is Garrison Hardie with your CrossPolitic Daily News Brief for Tuesday, April 25th, 2023.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Dime Payments</strong></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Dime Payments is a Christian owned processing payment business. Every business needs a payment process system, so please go to https://dimepayments.com/flf and sign your business up. Working with them supports us. They wont cancel you, like Stripe canceled President Trump. They wont cancel you, like Mailchimp canceled the Babylon Bee. Check them out. At least have a phone call and tell them that CrossPolitic sent you. Go to https://dimepayments.com/flf.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://thepostmillennial.com/breaking-tucker-carlson-leaves-fox-news-as-they-agree-to-part-ways?utm_campaign=64487"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://thepostmillennial.com/breaking-tucker-carlson-leaves-fox-news-as-they-agree-to-part-ways?utm_campaign=64487</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Tucker Carlson leaves Fox News as they 'agree to part ways'</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Fox News Media and Tucker Carlson have agreed to part ways, according to a statement released on Monday.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The statement reads: "Mr. Carlson&rsquo;s last program was Friday April 21st. Fox News Tonight will air live at 8 PM/ET starting this evening as an interim show helmed by rotating FOX News personalities until a new host is named.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Carlson's show was frequently the top-rated show on cable news, often surpassing 4.5 million viewers per episode.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The show premiered in November 2016, and took over the coveted 8 pm EST time slot in 2017.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The decision to part ways with Carlson comes less than a week after the broadcaster and Dominion Voting Systems reached a $787 million settlement. Carlson's show was not a main focus of Dominion's lawsuit.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Carlson's departure comes weeks after a former booker at the show, Abby Grossberg, sued Fox, citing "vile sexist stereotypes" working for Carlson. NBC reports that "Grossberg was fired in March after she filed a lawsuit claiming that Fox lawyers coerced her into giving misleading testimony in the Dominion case and that she was being made a scapegoat for the network&rsquo;s 2020 election coverage. Fox says she was fired for divulging privileged information."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Grossberg's lawyer has since said that his client has a "uniquely strong" case against Fox News.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Several former Fox News hosts reacted to the news of Carlson leaving the network, including Megyn Kelly, who said "Good for Tucker. Trust me, he doesn't need them."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Dan Bongino, who also split ways with the network last week, simply tweeted "WTF!" in response.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The media shakeup continued&hellip;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://thepostmillennial.com/breaking-don-lemon-terminated-by-cnn?utm_campaign=64487"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://thepostmillennial.com/breaking-don-lemon-terminated-by-cnn?utm_campaign=64487</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Don Lemon TERMINATED by CNN</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">On Monday, Don Lemon revealed to his Twitter followers that he has been terminated by CNN.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">"I was informed this morning by my agent that I have been terminated by CNN," Lemon&rsquo;s statement began. "I am stunned. After 17 years at CNN I would have thought that someone in management would have had the decency to tell me directly."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">In response to Lemon&rsquo;s statement, CNN said, "Don Lemon&rsquo;s statement about this morning&rsquo;s events is inaccurate. He was offered an opportunity to meet with management but instead released a statement on Twitter."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Most recently, Lemon was in hot water over comments made about Nikki Haley, being forced to undergo formal training and absent from CNN This Morning for several days.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">In Late February, Lemon said of presidential candidate Nikki Haley saying politicians over the age of 75 should undergo mental competency tests - saying she Nikki Haley&nbsp; wasn&rsquo;t in her prime.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Lemon went on to say women were in their prime "in their 20s and 30s and maybe 40s."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The next week though, Lemon didn&rsquo;t return to the program until Wednesday, undergoing "formal training" as to why his comments were wrong. During this time, female CNN staffers threatened to quit if Lemon was allowed back.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">During Lemon&rsquo;s absence from the morning show, CNN This Morning&rsquo;s ratings went up by five percent.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">In September, Lemon was removed from his long-held primetime slot to the morning show.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://thepostmillennial.com/nbcuniversal-ceo-ousted-after-having-inappropriate-relationship-with-coworker?utm_campaign=64487"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://thepostmillennial.com/nbcuniversal-ceo-ousted-after-having-inappropriate-relationship-with-coworker?utm_campaign=64487</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>NBCUniversal CEO ousted after having 'inappropriate relationship' with coworker</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The CEO of NBCUniversal Jeff Shell has been ousted from the company after an investigation revealed that he was having an 'inappropriate relationship' with a female employee at the company.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Shell, who made $21.6 million per year, risked his high earnings by going against company policy and admitting to executives that he was having an "inappropriate relationship" with another woman at the company. NBCUniversal made the announcement that Shell had been terminated in an email sent to employees on Sunday, according to CNBC.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The findings were revealed when an outside company was hired to investigate a complaint against Shell. Shell is currently married to Laura Fay Shell, who previously worked for the City of Los Angeles, Daily Mail reports.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&nbsp;</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">"Today is my last day as CEO of NBCUniversal. I had an inappropriate relationship with a woman in the company, which I deeply regret," Shell said in a statement. "I'm truly sorry I let my Comcast and NBCUniversal colleagues down, they are the most talented people in the business and the opportunity to work with them the last 19 years has been a privilege."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">In 2020, the vice president of NBCUniversal, Ron Meyer, was ousted from the company after improperly disclosing that he was ordered to pay a settlement to a woman he reportedly had a "consensual affair" with. Shell is the second executive to be ousted in recent years.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Lots of ousting lately&hellip; Now this&hellip;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://townhall.com/tipsheet/saraharnold/2023/04/23/canada-could-supply-us-with-abortion-pills-if-courts-ban-it-n2622298"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://townhall.com/tipsheet/saraharnold/2023/04/23/canada-could-supply-us-with-abortion-pills-if-courts-ban-it-n2622298</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Canada Suggests It Would Provide Women With the Abortion Pill If the U.S. Bans It</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The Canadian government said it "would work to provide" Americans access to the abortion pill, mifepristone, if the controversial drug gets banned in the U.S.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Families Minister Karina Gould said it concerns her that U.S. laws are looking to "criminalize" women seeking access to reproductive healthcare.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">On Friday, the Supreme Court paused a federal judge's order to restrict access to mifepristone after the 5th Circuit Court overlooked a case to take the dangerous drug off the market after Texas Judge Matthew Kacsmaryk ruled that it should not be allowed arguing that the FDA expedited the process to "green light elective chemical abortions on a wide scale."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Last year before the Supreme Court overturned Roe v. Wade, Gould said that Americans would be able to get an abortion in Canada, which is typically less regulated than it is in the U.S. and available at later stages of pregnancy.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://www.dailywire.com/news/newsom-directs-national-guard-to-combat-san-franciscos-fentanyl-crisis"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.dailywire.com/news/newsom-directs-national-guard-to-combat-san-franciscos-fentanyl-crisis</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Newsom Directs National Guard To Combat San Francisco&rsquo;s Fentanyl Crisis</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Governor Gavin Newsom (D-CA) directed the state National Guard and California Highway Patrol to help in the fight against fentanyl trafficking in San Francisco.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">As part of a new partnership, the agencies are tasked with identifying personnel and resources to assist San Francisco following a 41% spike in fentanyl overdose deaths in the first few months of this year.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&ldquo;We are providing more law enforcement resources and personnel to crack down on crime linked to the fentanyl crisis, holding the poison peddlers accountable, and increasing law enforcement presence to improve public safety and public confidence in San Francisco,&rdquo; Newsom said in a statement on Friday.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Newsom&rsquo;s office said the collaboration, which also includes the San Francisco Police Department and and the San Francisco District Attorney&rsquo;s Office, will be focused on drug suppliers and traffickers rather than seeking to criminalize those struggling with substance abuse in a city that has recorded several hundred accidental overdose deaths annually in recent years.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The agreement will &ldquo;lead to the formation of a new collaborative operation between all four agencies focused on dismantling fentanyl trafficking and disrupting the supply of the deadly drug in the city by holding the operators of large-scale drug trafficking operations accountable,&rdquo; the governor&rsquo;s office said.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Newsom paid a visit on Wednesday to San Francisco, a city he once led as mayor, and surveyed the Tenderloin neighborhood, which has been hit hard by crime and the fentanyl crisis. The trip took place a couple weeks after San Francisco Mayor London Breed requested federal assistance to arrest and prosecute drug dealers while the city contends with a short-staffed police department, according to local ABC affiliate KGO.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">During Newsom&rsquo;s visit to Tenderloin, activist JJ Smith pressed the governor on what he is doing to stop the fentanyl crisis, according to CBS News Bay Area. JJ Smith recalled Newsom saying he is working on the issue, a response which the activist felt was inadequate.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Newsom, who is widely seen as a top future presidential contender for the Democrats, says he has already invested more than $1 billion to tackle the opioid and fentanyl crisis in California. His new budget request seeks another $96 million in funding to tackle the problem.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Now for my favorite topic&hellip; sports!</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://dailycaller.com/2023/04/23/phil-jackson-nba-bubble-social-justice/"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://dailycaller.com/2023/04/23/phil-jackson-nba-bubble-social-justice/</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Legendary Coach Criticizes NBA For Being Too Political</strong></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Legendary coach Phil Jackson was trending on the Internet Saturday due to comments he made criticizing the NBA on the podcast &ldquo;Tetragrammaton with Rick Rubin.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">During the April 5 podcast, the 11-time NBA champion said he stopped watching games during the 2020 NBA Bubble in Orlando because the league had become too political.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The Orlando games were held during the COVID-19 pandemic and came on the heels of George Floyd&rsquo;s death in police custody and subsequent protests in May.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=nAoJmHekKdM"><span style="font-weight: 400;" data-rich-links="{&quot;fple-t&quot;:&quot;Legendary NBA coach Phil Jackson slams league for becoming too political&quot;,&quot;fple-u&quot;:&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=nAoJmHekKdM&quot;,&quot;fple-mt&quot;:null,&quot;type&quot;:&quot;first-party-link&quot;}">Legendary NBA coach Phil Jackson slams league for becoming too political</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;">-Play 0:12-0:32</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Jackson referred to social justice slogans the NBA allowed players to wear on the backs of their uniforms in 2020. The slogans included &ldquo;Black Lives Matter,&rdquo; &ldquo;Freedom,&rdquo; &ldquo;Justice,&rdquo; &ldquo;Enough,&rdquo; and &ldquo;Power to the People,&rdquo; among others.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Jackson said he didn&rsquo;t see how these gestures made an impact and commented on how past athletes kept their political views to themselves.&nbsp; &ldquo;Bill Bradley was a senator, a number of baseball players have been representatives and senators. . .But their politics stay out of the game. It doesn&rsquo;t need to be there.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Jackson, 77, played in the NBA for twelve seasons and coached for 20. He retired from coaching in 2011.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>]]></description>
   <author><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></author>
   <enclosure url="https://app.dropwave.io/episode/280988c9-bb85-4503-84b7-452622bdf242/daily-news-brief-for-tuesday-april-25th-2023.mp3" length="659" type="audio/mp3"/>
   <guid isPermaLink="false"><![CDATA[280988c9-bb85-4503-84b7-452622bdf242]]></guid>
   <pubDate>Tue, 25 Apr 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
   <source url=""><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></source>
   <itunes:author><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></itunes:author>
   <itunes:image href="https://assets-cdn2.dropwave.io/2ab40ac0-e99d-4f25-a6d2-541d2c9b290a/cover-art/hUZu1H9lrRY0wXg66WHC8eLwYBA3hbRNTAHQmHt2.png"/>
   <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
   <itunes:duration>659</itunes:duration>
   <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
  
  </item><item>
   <title><![CDATA[Daily News Brief for Friday, April 21st, 2023 [Daily News Brief]]]></title>
   <link>https://app.dropwave.io/episode/12309968-90d1-49f3-b539-6422ee581004/daily-news-brief-for-friday-april-21st-2023.mp3</link>
   <description><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">This is Garrison Hardie with your CrossPolitic Daily News Brief for Friday, April 21st, 2023.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>CrossPolitic Email List:</strong></span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Are you subscribed to our CrossPolitic email list? If you&rsquo;re not you really should be. Being subscribed to our email list means you won&rsquo;t miss any updates about CrossPolitic or the Fight Laugh Feast Network! You&rsquo;ll hear about what&rsquo;s on the schedule for the week, live events, conference updates, Rowdy Christian Merch, updates from other shows within the Fight Laugh Feast Network, and you&rsquo;ll hear from sponsors on the show, as they seek to take dominion for God&rsquo;s Kingdom in the business world. To subscribe, simply enter your email address at the bottom of the page at fightlaughfeast.com. Again, that&rsquo;s fightlaughfeast.com.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/policy/space/spacexs-largest-rocket-explodes-after-launch"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/policy/space/spacexs-largest-rocket-explodes-after-launch</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>SpaceX's largest rocket ever built explodes four minutes after launch</strong></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">SpaceX's Starship, the largest rocket ever launched, exploded four minutes after takeoff.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The spaceship exploded above the Gulf of Mexico shortly after takeoff, failing to achieve its ambitious goals, according to the New York Times. However, the explosion was only described as "A setback for Elon Musk and SpaceX, but not a fatal one."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">SpaceX described the event as a "rapid unscheduled disassembly before stage separation" on Twitter as the launch and short flight played out.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">SpaceX still saw the test flight as a partial success, with some employees busting open a bottle of champagne amid cheers of &ldquo;Go Starship!&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://www.dailyfetched.com/dom-lemon-loses-it-on-gop-candidate-gets-spooked-by-whats-said-in-earpiece/"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.dailyfetched.com/dom-lemon-loses-it-on-gop-candidate-gets-spooked-by-whats-said-in-earpiece/</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>Don Lemon LOSES IT on GOP Candidate</strong></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Business executive and the author of &ldquo;Woke Inc,&rdquo; Vivek Ramaswamy, who is vying for the 2024 presidential slot, appeared on &ldquo;CNN This Morning&rdquo; where he bumped heads with Lemon over whether the Civil War was fought to give blacks their constitutional rights.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Lemon became angered when Ramaswamy connected the Civil War, where gun rights were extended to freed blacks.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Ramaswamy argued the Democratic Party wishes to put black people &ldquo;back in chains&rdquo; with gun-control laws.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://youtu.be/-l5QqyN_How"><span style="font-weight: 400;" data-rich-links="{&quot;fple-t&quot;:&quot;Don Lemon argues with Vivek Ramaswamy over the Civil War&quot;,&quot;fple-u&quot;:&quot;https://youtu.be/-l5QqyN_How&quot;,&quot;fple-mt&quot;:null,&quot;type&quot;:&quot;first-party-link&quot;}">Don Lemon argues with Vivek Ramaswamy over the Civil War</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;">- Play Video&nbsp;</span></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Elsewhere&hellip;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2023/apr/20/north-carolina-shooting-girl-parents-basketball-yard"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2023/apr/20/north-carolina-shooting-girl-parents-basketball-yard</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>Man shoots girl, six, and her parents after ball rolls into his backyard</strong></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">A six-year-old girl and her parents were allegedly shot by a neighbor after a basketball that the child was playing with rolled into the attacker&rsquo;s yard, according to authorities and local media reporting.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The shooting occurred on Wednesday in North Carolina when several young children were playing with a basketball which rolled into the yard of Robert Singletary, who neighbors say was new to the area and often mad at the local children, the news outlet WSOC-TV reported. It continued a recent spate of shootings across the US involving a property owner who fired at young people who approached them either by mistake or for an innocent reason.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Witnesses told the station that Singletary ran out of his home upset after the ball rolled on to his yard and started firing a gun at a neighbor. William White and his six-year-old daughter Kinsley were seriously hurt during the shooting. White had his own gun and tried to shoot back at Singletary, who witnesses say unloaded an entire magazine at White and his daughter.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">White was seriously injured after being shot in the back. Hilderbrand was grazed by a bullet and was back home on Wednesday after being discharged from a hospital.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Singletary remained at large as of Thursday morning. Police warned local residents that he is armed and dangerous.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Wednesday was not the first time Singletary was accused of acting violently. He was separately charged in December with assaulting his girlfriend with a miniature sledgehammer and keeping her in their apartment for two hours as she was bleeding, ABC News reported.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/policy/energy-environment/berkeley-ruling-threatens-gas-stove-bans"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/policy/energy-environment/berkeley-ruling-threatens-gas-stove-bans</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>Berkeley ruling threatens gas stove bans all over the country</strong></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The 9th U.S. Circuit Court of Appeals decision to overturn Berkeley's ban on natural gas stoves could threaten dozens of similar restrictions nationwide.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">A three-judge panel sided with the California Restaurant Association in voting unanimously that the city's 2019 ban on gas stoves ran afoul of the Energy Policy and Conservation Act of 1975, which they said preempted a local gas stove ban &mdash; a ruling that now puts into doubt the scores of similar bans advanced across the nation in recent years.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The appellate court decision may have "ripple effects" for gas appliance restrictions nationwide and provide a road map of sorts for industry and consumer groups looking to halt such policies, said Rob Rains, a senior vice president at the independent research firm Washington Analysis.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The ruling "does provide a playbook for opponents of these policies to kind of 'storm the walls,' so to speak, and seek for them to be thrown out as well," he said in an interview.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">More than 100 U.S. cities and localities have moved to restrict gas-powered appliances, including 75 cities in California alone.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Monday's ruling only technically applies to states that fall under the 9th Circuit's jurisdiction: California, Alaska, Arizona, Hawaii, Idaho, Nebraska, Nevada, Oregon, and Washington, as well as Guam and the Mariana Islands. But it sets the stage for a challenge to regulations in other states. Even if bans are upheld by courts, any such ruling would create a split between circuits, raising the prospect of the Supreme Court weighing in for the whole country.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The court's decision hinged on its reading of the Energy Policy and Conservation Act of 1975, which gives the Department of Energy the legal right to set conservation standards for certain building appliances, including hot water heaters, furnaces, and HVAC systems &mdash; and preempts local laws in those areas.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The California Restaurant Association argued that gas-powered stoves are crucial for chefs to prepare food the way they are classically trained.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">In California, more than 75 cities and counties have modeled Berkeley's ordinance in crafting their own gas bans.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Major cities, including San Francisco, Oakland, Los Gatos, and Sunnyvale, as well as Marin County, have adopted similar bans, either banning or restricting natural gas appliances, including gas-powered stoves.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">It is possible that gas stove critics may regroup and rework policies to sidestep the 9th Circuit ruling.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Notably, the California Air Resources Board approved a plan last September to ban the sale of new natural gas-fired furnaces and home water heaters in the state by 2030. But it doesn't include gas stoves, though its final rules will not come up for a final vote until 2035.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Beyond the Golden State, cities in New York, Washington, Massachusetts, and Maryland have passed ambitious plans to phase out or ban natural gas appliances in new buildings.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/policy/courts/alito-extends-administrative-stay-on-abortion-pill-case-till-friday"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/policy/courts/alito-extends-administrative-stay-on-abortion-pill-case-till-friday</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>Justice Samuel Alito extends administrative stay on major abortion pill case until Friday</strong></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Supreme Court Justice Samuel Alito extended an administrative stay over a lower court ruling that threatened to limit access to a common abortion pill until Friday, giving the justices more time to mull their decision.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The move to extend an administrative stay is procedural and comes just days after Alito froze a lower judge's decision to reverse the government's 2000 approval of the common abortion drug, muh - fuh - pri - stown.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The decision means that all of District Judge Matthew Kacsmaryk's April 7 ruling that threatened to revoke the Food and Drug Administration's approval of the drug will not go into effect until at least Friday at 11:59 p.m. Eastern time.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Days after the district judge's decision, the U.S. Court of Appeals for the 5th Circuit unwound some of the lower court's decision but kept in place a block on a seven-year effort by the agency to widen access to the drug.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Ahead of Alito's decision, the manufacturer of the generic version of mifepristone, GenBioPro, filed a lawsuit against the FDA in Maryland federal court to maintain its ability to market the drug.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The 5th U.S. Circuit Court of Appeals halted some of the Texas decision while maintaining stays on more recent FDA changes that expanded access to the pill through telemedicine, mail, and retail pharmacies. With Alito's decision, no part of that appeals court ruling would go into effect until the late-Friday deadline.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Alito, who is also the author of the opinion last summer that allowed states to impose laws severely restricting abortion access, is handling the matter because he is tasked to oversee requests stemming from the Louisiana-based 5th Circuit.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Meanwhile, the Supreme Court must consider a separate district court ruling, issued less than an hour after Kacsmaryk's initial decision, that complicated the matter with a conflicting decision. Washington-based District Judge Thomas O. Rice, an appointee of former President Barack Obama, blocked the FDA from limiting the availability of mifepristone in much of the country. That ruling, also issued April 7, applies to just 17 liberal-leaning states and Washington, D.C., which filed a lawsuit in February challenging the FDA&rsquo;s regulations over the drug.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">As of Wednesday, mifepristone is lawful and remains available in some form in 37 states, even some states with abortion restrictions.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://www.foxnews.com/politics/save-womens-sports-bill-passes-house-zero-votes-dems-transgender-bullying"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.foxnews.com/politics/save-womens-sports-bill-passes-house-zero-votes-dems-transgender-bullying</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>'Save women's sports' bill passes House with zero votes from Dems, who call it transgender 'bullying'</strong></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The House on Thursday passed legislation aimed at preventing biological males from competing as transgender athletes in girls&rsquo; and women&rsquo;s sports at schools across the country, after a debate in which several Democrats accused Republicans of "bullying" transgender students by calling up the bill.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The Protection of Women and Girls in Sports Act passed in a 219-203 vote Thursday morning &mdash; all the "yes" votes came from Republicans, and all the "no" votes came from Democrats.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Republicans defended the bill as an attempt to spare women and girls from having to compete against transgender women and girls &mdash; biological males who can sometimes dominate these sports and prevent some female athletes from making the team. But several Democrats argued in debate that the GOP bill is an extension of the bullying that transgender students are already facing at school.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Rep. Mark Takano, D-Calif., said the bill would make school sports "less safe for women and girls," and argued that even discussing the legislation on the House floor was doing harm to transgender students.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Republicans rejected these arguments and said they are trying to protect girls&rsquo; and women&rsquo;s sports from being taken over by biological males. Rep. Virginia Foxx, R-N.C., said Democrats are ignoring the "physical advantages" that men have over women and rejected Jayapal&rsquo;s argument that the GOP is waging a "hate" campaign against transgender students.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Republicans also accused Democrats of pursuing transgender rights to an illogical end that goes against the intent of Title IX, which most credit with dramatically expanding participation in women&rsquo;s sports.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">"Congress in 1972 created Title IX to protect women's sports to enable women to have an equal playing field in athletics," said Rep. Greg Steube, R-Fla., who sponsored the Protection of Women and Girls in Sports Act. "In worship to their trans idols, the administration wants to flip that on its head. It is insane."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Under Steube&rsquo;s bill, educational institutions that receive Title IX funding from the federal government would not be allowed to "permit a person whose sex is male to participate in an athletic program or activity that is designed for women or girls." The bill adds that the sex of an athlete is defined only by their "reproductive biology and genetics at birth."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Steube has said he introduced his bill in order to "save women&rsquo;s sports" from transgender women and girls who are denying biological women and girls spots on the team&rsquo;s roster, and sometimes dominate these sports. He said a dangerous shift in U.S. culture requires a defense from Congress.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Speaking of women&rsquo;s sports&hellip; a win for Australia today!</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://www.breitbart.com/sports/2023/04/19/trans-female-nixed-from-competing-as-woman-in-semi-pro-basketball-league/"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.breitbart.com/sports/2023/04/19/trans-female-nixed-from-competing-as-woman-in-semi-pro-basketball-league/</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>Trans &lsquo;Female&rsquo; Nixed from Competing as Woman in Semi-Pro Basketball League</strong></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">An application to become a player submitted by a man claiming to be a transgender female has been rejected by Australia&rsquo;s WNBL 1 South women&rsquo;s semi-pro basketball league, a report says.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The application was submitted by a biological man calling himself Lexi Rodgers, who wanted to play for the Kilsyth Cobras in Kilsyth, Australia, a town in the western suburbs of Melbourne.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The request, though, was denied by Basketball Australia, the governing body for the sport there, Fox News reported.</span></p>
<p><br /><br /></p>]]></description>
   <author><![CDATA[Garrison Hardie]]></author>
   <enclosure url="https://app.dropwave.io/episode/12309968-90d1-49f3-b539-6422ee581004/daily-news-brief-for-friday-april-21st-2023.mp3" length="1047" type="audio/mp3"/>
   <guid isPermaLink="false"><![CDATA[12309968-90d1-49f3-b539-6422ee581004]]></guid>
   <pubDate>Fri, 21 Apr 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
   <source url=""><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></source>
   <itunes:author><![CDATA[Garrison Hardie]]></itunes:author>
   <itunes:image href="https://assets-cdn2.dropwave.io/2ab40ac0-e99d-4f25-a6d2-541d2c9b290a/cover-art/hUZu1H9lrRY0wXg66WHC8eLwYBA3hbRNTAHQmHt2.png"/>
   <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
   <itunes:duration>1047</itunes:duration>
   <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
  
  </item><item>
   <title><![CDATA[Daily News Brief for Thursday, April 20th, 2023 [Daily News Brief]]]></title>
   <link>https://app.dropwave.io/episode/69e4f81b-f5cd-4676-86e9-a4b2ab0829f8/daily-news-brief-for-thursday-april-20th-2023.mp3</link>
   <description><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">This is Garrison Hardie with your CrossPolitic Daily News Brief for Thursday, April 20th, 2023.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>Fight Laugh Feast Conference - Ark Encounter</strong></span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">This year, our Fight Laugh Feast Conference is at the Ark Encounter in Kentucky on The Politics of Six Day Creation. The politics of six day creation is the difference between a fixed standard of justice and a careening standard of justice, the difference between the corrosive relativism that creates mobs and anarchy and the freedom of objectivity, truth, and due process. The politics of six day creation establishes the authority and sufficiency of God&rsquo;s Word for all of life: from what is a man or a woman, when does human life begin, and how is human society best organized?</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Come hear Ken Ham, Pastor Doug Wilson, Dr. Ben Merkle, Dr. Gordon Wilson, me and more, and of course a live CrossPolitic show! Mark your calendars for October 11th-14th, as we fight, laugh, and feast, with beer &amp; psalms, our amazing lineup of speakers, our Rowdy Christian Merch, and a Sabbath Feast to wrap up the occasion. Maybe an infant baptism while we&rsquo;re at it! Visit fightlaughfeast.com for more information!</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">We start this off with some somber news coming out of Alabama.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://www.foxnews.com/us/two-teens-charged-dadeville-alabama-mass-shooting-sweet-16-birthday-party"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.foxnews.com/us/two-teens-charged-dadeville-alabama-mass-shooting-sweet-16-birthday-party</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;">&nbsp;</span></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>Two teens charged in Dadeville, Alabama, mass shooting at Sweet 16 birthday party</strong></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Alabama authorities announced Wednesday that two teenagers have been arrested and charged in the Dadeville mass shooting at a Sweet 16 birthday party last weekend.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Four people were killed, and another 32 people were injured when gunfire erupted at approximately 10:34 p.m. Saturday at the Mahogany Masterpiece dance studio, located in the 200 Block of Broadnax Street in Dadeville, a sleepy town of just 3,200 people in Tallapoosa County, about 62 miles northeast of the state capital of Montgomery.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Days later, the Alabama Law Enforcement Agency announced Ty Reik McCullough, 17, and Travis McCullough, 16, were both formally charged with four counts of reckless murder.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The teens from Tuskegee were arrested by Special Agents with the Alabama Law Enforcement Agency&rsquo;s (ALEA) State Bureau of Investigation (SBI).&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">"These individuals have been charged after a complex and thorough investigation was conducted with assistance from a multitude of law enforcement agencies," the ALEA said in a statement.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">At a press conference Wednesday, District Attorney Mike Segrest said the pair would be charged as adults and that prosecutors would ask a judge to hold them without bail. A bond hearing must be held by Friday under Alabama law. He said four people remain in the hospital in critical condition and that more charges would be coming.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The gunfire broke out Saturday at a 16th birthday party for Alexis Dowdell, which was being held at the dance studio just off the town&rsquo;s courthouse square. Witnesses have said multiple people began shooting some time after Dowdell&rsquo;s mother paused the celebration to ask people with guns to leave.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The birthday girl&rsquo;s brother, Philstavious "Phil" Dowdell, reportedly died in his sister&rsquo;s arms.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Besides Phil Dowdell, a star wide receiver with plans to play college football at Jacksonville State this fall, those killed were fellow Dadeville High senior Shaunkivia Nicole "KeKe" Smith, 17, an athlete-turned-team manager; 2022 Opelika High School graduate Marsiah Emmanuel "Siah" Collins, 19, an aspiring singer who planned to start college this fall; and 2018 Dadeville High graduate Corbin Dahmontrey Holston, 23, another former athlete at the school.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Holston had gone to the party to check on a younger family member who feared trouble, Holston&rsquo;s mother Janett Heard told AL.com. Relatives told the news outlet that the shooting began shortly after Holston arrived, and that he pulled his younger relative to safety.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://nypost.com/2023/04/18/chinese-police-stations-allegedly-spying-on-nyc-la-more/"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://nypost.com/2023/04/18/chinese-police-stations-allegedly-spying-on-nyc-la-more/</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>After FBI busts Chinese &lsquo;police station&rsquo; in NYC, six more exposed in US</strong></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The FBI helped shut down a clandestine Chinese &ldquo;police station&rdquo; in Manhattan after the arrest of two alleged operatives earlier this week &mdash; but The Post is told that there are several more of these illegal organizations scattered across the US.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">In addition to the Chinese police station above a noodle restaurant in Manhattan&rsquo;s Chinatown, there is another station at an undisclosed address in New York City, as well as an outpost in Los Angeles, according to a new report by Safeguard Defenders.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The Madrid-based human rights group initially published a report last year detailing 100 clandestine Chinese police stations around the world.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">In addition to Los Angeles and New York, the nonprofit has found so-called &ldquo;overseas service stations&rdquo; in San Francisco and Houston as well as in cities in Nebraska and Minnesota.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">These law enforcement organizations, operated by the Chinese Communist Party, are tasked with spying on Chinese nationals around the world.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">UFWD is an acronym for United Front Work Department, a Chinese government agency that controls overseas ethnic and religious affairs.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Often, the police stations &mdash; whose operatives allegedly spy on dissidents and others &mdash; hide behind nonprofits and community associations, according to Safeguard Defenders&rsquo; reports.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">In Chinatown, the police station was run by the America ChangLe Association NY Inc., which owns the building at 107 East Broadway where the operation was located, The Post revealed in October.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The nonprofit, which listed its charitable mission as a &ldquo;social gathering place for Fujianese people,&rdquo; paid $1.3 million in 2016 for the suite of offices that houses the Fuzhou Police Overseas Chinese Affairs bureau at the East Broadway location, filings show.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Last year, the group held its annual gala dinner, featuring New York City Mayor Eric Adams as the guest of honor &mdash; an event that was not disclosed on the mayor&rsquo;s official agenda.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">On Monday, federal agents arrested &ldquo;Harry&rdquo; Lu Jianwang, 61, of the Bronx, and Chen Jinping, 59, of Manhattan for allegedly establishing the East Broadway station, known as the Fuzhou branch of the Ministry of Public Security in China.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The men allegedly shut down the station last year when they became aware of a federal investigation, according to a statement from the Department of Justice.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">According to the criminal complaint, Lu also helped track down dissidents who were living in the city. Chinese officials also requested that he participate in demonstrations against Falun Gong, a religious movement subject to crackdown across the globe by the Chinese Communist Party, the complaint said.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Lu and Chen also tried to obstruct the DOJ&rsquo;s investigation by deleting their communications with an official of MPS after finding out about the FBI investigation, federal prosecutors said.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The criminal complaint against Lu and Chen was unsealed Monday at the same time that 44 other defendants were charged, in two separate complaints in Brooklyn federal court, for various crimes related to illegally acting on behalf of China in the US.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Speaking of China, "PrayforChina.us is a nationwide initiative helping Christians pray more strategically for China by matching up every state (and eventually every county) with their own Chinese province (and county) to adopt for prayer! Learn more at Pray for China dot us."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2023/04/19/meta-started-latest-round-of-layoffs-focusing-on-technical-employees.html"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.cnbc.com/2023/04/19/meta-started-latest-round-of-layoffs-focusing-on-technical-employees.html</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>Meta has started its latest round of layoffs, focusing on technical employees</strong></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">As part of Meta&rsquo;s latest round of job cuts announced in March, the company on Wednesday started laying off employees in technical roles.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Employees with technical backgrounds like user experience, software engineering, graphics programming and other roles announced on LinkedIn that they had been let go by the company on Wednesday morning. A Meta spokesperson confirmed to CNBC the cuts had started.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">One employee impacted by the moves told CNBC that Wednesday&rsquo;s layoffs also hit product-facing teams and that Meta plans to cut business-facing roles, such as finance, legal and HR, beginning in May. The employee, who discussed the layoffs under condition of a-nuh-ni-muh-tee&nbsp; to speak freely, said Meta suggested tech teams who weren&rsquo;t impacted by Wednesday&rsquo;s cuts may also be included in layoffs next month.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">LinkedIn posts indicated that multiple people who worked as gameplay programmers were also affected by the layoffs. Gameplay engineers work on virtual and augmented reality products, according to a Meta job listing.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">With ad revenue slumping last year and its stock price in free-fall, Facebook&rsquo;s parent announced its first round of layoffs in November, affecting some 11,000 workers. Meta CEO Mark Zuckerberg then declared 2023 the &ldquo;year of efficiency,&rdquo; and proceeded with a plan of an additional 10,000 job cuts in March, resulting in restructuring costs of between $3 billion and $5 billion.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">As Zuckerberg said at the time, the new round of April layoffs targets technical workers. He said cuts in the business groups would take place in late May.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Wall Street has applauded the downsizing. Meta shares have soared 81% this year after losing about two-thirds of their value last year. Revenue has declined for three straight quarters, and analysts are projecting another quarterly sales drop when Meta reports its first-quarter earnings next week. The company&rsquo;s previous guidance called for sales of between $26 billion and $28.5 billion, which means the streak of revenue declines could end if Meta reaches the top end of the range.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://www.breitbart.com/immigration/2023/04/18/bidens-border-roughly-180000-more-migrants-in-march/"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.breitbart.com/immigration/2023/04/18/bidens-border-roughly-180000-more-migrants-in-march/</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>Biden&rsquo;s Border Flood: 180,000 More Migrants in March</strong></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">President Joe Biden&rsquo;s deputies accepted roughly 180,000 more illegal migrants in March to take jobs and homes that would otherwise go to better-paid Americans.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The March inflow brings Biden&rsquo;s total southern inflow to roughly 4.3 million &mdash; or more than one migrant for every American born in 2022. That massive inflow spikes Wall Street by cutting Americans&rsquo; wages, inflating housing prices, and shifting new jobs and wealth to the coastal states.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The two leading GOP candidates for 2024 &mdash; Donald Trump and Florida Gov. Ron DeSantis &mdash; are promising to end the illegal migrant inflow.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Federal data released on April 17 shows that 162,317 illegal migrants were arrested at the border in March by the border agents.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Biden&rsquo;s deputies rejected 90,000 of the migrants under the Title 42 border barrier, which is due to expire on May 11. They allowed 104,238 migrants into the United States to take jobs while they plead for asylum.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The 104,238 accepted migrants include roughly 80,000 people admitted after they were arrested along the borders, plus 26,583 people who used the agency&rsquo;s &ldquo;CBP One&rdquo; to get an appointment inside the United States for the catch-and-release process.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">But federal officials also allowed in another 30,000 migrants via quasi-legal loopholes cut by Biden&rsquo;s pro-migration, Cuban-born border chief, Alejandro Mayorkas. These Cuban, Haitian, Venezuelan, and Nicaraguan migrants fly into the United States by aircraft and are not recorded in the border arrest data.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">This legal trick allows Mayorkas to claim that he is managing the border chaos created by Biden&rsquo;s welcome for migrants, despite a judge&rsquo;s order barring the process.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">But the monthly data also excludes the so-called &ldquo;gotaways&rdquo; who sneak past the half-built wall, decommissioned sensor networks, and diminished border patrol.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">This &ldquo;gotaway&rdquo; population added roughly 50,000 more job-seeking illegal migrants in March.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">These gotaways are quasi-legal because Mayorkas has announced he will not deport them unless they commit a violent crime.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">So the total inflow in March was about 180,000 &mdash; 104,238 let through the border, 30,000 lets in via Mayorkas&rsquo; pathway, plus 50,000 gotaways.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Biden&rsquo;s policies have allowed entry by roughly 4.3 million illegal migrants since January 2021 &mdash; or roughly one migrant for every two births in the United States during his tenure.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">In their press release on the monthly numbers, GOP leaders touted the bigger number of migrants who arrived at the border, not the smaller number of migrants who were actually admitted by Mayorkas.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Donor-backed GOP officials rarely mention the huge economic impact of Biden&rsquo;s migration on voters &mdash; or even on swing voters.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Roughly 75 percent of the welcomed migrants in March are working-age job-seekers who need to pay their high-interest smuggling debts by working even tough jobs at low wages. That makes them attractive hires for U.S. employers who do not want to hire the roughly six million Americans who have been sidelined by age, criminal records, drugs, laziness, obesity, disability, or reluctance to take jobs for wages below what they have been paid before.</span><span style="font-weight: 400;"><br /><br /></span></span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The federal government annually admits about 1 million temporary workers &mdash; many of whom never go home &mdash; plus about 1 million legal immigrants. Those numbers were largely set by Congress in 1990.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">All told the combination of legal and illegal immigrants delivers roughly one migrant for every American birth each year.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">And now this!</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Florida Gov. Ron DeSantis released a parody of the old Bud Light "Real Men of Genius" commercials taking aim at transgender female athletes, including Lia Thomas and CeC&eacute; Telfer among others.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Instead of Bud Light, which has been involved in a massive controversy over the brand&rsquo;s partnership with Dylan Mulvaney, the ad introduces Freedom Heavy and "real men of women&rsquo;s sports."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://twitter.com/i/status/1648126878207680513"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://twitter.com/i/status/16481268 78207680513</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> - Play Video 0:00-0:30</span></span></p>]]></description>
   <author><![CDATA[Garrison Hardie]]></author>
   <enclosure url="https://app.dropwave.io/episode/69e4f81b-f5cd-4676-86e9-a4b2ab0829f8/daily-news-brief-for-thursday-april-20th-2023.mp3" length="870" type="audio/mp3"/>
   <guid isPermaLink="false"><![CDATA[69e4f81b-f5cd-4676-86e9-a4b2ab0829f8]]></guid>
   <pubDate>Thu, 20 Apr 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
   <source url=""><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></source>
   <itunes:author><![CDATA[Garrison Hardie]]></itunes:author>
   <itunes:image href="https://assets-cdn2.dropwave.io/2ab40ac0-e99d-4f25-a6d2-541d2c9b290a/cover-art/hUZu1H9lrRY0wXg66WHC8eLwYBA3hbRNTAHQmHt2.png"/>
   <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
   <itunes:duration>870</itunes:duration>
   <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
  
  </item>
 </channel>
</rss>
