<?xml version="1.0"?>
<?xml-stylesheet href="/storage/feed-stylesheet.xsl" type="text/xsl"?>

<rss xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
 <channel>
  <title>FLF - Daily News Brief</title>
  <link>https://dropwave.io</link>
  <description><![CDATA[FIGHT LAUGH FEAST PRESENTS SHOWS PROCLAIMING THE LORDSHIP OF CHRIST OVER ALL OF LIFE.
]]></description>
  <language>en</language>
  <managingEditor><![CDATA[fightlaughfeast@gmail.com (FLF, LLC)]]></managingEditor>
  <webMaster><![CDATA[support@dropwave.io (DropWave Support)]]></webMaster>
  <pubDate>Mon, 11 Dec 2023 01:25:57 +0000</pubDate>
  <lastBuildDate>Mon, 11 Dec 2023 01:25:57 +0000</lastBuildDate>
  <image>
   <url>https://is4-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Podcasts113/v4/58/56/52/5856525c-2973-cf29-3db9-21faa8595391/mza_1144696925612154085.png/1200x1200bb.jpg</url>
   <link>https://dropwave.io</link>
   <title><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></title>
  </image>
  <itunes:author><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></itunes:author>
  <itunes:image href="https://is4-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Podcasts113/v4/58/56/52/5856525c-2973-cf29-3db9-21faa8595391/mza_1144696925612154085.png/1200x1200bb.jpg"/>
  <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
  <itunes:owner>
   <itunes:name><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></itunes:name>
   <itunes:email>fightlaughfeast@gmail.com</itunes:email>
  </itunes:owner>
  <itunes:category text="News"/>
  <item>
   <title><![CDATA[Daily News Brief for Thursday,, December 7th, 2023. [Daily News Brief]]]></title>
   <link/>
   <description><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">This is Garrison Hardie with your CrossPolitic Daily News Brief for Thursday,, December 7th, 2023.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Fight Laugh Feast Magazine</strong></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Our Fight Laugh Feast Magazine is a quarterly issue that packs a punch like a 21 year Balvenie, no ice. We don&rsquo;t water down our scotch, why would we water down our theology? Order a yearly subscription for yourself and then send a couple yearly subscriptions to your friends who have been drinking luke-warm evangelical cool-aid. Every quarter we promise quality food for the soul, wine for the heart, and some Red Bull for turning over tables. Our magazine will include cultural commentary, a Psalm of the quarter, recipes for feasting, laughter sprinkled through out the glossy pages, and more. Sign up today, at fightlaughfeast.com.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-12833565/Biden-Russia-Ukraine-Congress-war-conflict-aid-NATO.html"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-12833565/Biden-Russia-Ukraine-Congress-war-conflict-aid-NATO.html</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Joe Biden raises the specter of American troops having to fight Russians in Europe if Congress stands by and allows Ukraine to fall</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">President Joe Biden on Wednesday warned that American troops could have to fight Russian forces if Congress prevents further aid being sent to Ukraine.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">He demanded that lawmakers approve his request for tens of billions in military and economic assistance.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Republicans have said they are not willing to countenance another major package of aid unless the administration takes action on the southern border.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">But Biden said Republicans were handing Russian President Vladimir Putin a gift.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">'This cannot wait,' he said in a televised address.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">'Congress needs to pass supplemental funding for Ukraine before they break for the holiday recess, simple as that, frankly.'</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://youtu.be/7UBC-UluphU?list=RDNS7UBC-UluphU"><span style="font-weight: 400;" data-rich-links="{&quot;fple-t&quot;:&quot;Biden presses Congress to pass Ukraine aid to prevent Russian win&quot;,&quot;fple-u&quot;:&quot;https://youtu.be/7UBC-UluphU?list=RDNS7UBC-UluphU&quot;,&quot;fple-mt&quot;:null,&quot;type&quot;:&quot;first-party-link&quot;}">Biden presses Congress to pass Ukraine aid to prevent Russian win</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;" data-rich-links="{&quot;fple-t&quot;:&quot;Biden presses Congress to pass Ukraine aid to prevent Russian win&quot;,&quot;fple-u&quot;:&quot;https://youtu.be/7UBC-UluphU?list=RDNS7UBC-UluphU&quot;,&quot;fple-mt&quot;:null,&quot;type&quot;:&quot;first-party-link&quot;}"> </span><span style="font-weight: 400;">Play 1:24-3:00</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">He accused Republicans of holding aid 'hostage' over the border and of being willing to 'kneecap' Ukrainian forces on the battlefield</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">But he hinted that he was ready to do a deal with Republicans, even if they would have to accept they were not going to get everything they wanted.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Biden's speech came soon after he held a video call with leaders of the Group of Seven advanced democracies, who have all backed Ukraine, and Ukrainian President Volodymyr Zelensky.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Biden has asked Congress for more than $100 billion to fund conflicts in Ukraine and Israel, as well as other matters of national security. However, Republicans on Capitol Hill have resisted the request, some insisting that Biden first take measures to secure the nation's southern border.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The White House has warned repeatedly of the consequences of failing to back Ukraine.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">In a blunt letter sent to Congress on Monday, Office of Management and Budget Director Shalanda Young wrote: 'We are out of money to support Ukraine in this fight. This isn't a next year problem. The time to help a democratic Ukraine fight against Russian aggression is right now.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">However, Republican leaders quickly dug in.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Speaker Mike Johnson promised there would be no funding for Ukraine without 'transformative' border security provisions.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://americanmilitarynews.com/2023/12/us-troops-suing-govt-for-billions-in-backpay-over-covid-vaccine-mandate/"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://americanmilitarynews.com/2023/12/us-troops-suing-govt-for-billions-in-backpay-over-covid-vaccine-mandate/</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>US troops suing gov&rsquo;t for &lsquo;billions&rsquo; in backpay over Covid vaccine mandate</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">In a groundbreaking development, three lawsuits with the potential for a class action suit are being filed on behalf of former United States service members. The service members, represented by attorneys Dale Saran, Andy Meyer, and Brandon Johnson, allege they were unjustly discharged or prevented from drilling, causing significant financial loss, as a result of the Biden administration&rsquo;s vaccine mandate policies.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">According to Breitbart, the lawsuits, which are currently in the U.S. Court of Federal Claims, could involve backpay claims totaling billions of dollars.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Saran, a retired Marine, emphasized the massive scale of the compensation, telling Breitbart, &ldquo;It&rsquo;s worth billions. That&rsquo;s just flat-out. That&rsquo;s what it is in backpay. It&rsquo;s billions of dollars.&rdquo; This statement underscores the potential magnitude of the lawsuit&rsquo;s financial implications for the Department of Defense.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The court, with its roots in the Reconstruction Era, is known for handling cases of illegal discharge and pay-related grievances in the military. Saran explained its unique role, saying that the Court of Claims is where service members can go when they have a claim and say, &ldquo;Hey, I was illegally discharged, or the military did something to impede my pay.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">According to Breitbart, the lawsuits allege that 80,000 to 100,000 service members, including both active-duty personnel and reservists, were impacted by the Biden administration&rsquo;s actions. Saran detailed the lack of due process in the cases, noting, &ldquo;They were basically [without] the benefit of any due process. No boards were held. They didn&rsquo;t hold any administrative separation boards; they didn&rsquo;t hold any hearings. They didn&rsquo;t do any federal recognition boards; none of the administrative or judicial procedures were used. They just flat-out did it.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">One notable case involves former Coast Guard member Zach Loesch, who was commended by President Joe Biden for his heroics during Hurricane Ian but faced discharge for not complying with a vaccine mandate, according to Breitbart.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The claims also involve the repayment of enlistment bonuses, adding to the financial stakes. Saran stated, &ldquo;Not only did they throw them out &mdash; unceremoniously [and] wrongfully &mdash; now they&rsquo;re&hellip;without a job instantly, no separation pay, none of that. And instead, they&rsquo;re standing out in the cold, and worse yet, here comes the government&hellip;here comes the debt collectors. Now you owe us money.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Saran drew parallels between the current situation with the service members who were negatively impacted by the COVID-19 vaccine mandate policies and his past experience defending service members who refused the Anthrax vaccine in the late 1990s.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&ldquo;I did some work on the lawsuit Doe v. Rumsfeld that shut down the anthrax vaccine,&rdquo; he said. &ldquo;And so&hellip;here we are, second go around again, 15 years in, and we&rsquo;re right back at the mass vaccination of unlicensed vaccines like the government didn&rsquo;t learn last time.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">According to Saran, those interested in more information about the current lawsuits can learn more at militarybackpay.com. The ongoing legal battle, with cases like Bassen v. USA, Botello v. USA, and Harkins v. USA, marks a significant moment in military legal history, raising questions about due process, financial responsibility, and the broader implications for the rights of U.S. service members.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://www.foxnews.com/world/israel-constructs-large-pumps-flood-hamas-terror-tunnels-seawater-wall-street-journal"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.foxnews.com/world/israel-constructs-large-pumps-flood-hamas-terror-tunnels-seawater-wall-street-journal</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Israel constructs large pumps to flood Hamas terror tunnels with seawater</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The Israeli military has assembled several large pumps it could use to flood the Hamas tunnels beneath the Gaza Strip with seawater, driving out terrorists hiding there, The Wall Street Journal reported, citing U.S. officials.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Construction of five large seawater pumps was completed in November about one mile north of the Al-Shati refugee camp. Each pump is capable of drawing water from the Mediterranean Sea and can move thousands of cubic meters of water per hour, which would flood the tunnels within weeks, the report said.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Israel has not yet committed to the plan, and it is unclear whether it would attempt to flood the tunnels while there are still hostages, including Americans, held by Hamas. The Palestinian terror group took some 240 people captive during the Oct. 7 attack on Israel and brought them back to the Gaza Strip.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">According to the report, Israel has identified about 800 tunnels beneath Gaza that Hamas has used to move fighters, store weapons and plan terror attacks on Israel. However, Israeli officials believe the tunnel network is much larger.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">By flooding the tunnels over several weeks, Israel would enable Hamas terrorists and potentially hostages to move out, the outlet reported, citing a source familiar with the plan.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">"We are not sure how successful pumping will be since nobody knows the details of the tunnels and the ground around them," the source said. "It&rsquo;s impossible to know if that will be effective because we don&rsquo;t know how seawater will drain in tunnels no one has been in before."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The Wall Street Journal said an Israel Defense Forces official declined to comment on the flooding plan, but said: "The IDF is operating to dismantle Hamas&rsquo;s terror capabilities in various ways, using different military and technological tools."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">U.S. officials were informed of the plan last month, the Wall Street Journal reported, but the U.S. does not know how close Israeli Prime Minister Benjamin Netanyahu's government is to executing the plan.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Israel has committed to continuing its war effort until Hamas is eradicated in Gaza. The Israeli military said it launched its 10,000th airstrike against the terror group in the Gaza Strip late Sunday.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://thepostmillennial.com/dem-witness-who-cannot-define-what-a-woman-is-says-women-should-learn-to-lose-gracefully-against-trans-athletes?utm_campaign=64487#google_vignette"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://thepostmillennial.com/dem-witness-who-cannot-define-what-a-woman-is-says-women-should-learn-to-lose-gracefully-against-trans-athletes?utm_campaign=64487#google_vignette</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Dem witness who cannot define what a woman is says women should 'learn to lose gracefully' against trans athletes</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Head of the National Women's Law Center, Fatima Goss Graves, encouraged women who are forced to compete against men in women's sports to "lose gracefully." This she sees as the preferable alternative to keeping men out of women's sports at the scholastic level altogether. She made these remarks at a hearing over Title IX in the US House.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">"The reality is, that like their peers, trans girls and women, they sometimes lose at sports and sometimes they win. And success in school sports depends on a whole range of factors including how hard you work and coaching and access to really good resources and facilities," Goss Graves said. Goss Graves is married to Matthew Graves, a key prosecutor in J6 cases. She also co-founded Times Up to hold high-profile men accountable for sexual misconduct.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">She did not address the problems that arise when boys shower in girls locker rooms and expose themselves, or when girls miss out on opportunities because men have taken their places in the winners' circle.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://twitter.com/i/status/1732214013499412976"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://twitter.com/i/status/1732214013499412976</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> - Play Video (If you can find it somewhere else that&rsquo;s fine.)&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Goss Graves also does not know what a woman is. Or at least she refused to define the term when asked. She was asked in July 2022 by Rep Andrew Clyde - </span><a href="https://www.youtube.com/shorts/2Uo111tBKd4?feature=share"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.youtube.com/shorts/2Uo111tBKd4?feature=share</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> - Play Video&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The hearing was to consider changes proposed by the Department of Education to Title IX of the Civil Rights Act of 1964. The change would prevent schools from having women's or girl's-only sports. It would bring a new understanding and interpretation of Title IX, removing protections for women and girls and changing that to protection against discrimination for gender identity as a protected class. Under those provisions, the male student's stated gender identity would give him the standing to shower with girls and use other facilities that were previously women only.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://thepostmillennial.com/auto-makers-seek-to-remove-am-radio-from-all-new-models?utm_campaign=64487"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://thepostmillennial.com/auto-makers-seek-to-remove-am-radio-from-all-new-models?utm_campaign=64487</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Automakers seek to remove AM radio from all new models</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">As vehicles become more and more complex, many manufacturers have begun doing away with AM radios, citing concerns that the proximity of electrical components could potentially negatively interact with signals from short-wave broadcasts.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">While it could be argued that the AM radio one day going the way of the dashboard tape deck was inevitable, the fact that many Americans still tune into, and in some cases rely on, the technology has led to pushback against the companies attempting to omit it from new cars.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">In May, Sens. Ted Cruz (R-TX) and Ed Markey (D-MA) joined a bipartisan group of their colleagues in the House to introduce the AM for Every Vehicle Act, which, if passed, will direct the National Highway Traffic Safety Administration to require manufacturers to ensure AM radio is included free of charge in every model for the foreseeable future.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">According to a press release that announced the bill in May, eight of the world's 20 leading car makers, BMW, Ford, Mazda, Polestar, Rivian, Tesla, Volkswagen and Volvo, have done away with AM radio in their vehicles.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&nbsp;</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">"I would think that if Elon Musk has enough money to buy Twitter and send rockets to space, he can afford to include AM radio in his Teslas," New Jersey Rep. Josh Gottheimer lamented. "Instead, Elon Musk and Tesla and other car manufacturers are putting public safety and emergency response at risk."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">While many of the bill's proponents cited the use of AM radio for emergency alerts, others pointed out that despite its archaic reputation, it is still an integral part of many people's technology arsenal.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Arkansas Rep. Bruce Westerman, for example, said that his constituents "rely on AM broadcast radio for breaking news and entertainment as they make their daily commutes, especially in rural areas where constituents spend a lot of time in their vehicles."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">As Spectrum News covered, a report from the Center for Automotive Research found that the electromagnetic interference generted by EVs can make the AM signals fuzzy and unlistenable, and that while there is a workaround, it may cost automakers an estimated $3.8 billion over the next seven years.</span></p>]]></description>
   <author><![CDATA[Garrison Hardie]]></author>
   <enclosure url="https://app.dropwave.io/episode/5826c57a-dca6-48b7-994f-eaa9dfbac9c2/daily-news-brief-for-thursday-december-7th-2023.mp3" length="996" type="audio/mp3"/>
   <guid isPermaLink="false"><![CDATA[5826c57a-dca6-48b7-994f-eaa9dfbac9c2]]></guid>
   <pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
   <source url=""><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></source>
   <itunes:author><![CDATA[Garrison Hardie]]></itunes:author>
   <itunes:image href="https://assets-cdn2.dropwave.io/2ab40ac0-e99d-4f25-a6d2-541d2c9b290a/cover-art/mUK8zsnHkCK3vep7E1W6UgYb9dTnLenASAMEFha3.jpg"/>
   <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
   <itunes:duration>996</itunes:duration>
   <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
  
  </item><item>
   <title><![CDATA[Daily News Brief for Wednesday, December 6th, 2023 [Daily News Brief]]]></title>
   <link/>
   <description><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">This is Garrison Hardie with your CrossPolitic Daily News Brief for Wednesday, December 6th, 2023.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Tactics Conference</strong></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The Tactics Conference is coming! Learn how to build Christ&rsquo;s kingdom from those that are doing it. Join C.R. Wiley, the campus preacher Keith Darrel, Gabe Rench, Chocolate Knox, and Pastor Toby Sumpter for two days of boots on the ground training on how to take your community for Christ. Great talks, great food, and great people. Come see us in Lafayette, Louisiana (that's only about 2 and a half hours east of Houston, Texas) on January 19th-20th.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">And take note - Seating is limited. Families are welcome, come experience some Cajun hospitality, while we labor together to build the new Christendom.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Beer and psalms, panel discussions, Cajun dancing, and more&hellip;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Go to TacticsCon.com to buy your tickets today AND use the coupon code &ldquo;FLFPUB&rdquo; to get 20$ off your ticket price. That&rsquo;s TacticsCon.com - and we&rsquo;ll see you in South Louisiana this January.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://thepostmillennial.com/72-of-canadians-want-trudeau-gone-poll?utm_campaign=64487"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://thepostmillennial.com/72-of-canadians-want-trudeau-gone-poll?utm_campaign=64487</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>72% of Canadians want Trudeau gone</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Canadian Prime Minister Justin Trudeau is in political free-fall.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">In the latest Ipsos poll, 72 percent of Canadians want Trudeau to exit federal politics and leave as leader of the Liberal Party of Canada.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Ipsos says that number is up from 60 percent in September. Even within his own party, 33 percent of Liberal supporters would like Trudeau to resign.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">That's consistent with other recent polls that show the Conservative Party of Canada, under its leader Pierre Poilievre, 19 percentage points ahead of the Liberals and headed for one of the larger majority governments in Canadian history.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Nanos Research founder Nik Nanos described what the Liberals need to stand a chance in the next federal election is a "complete reboot."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">"Either with a new leader or&hellip; Justin Trudeau with a renewed vision of why he believes that he should deserve another mandate," Nanos said in a recent episode of CTV News Trend Line.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Canadians have even taken to the internet to try to remove Trudeau from office through the traditional legislative process.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">As of Monday morning, more than 175,000 Canadians have signed a petition for a vote of non-confidence in the House of Commons against the minority Liberal government.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The petition is sponsored by MP Michelle Ferreri (CPC-Peterborough-Kawartha) and reads:</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&nbsp;"The policies of this government aren't aligning with the crisis Canada is facing: housing costs, infringement of civil liberties, highest inflation in history, unbalanced immigration policies, taxation to the point of poverty, weakening of our economy by importing natural resources that Canada already has and under-utilizes; and based on the past eight years of this Prime Minister, Canadians do not have confidence in this Prime Minister, after five ethics investigations and Canada's reputation being tarnished on a global scale under his leadership. To the extent that Canada is being discluded from participating in statements regarding important geopolitical events."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Sen. Percy Downe, a Liberal who was chief of staff to former Prime Minister Jean Chretien, recently wrote that it is time Trudeau left office.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Trudeau laughed off the appeal. There is considerable doubt that his departure would save the Liberals' fortunes in the next federal election.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Trudeau's father, Pierre Trudeau, who was prime minister of Canada from 1968-1984 with the exception of a nine-month period in 1979 when a minority Progressive Conservative government was in power, famously took "a walk in the snow" on Feb. 28, 1984 when he decided to leave politics.&nbsp;&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">He announced his resignation the following day, Feb. 29 &ndash; a date that only occurs on a leap year.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://www.foxnews.com/media/doctor-treating-freed-hamas-hostages-reveals-unprecedented-abuse-rewrite-textbooks"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.foxnews.com/media/doctor-treating-freed-hamas-hostages-reveals-unprecedented-abuse-rewrite-textbooks</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Doctor treating freed Hamas hostages reveals unprecedented abuse: 'We have to rewrite the textbooks'</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">A doctor treating freed Hamas hostages in Israel says survivors are suffering from an unprecedented level of "extremely severe psychological abuse" endured during captivity.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">"I can tell you that on behalf of all the medical and psychological teams treating those who return, the mental states we encountered have no precedent in medical literature. We feel that we have to rewrite the textbooks of post-trauma," Dr. Renana Eitan told "Sunday Night in America."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Eitan revealed the Tel Aviv Medical Center is actively treating more than 15 former hostages and described their "severe physical and mental abuse."</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">"Those held captive were subject to starvation, to beating, to sexual abuse. They were being held in inhumane sanitary conditions. Extremely severe psychological abuse was inflicted on them, including separation from family members, separation of siblings, separation of children from their mothers. They were held in solitary confinement and spent long days in total darkness until they developed severe hallucinations," Eitan claimed. "Children were forced to watch brutal videos. They were under constant threats by weapons and threats to harm them even after they were released. They refer to the forced use of psychiatric drugs and other substances."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Eitan also detailed cases where individuals, though appearing physically unharmed, are dealing with "severe post-traumatic symptoms."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">"Some of the home comers, they look happy, they look fine, they look physically fine, and we try to hold on to those optimistic signs, but still, even those who seem fine, we know that most of them [are] suffering from severe post-traumatic symptoms, they have painful, traumatic memories. And they are entering into dissociative states, where for a moment they feel as if they are still in captivity and only later do they return to the understanding that they have been released," she said.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">This week marks two months since the Hamas terror attack on Israel which left 1,200 dead and 240 held hostage. According to the Israeli Ministry of Health, 73 Israelis and 24 foreign citizens have been released from Hamas to date.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Eitan urged the release of the remaining hostages "as soon as possible" as they face a long road ahead of physical and mental rehabilitation.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://www.breitbart.com/2nd-amendment/2023/12/04/israeli-security-minister-we-are-approving-up-to-3000-gun-license-applications-day/"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.breitbart.com/2nd-amendment/2023/12/04/israeli-security-minister-we-are-approving-up-to-3000-gun-license-applications-day/</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Israeli Security Minister: We Are Approving &lsquo;Up to 3,000&rsquo; Gun License Applications A Day</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Israel Security Minister Itamar Ben Gvir says his ministry is now approving &ldquo;up to 3,000&rdquo; gun license applications a day.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The Times of Israel quoted Ben Gvir saying, &ldquo;When the war started, we knew that we were right when we said that every place that has a weapon can save a life.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">He went on to say, &ldquo;My policy within the office was to permit as many people as possible to get a weapon&hellip;[and] in a short period of time, we were giving up to 3,000 approvals a day.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Ben Gvir indicated over 260,000 gun license applications have been approved since October 7, 2023.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">On November 15, 2023, Breitbart News pointed to a Times of Israel report which indicated over 236,000 gun license applications had been filed in Israel at that point in time.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">In mid-November roughly 1,700 applications were being approved daily, and the number of daily approvals has nearly doubled since then.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Breitbart News noted that an armed civilian opened fire Thursday on terrorists who attacked a Jerusalem bus stop. Two off-duty soldiers opened fire as well and the terrorists were killed.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://thepostmillennial.com/arlington-home-explodes-after-suspect-sets-off-flares-as-police-serve-search-warrant?utm_campaign=64487"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://thepostmillennial.com/arlington-home-explodes-after-suspect-sets-off-flares-as-police-serve-search-warrant?utm_campaign=64487</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Arlington home explodes after suspect sets off flares as police serve search warrant</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">On Monday, a home in the Bluemont neighborhood of Arlington, Virginia exploded as police were attempting to serve a search warrant following reports that a flare gun had been fired from within earlier in the evening.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">While three members of law enforcement suffered minor injuries, the fate of the suspect, who is believed to have been in the home at the time, has not been revealed.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">According to the Arlington County Police Department, officers were called to a duplex on the 800 block of North Burlington Street around 4:45 pm to investigate reports that someone had "discharged a flare gun 30 - 40 times from inside his residence into the surrounding neighborhood."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">While his actions did not result in any injuries or property damage, officers nonetheless obtained a search warrant and tried to make contact with him via telephone and loudspeaker. Their attempts proved fruitless, and the suspect remained "barricaded" inside.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">At around 8:25 pm, he "discharged several rounds" from what authorities believe was a firearm, resulting in the aforementioned explosion. The blast sent shockwaves through the surrounding area as residents watched debris fly into the air and the structure burn to the ground.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The fire department arrived on the scene a short time later, and by 10:30 pm, the blaze was extinguished.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">While police have not released the name of the suspect, local outlet ARLNow has reported that public records show the resident of the now-leveled home to be a man named James Yoo.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">According to Newsweek, Yoo's social media posts were reportedly filled with rants about the government, the police, and his own neighbors, who he repeatedly labeled "spies," suggesting they had fake identities and were assigned to monitor him for their "handlers." His YouTube channel included videos with pictures from his LinkedIn page depicting people he claimed were his neighbors entering and leaving their homes, according to the outlet.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">One of Yoo's neighbors, Alex Wilson, told ARLNow that he kept to himself and often had his windows covered with aluminum foil. Yoo also allegedly chased away prospective buyers with a knife while his house was on the market.</span></p>]]></description>
   <author><![CDATA[Garrison Hardie]]></author>
   <enclosure url="https://app.dropwave.io/episode/d6574dcf-b79a-4017-b782-aeaf678a8d4c/daily-news-brief-for-wednesday-december-6th-2023.mp3" length="592" type="audio/mp3"/>
   <guid isPermaLink="false"><![CDATA[d6574dcf-b79a-4017-b782-aeaf678a8d4c]]></guid>
   <pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
   <source url=""><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></source>
   <itunes:author><![CDATA[Garrison Hardie]]></itunes:author>
   <itunes:image href="https://assets-cdn2.dropwave.io/2ab40ac0-e99d-4f25-a6d2-541d2c9b290a/cover-art/mUK8zsnHkCK3vep7E1W6UgYb9dTnLenASAMEFha3.jpg"/>
   <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
   <itunes:duration>592</itunes:duration>
   <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
  
  </item><item>
   <title><![CDATA[Daily News Brief for Tuesday, December 5th, 2023 [Daily News Brief]]]></title>
   <link/>
   <description><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">This is Garrison Hardie with your CrossPolitic Daily News Brief for Tuesday, December 5th, 2023.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>VanGelder Technologies:</strong></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">VanGelder Technologies is a US-based custom software development company specializing in cross-platform mobile applications, web applications, and desktop programs. Leveraging open-source frameworks, they quickly and efficiently build custom software solutions that are tailor made to fit your specific needs.   </span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">There&rsquo;s no need for New Christendom companies to be content with offering sub-par mobile or web experiences. VanGelder Technologies can help you build better software for the glory of God! You can learn more, view examples of their work, or get in touch, at www.vangelder.tech  </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">That&rsquo;s V-A-N, G-E-L, D-E-R dot T-E-C-H VanGelder Technologies, where technology and tradition meet.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://hotair.com/jazz-shaw/2023/12/04/congress-freezes-6-billion-for-iran-n596478#google_vignette"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://hotair.com/jazz-shaw/2023/12/04/congress-freezes-6-billion-for-iran-n596478#google_vignette</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Congress Freezes $6 Billion for Iran</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">This took place on Thursday, but it&rsquo;s looking increasingly real. In a move that the Daily Mail described as &ldquo;humiliating&rdquo; for Joe Biden, lawmakers cast a bipartisan vote to freeze the six billion dollars that the President had previously freed up for Iran as part of his hostage negotiation deal. The move drew the support of nearly every Republican but also attracted nearly 100 Democrats. Now it&rsquo;s looking as if it might pass in the Senate as well. During a time when it&rsquo;s been seeming as if common sense had been banned in Washington, we have lawmakers seemingly conceding that sending billions of dollars to the world&rsquo;s largest state sponsor of terrorism might not be such a great idea.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">President Biden is facing a humiliating foreign policy setback as $6 billion he used to leverage the release of five imprisoned Americans from Iran could be frozen.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Lawmakers including members of Biden&rsquo;s own party voted on Thursday to approve a bill that would permanently freeze the funds, which were unfrozen by the White House in September as part of a controversial deal.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The bill, named the No Funds for Iranian Terrorism Act, passed in a 307 to 119 vote &ndash; which was approved by almost every Republican and 90 Democrats.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The money is being held in Qatar, where most negotiations between the West and terror groups take place these days. The reality is that Joe Biden had already &ldquo;refrozen&rdquo; the money after the October 7 Hamas terror attacks. Congress is now close to locking the door to those funds indefinitely.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Keep in mind that the money was originally leveraged to free five American hostages as well as five Iranian prisoners. But before the cash transfer was even complete, an even larger number of Americans were taken hostage by Hamas, which is almost entirely funded by Iran. In that sense, the United States was losing ground in the exchange, rather than getting something of value for the money.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Plenty of people were warning the Biden administration about this when the talks first began. This is why we&rsquo;ve long had a rule about not negotiating with terrorists. If you pay to secure the release of hostages, you will inevitably wind up with more hostages because the terrorists see that their tactics are working. And that&rsquo;s precisely where we are today.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://www.dailyfetched.com/blm-rioters-in-atlanta-who-burnt-down-wendys-get-500-fine/"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.dailyfetched.com/blm-rioters-in-atlanta-who-burnt-down-wendys-get-500-fine/</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>BLM Rioters in Atlanta Who Burnt Down Wendy&rsquo;s Get $500 Fine</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Two Black Lives Matter (BLM) rioters who pleaded guilty to torching Wendy&rsquo;s fast food restaurant in Atlanta in 2020 were sentenced to five years of probation and a $500 fine.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Chisom Kingston and Natalie White were charged with conspiracy to commit arson in the first degree, and two counts of first-degree arson.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Both pleaded guilty in a plea deal, according to court records.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Kingston and White must complete 150 hours of community service.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">In addition to charges, John Wesley Wade, 35, was indicted for the same fire in January this year.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Initially, all three pleaded not guilty and waived their arraignments in March 2022,</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The charges stem from BLM riots, which took place over the death of Rayshard Brooks, who was killed in a police-involved shooting in June 2020.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Brooks allegedly punched police officer David Brosnan and stole his taser while under investigation for a DUI in the parking lot of the Wendy&rsquo;s restaurant.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Brooks reportedly aimed the Taser at Officer Brosnan.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">However, a second officer, Garrett Rolfe, shot and killed rooks during the altercation.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Brooks allegedly punched Brosnan, causing a concussion.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">In response to the incident, BLM rioters burnt down Wendy&rsquo;s in protest of Brooks&rsquo; death.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Later, violent demonstrations exploded over the city in the months following.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Former Fulton County District Attorney charged officers Rolfe and Brosnan.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Brosnan was charged with aggravated assault, while Rolfe faces felony murder and assault charges.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Ninety-nine percent of charges brought against BLM rioters in 2020 were dropped by local prosecutors, according to an analysis from The Guardian.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Earlier this year, the United States Court of Appeals in Washington, DC, admitted that BLM rioters were treated better compared to some pro-life protesters.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The news comes just under a month after New York City officials agreed to pay $13 million to violent &ldquo;2020 Summer of Love&rdquo; BLM and Antifa protesters after they caused damage to 45 businesses.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://www.foxnews.com/us/derek-chauvin-returns-prison-after-alleged-blm-inspired-stabbing"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.foxnews.com/us/derek-chauvin-returns-prison-after-alleged-blm-inspired-stabbing</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Derek Chauvin returns to prison after alleged BLM-inspired stabbing</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Former Minneapolis police officer Derek Chauvin has returned to a federal prison in Arizona more than a week after a fellow inmate allegedly stabbed him 22 times with a shank in the library in a Black Friday attack partially inspired by the Black Lives Matter movement.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Chauvin is serving more than 20 years for the death of George Floyd and for depriving him of his civil rights in a May 2020 encounter that kicked off nationwide protests.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Chauvin's family is "very concerned about the facility&rsquo;s capacity to protect Derek from further harm," his lawyer, Greg Erickson, told the Minneapolis Star Tribune. "They remain unassured that any changes have been made to the faulty procedures that allowed Derek&rsquo;s attack to occur in the first place."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">John Turscak, 52, allegedly told federal correction officers that he targeted Chauvin because he was a high-profile inmate, that he plotted the attack for a month and that he would have killed him if guards had not intervened, according to court documents.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Turscak could see 60 years added to his federal sentence if he gets the maximum punishment on the four new charges he faces, which includes attempted murder. He was due for release in 2026, according to the Bureau of Prisons.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Turscak, a former gang member and snitch, was dropped as an FBI informant for dealing drugs, greenlighting assaults and extorting money, according to prosecutors.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">He allegedly told investigators that he picked Black Friday for the attack to symbolize both BLM and the "Black Hand" of the Mexican Mafia prison gang.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The attack took place from behind in the law library inside Federal Correctional Institution Tucson on Nov. 24.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Authorities said guards intervened "immediately," but Erickson questioned how fast the response really was &ndash; noting Chauvin's 22 stab wounds.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">"Why was Derek allowed into the law library without a guard in close enough proximity to stop a possible attack?" he asked. "His family continues to wonder."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Prison experts have warned that Chauvin, like other high-profile inmates, is at increased risk.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">"He was a dead man walking his first day in prison," said Keith Rovere, a former prison minister and the host of the "Lighter Side of Serial Killers" podcast. "This definitely won't be the last attack."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">In an appeal filed last month, Chauvin claimed new evidence shows he was not responsible for the death. Separately, the Supreme Court rejected his appeal for a new trial just days before the stabbing.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Chauvin was one of four officers who arrested Floyd that day after he allegedly passed a counterfeit $20 bill at a coffee shop and refused to cooperate with police.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Chauvin, who was seen on a video that prompted riots around the country, knelt on Floyd's neck for more than nine minutes leading up to his death.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Erickson previously slammed the prison for "poor procedures and lack of institutional control" &ndash; referencing an incident last year in which an inmate allegedly smuggled a firearm into the facility and tried to shoot someone.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Prison officials said they "[take] seriously our duty to protect the individuals entrusted in our custody, as well as maintain the safety of correctional employees and the community."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Citing privacy and safety concerns, authorities said they do not discuss the medical status or other "conditions of confinement" for inmates.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://www.worldofreel.com/blog/2023/12/1/hb03oy7zedb5m0rhj557tbnr6znepm"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.worldofreel.com/blog/2023/12/1/hb03oy7zedb5m0rhj557tbnr6znepm</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Raves for &lsquo;Godzilla Minus One&rsquo;</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Who&rsquo;s seen Toho&rsquo;s &ldquo;Godzilla Minus One&rdquo;? The reviews are almost all glowing. Unless I somehow missed my invitation, I don&rsquo;t believe there was a press screening for this one. Regardless, it made $11 million domestically this weekend, a real success.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&ldquo;Godzilla Minus One&rdquo; has a 97% (8.2/10) with critics, from 75 reviews. On Metacritic it&rsquo;s scoring a very strong 79/100 from 24 reviews. On IMDB, it has an impressive 8.5 user rating.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The film takes place in a devastated post-war Japan where Godzilla goes on a rampage. This is the second of the live-action Reiwa era &lsquo;Godzilla&rsquo; films, the first being 2016&rsquo;s &ldquo;Shin Godzilla&rdquo;. It looks as though director Takashi Yamazaki has made one of the better films of the franchise.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">This is the 37th film in the &lsquo;Godzilla&rsquo; franchise, and Toho's 33rd Godzilla film.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>It&rsquo;s been awhile guys&hellip; how about a little on this day in history?&nbsp;</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">On this day December 5th</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">771 Charlemagne becomes the sole King of the Franks after the death of his brother Carloman</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">1848 US President James K. Polk triggers gold rush of 1849 by confirming a gold discovery in California</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">1933 Prohibition ends in the US when 21st Amendment to the US Constitution ratified, 18th Amendment repealed (5:32 PM EST)</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">1973 Apple Records releases Paul McCartney &amp; Wings album "Band on the Run" in US; the commercial and critical pinnacle of his post-Beatle work tops the charts in 7 countries</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">2001 "Ocean's Eleven" directed by Steven Soderbergh, starring George Clooney, Brad Pitt, Matt Damon and Julia Roberts premieres in Westwood, California</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">2017 Russia is banned from the next Winter Olympics in South Korea over state-sponsored doping</span></li>
</ul>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Did you know? Ship the Mary Celeste is discovered mysteriously abandoned by her crew in the Atlantic Ocean on December 5th, 1872?&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">On November 7, 1872, the Mary Celeste set sail from New York City, with more than 1,700 barrels of alcohol destined for Genoa, Italy. On board were 10 people, including Captain Briggs, his wife, and their two-year-old daughter. Over the next two weeks, the ship encountered harsh weather. According to the last log entry&mdash;dated November 25&mdash;the Mary Celeste was some 6 nautical miles (11 km) from the Azores. Ten days later, December 5th, the vessel was spotted by the British brig Dei Gratia. Crew from that ship boarded the Mary Celeste and discovered it deserted. Although there was more than 3 feet (1 metre) of water in the hold&mdash;an amount that would not have caused panic&mdash;the vessel was seaworthy. Adding to the mystery was the fact that the cargo and personal belongings were largely undisturbed, although a longboat was missing. It appeared that the ship had been abandoned quickly. Crewmen from the Dei Gratia sailed the Mary Celeste to Gibraltar, some 800 miles (1,482 km) away. There British authorities conducted an investigation, which ultimately found no evidence of foul play.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">How about some famous birthdays for December 5th?</span></p>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Martin Van Buren was born on December 5th - 1782</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">George Armstrong Custer - 1839</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Walt Disney - 1901</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Little Richard - 1932</span></li>
</ul>]]></description>
   <author><![CDATA[Garrison Hardie]]></author>
   <enclosure url="https://app.dropwave.io/episode/9becad44-c74d-43be-ab58-78eeb4540012/daily-news-brief-for-tuesday-december-5th-2023.mp3" length="789" type="audio/mp3"/>
   <guid isPermaLink="false"><![CDATA[9becad44-c74d-43be-ab58-78eeb4540012]]></guid>
   <pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
   <source url=""><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></source>
   <itunes:author><![CDATA[Garrison Hardie]]></itunes:author>
   <itunes:image href="https://assets-cdn2.dropwave.io/2ab40ac0-e99d-4f25-a6d2-541d2c9b290a/cover-art/mUK8zsnHkCK3vep7E1W6UgYb9dTnLenASAMEFha3.jpg"/>
   <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
   <itunes:duration>789</itunes:duration>
   <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
  
  </item><item>
   <title><![CDATA[Daily News Brief for Friday, December 1st, 2023 [Daily News Brief]]]></title>
   <link/>
   <description><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">This is Garrison Hardie with your CrossPolitic Daily News Brief for Friday, December 1st, 2023.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Pub Membership Plug:</strong></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Public Houses, or Pubs, are not just places to drink beer, wine, cider or even something a little stronger. It is also a unique social centre, very often the focus of community life in villages, towns and cities throughout the length and breadth of the world. We here at CrossPolitic hope to emulate that for you and yours. That&rsquo;s why you should grab yourself a pub membership at fightlaughfeast.com&hellip; we need you on this ride with us. So pull up a chair, grab a pint, and join us on this ride at fightlaughfeast.com - that&rsquo;s fightlaughfeast.com.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://www.theblaze.com/news/damning-study-suggests-pandemic-lockdowns-accelerated-significant-memory-and-cognitive-decline-in-seniors"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.theblaze.com/news/damning-study-suggests-pandemic-lockdowns-accelerated-significant-memory-and-cognitive-decline-in-seniors</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Damning study suggests pandemic lockdowns accelerated 'significant' memory and cognitive decline in seniors</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The lockdowns and societal restrictions championed by teachers' unions and other leftists during the pandemic were not just ruinous for the mental health of children and teens. A new study out of the U.K. indicates pandemic restrictions also had a deleterious impact on the minds of the elderly.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Dr. Anne Corbett of the University of Exeter Medical School and her team examined neuropsychology data from 3,142 individuals, all 50 years of age or over, who had been participating in a multi-decade dementia study in Britain. The researchers compared data on this cohort collected before the pandemic, early in the pandemic, then once more toward the tail end of the pandemic.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The researchers observed "[s]ignificant worsening of executive function and working memory" in the first year of the pandemic across the whole cohort, the average age of which was 67.5. Working memory continued to worsen across the whole cohort in the second year of the pandemic. By the time restrictions had ultimately been eased, the damage had been done.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">According to the study, cognitive decline was significantly associated with reduced exercise and increased drinking across the whole cohort. Depression, another driving factor of cognitive decline, was notable amongst those who contracted COVID-19. Loneliness proved especially detrimental to those with mild cognitive impairment.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">"People aged 50 years and older in the UK had accelerated decline in executive function and working memory during the first year of the COVID-19 pandemic, during which the UK was subjected to three societal lockdowns for a total period of 6 months," said the study, published in the Lancet journal Healthy Longevity.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The British government, which funded this study via the National Institute for Health and Care Research, not only limited the number of times citizens could exercise outside during the pandemic, but shuttered gyms, golf courses, sports courts, swimming pools, and indoor sports facilities.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">"The scale of change is also of note, with all groups&mdash;the whole cohort and the individual subgroups&mdash;showing more than a 50% greater decline in working memory and executive function and many effect sizes reaching a clinically significant threshold of greater than 0&middot;3," said the researchers.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The researchers further stressed that "[t]hese factors map closely to the population-wide changes in health and lifestyle seen during and after the lockdowns, raising the important question of the effect of the pandemic on cognitive health and risk across populations."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://www.foxnews.com/politics/appeals-court-reinstates-gag-order-trump-fraud-case"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.foxnews.com/politics/appeals-court-reinstates-gag-order-trump-fraud-case</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Appeals court reinstates gag order in Trump fraud case</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">A New York appeals court reinstated a gag order preventing former President Donald Trump from maligning court staffers on Thursday.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">New York Judge Arthur Engoron had initially issued the gag order in early October after Trump lashed out at one of his law clerks on social media. Trump is currently fighting accusations of business fraud leveled by New York Attorney General Letitia James.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Appeals court Judge David Friedman had issued a stay on Engoron's gag order on Nov. 16, saying it potentially infringed on Trump's First Amendment rights.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">By that time, Engoron had already fined Trump $5,000 for violating the order on social media on Oct. 20, and did so again on Oct. 25 for another $10,000 before threatening imprisonment if further violations were committed.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Trump took the stand to testify personally in early November. He repeatedly cast James&rsquo; yearslong investigation and lawsuit as a "disgrace" and an attack on his business and his family.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Trump has denied any wrongdoing and insists his assets were actually undervalued. Trump has repeatedly said his financial statements had disclaimers requesting that the numbers be evaluated by the banks.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Engoron ruled in September that both Trump and his company had committed fraud by deceiving banks, insurers and others by overvaluing his assets and exaggerating his net worth on paperwork used in making deals and securing financing.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Trump has attacked Engoron and James &mdash; both Democrats &mdash; as politically biased "operatives."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">"They are defending the Worst and Least Respected Attorney General in the United States, Letitia James, who is a Worldwide disgrace, as is her illegal Witch Hunt against me. The Radical and Unprecedented actions of Judge Engoron will keep BUSINESSES and JOBS forever out of New York State," Trump wrote in a recent social media post.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://www.justfactsdaily.com/1-in-every-39-americans-will-die-of-a-drug-overdose-at-current-rate"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.justfactsdaily.com/1-in-every-39-americans-will-die-of-a-drug-overdose-at-current-rate</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>1 in Every 39 Americans Will Die of a Drug Overdose at Current Rate</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Despite the passage of state and federal laws that were supposed to reduce fatal drug overdoses, the annual U.S. drug overdose death rate has quintupled over recent decades:</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Over the most current year of available data, more than 110,000 people in the U.S. died of drug overdoses, a rate of 33 per 100,000 population.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">In order to measure these deaths in clear, relevant terms, Just Facts enlisted the expertise of a licensed actuary and a Ph.D. mathematician to calculate, double-check, and triple-check the average lifetime odds of dying of a drug overdose.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The shocking result of these calculations is that 1 in 39 people will have their lives cut short by drug overdoses if the rate of such deaths stays at the current level. Those odds will become far worse if the rising trend continues.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The lifetime risks of tragic events are much more revealing than the raw numbers or annual rates commonly reported by government agencies and the media. This is partly because the U.S. is the third-most populous nation in the world, so tens, hundreds, or even thousands of events may amount to a very low risk.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The other reason, which is less obvious, is explained by a 1987 Department of Justice report on the likelihood of being a crime victim:</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Annual victimization rates alone do not convey the full impact of crime as it affects people. No one would express his or her concern by saying, &ldquo;I am terribly afraid of being mugged between January and December of this year.&rdquo; People are worried about the possibility that at some time in their lives they will be robbed or raped or assaulted, or their houses will be burglarized.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Each month, the CDC estimates drug overdose deaths based on data reported by the 50 states and the District of Columbia. The latest estimates, which include deaths up through June 2023, show that 111,877 people died of a drug overdose in the prior 12 months.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">To place such figures into the broader context of the U.S. population and people&rsquo;s lifespans, Just Facts asked a licensed actuary to develop a method for calculating the average lifetime risk of death from various causes. The actuary used two separate methods, both of which yielded the same results. To further ensure accuracy, Just Facts had a Ph.D. mathematician check the formulas.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Applying this methodology to the CDC&rsquo;s latest estimates of overdose deaths, roughly 1 in every 39 people will die of drug overdose if the rate of such deaths stays at its current level.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Beyond lifetime risk, another important measure of a mortal danger is the years of life that it robs from its victims. Because humans cannot prevent death but only delay it, there is a material difference between the tragic premature deaths of a 20-year-old in the prime of her life and a 90-year-old in poor health.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Although some leading medical scholars ignored that vital fact during the Covid-19 pandemic, a 1983 CDC report about fatal accidents explains that the &ldquo;the allocation of health resources must consider not only the number of deaths by cause but also by age.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The average age of people who die of drug overdoses is about 43 years, while the average U.S. lifespan is about 77 years. In contrast, the average age of people whose deaths involved Covid-19 is about 75 years. Yet, government officials locked down entire states for extended periods to prevent the spread of Covid, causing multitudes of collateral deaths. This likely included overdoses, which soared in the wake of these measures.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://www.foxnews.com/sports/jets-aaron-rodgers-takes-big-step-hopeful-return-achilles-injury"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.foxnews.com/sports/jets-aaron-rodgers-takes-big-step-hopeful-return-achilles-injury</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Jets' Aaron Rodgers takes big step in hopeful return from Achilles injury</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The New York Jets opened the 21-day practice window for Aaron Rodgers on Wednesday, sparking hope the quarterback could return this season just mere months after tearing his Achilles.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Jets head coach Robert Saleh told reporters that it doesn&rsquo;t necessarily mean Rodgers is going to come back and play, but is rather a "progression in his rehab."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">"For Aaron, what he would be doing in practice is no different than what he&rsquo;d be doing on the field with regard to certain drills in the individual &ndash; instead of throwing with staff members, he&rsquo;s throwing with teammates," Saleh told reporters. "There&rsquo;s no added risk to it. There&rsquo;s certain things he&rsquo;s been cleared for that we&rsquo;re going to allow him to do."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Saleh lauded Rodgers&rsquo; drive and motivation for pushing himself to get back to where he is and the want and need for him to be with his teammates.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">"He&rsquo;s sacrificed so much already for the organization and himself and his teammates and he&rsquo;s doing it again. I think it&rsquo;s a testament to who he is as a human," Saleh added.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Rodgers&rsquo; timeline is still really unclear.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">He tried to lay it out the best he could in his appearance on "The Pat McAfee Show" this week.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">"Once I'm healthy, then it's where we're at, are we alive, are we in it&hellip; It's health first, and are we alive for the playoffs second.".</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">New York is 4-7 entering Week 13 and their playoff hopes are dwindling.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>]]></description>
   <author><![CDATA[Garrison Hardie]]></author>
   <enclosure url="https://app.dropwave.io/episode/eb95130b-9887-45f4-8c51-6a03065d5bcd/daily-news-brief-for-friday-december-1st-2023.mp3" length="652" type="audio/mp3"/>
   <guid isPermaLink="false"><![CDATA[eb95130b-9887-45f4-8c51-6a03065d5bcd]]></guid>
   <pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
   <source url=""><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></source>
   <itunes:author><![CDATA[Garrison Hardie]]></itunes:author>
   <itunes:image href="https://assets-cdn2.dropwave.io/2ab40ac0-e99d-4f25-a6d2-541d2c9b290a/cover-art/mUK8zsnHkCK3vep7E1W6UgYb9dTnLenASAMEFha3.jpg"/>
   <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
   <itunes:duration>652</itunes:duration>
   <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
  
  </item><item>
   <title><![CDATA[Daily News Brief for Thursday, November 30th, 2023 [Daily News Brief]]]></title>
   <link/>
   <description><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">This is Garrison Hardie with your CrossPolitic Daily News Brief for Thursday, November 30th, 2023.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Download our new app!:</strong></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">You guys are aware that we have a new app right? If not you should download it right now! Head on over to your app store, and type in &ldquo;CrossPolitic&rdquo;, &ldquo;Fight Laugh Feast&rdquo;, or &ldquo;PubTV&rdquo;. Once you find the app, you may need to update your app, or if you have a droid phone, you may need to delete your current FLF app, and re-download it! Once downloaded you&rsquo;ll be able to view or listen to our content right on your mobile device! As always, if you&rsquo;d like to sign up for a pub membership, you can head on over to fightlaughfeast.com&hellip; that&rsquo;s fightlaughfeast.com.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://www.dailysignal.com/2023/11/29/hidden-tax-how-much-does-regulation-cost-average-american-family/"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.dailysignal.com/2023/11/29/hidden-tax-how-much-does-regulation-cost-average-american-family/</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Here&rsquo;s How Much Regulations Cost Average American Family&mdash;and How Biden Is Making It Worse</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">FIRST ON THE DAILY SIGNAL&mdash;Americans expect to pay federal taxes, but the federal government also picks their pockets in more hidden ways, and President Joe Biden is making the problem worse in pursuing his political agenda, according to the Competitive Enterprise Institute.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">American households pay at least $14,000 in hidden regulatory costs every year,&rdquo; Wayne Crews, the Fred L. Smith fellow in regulatory studies at the institute, says in a new video provided exclusively to The Daily Signal.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://youtu.be/ANxJVzePPG0"><span style="font-weight: 400;" data-rich-links="{&quot;fple-t&quot;:&quot;10,000 Reasons to Reform the Regulatory State&quot;,&quot;fple-u&quot;:&quot;https://youtu.be/ANxJVzePPG0&quot;,&quot;fple-mt&quot;:null,&quot;type&quot;:&quot;first-party-link&quot;}">10,000 Reasons to Reform the Regulatory State</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;">- Play 0:00-1:18</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">His analysis&mdash;the latest in a series of annual reports&mdash;finds that the average American household pays $14,514 annually in a hidden regulatory cost.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Crews calculated the costs of regulation on the entire economy as $1.939 trillion, and found the average cost per household by dividing that gargantuan number by 133.6 million households.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">While federal law requires an annual estimate of the cost of regulation, the federal government has not met that requirement since 2002, according to the report. While the Office of Management and Budget has estimated some costs and benefits of major rules, the report finds those analyses incomplete because they do not encompass all rulemaking in each year.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Crews&rsquo; report uses a baseline of roughly $1.9 trillion for the costs of federal regulation, encompassing compliance costs, economic losses and losses in gross domestic product, social costs, and other costs. The analyst took recent government reports into account to reach the $1.939 trillion figure, although he acknowledged that it represents an estimate &ldquo;based on a nonscientific, disclaimer-laden, of GDP losses and compliance costs derived from available official data and other accessible sources.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The $1.9 trillion represents more than three-fifths the level of corporate pretax profits in 2022 ($3.138 trillion) and a far larger number than estimated corporate tax revenues ($382 billion).</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The report notes that while President Donald Trump&rsquo;s four years &ldquo;brought unique reversals, such as a reduced flow of new rules and some rollbacks of existing ones&rdquo;, President Joe Biden reversed those trends. &ldquo;Unprecedented open-ended deficits now standing at $1.4 trillion annually are expected to top $2 trillion annually by 2030,&rdquo; Crews writes. The national debt is nearing $34 trillion (at $33.8 trillion now, according to the U.S. Treasury), which Crews notes is &ldquo;up from almost $20 trillion when Donald Trump assumed office in 2017.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The report notes that Biden has launched many &ldquo;whole-of-government interventions,&rdquo; most notably on climate change and rooting out &ldquo;inequity from our economy.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&ldquo;These efforts have accelerated a long-standing process that is replacing self-determination and limited government with top-down behavioral, social, and civil rights codes,&rdquo; Crews writes.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Regulations issued by the executive branch far outstrip the number of laws Congress passes each year. During the 2022 calendar year, agencies issued 3,168 rules, while Congress enacted only 247 laws.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">While taxes clearly impact Americans&rsquo; pocketbooks and appear itemized on pay stubs, &ldquo;regulatory costs are baked into prices, without separate charges on receipts,&rdquo; the report notes. &ldquo;Many regulations have opportunity costs, which are invisible and impossible to calculate. They can affect households directly or indirectly, such as when businesses will pass some regulatory costs on to consumers, just as they do the corporate tax.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The report suggests a wide range of reforms to check the growth of regulation. It urges Congress to require congressional approval of significant or controversial agency rules before they become binding. It urges Congress to require annual regulatory transparency report cards and legislation requiring the automatic sunsetting of regulations. It urges Congress to pass a law preventing presidents from using &ldquo;emergency declarations&rdquo; to impose permanent government controls. It also urges Congress to identify which federal agencies do more harm than good and to eliminate them or shrink their budgets. It also urges Congress to set up a regulation-reduction commission to identify unneeded regulations to eliminate.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://mynorthwest.com/3940877/rantz-inside-look-seattle-antifa-antisemites-starbucks/"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://mynorthwest.com/3940877/rantz-inside-look-seattle-antifa-antisemites-starbucks/</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>An inside look as Seattle Antifa, antisemites vandalized Starbucks</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Antisemitic Antifa activists, anarchists and other radicals targeted the Seattle Starbucks Reserve Roastery as part of a call to &ldquo;Block Black Friday.&rdquo; They caused felony-level damage that led to one arrest.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Activists promoted direct action by sharing social media flyers. The flyer claims the protest and mass vandalism were &ldquo;autonomously organized by Seattle area radicals, anarchists, and community members.&rdquo; The hope was to &ldquo;shut [Black Friday] down for Palestine.&rdquo; They were mostly successful.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Exclusive videos from inside the caf&eacute; as Antifa and anarchists vandalized the storefront and taunted customers with vulgar hand gestures and taunts. It got so rowdy and dangerous that activists said they forced Starbucks to close.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Several dozen activists surrounded the Starbucks Roastery. Many of them were dressed in black bloc, a style of clothing intended to hide personally identifiable characteristics so that police have trouble making arrests. It&rsquo;s a hallmark of Antifa action.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The video shows one masked activist tagging the building with the phrase &ldquo;Free Palestine&rdquo; in spray paint. They also spray-painted the Palestinian flag, anarchist symbols and messages like &ldquo;Never Again,&rdquo; &ldquo;Free Gaza,&rdquo; , &ldquo;You are genocide supporters&rdquo; and &ldquo;Land Back.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The video also captures a masked activist flipping off customers. They even carved &ldquo;Free Gaza&rdquo; into the store&rsquo;s wooden door. Another activist pounds his hand on the storefront window, taunting customers. One of the windows was nearly shattered and must be replaced and security cameras on the roof were sprayed with paint.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&ldquo;During all of this, the atmosphere was upbeat but chill, with people eating tamales and drinking coffee that were being distributed from a truck parked next to the demo,&rdquo; an anonymous author published on Puget Sound Anarchists.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The anarchist went on to brag about how effective the Starbucks protest was for their movement.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The damage was significant, yet Seattle Police (SPD) did not intervene.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&ldquo;It was a temporary disruption that was handled and thankfully did not turn into a major issue,&rdquo; a Seattle Police Department spokesperson told The Jason Rantz Show on KTTH. &ldquo;As with any crime, incidents of vandalism are handled on a case-by-case basis. There are a multitude of factors that can determine when officers intervene. We are not at liberty to discuss our tactics as far as when officers will intervene.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The group marched into downtown Seattle after their assault on Starbucks. Once there, they disrupted the annual Seattle Christmas tree lighting ceremony.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The author admits that activists &ldquo;took over the stage soon after arriving and started throwing Christmas decorations to the ground and trashing the scenery.&rdquo; There were a handful of activists who stayed on the stage, holding a banner reading &ldquo;From Turtle Island to Gaza: Land Back.&rdquo; Land Back refers to a movement of literal land reclamation to its so-called original stewards.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">As activists chanted and gave speeches in front of a crowd angry that the ceremony was interrupted, an officer spotted suspect Tarik Aly Youssef, who is based in Vancouver, Washington.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">On a TikTik account (@_thesphinx_) that appears to belong to the 25-year-old suspect, Youssef described himself as a transgender, polyamorous, pansexual, anti-capitalist, autistic Egyptian who is an &ldquo;honorary member of Trantifa&rdquo; (a name for transgender Antifa members). After The Jason Rantz Show on KTTH contacted Youssef via TikTok, the account&rsquo;s videos were removed, and the account appears to be deleted.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://www.foxnews.com/politics/united-nations-set-call-americans-reduce-meat-consumption"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.foxnews.com/politics/united-nations-set-call-americans-reduce-meat-consumption</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>United Nations set to call on Americans to reduce meat consumption</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">A lead United Nations agency overseeing food and agriculture policy is expected to issue a road map in the coming weeks which will call on the West, including America, to dramatically reduce its meat consumption.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The UN's Food &amp; Agriculture Organization (FAO) will publish its so-called global food systems&rsquo; road map during the upcoming COP28 climate summit in Dubai which will kick off on Thursday and extend nearly two weeks until mid-December. FAO's first-of-its-kind document will recommend nations that "over-consume meat" to limit their consumption as part of a broader effort to reduce greenhouse gas emissions, Bloomberg reported.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">"The failure of leading meat and dairy companies to reduce emissions underlines the urgent need for more policy focus on the food and agriculture sector," Jeremy Coller, the chair and founder of the FAIRR Initiative, an investor network that works with financial institutions to promote climate-friendly agriculture worldwide, said in a recent statement.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">In addition to issuing guidelines for reducing meat consumption in the West, the FAO is expected to highlight how farmers should adapt to "erratic weather" and tackle their emissions produced from food waste and use of fertilizer, according to Bloomberg. The recommendations, which the U.S. COP28 delegation may sign onto, will not be binding.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Overall, the road map will seek to guide policy on lowering the climate impact of the global agriculture industry, which has rarely received such attention at past UN climate conferences. Past COP summits have been far more keen to address emissions generated from the global power, transportation and manufacturing sectors.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The global food system &mdash; which includes land-use change, actual agricultural production, packaging and waste management &mdash; generates about 18 billion tons of carbon dioxide per year, the equivalent of 34% of total worldwide emissions, according to a March 2021 study published in the Nature Food journal. FAO data indicates livestock alone is responsible for around 14.5% of global greenhouse gas emissions.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The UN has, for years, called for individuals to ditch animal-based diets, which it says "have a high impact on our planet." Instead, individuals should choose plant-based foods, according to the UN, which can reduce a person's annual carbon footprint by up to 2.1 tons.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">In the U.S., though, agriculture alone generates about 10% of total greenhouse gas emissions, federal data shows. The American agriculture sector accounts for just 1.4% of global emissions and has implemented a wide range of solutions, making it the nation's lowest-emitting economic sector.</span></p>]]></description>
   <author><![CDATA[Garrison Hardie]]></author>
   <enclosure url="https://app.dropwave.io/episode/e7b7fcfd-dbcb-4478-a3a9-86bc9a32656c/daily-news-brief-for-thursday-november-30th-2023.mp3" length="814" type="audio/mp3"/>
   <guid isPermaLink="false"><![CDATA[e7b7fcfd-dbcb-4478-a3a9-86bc9a32656c]]></guid>
   <pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
   <source url=""><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></source>
   <itunes:author><![CDATA[Garrison Hardie]]></itunes:author>
   <itunes:image href="https://assets-cdn2.dropwave.io/2ab40ac0-e99d-4f25-a6d2-541d2c9b290a/cover-art/mUK8zsnHkCK3vep7E1W6UgYb9dTnLenASAMEFha3.jpg"/>
   <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
   <itunes:duration>814</itunes:duration>
   <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
  
  </item><item>
   <title><![CDATA[Daily News Brief for Tuesday, November 28th, 2023 [Daily News Brief]]]></title>
   <link/>
   <description><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">This is Garrison Hardie with your CrossPolitic Daily News Brief for Tuesday, November 28th, 2023.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Kepler Education:</strong></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Kepler is an online marketplace for Classical Christian education that assures parents maintain their agency without forfeiting the assistance and expertise of qualified conservative Christian teachers. Kepler offers university model courses in the classical tradition that fit your schedule and budget. Visit </span><a href="http://www.kepler.education/"><span style="font-weight: 400;">www.kepler.education</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> and use our simple search tool to find the course and teacher that meets your child&rsquo;s needs. Or simply ask for help to get assistance from a real human being.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://www.theguardian.com/world/2023/nov/27/talks-under-way-to-extend-israel-hamas-ceasefire-as-return-to-fighting-looms"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.theguardian.com/world/2023/nov/27/talks-under-way-to-extend-israel-hamas-ceasefire-as-return-to-fighting-looms</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Talks under way to extend Israel-Hamas ceasefire as return to fighting looms</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Talks are under way to extend the temporary ceasefire in Gaza, with Hamas and Israel both saying they would like to see further releases of hostages in return for freedom for more Palestinians held in Israeli jails.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">But the ceasefire is due to expire, threatening a return to the bloody fighting and bombardment that has devastated swaths of Gaza, killed many thousands of civilians and caused an acute humanitarian crisis.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The third release of prisoners and of mostly Israeli hostages held in Gaza by Hamas took place without major problems on Sunday night.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Israel and Hamas have each raised concerns over the lists of hostages and Palestinian prisoners due to be released on Monday, which Qatari mediators are now working to resolve.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&ldquo;There is a slight issue with today&rsquo;s lists. The Qataris are working with both sides to &hellip; avoid delays,&rdquo; an official briefed on the matter said.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Seventeen hostages were released by Hamas on Sunday, including a Russian national and three Thai nationals. The Israelis were all women or children. Thirty-nine Palestinian prisoners, mostly children, were freed from Israeli jails, authorities said.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Benjamin Netanyahu, the Israeli prime minister, has said he did not want to end the ceasefire but pledged that Israel would resume its military offensive in Gaza at the end of the truce.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Netanyahu, who has promised Israelis he will &ldquo;crush&rdquo; Hamas, said he would welcome an extension to allow the release of 10 additional hostages every day in return for freedom for 30 Palestinian prisoners, as agreed under the original deal.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Israeli officials insist they will not call off their offensive until they are certain that Hamas no longer poses a threat to Israel.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Joe Biden said on Sunday that his administration would &ldquo;continue to remain personally engaged to see that this deal is fully implemented and work to extend the deal as well&rdquo;.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Local media in Israel reported optimism among senior officials that the truce, which was the result of several weeks of complex indirect negotiations mediated by the US, Qatar and Egypt, would be extended.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Sixty-two of the more than 240 hostages held by Hamas since last month have been released, one hostage was freed by Israeli forces, and two were found dead inside Gaza. A total of 117 Palestinians have been freed since the truce began.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Between 13,000 and 15,000 Palestinians have been killed by the Israeli offensive launched after the Hamas attack, roughly two-thirds of them women and children, according to the health ministry in Hamas-ruled Gaza. More than 1 million people have been forced from their homes.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The UN says the truce has made it possible to scale up the delivery of food, water and medicine to the largest volume since the start of the war. But the 160 to 200 trucks a day is still less than half what Gaza was importing before the fighting, while humanitarian needs have soared.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Details have emerged of the conditions of the detention of some hostages. Local media has reported shortages of food and medicine, and cramped accommodation possibly underground, but no physical mistreatment. According to one report, a former hostage has told his friends that his captors had brought other children to play with him while he was in captivity. Some learned of the fate of relatives from Hebrew-language radio networks they could listen to. Two teenagers learned that their mother had been killed and their father remained missing only when released.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Calls from the hostages&rsquo; families to prioritise their release have sharpened the dilemma facing Israel&rsquo;s leaders as they seek to reconcile the military offensive with the goal of freeing all of the captives.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://www.dailysignal.com/2023/11/23/new-biden-rule-reveals-transgender-movements-endgame-no-dissenting-parents-allowed/"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.dailysignal.com/2023/11/23/new-biden-rule-reveals-transgender-movements-endgame-no-dissenting-parents-allowed/</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Lack of &lsquo;Affirmation&rsquo; Is Child Abuse: New Biden Rule Applies Transgender Standard to Foster Care</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The transgender standard is set to become a litmus test for parenthood, according to the logic of a new policy working its way through the Department of Health and Human Services under President Joe Biden.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">A new rule in HHS&rsquo; Administration for Children and Families would apply the idea that any lack of &ldquo;affirmation&rdquo; constitutes a form of child abuse to foster care placements. Once that idea takes root in foster care, child protective services agencies might start applying it more broadly.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The rule would reinterpret the Social Security Act, which requires agencies to ensure that each child in foster care receives &ldquo;safe and proper&rdquo; care. The rule would lay out steps agencies must take to meet that requirement for &ldquo;LGBTQI+ children,&rdquo; defined as kids who &ldquo;identify as lesbian, gay, bisexual, transgender, queer or questioning, intersex, as well as children who are non-binary, or have non-conforming gender identity or expression.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Before agencies place a child with a foster parent, known as a &ldquo;provider,&rdquo; that person must &ldquo;establish an environment free of hostility, mistreatment, or abuse based on the child&rsquo;s LGBTQI+ status;&rdquo; receive training &ldquo;to be prepared with the appropriate knowledge and skills to provide for the needs of the child related to the child&rsquo;s self-identified sexual orientation, gender identity, and gender expression;&rdquo; and must be able to &ldquo;facilitate the child&rsquo;s access to age-appropriate resources, services, and activities that support their health and well-being.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">As the Ethics and Public Policy Center&rsquo;s Rachel Morrison pointed out for The Federalist Society, the rule does not define &ldquo;hostility,&rdquo; &ldquo;mistreatment,&rdquo; or &ldquo;abuse.&rdquo; However, it does clarify that &ldquo;a provider who attempted to undermine, suppress, or change the sexual orientation, gender identity, or gender expression of a child, including through the use of so-called &lsquo;conversion therapy,&rsquo; would not be a safe and appropriate placement.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The proposed rule cites medical associations such as the American Psychological Association to claim that efforts to &ldquo;undermine, suppress, or change&rdquo; sexual orientation, gender identity, or gender expression &ldquo;are not supported by evidence and have been rejected as harmful.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The rule does not acknowledge that gender ideology has infiltrated these medical associations and that many doctors&mdash;including those who once embraced gender ideology&mdash;have warned against confusing children on their gender and putting them on a path to mutilating their own bodies.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Dr. Stephen B. Levine, a psychiatrist and early proponent of transgender medical interventions, joined and briefly helped lead the Harry Benjamin International Gender Dysphoria Association, which later became the World Professional Association for Transgender Health, the central medical group that organizations such as the American Psychiatric Association rely upon.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">European countries, long considered more &ldquo;progressive&rdquo; than the U.S., have found a lack of evidence for medical interventions on children and are recommending a &ldquo;watchful waiting&rdquo; approach for minors.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Yet Levine argues that &ldquo;affirming&rdquo; a transgender identity is a &ldquo;powerful psychotherapeutic intervention&rdquo; that will set kids on the path to mutilation and sterilization&mdash;long before they have any concept about what their own fertility means.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Under Biden&rsquo;s proposed new rule, any potential foster parent who aims to protect a child from this confusion and damage may soon face expulsion from the program. That means the process will be designed to weed out guardians who actually would take good care of the kids and enable guardians who would assist in harming them.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">California&rsquo;s Democratic governor, Gavin Newsom, signed a bill turning California into a &ldquo;sanctuary state&rdquo; for &ldquo;gender-affirming care,&rdquo; which the law defines as an absolute right. The law gives California courts the ability to award custody over a child if someone removes the child from his or her parents in another state in order to obtain such &ldquo;care&rdquo; for that child despite the parents&rsquo; disagreement.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://dailycaller.com/2023/11/27/businesses-diversity-equity-inclusion-economic-uncertainty/"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://dailycaller.com/2023/11/27/businesses-diversity-equity-inclusion-economic-uncertainty/</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Businesses Ditch &lsquo;Diversity&rsquo; Initiatives In Droves Amid Economic Uncertainty</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Diversity, equity and inclusion (DEI) initiatives lost steam in 2023 compared to previous years as companies increasingly shift resources due to tightening economic condition</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The total percentage of American organizations with a DEI budget dropped 4 percentage points, from 58% in 2022 to 54% in 2023, while the number of organizations with a DEI strategy fell 9 points in that same time frame, according to a report from a consulting firm. DEI initiatives in the workplace gained huge traction following the death of George Floyd, which encouraged companies to divert resources to the practice, but now &ldquo;external forces,&rdquo; including tightening economic conditions as well as public and judicial pressure, are pushing back on those efforts.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&ldquo;After two years of unprecedented investment sparked by 2020&rsquo;s racial justice movement, this year, global momentum around DEI slowed,&rdquo; according to the report from Paradigm. &ldquo;There are a number of headwinds contributing to this shift: the first is economic uncertainty that not only led to reduced spending across the board, it also firmly shifted the power balance back to employers.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Despite the decline in funding, there was a 6-point increase in the number of companies that had a senior DEI leader and an 8-point increase in organizations that had goals related to representation for women in leadership from 2022 to 2023, according to Paradigm. A total of 20% of companies in 2023 had goals related to increasing employment related to race or ethnicity, which is a 4-point increase year-over-year.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The shift follows concerns from companies that the Supreme Court could target DEI and race-based hiring in the workplace the same way it struck down race-based admissions at colleges and universities earlier this year. A pair of decisions by the Supreme Court in June involving Harvard and the University of North Carolina cumulatively ruled that using race as a factor in college admissions is not permissible under the Fourteenth Amendment of the U.S. Constitution.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&ldquo;Over the past several months, we&rsquo;ve heard from a number of HR leaders who are de-emphasizing data and analytics as a part of their DEI efforts, in response to the changing legal landscape and increased scrutiny on DEI efforts,&rdquo; according to the report from Paradigm.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Only 26% of companies examine the final results of hiring by race or ethnicity, while 33% analyze promotions in the same manner, according to Paradigm. Around 36% of organizations measured the attrition rate of their employees by race or ethnicity.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Businesses pulled back from hiring in October, adding only 150,000 jobs for the month compared to 297,000 in September, while unemployment ticked up to 3.9% from 3.8%. The Leading Economic Index predicted that 2024 will only see 0.8% in the U.S. economy due to a possible recession.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://nypost.com/2023/11/26/business/ny-retailers-blast-hochul-over-theft-which-has-cost-stores-4-4-billion/"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://nypost.com/2023/11/26/business/ny-retailers-blast-hochul-over-theft-which-has-cost-stores-4-4-billion/</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>NY retailers lost $4.4 billion due to organized shoplifting rings in 2022: group</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Retailers across New York state say there&rsquo;s no end in sight to the rising epidemic of organized shoplifting rings &mdash; and warn it could lead to more store closures, increased costs for consumers and threats of violence against store employees.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Store owners said they lost $4.4 billion last year as a result of retail theft &mdash; which they say adds to the urgency for Gov. Kathy Hochul to crack down.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">However, Hochul vetoed a bipartisan bill last week &mdash; to the chagrin of store owners &mdash; that would have created a task force to combat organized theft.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Hochul rejected a proposal that would have created a 15-member panel made up of experts appointed by the governor, Legislature and the state attorney general that would have put together a list of recommendations to respond to retail theft.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The Retail Council of New York State, the Albany-based lobbying group which represents retailers statewide, said it was &ldquo;extremely disappointed&rdquo; by Hochul&rsquo;s veto.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Melissa O&rsquo;Connor, the president and CEO of the group, released a statement saying that she urged the governor to take &ldquo;immediate action&rdquo; so as to formulate &ldquo;an effective, collaborative response to this problem.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&ldquo;She made it abundantly clear that retail theft prevention will be a priority for her administration, and we look forward to working with her to achieve results,&rdquo; O&rsquo;Connor said.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">A spokesperson for Hochul said that adopting the proposal would have cost the state $35 million &mdash; an expenditure that wasn&rsquo;t allotted in the most recent budget.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Law enforcement officials from New York City to Albany to Syracuse have reported increases in incidents of retail theft &mdash; blaming the spike on progressive prosecutors who encourages criminal behavior with lenient punishment for shoplifters.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Last month, the chief of police in Syracuse said that the city has seen a 55% spike in shoplifting since 2021 &mdash; and that&rsquo;s a conservative estimate.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&ldquo;That number is likely higher because businesses often don&rsquo;t report it &mdash; but they do continue to express concerns,&rdquo; Syracuse Police Chief Joe Cecile said.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">So far this year, the Albany Police Department has fielded 23 calls for larcenies at a single Stewart&rsquo;s convenience store on Central Avenue &mdash; up from 14 at the same time in 2022.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The rash of retail thefts at the location forced the owner to shut down.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">A New York Police Department spokesperson pointed to crime statistics showing that there were more than 93,000 incidents of petty larceny through the end of October &mdash; which is 29% higher compared to the same period two years ago but 5% lower compared to the same period last year.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Around one-third of all shoplifting arrests in the five boroughs last year involved just 327 people who were collectively arrested and re-arrested a total of more than 6,000 times, according to the NYPD.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">These 327 alleged shoplifters targeted 18 department stores and seven chain pharmacy locations, which accounted for 20% of all complaints, the NYPD said.</span></p>]]></description>
   <author><![CDATA[Garrison Hardie]]></author>
   <enclosure url="https://app.dropwave.io/episode/83f73ff3-9ea0-429b-85a4-4be78e6bc1c4/daily-news-brief-for-tuesday-november-28th-2023.mp3" length="864" type="audio/mp3"/>
   <guid isPermaLink="false"><![CDATA[83f73ff3-9ea0-429b-85a4-4be78e6bc1c4]]></guid>
   <pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2023 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
   <source url=""><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></source>
   <itunes:author><![CDATA[Garrison Hardie]]></itunes:author>
   <itunes:image href="https://assets-cdn2.dropwave.io/2ab40ac0-e99d-4f25-a6d2-541d2c9b290a/cover-art/mUK8zsnHkCK3vep7E1W6UgYb9dTnLenASAMEFha3.jpg"/>
   <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
   <itunes:duration>864</itunes:duration>
   <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
  
  </item>
 </channel>
</rss>
