<?xml version="1.0"?>
<?xml-stylesheet href="/storage/feed-stylesheet.xsl" type="text/xsl"?>

<rss xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
 <channel>
  <title>FLF - Daily News Brief</title>
  <link>https://dropwave.io</link>
  <description><![CDATA[FIGHT LAUGH FEAST PRESENTS SHOWS PROCLAIMING THE LORDSHIP OF CHRIST OVER ALL OF LIFE.
]]></description>
  <language>en</language>
  <managingEditor><![CDATA[fightlaughfeast@gmail.com (FLF, LLC)]]></managingEditor>
  <webMaster><![CDATA[support@dropwave.io (DropWave Support)]]></webMaster>
  <pubDate>Fri, 05 Jan 2024 13:26:04 +0000</pubDate>
  <lastBuildDate>Fri, 05 Jan 2024 13:26:04 +0000</lastBuildDate>
  <image>
   <url>https://is4-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Podcasts113/v4/58/56/52/5856525c-2973-cf29-3db9-21faa8595391/mza_1144696925612154085.png/1200x1200bb.jpg</url>
   <link>https://dropwave.io</link>
   <title><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></title>
  </image>
  <itunes:author><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></itunes:author>
  <itunes:image href="https://is4-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Podcasts113/v4/58/56/52/5856525c-2973-cf29-3db9-21faa8595391/mza_1144696925612154085.png/1200x1200bb.jpg"/>
  <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
  <itunes:owner>
   <itunes:name><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></itunes:name>
   <itunes:email>fightlaughfeast@gmail.com</itunes:email>
  </itunes:owner>
  <itunes:category text="News"/>
  <item>
   <title><![CDATA[Daily News Brief for Friday, January 5th, 2024 [Daily News Brief]]]></title>
   <link/>
   <description><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">This is Garrison Hardie with your CrossPolitic Daily News Brief for Friday, January 5th, 2024.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Download our new app!:</strong></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">You guys are aware that we have a new app right? If not you should download it right now! Head on over to your app store, and type in &ldquo;CrossPolitic&rdquo;, &ldquo;Fight Laugh Feast&rdquo;, or &ldquo;PubTV&rdquo;. Once you find the app, you may need to update your app, or if you have a droid phone, you may need to delete your current FLF app, and re-download it! Once downloaded you&rsquo;ll be able to view or listen to our content right on your mobile device! As always, if you&rsquo;d like to sign up for a pub membership, you can head on over to fightlaughfeast.com&hellip; that&rsquo;s fightlaughfeast.com.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://www.foxnews.com/us/police-investigating-active-shooter-scene-high-school-perry-iowa"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.foxnews.com/us/police-investigating-active-shooter-scene-high-school-perry-iowa</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Multiple people injured in shooting at Perry, Iowa, high school</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Multiple people were injured in a shooting at an Iowa high school on Thursday morning, authorities said.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">At approximately 7:37 a.m., police received reports of an active scene at Perry High School in Perry. Officers responded within seven minutes of the active shooter alarm, Dallas County Sheriff Adam Infante told reporters.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The total number of victims and their status have not been confirmed. Infante said authorities are working to determine that information and that there is no further danger to the public.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">"The community is safe," the sheriff said. "We're just now working backwards, trying to figure out everything that happened and make notifications. There will be another update later on today."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The Associated Press reported two gunshot victims were taken by ambulance to Iowa Methodist Medical Center in the state capital of Des Moines.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">A law enforcement source told the AP the suspect in the shooting has died of what investigators believe is a self-inflicted gunshot wound.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Infante said the shooting happened before school began.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">"Luckily, there was very few students and faculty in the building, which I think contributed to a good outcome in that sense," he said.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Zander Shelley, 15, was in a hallway waiting for the school day to start when he heard gunshots and dashed into a classroom, his father, Kevin Shelley, told the AP. Zander was grazed twice and hid in the classroom before texting his father at 7:36 a.m.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Kevin Shelley, who drives a garbage truck, told his boss he had to run. "It was the most scared I&rsquo;ve been in my entire life," he said.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Rachael Kares, an 18-year-old senior, told the AP she was at jazz band practice when students heard what sounded like four gunshots, spaced apart.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">"We all just jumped," Kares said. "My band teacher looked at us and yelled, &lsquo;Run!&rsquo; So we ran."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Kares said students and faculty ran out past the football field, with people yelling, "Get out! Get out!" as they ran. She said she heard additional shots while she fled, but was most concerned about getting home to her 3-year-old son.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">"At that moment I didn&rsquo;t care about anything except getting out because I had to get home with my son," she told the AP.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The sheriff's office, Perry Police Department and multiple federal agencies also responded to the shooting.&nbsp;&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Authorities have identified a suspect but have not released their name at this time, the sheriff said.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Multiple EMS vehicles were sent to the scene at 1200 18th Street, according to public safety radio traffic.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Federal agents from the FBI and Bureau of Alcohol, Tobacco, Firearms and Explosives (ATF) also said they were on the ground.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Perry High School belongs to the Perry Community School District, about 25 miles northwest of Des Moines. About 1,785 students are enrolled in the school district, according to its website.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Thursday was the first day of school after the winter break, according to the school's calendar.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">"Our hearts are broken by this senseless tragedy. Our prayers are with the students, teachers &amp; families of the Perry Community," Iowa Gov. Kim Reynolds said in a statement. "I have been in contact with law enforcement agencies &amp; am continuing to monitor the situation. I will be joining their press conference today."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://www.theepochtimes.com/us/federal-judge-dismisses-trump-ballot-disqualification-case-with-prejudice-5558227?utm_source=partner&amp;utm_campaign=BonginoReport"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.theepochtimes.com/us/federal-judge-dismisses-trump-ballot-disqualification-case-with-prejudice-5558227?utm_source=partner&amp;utm_campaign=BonginoReport</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Federal Judge Dismisses Trump Ballot Disqualification Case &lsquo;With Prejudice&rsquo;</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">A federal judge in California on Jan. 3 dismissed a lawsuit that sought to keep former President Donald Trump off the 2024 Republican primary ballot in that state.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">District Judge David Carter granted a motion to dismiss the lawsuit &ldquo;with prejudice,&rdquo; which means that it can&rsquo;t be submitted to the same court again, according to court papers.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">A plaintiff attempted to argue that they suffered &ldquo;emotional injury&rdquo; as a result of the breach of the U.S. Capitol on Jan. 6, 2021, while watching the events unfold on television, on the radio, and in various publications. They then argued that the incident caused them &ldquo;severe emotional distress&rdquo; and then filed a lawsuit to keep the former president off California&rsquo;s ballot.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">However, the judge wrote that because the events occurred &ldquo;more than two years before the plaintiff&rdquo; filed suit, it was outside of the two-year statute of limitations.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The decision by Judge Carter, a Clinton-appointed jurist who has ruled against President Trump in a separate case, was posted online by former Republican National Committee for California Chair Harmeet Dhillon.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&ldquo;The remnants of the last California case to keep President Trump off the ballot here were dismissed today by Judge David O. Carter!!&rdquo; she wrote on X, formerly known as Twitter, on Jan. 3.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">In recent days and weeks, a number of lawsuits have been filed in different states seeking to bar President Trump from appearing on the ballot ahead of the 2024 election. Those suits have claimed that the former president engaged in &ldquo;insurrection or rebellion&rdquo; against the United States under an interpretation of the Constitution&rsquo;s 14th Amendment&rsquo;s Section 3, which was written in the immediate aftermath of the U.S. Civil War.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">At least two of those challenges have seen some success in Maine and Colorado, although there has been widespread speculation that higher courts or even the U.S. Supreme Court will strike those rulings down.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Days before Christmas, Colorado&rsquo;s highest court ruled to keep the former president off the primary ballot in the state, which was promptly appealed to the Supreme Court. Last week, Maine Secretary of State Shenna Bellows, a Democrat, unilaterally decided to keep President Trump off the ballot, which also has been appealed.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Ahead of the Supreme Court appeal, Trump campaign spokesman Steven Cheung said that &ldquo;unsurprisingly, the all-Democrat-appointed Colorado Supreme Court has ruled against President Trump, supporting a Soros-funded, left-wing group&rsquo;s scheme to interfere in an election on behalf of Crooked Joe Biden by removing President Trump&rsquo;s name from the ballot and eliminating the rights of Colorado voters to vote for the candidate of their choice.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Legal analysts have suggested that the U.S. Supreme Court would take up those two cases and likely would rule against the plaintiffs at least on procedural grounds. However, it isn&rsquo;t clear whether the court will take up the more thorny questions presented under the 14th Amendment&rsquo;s insurrection clause.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&ldquo;It seems a certainty that SCOTUS will have to address the merits sooner or later,&rdquo; Rick Hasen, a law professor at the University of California&ndash;Los Angeles, wrote on his website last month, referring to the Supreme Court.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Several other federal judges have also dismissed attempts to block the former president from appearing on ballots. In a ruling issued in late December 2023, U.S. District Judge Leonie Brinkema wrote that the plaintiffs&mdash;two activists&mdash;who filed suit against President Trump in Virginia to keep him on that state&rsquo;s ballot lacked standing.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://hotair.com/jazz-shaw/2024/01/03/trans-murderer-sent-to-womens-prison-n602445"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://hotair.com/jazz-shaw/2024/01/03/trans-murderer-sent-to-womens-prison-n602445</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Trans Murderer Sent to Women's Prison</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">In 2012 and 2013, a man named Steven Buchanan murdered two handymen he had hired to do some labor around his farm in Oregon. After killing them, he fed their corpses to his pigs. He was eventually discovered and arrested for the crimes. In 2015 he was convicted, with the judge telling him that he was &ldquo;a cold-blooded killer&rdquo; who &ldquo;valued pigs more than you value human life.&rdquo; Buchanan was sentenced to fifty years in prison. But then things reportedly took a turn for the strange. The killer was no longer Steven Buchanan. Instead, he was &ldquo;Susan Monica,&rdquo; claiming to be a transgender woman. As our colleague Madeline Lessman reports this week at Townhall, Monica nee Buchanan is now being housed at Coffee Creek Correctional Facility, a women&rsquo;s prison located in Wilsonville, Oregon.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">A &ldquo;transgender&rdquo; biological male who was convicted of murdering two men is serving a 50-year sentence in a women&rsquo;s prison, according to a report from Reduxx.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The prisoner, Steven Buchanan, who goes by &ldquo;Susan Monica,&rdquo; dismembered the bodies of his victims and fed them to pigs on a 20-acre farm he owned in Oregon, Reduxx noted. Buchanan bought the farm in 1991 and killed two handymen in 2012 and 2013. In 2015, he was reportedly sentenced to a minimum of 50 years behind bars.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&ldquo;You shot two people and fed them to your pigs,&rdquo; Judge Tim Barnack told Buchanan during sentencing. &ldquo;I don&rsquo;t know how else I can put it. You valued pigs more than you value people. It may sound harsh, but you are a cold-blooded killer.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">By this time, we&rsquo;ve covered enough of these transgender prisoner stories that you should have already noticed a pattern emerging. There are men behaving badly who never seemed to have any problem living as men. Then, why they are facing the possibility of a long stretch in the Crowbar Motel, they suddenly &ldquo;realize&rdquo; that they are actually women trapped in men&rsquo;s bodies and they demand special accommodations. And if they live in a blue state on the West Coast, those demands are almost always met.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">If the details of those two killings don&rsquo;t do enough to send chills down your spine and make you realize how dangerous this guy almost certainly is (even at the age of 75), there is more. During court proceedings, the lead detective in the case told the judge that Buchanan had said he was worried that if police found &ldquo;the other seventeen&rdquo; bodies on his farm, he might never get out of jail. Police searched and did some digging, but additional bodies were not located. That doesn&rsquo;t mean they&rsquo;re not there, though. This guy is a certifiable lunatic who told the police &ldquo;I do not value human life very much.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">This is the sort of person we&rsquo;re putting in a women&rsquo;s prison? I&rsquo;m sure some of the actual females at Coffee Creek Correctional Facility did some bad things to wind up there, though hopefully not involving feeding body parts to swine. But do they deserve to be exposed to a proven homicidal maniac who is pretending to be a woman? Townhall has been covering stories like this for a while and it never seems to end well. One trans inmate in New Jersey wound up impregnating two female inmates. (His own mother said that the trans thing was a scam allowing him access to women.) Another inmate was sexually assaulted by a trans inmate..</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://www.breitbart.com/europe/2024/01/03/sweden-records-coldest-january-evening-in-25-years/"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.breitbart.com/europe/2024/01/03/sweden-records-coldest-january-evening-in-25-years/</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Sweden Records Coldest January Evening in 25 Years</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Europe experienced stark weather contrasts on Wednesday, with extreme cold and snowstorms disrupting transportation and closing schools in Scandinavia while strong winds and heavy rain in western Europe caused flooding and at least one death.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Temperatures fell below minus 40 degrees Celsius (minus 40 degrees Fahrenheit) in the Nordic region for a second day in a row Wednesday. In Kvikkjokk-&Aring;rrenjarka in Swedish Lapland, the mercury dropped to minus 43.6 C (minus 46.5 F), the lowest January temperature recorded in Sweden in 25 years, Sweden&rsquo;s TT news agency reported.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Extremely cold temperatures, snow and gale-force winds disrupted transportation throughout the Nordic region, with several bridges closed and some train and ferry services suspended. Several schools in Scandinavia were closed.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Police across most of Denmark urged motorists to avoid unnecessary trips as wind and snow battered the northern and western parts of the country.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Mild but wet and windy conditions prevailed further south, where a storm wreaked havoc in parts of western Europe.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">In Britain, a driver died after a tree fell on his car in western England. Gloucestershire Police said the man died in the incident near the town of Kemble on Tuesday afternoon.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The storm, which has been named Henk by the official weather services of Britain, Ireland and the Netherlands, has caused power cuts, transport troubles, property damage and disruption across the U.K.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">More than 300 flood warnings were in place across England and Wales on Wednesday, while 10,000 homes remained without power. A severe flood alert, meaning a danger to life, was announced for the River Nene in Northampton in central England. Several residents were evacuated from houseboats and caravans at the nearby Billing Aquadrome.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The U.K.&rsquo;s rail network was hit by flooding and power cuts, with many operators reporting ongoing issues for the Wednesday morning commute into work.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The strongest gales in the U.K. were recorded on the Isle of Wight, just off the coast in southern England, where wind speeds reached 94 miles per hour (151 kilometers per hour).</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">In the Netherlands, police near the city of Eindhoven said strong winds may have played a role in the death of a 75-year-old man who fell off his bicycle late Tuesday as high winds lashed much of the country.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Parts of Germany were also grappling with flooding, which could be aggravated by more rain falling in the worst-affected northwestern state of Lower Saxony.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://www.boundingintosports.com/2024/01/aaron-rodgers-says-jimmy-kimmel-is-worried-about-the-jeffrey-epstein-files-suggests-nfl-is-rigged/"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.boundingintosports.com/2024/01/aaron-rodgers-says-jimmy-kimmel-is-worried-about-the-jeffrey-epstein-files-suggests-nfl-is-rigged/</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Aaron Rodgers Says Jimmy Kimmel Is Worried About The Jeffrey Epstein Files, Suggests NFL Is Rigged</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">If you thought New York Jets quarterback Aaron Rodgers had any designs on pulling back on his opinions in the new year, think again. During an appearance on The Pat McAfee Show, the 40-year-old future NFL Hall of Famer suggested late-night talk show host Jimmy Kimmel might be nervous about the release of the Jeffrey Epstein files. Oh, and he also floated the idea that the NFL is rigged.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Aaron Rodgers kicked off a segment with the host by embracing a conspiracy theory that the Super Bowl logo features the colors of the teams that eventually end up playing in the game.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">An X post by NFL Memes in September included an image that explained the theory and showed recent examples. The group also predicted that based on this theory, the Baltimore Ravens and San Francisco 49ers would be facing each other in Super Bowl LVIII.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&ldquo;If the Super Bowl Baltimore and San Fran, I&rsquo;ll tell you what, that Super Bowl 59 emblem better have Jet green on it,&rdquo; Rodgers said.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&ldquo;I know you&rsquo;ve seen that one &hellip; that&rsquo;s a real interesting one,&rdquo; Rodgers said of the conspiracy theory.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://twitter.com/i/status/1742256969883492467"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://twitter.com/i/status/1742256969883492467</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> - Play Video&nbsp;</span></p>]]></description>
   <author><![CDATA[garrison Hardie]]></author>
   <enclosure url="https://app.dropwave.io/episode/017c1681-8632-424b-804d-0dae83fc3069/daily-news-brief-for-friday-january-5th-2024.mp3" length="957" type="audio/mp3"/>
   <guid isPermaLink="false"><![CDATA[017c1681-8632-424b-804d-0dae83fc3069]]></guid>
   <pubDate>Fri, 05 Jan 2024 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
   <source url=""><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></source>
   <itunes:author><![CDATA[garrison Hardie]]></itunes:author>
   <itunes:image href="https://assets-cdn2.dropwave.io/2ab40ac0-e99d-4f25-a6d2-541d2c9b290a/cover-art/mUK8zsnHkCK3vep7E1W6UgYb9dTnLenASAMEFha3.jpg"/>
   <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
   <itunes:duration>957</itunes:duration>
   <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
  
  </item><item>
   <title><![CDATA[Daily News Brief for Thursday, January 4th, 2024 [Daily News Brief]]]></title>
   <link/>
   <description><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">This is Garrison Hardie with your CrossPolitic Daily News Brief for Thursday, January 4th, 2024.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Pub Membership Plug:</strong></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Public Houses, or Pubs, are not just places to drink beer, wine, cider or even something a little stronger. It is also a unique social centre, very often the focus of community life in villages, towns and cities throughout the length and breadth of the world. We here at CrossPolitic hope to emulate that for you and yours. That&rsquo;s why you should grab yourself a pub membership at fightlaughfeast.com&hellip; we need you on this ride with us. So pull up a chair, grab a pint, and join us on this ride at fightlaughfeast.com - that&rsquo;s fightlaughfeast.com.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://www.foxbusiness.com/politics/us-national-debt-tops-34t-first-time-history"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.foxbusiness.com/politics/us-national-debt-tops-34t-first-time-history</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>US national debt tops $34T for first time in history</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The U.S. national debt topped $34 trillion for the first time ever, crossing a critical milestone at a time when government spending is already under scrutiny.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The national debt &ndash; which measures what the U.S. owes its creditors &mdash; hit $34 trillion as of Friday afternoon, according to new data published by the Treasury Department. By comparison, just four decades ago, the national debt hovered around $907 billion.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&nbsp;"We are beginning a new year, but our national debt remains on the same damaging and unsustainable path," said Michael Peterson, CEO of the Peter G. Peterson Foundation, which advocates for fiscal sustainability.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The historic debt level comes as Congress races to finalize critical funding bills in order to prevent a government shutdown.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The national debt is expected to nearly double in size over the next three decades, according to the latest findings from the Congressional Budget Office. At the end of 2022, the national debt grew to about 97% of gross domestic product.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Under current law, that figure is expected to skyrocket to 181% at the end of 2053 &ndash; a debt burden that will far exceed any previous level.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">"Though our level of debt is dangerous for both our economy and for national security, America just cannot stop borrowing," said Maya MacGuineas, president of the Committee for a Responsible Federal Budget.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The White House was quick to blame Republicans on Tuesday evening for the astronomical rise in the federal debt.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">"This is the trickle-down debt &mdash; driven overwhelmingly by repeated Republican giveaways skewed to big corporations and the wealthy," Michael Kikukawa, White House assistant press secretary, said in a statement provided to FOX Business.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Even more worrisome is that the spike in interest rates over the past year and a half has made the cost of servicing the national debt more expensive.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">That is because as interest rates rise, the federal government's borrowing costs on its debt will also increase. In fact, interest payments on the national debt are projected to be the fastest-growing part of the federal budget over the next three decades, according to the CRFB.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Payments are expected to triple from nearly $475 billion in fiscal year 2022 to a stunning $1.4 trillion in 2032. By 2053, the interest payments are projected to surge to $5.4 trillion.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">To put that into perspective, that will be more than the U.S. spends on Social Security, Medicare, Medicaid and all other mandatory and discretionary spending programs.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://mynorthwest.com/3944857/rantz-homeless-fecal-matter-behind-explosion-shigella-cases-portland/"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://mynorthwest.com/3944857/rantz-homeless-fecal-matter-behind-explosion-shigella-cases-portland/</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Homeless fecal matter behind explosion of Shigella cases in Portland</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Homeless people are spreading Shigella in and around downtown Portland, Oregon. Cases are now surging and could lead to a public health emergency.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Shigella is a highly contagious bacteria that spreads through fecal matter. It&rsquo;s usually spread when the bacteria is on someone&rsquo;s hand and then they touch their mouth, or through sex. The Portland metro saw at least 218 cases of shigellosis in 2023, with 45 cases in December alone. Many of them occurred in Old Town.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">As cases rise, Multnomah County Deputy Health Officer Dr. Teresa Everson is advising the public to be alert, but not panic, as the cases are not occurring in the general public. But there&rsquo;s fear in the community that that may change. The county is offering some infected homeless people free motel rooms to isolate in so they can mitigate the spread.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&ldquo;These cases can occur because bathrooms, handwashing sinks and soap can be hard to access when you aren&rsquo;t housed,&rdquo; she told KGW-TV. &ldquo;And unhoused community members are at higher risk of infectious diseases in general, as they experience poorer health than the broader public.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Still, Everson advises people living and working in Old Town to be extra vigilant in washing hands. Though, she said most of the cases appear to be a result of sexual contact.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Symptoms of Shigella infection include diarrhea, stomach cramps fever and vomiting that can last anywhere from three to 10 days. It can be treated with antibiotics.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Though it&rsquo;s rare to see this specific kind of outbreak amongst the homeless, once it spreads, it may be hard to contain since the homeless aren&rsquo;t especially hygienic with a lack of access to restrooms. But it&rsquo;s a crisis of Portland&rsquo;s own making. Permissive left-wing policies have allowed homelessness to explode in Portland, rendering the city unrecognizable.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">In the waning months of 2023, officials finally committed to implementing a new strategy to target homelessness after public pressure forced them to accept the reality on its streets. In a long-overdue move, the city finally decided to enforce a camping ban on public property. The new policy was set to put much-needed restrictions in place, banning camping on all public property from 8 a.m. to 8 p.m. and limiting it during other hours. It&rsquo;s a clear message: No more overnight stays in city parks, along riverbanks or near busy streets.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">But a judge stopped the ban from commencing after activist attorneys representing five homeless Portlanders sued the city. It&rsquo;s part of a consistent strategy to stop any homeless policies from being enforced, with Radical Left activists fighting to keep homeless on the streets where they will now spread Shigella.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Seattle and King County experienced a similar surge in cases that were addressed in 2021 after Public Health learned that 84% of the cases hit the homeless.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://www.foxnews.com/world/japan-airlines-passenger-plane-burst-flames-tokyos-haneda-airport"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.foxnews.com/world/japan-airlines-passenger-plane-burst-flames-tokyos-haneda-airport</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Japan Airlines plane bursts into flames after collision at Tokyo's Haneda airport, leaving 5 dead</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">A thick plume of black smoke rose over an airport runway in Japan on Tuesday after a Japanese aircraft collided with a coast guard aircraft and burst into flames, local media reported.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Live footage on public broadcaster NHK showed Japan Airlines passenger plane JAL-516 on a runway at Tokyo's Haneda airport with flames coming out of its windows. Shortly after, the plane was entirely consumed.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The coast guard aircraft pilot escaped, but the five crewmembers were killed, NHK reported. An official confirmed that a Bombardier Dash-8 Coast Guard plane was involved in the collision.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">A Japan Airlines spokesperson said more than 300 passengers were on board when the aircraft initially caught fire. NHK reported all 379 passengers and crew ultimately escaped from the plane.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The aircraft JAL flight 516 had flown out of Shin Chitose airport in Japan to Haneda, officials said. Haneda is one of the busiest airports in Japan.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">All runways and services at the airport were suspended.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://townhall.com/tipsheet/spencerbrown/2024/01/02/veterans-and-service-members-demand-pentagon-accountability-for-vaccine-mandates-n2633048"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://townhall.com/tipsheet/spencerbrown/2024/01/02/veterans-and-service-members-demand-pentagon-accountability-for-vaccine-mandates-n2633048</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>'Enough Is Enough': Veterans and Service Members Demand Accountability From DoD</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Saying that "all internal efforts to rectify recent criminal activity within the Armed forces" have been "exhausted," more than 200 military veterans and service members signed and published a "Declaration of Military Accountability" on January 1 over the Department of Defense's its enactment and enforcement of the COVID-19 vaccine mandate.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Invoking the Declaration of Independence in a declaration of their own, the current and former members of the U.S. military state that America has reached a point in its history where it is "necessary to admonish the lawless, encourage the fainthearted, and strengthen the weak" as the "affairs of our nation are now steeped in avaricious corruption and our once stalwart institutions, including the Dept of Defense, are failing to fulfill the moral obligations upon which they were founded."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Unlike the Declaration of Independence, the signers of the Declaration of Military Accountability "seek no separation" as the patriots of 1776 did from Great Britain, "but through this letter and the efforts we pledge herein, we pursue restoration through accountability."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">On the Pentagon's enactment of the COVID-19 vaccine mandate, the declaration states that "military leaders broke the law, trampled constitutional rights, denied informed consent, permitted unwilling medical experimentation, and suppressed the free exercise of religion," actions that meant "[s]ervice members and families were significantly harmed."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">"Their suffering continues to be felt financially, emotionally, and physically," the declaration emphasizes of those affected by the DoD's COVID-19 vaccine mandate. "Some service members became part of our ever-growing veteran homeless population, some developed debilitating vaccine injuries, and some even lost their lives."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Despite these outcomes, the declaration says "military leaders are continuing to ignore our communications regarding these injuries and the laws that were broken," calling the DoD's silence "an apparent attempt to avoid accountability."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Naming a list of military leaders who "enabled lawlessness and the unwilling experimentation on service members" including "GEN Milley, ADM Grady, GEN McConville, ADM Gilday, ADM Lescher, Gen Brown, Gen Berger, Gen Smith, VADM Kilby, VADM Nowell, VADM Fuller, LTG Martin, Lt Gen Davis, MG Edmonson, GEN Williams, ADM Fagan, VADM Buck, Lt Gen Clark, MG Francis, LTG Dingle, Lt Gen Miller, RADM Gillingham, and numerous others," the declaration emphasizes that they "betrayed the trust of service members and the American people."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">"Their actions caused irreparable harm to the Armed Forces and the institutions for which we have fought and bled," the current and former members of the military say. "These leaders refused to resign or take any other action to hold themselves accountable, nor have they attempted to repair the harm their policies and actions have caused."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Due to this lack of accountability, the 231 signatories to the declaration state their intention to "do everything morally permissible and legally possible to hold our own leadership accountable" because they "as service members and veterans...feel particularly responsible for the DoD and, in according with our oaths...will make every effort to demonstrate by example how an institution can put its own house in order."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Signing "on behalf of hundreds of thousands of service members and the American people, while appealing to the Supreme Judge of the world for guidance and purity of intention, mutually pledge to each other that we will do everything in our power, through lawful word and action, to hold accountable military leaders who failed to follow the law when their leadership and moral courage was most desperately needed," the declaration explains.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The action that will follow from the declaration, it explains, includes running for Congress and seeking appointments within the executive branch while those in active service "will continue to put fulfilling our oaths ahead of striving for rank or position."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">In addition, the declaration pledges that those who have the legal authority to do so will "recall from retirement the military leaders who broke the law and will convene courts-martial for the crimes they committed." Those who become lawmakers will "introduce legislation to remove all retirement income for the military leaders who were criminally complicit, and we will ensure none serve in or retire from the Senior Executive Service."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Emphasizing that fulfilling their oaths to the Constitution requires "persistent vigilance," the declaration's signers also pledge to "train those who come after us to fulfill their duty in achieving this accountability and safeguarding against such leadership failures hereafter."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">"While all good things come to an end, we refuse to allow our nation to go quietly into the depths of decadence and decay," the veterans and service members declare. "We promise to exhaust all moral, ethical, and legal means to restore the rule of law and will begin by attempting to hold senior military leaders accountable" in addition to fighting to enforce the Constitution and "put an end to the two-tiered justice system."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The Declaration concludes: "May future generations see our efforts and, God willing, may they also be recipients of the great gift of liberty that we have had the honor of safeguarding.&rdquo;</span></p>]]></description>
   <author><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></author>
   <enclosure url="https://app.dropwave.io/episode/8d72ead1-fcce-4b4b-8a98-65694e62b5e6/daily-news-brief-for-thursday-january-4th-2024.mp3" length="742" type="audio/mp3"/>
   <guid isPermaLink="false"><![CDATA[8d72ead1-fcce-4b4b-8a98-65694e62b5e6]]></guid>
   <pubDate>Thu, 04 Jan 2024 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
   <source url=""><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></source>
   <itunes:author><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></itunes:author>
   <itunes:image href="https://assets-cdn2.dropwave.io/2ab40ac0-e99d-4f25-a6d2-541d2c9b290a/cover-art/mUK8zsnHkCK3vep7E1W6UgYb9dTnLenASAMEFha3.jpg"/>
   <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
   <itunes:duration>742</itunes:duration>
   <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
  
  </item><item>
   <title><![CDATA[Daily News Brief for Wednesday, January 3rd, 2024 [Daily News Brief]]]></title>
   <link/>
   <description><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">This is Garrison Hardie with your CrossPolitic Daily News Brief for Wednesday, January 3rd, 2024.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>Fight Laugh Feast Magazine&nbsp;&nbsp;</strong></span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Our Fight Laugh Feast Magazine is a quarterly issue that packs a punch like a 21 year Balvenie, no ice. We don&rsquo;t water down our scotch, why would we water down our theology? Order a yearly subscription for yourself and then send a couple yearly subscriptions to your friends who have been drinking luke-warm evangelical cool-aid. Every quarter we promise quality food for the soul, wine for the heart, and some Red Bull for turning over tables. Our magazine will include cultural commentary, a Psalm of the quarter, recipes for feasting, laughter sprinkled through out the glossy pages, and more. Sign up today, at fightlaughfeast.com.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://dailycaller.com/2024/01/01/universities-college-course-queer-sex-bdsm-bitch/"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://dailycaller.com/2024/01/01/universities-college-course-queer-sex-bdsm-bitch/</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>&lsquo;Queering God&rsquo; And &lsquo;How To Be A Bitch&rsquo;: Here Are Just A Few Of The Craziest Courses Universities Offered In 2023</strong></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Universities offered students in the U.S. the opportunity to enroll in many courses that push gender ideology and left-wing activism during the 2023-2024 school year.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Princeton University offered a class titled &ldquo;Black + Queer in Leather: Black Leather/BDSM Material Culture&rdquo; in the Spring 2023 semester, according to the university&rsquo;s course catalog. The class will survey black BDSM culture via research available in libraries and individuals involved in the groups that participate in the culture.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">&ldquo;We will consider the fragility of archival engagement with these communities by surveying existing BDSM archives in research libraries, community groups,&rdquo; the course description reads.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Princeton made headlines in 2022 following the addition of this course to the catalog as well as &ldquo;FAT: The F-Word and the Public Body&rdquo; and &ldquo;Anthropology of Religion: Fetishism and Decolonization.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Tuition at Princeton costs more than $59,000 per year and can cost more than $76,000 including housing and food costs, according to the university&rsquo;s website.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Westminster College offers a course titled &ldquo;How to Be a Bitch.&rdquo; Students are encouraged to &ldquo;unpack&rdquo; the words &ldquo;bitch&rdquo; and bossy,&rdquo; which are &ldquo;interesting but problematic.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">One course offered at Wesleyan University, titled &ldquo;Queer Russia,&rdquo; offers students an overview of the influence of queer people on Russian culture, according to the university&rsquo;s 2023-2024 course catalog. The course &ldquo;focuses on gender and sexuality in exploring an alternative cultural history of Russia, which highlights its queer legacy from the nineteenth century to the present.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Wesleyan announced it would cover abortion-related costs and emergency contraception for students in the fall 2023 semester. The university charges more than $66,000 a year for tuition and nearly $20,000 for housing, according to their website.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Occidental College in California offers a course titled &ldquo;Black Queer Thought,&rdquo; according to the university&rsquo;s 2023-2024 course catalog. The course critiques &ldquo;the demands of heteronormativity, white supremacy, patriarchy and capitalism.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The course also explores &ldquo;how the cultural producers in question complicate and elaborate upon the sometimes static and often U.S.-centered definitions we hold for &lsquo;Black&rsquo; and &lsquo;queer,'&rdquo; according to the course&rsquo;s description.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The Southern University of Oregon (SOU) offered a class titled &ldquo;Decolonizing Transgender&rdquo; in the 2023-2024 academic year, according to the university&rsquo;s course catalog. The course examines the development of the word transgender across &ldquo;social, cultural, historical, legal, medical, and political contexts.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The course can be taken as a part of the university&rsquo;s &ldquo;Certificate in Transgender Studies,&rdquo; according to the school&rsquo;s website.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The University of Chicago offered a course titled &ldquo;Queering God&rdquo; that questions if God is queer and what queerness has to do with the concept of God. &ldquo;What does queerness have to do with Judaism, Christianity, or Islam?&rdquo; the course description reads.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The university made headlines for its &ldquo;Queering God&rdquo; class in July. The school also offered a class titled &ldquo;The Problem of Whiteness&rdquo; initially in December 2022 but later moved the course to the Spring 2023 semester after backlash to the course.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">A course titled &ldquo;Unsettling Whiteness&rdquo; was offered by Northwestern University in the 2023-2024 school year, according to the university&rsquo;s course catalog. The course seeks to make the &ldquo;historical, political, and cultural formation of whiteness in Western modernity visible&rdquo; for analysis.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Students at Northwestern hosted a speaker in April that accused Israelis of eating the organs of Palestinians. Tuition at the school for the 2023&ndash;24 academic year was estimated to be nearly $65,000 and nearly $92,000 with all expenses including books, fees, room and board, according to the university&rsquo;s website.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Davidson College offered a course titled &ldquo;Latinx Sexual Dissidence and Guerrilla Translation,&rdquo; according to the university&rsquo;s 2023-2024 course catalog. The class seeks to mix feminist, queer, body positivity and leftist activism all into one class.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">&ldquo;Students will study the rhetorics and aesthetic strategies of feminist and queer activist collectives focused on social issues such as immigration, transgender rights, anti-racism, economic equality, anti-speciesim, body positivity, and prison abolition with a pro-pleasure, leftist perspective,&rdquo; the course description reads.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Westminster College, Princeton, Wesleyan, Occidental College, SOU, Northwestern, the University of Chicago and Davidson College did not respond to the Daily Caller News Foundation&rsquo;s requests for comments.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/news/campaigns/trump-fox-news-town-hall-snub-cnn-iowa-debate"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/news/campaigns/trump-fox-news-town-hall-snub-cnn-iowa-debate</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>Trump holds Fox News town hall to counter CNN Iowa debate with DeSantis and Haley</strong></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Fox News is set to hold a town hall event in Des Moines, Iowa, with President Donald Trump on Jan. 10 at 9 p.m. Eastern time, a move that directly competes with CNN's Iowa GOP primary debate held on the same night at the same time.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The Fox News Trump event, announced on Tuesday, marks the former president's fifth time snubbing a debate matchup with his 2024 Republican rivals. He has skipped all four primary debates sponsored by the Republican National Committee.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Bret Baier and Martha MacCallum will co-moderate the Trump town hall for the first time since May 2020, when Trump last sat down for an interview with the pair. The Jan. 10 town hall, just five days before the Iowa caucuses, also marks Trump's return to holding counterevents during GOP debate nights.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">He held a competing event during the first three GOP debates, including the first one in late August, which was co-sponsored with Fox News. But the former president did not seek to take attention from his rivals during last month's fourth GOP debate in Tuscaloosa, Alabama.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">CNN's debate on Jan. 10 required candidates to reach at least 10% in three national or Iowa polls, but only Trump, Gov. Ron DeSantis (R-FL), and former United Nations Ambassador Nikki Haley have met the qualifications.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Vivek Ramaswamy also announced on Tuesday he will participate in a live studio town hall with podcast host Tim Pool, as it appears he likely won't make the CNN debate qualification deadline on Tuesday. "Forget @CNN&rsquo;s fake Iowa 'debate' on Jan 10 which will be the most boring in modern history," he posted on X, formerly known as Twitter. "We&rsquo;re doing a live-audience show that night in Des Moines with @Timcast instead. Won&rsquo;t hold back."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Trump dominates his competitors at 62.5%, according to a RealClearPolitics poll average. DeSantis and Haley are polling at 11.2%, followed by Ramaswamy at 4.2%.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The former president is seeking a strong showing in Iowa as DeSantis and Haley seek to become the dominant second place in the field. CNN's debate will be the final time before the Iowa caucuses that DeSantis and Haley will face off. Trump, meanwhile, is likely to brag about his advantageous lead during the competing town hall and denigrate his competitors.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://www.dailyfetched.com/tucker-tells-dan-bongino-that-trump-assassination-could-be-next/"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.dailyfetched.com/tucker-tells-dan-bongino-that-trump-assassination-could-be-next/</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>Tucker Tells Dan Bongino That Trump &lsquo;Assassination&rsquo; Could Be Next</strong></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Former Fox News host Tucker Carlson warned in an interview with conservative commentator and author Dan Bongino that the establishment may be preparing to assassinate President Donald Trump in a desperate move to stop his political momentum.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Carlson emphasized that Trump&rsquo;s political opponents are prepared to do anything to make sure the president does not take back the White House.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Tucker charted out whether circumstances are accelerating toward a possible Trump assassination, which is looking more likely due to Trump&rsquo;s soaring popularity.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://twitter.com/i/status/1741572121346683017"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://twitter.com/i/status/1741572121346683017</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> - Play Video&nbsp;</span></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Last year, Megyn Kelly voiced fears that the demonization of Trump could eventually lead to his assassination.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">During an episode of &ldquo;The Megyn Kelly Show&rdquo; on YouTube, Kelly was joined by former Secret Service agent and author of &ldquo;The Gift of Failure,&rdquo; Dan Bongino, as the pair discussed the portrayal of Trump and its potential escalation.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">&ldquo;You heard Tucker asked Trump about it when he interviewed him,&rdquo; Kelly said, referring to an August interview between Trump and Tucker Carlson.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">&ldquo;Whether Trump is worried, whether there&rsquo;s a realistic possibility, the left is going to so meltdown as his power rises, as he rises toward a second term &hellip; that they try to do something to him, God forbid, or that they try to do something to our country,&rdquo; she added.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://www.thefencepost.com/news/water-fight-federal-government-sues-state-of-idaho-over-water-rights/"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.thefencepost.com/news/water-fight-federal-government-sues-state-of-idaho-over-water-rights/</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>Water fight: Federal government sues state of Idaho over water rights</strong></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">A lawsuit brought by the U.S. government against the State of Idaho will have far-reaching implications for both how water is managed in the West and states&rsquo; rights.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">According to Idaho Farm Bureau government affairs specialist, Russ Hendricks, the state of Idaho began adjudicating water rights in Idaho&rsquo;s Snake River Basin (southern Idaho) in the late 1980s. As is the case with many western states, Idaho&rsquo;s water law provides a right to the beneficial user of the water. During this adjudication process in the &rsquo;80s and &rsquo;90s, many ranchers considered claiming their stockwater rights on federally administered grazing allotments through the state, but were convinced by the federal government to withdraw their claims, being told that the government was prepared for a lengthy legal battle. Only a few ranchers ignored the &ldquo;strong-arming, bullying&rdquo; by the federal government, said Hendricks. So, according to Hendricks, the federal government ended up with nearly all of the stockwater rights on federal allotments in the Snake River Basin, save for those claimed by Paul Nettleton and Tim Lowry (called the &ldquo;Joyce&rdquo; case.) Those men entered what eventually was a 15-year battle with the federal government. Eventually they won their case in the Idaho Supreme Court on the simple premise that the federal government does not own cattle and therefore is not able to put the water to beneficial use.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">And that brings us to the current lawsuit wherein the federal government has filed suit against the state of Idaho in federal district court, saying that they are being discriminated against. Hendricks believes this suit will have far reaching affects, not only for Idaho water users, but for any water users across the country.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The Idaho Farm Bureau has enlisted the help of the Mountain States Legal Foundation in the legal battle.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The reason I bring this up - is The WEF has already announced that "water was the next crisis, everyone understands water" since "climate change was too difficult to get people to understand"</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/posts/mark-seiler-robos-llc_the-wef-has-already-announced-that-water-activity-7145163060037513216-aEqk/"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.linkedin.com/posts/mark-seiler-robos-llc_the-wef-has-already-announced-that-water-activity-7145163060037513216-aEqk/</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> - Play Video&nbsp;</span></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The US Government Is Attempting to Seize All Water Rights for All Bodies of Water on American&rsquo;s Property in Idaho. If Residents Do Not Register For Each Body Of Water Individually By Their Timeline The State Takes Control &amp; Owns Them Forever. The "state" requires you to register your well, pond, creek or the water automatically become the "state's" property.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://www.breitbart.com/sports/2023/12/31/video-appears-to-show-panthers-owner-david-tepper-throwing-a-drink-at-panthers-fan/"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.breitbart.com/sports/2023/12/31/video-appears-to-show-panthers-owner-david-tepper-throwing-a-drink-at-panthers-fan/</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> - Play Video&nbsp;</span></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Now it&rsquo;s time for my favorite topic, sports! This is for my friends out in North Carolina&hellip;&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>Video Appears to Show Panthers Owner David Tepper Throwing a Drink at Panthers Fan</strong></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Completions have been tough to come by this year for the Carolina, but a thrown drink from Panthers Owner Dave Tepper hit its intended receiver on Sunday.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">During Carolina&rsquo;s 26-0 demolition at the hands of the Jacksonville Jaguars, Panthers Owner Dave Tepper appeared to throw a drink at a fan.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Tepper beats a hasty retreat after tossing the drink. It was probably a good thing since the fan turned around and immediately climbed up to the opening of the suite.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The NFL has said they are &ldquo;aware&rdquo; of the incident. However, they have not said whether Tepper&rsquo;s display is actionable under the league&rsquo;s Personal Conduct Policy. Presumably, some disciplinary action will be taken against Tepper lest the league allow fans to labor under the impression that they&rsquo;re perfectly okay with their owners showing extreme disrespect for their paying customers.</span></p>]]></description>
   <author><![CDATA[Garrison Hardie]]></author>
   <enclosure url="https://app.dropwave.io/episode/81a52c9c-66c1-4038-af1b-c320ce930b5c/daily-news-brief-for-wednesday-january-3rd-2024.mp3" length="1177" type="audio/mp3"/>
   <guid isPermaLink="false"><![CDATA[81a52c9c-66c1-4038-af1b-c320ce930b5c]]></guid>
   <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jan 2024 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
   <source url=""><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></source>
   <itunes:author><![CDATA[Garrison Hardie]]></itunes:author>
   <itunes:image href="https://assets-cdn2.dropwave.io/2ab40ac0-e99d-4f25-a6d2-541d2c9b290a/cover-art/mUK8zsnHkCK3vep7E1W6UgYb9dTnLenASAMEFha3.jpg"/>
   <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
   <itunes:duration>1177</itunes:duration>
   <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
  
  </item><item>
   <title><![CDATA[Daily News Brief for Friday, December 22nd, 2023 [Daily News Brief]]]></title>
   <link/>
   <description><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">This is Garrison Hardie with your CrossPolitic Daily News Brief for Friday , December 22nd, 2023.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Quick shout out to Andrea &amp; Jonah Briggs!&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>Samaritan Ministries: November</strong></span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">This is the time of year many of us are thinking about how we&rsquo;re going to pay our medical bills</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">next year. Before making a final decision, take a look at health care sharing with Samaritan</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Ministries. As a Samaritan member, you&rsquo;re connected to 80,000 Christan households across the nation who stand ready to care for one another spiritually and financially when a medical need arises. Samaritan Ministries is affordable, and with no network restrictions you&rsquo;re in control of your health care, choosing the doctors, hospitals, and treatments that are right for you.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">And with direct member-to-member sharing, you&rsquo;ll always know who your money is helping,</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">and that you&rsquo;re not supporting medical procedures that go against your values.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Get started today at samaritan ministries dot org slash cross politic.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2023/12/19/us/politics/trump-colorado-ballot-14th-amendment.html"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.nytimes.com/2023/12/19/us/politics/trump-colorado-ballot-14th-amendment.html</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>Trump Is Disqualified From 2024 Ballot, Colorado Court Says in Explosive Ruling</strong></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Colorado&rsquo;s top court ruled on Tuesday that President Donald J. Trump is disqualified from holding office again because he engaged in insurrection with his actions leading up to the Jan. 6 storming of the Capitol, an explosive ruling that is likely to put the basic contours of the 2024 election in the hands of the U.S. Supreme Court.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The Colorado Supreme Court was the first in the nation to find that Section 3 of the 14th Amendment &mdash; which disqualifies people who engage in insurrection against the Constitution after taking an oath to support it &mdash; applies to Mr. Trump, an argument that his opponents have been making around the country.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The ruling directs the Colorado secretary of state to exclude Mr. Trump&rsquo;s name from the state&rsquo;s Republican primary ballot. It does not address the general election.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">&ldquo;We do not reach these conclusions lightly,&rdquo; a four-justice majority wrote, with three justices dissenting. &ldquo;We are mindful of the magnitude and weight of the questions now before us. We are likewise mindful of our solemn duty to apply the law, without fear or favor, and without being swayed by public reaction to the decisions that the law mandates we reach.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Mr. Trump&rsquo;s campaign said immediately that it would appeal the decision to the U.S. Supreme Court. The Colorado justices anticipated that likelihood by putting their ruling on hold at least until Jan. 4; if Mr. Trump appeals before then, the hold will continue until the Supreme Court rules. And while Tuesday&rsquo;s ruling applies only to one state, it could all but force the nation&rsquo;s highest court to decide the question for all 50.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">&ldquo;It&rsquo;s hard for me to see how they don&rsquo;t take this one, because this certainly seems to be one of those questions that requires some national resolution,&rdquo; said Anthony Michael Kreis, an assistant professor of law at Georgia State University who has closely followed the Colorado case and related lawsuits around the country.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">If the justices take up the case, it will join a pile of other Trump-related matters they have agreed or are likely to decide, including whether he is immune from criminal prosecution for actions he took in office and the scope of an obstruction charge that is central to his federal Jan. 6 case.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The U.S. Supreme Court has a 6-to-3 conservative majority, with three justices appointed by Mr. Trump himself, and it is already under extraordinary political pressure and scrutiny both for its rulings and its justices&rsquo; ethics.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">&ldquo;Once again, the Supreme Court is being thrust into the center of a U.S. presidential election,&rdquo; said Richard L. Hasen, an election law expert at the University of California, Los Angeles, who compared the stakes to Bush v. Gore. &ldquo;But, unlike in 2000, the general political instability in the United States makes the situation now much more precarious.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">In the Colorado court&rsquo;s lengthy ruling on Tuesday, the justices there reversed a Denver district judge&rsquo;s finding last month that Section 3 did not apply to the presidency. They affirmed the district judge&rsquo;s other key conclusions: that Mr. Trump&rsquo;s actions before and on Jan. 6, 2021, constituted engaging in insurrection, and that courts had the authority to enforce Section 3 against a person whom Congress had not specifically designated.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">&ldquo;A majority of the court holds that President Trump is disqualified from holding the office of president under Section 3 of the 14th Amendment to the United States Constitution,&rdquo; the justices wrote. &ldquo;Because he is disqualified, it would be a wrongful act under the Election Code for the Colorado secretary of state to list him as a candidate on the presidential primary ballot.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Mr. Trump&rsquo;s campaign denounced the ruling, which is likely to inflame a Republican base that he has primed to see the array of civil and criminal cases against him as a witch hunt. Politically, his standing among Republican primary voters has only risen in the wake of the dozens of criminal charges against him.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">&ldquo;Unsurprisingly, the all-Democrat appointed Colorado Supreme Court has ruled against President Trump, supporting a Soros-funded, left-wing group&rsquo;s scheme to interfere in an election on behalf of Crooked Joe Biden by removing President Trump&rsquo;s name from the ballot and eliminating the rights of Colorado voters to vote for the candidate of their choice,&rdquo; a campaign spokesman, Steven Cheung, said. &ldquo;We have full confidence that the U.S. Supreme Court will quickly rule in our favor and finally put an end to these un-American lawsuits.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Similar lawsuits in Minnesota and New Hampshire were dismissed on procedural grounds. A judge in Michigan ruled last month that the issue was political and not for him to decide, and an appeals court affirmed the decision not to disqualify Mr. Trump there. The plaintiffs have appealed to the Michigan Supreme Court.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Tuesday&rsquo;s ruling &ldquo;is not only historic and justified, but is necessary to protect the future of democracy in our country,&rdquo; Noah Bookbinder, the president of Citizens for Responsibility and Ethics in Washington, said in a statement. His organization represented the voters seeking to disqualify Mr. Trump in Colorado.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Mr. Trump himself, who has routinely railed against unfavorable rulings, did not explicitly mention the Colorado Supreme Court decision in a speech Tuesday evening in Waterloo, Iowa &mdash; but his campaign was already fund-raising off it. An email to his supporters accused Democrats of trying to &ldquo;nullify&rdquo; Trump votes and asked for contributions to help defend his place on ballots.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Republican elected officials quickly circled the wagons around Mr. Trump, and a super PAC supporting him blasted out some of their comments to supporters.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">In one more illustration of the unusual nature of the 2024 Republican primary race &mdash; in which even the candidates seeking to defeat Mr. Trump for the party&rsquo;s nomination have largely shied away from condemning him &mdash; his main rivals, Ron DeSantis and Nikki Haley, both suggested that the ruling was an abuse of judicial power.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The case hinged on several questions: Was it an insurrection when Trump supporters stormed the Capitol on Jan. 6, 2021, trying to stop the certification of the 2020 election? If so, did Mr. Trump engage in that insurrection through his messages to his supporters beforehand, his speech that morning and his Twitter posts during the attack? Do courts have the authority to enforce Section 3 of the 14th Amendment without congressional action? And does Section 3 apply to the presidency?</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Again, an explosive ruling that is likely to put the basic contours of the 2024 election in the hands of the U.S. Supreme Court.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://thenationalpulse.com/2023/12/21/at-least-11-dead-in-prague-shooting/"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://thenationalpulse.com/2023/12/21/at-least-11-dead-in-prague-shooting/</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>At Least 15 Dead in Prague Shooting.</strong></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">At least 15 people have been reported dead and injured in a shooting incident at Charles University&rsquo;s Faculty of Arts located near the Old Town, a major tourist hub within the city, as per the official statement from Prague police. The horrific event unraveled at this educational facility in the capital city of the Czech Republic, erupting fear and panic among students and faculty present at the scene. Local authorities confirmed the shooter&rsquo;s elimination shortly after the attack, while refraining from revealing exactly how many victims were impacted.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Eyewitness reports and visual evidence posted on social media depicted the terrifying scene on the university campus, with sirens blaring and police vehicles flooding the streets around the building. Videos on social media platforms showed bystanders looking visibly panicked and attempting to escape the premises. Prague police issued a plea, urging residents to stay away from the area and to remain indoors for safety reasons.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Jakob Weizman, a journalist sheltering inside a darkened classroom, shared his experience on social media: &ldquo;Currently stuck inside my classroom in Prague. Shooter is dead, but we&rsquo;re waiting to be evacuated. Praying to make it out alive,&rdquo; he wrote. He later added, &ldquo;Locked the door before the shooter tried to open it. F&mdash;ing hell.&rdquo; Yet another social media user furnished the world with a chilling image of what appeared to be students desperately huddled on the university building&rsquo;s scaffolding, emphasizing the level of fear and panic induced by the tragic event.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://www.eurasiantimes.com/game-on-with-china-us-to-restore-tinian-airfield-once-home/"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.eurasiantimes.com/game-on-with-china-us-to-restore-tinian-airfield-once-home/</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>Game-On With China! US To Restore Tinian Airfield Once Home To Largest B-29 Bomber Fleet During WWII</strong></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">US Air Force General Kenneth Wilsbach shared this development in a discussion with Asia Nikkei, revealing that the military branch is increasing construction efforts at Tinian North Airfield and Tinian International Airfield.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">This effort is a crucial component of a broader initiative to disperse aircraft strategically across the Indo-Pacific region, responding to the escalating missile threat posed by China.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">&ldquo;If you pay attention in the next few months, you will see significant progress, especially at Tinian North,&rdquo; Wilsbach said. During World War II, the Tinian North Airfield served as the operational base for the largest B-29 bomber fleet.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Describing the airfield as having extensive pavement hidden beneath an overgrown jungle, he revealed plans to clear the jungle between now and summertime. The goal is to transform the site into a comprehensive facility upon completion.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Tinian, positioned approximately 200 kilometers north of Guam within the Northern Mariana Islands, is undergoing a revitalization in line with the US Air Force&rsquo;s operational strategy, Agile Combat Employment.&nbsp;&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">This strategic approach, a departure from post-Cold War era tactics, involves deliberately relocating aircraft to various sites across the western Pacific. The primary goal is to mitigate vulnerability to potential enemy missile strikes during periods of crisis.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">As documents released in March revealed, as part of the Air Force&rsquo;s 2024 budget request, several projects are outlined for Tinian, seeking a budget allocation of US$78 million for the fiscal year.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Among these projects is an airfield development initiative encompassing the demolition of World War II-era airfield pavements, clearing and leveling surfaces, and installing drainage, utilities, and secure fencing.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Another project focuses on establishing a fuel-pipeline system involving the installation of storage tanks, pipes, and safety equipment to facilitate fuel unloading from ships for transport to the airfield via pipeline and truck.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Additionally, a parking-apron project is detailed, which aims to pave areas designated for aircraft parking and taxiways. The taxiways must adhere to the Pentagon&rsquo;s standards for ground control operations for large-frame aircraft, as specified in the documents.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The proposed apron size would accommodate up to 12 KC-135 and KC-46 tanker aircraft and the necessary fueling equipment.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Tinian currently houses one international airfield, while Tinian North Airfield, once the most extensive B-29 base during World War II, lies largely concealed by jungle growth. However, the runways and taxiways remain intact.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Tinian was captured from Japanese control by US forces in the summer of 1944, toward the end of World War II. The northern expanse of the island hosted a substantial and historically momentous airfield, famously recognized as North Field.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">This airfield played a crucial role in Operation Silverplate, serving as the departure point for two specially modified B-29 bombers on separate sorties, marking the sole operational use of nuclear weapons to date.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Beyond these historic missions, North Field was instrumental as the launch site for many bomber and reconnaissance flights conducted over Japan and across the Western Pacific during the latter phases of the war.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">In the aftermath of World War II, the airfield witnessed a substantial deterioration in maintenance, resulting in the decline of its expansive parallel runways, aprons, and supporting infrastructure.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The US Air Force is now intensifying its endeavors to enhance the airfield&rsquo;s capabilities to accommodate fighter jets, bombers, and significant support aircraft. These expanded capabilities align with the standards commonly met by the nearby Andersen Air Force Base on Guam.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">However, the US believes that if Andersen Air Force Base faces disruption due to enemy actions, notably those from China, or natural disasters, this facility on Tinian would be crucial in ensuring continuity and resilience in US military operations in the Pacific region.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://pagesix.com/2023/12/20/celebrity-news/hulk-hogan-70-gets-baptized-surrenders-to-jesus-greatest-day-of-my-life/"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://pagesix.com/2023/12/20/celebrity-news/hulk-hogan-70-gets-baptized-surrenders-to-jesus-greatest-day-of-my-life/</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>Hulk Hogan, 70, gets baptized, &lsquo;surrenders&rsquo; to Jesus: &lsquo;Greatest day of my life&rsquo;</strong></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">WWE icon Hulk Hogan has been baptized.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">His ceremony took place at Indian Rocks Baptist Church in Florida, as noted by the social media slideshow he shared Wednesday night.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">&ldquo;Total surrender and dedication to Jesus is the greatest day of my life,&rdquo; the 70-year-old star captioned the post.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">&ldquo;No worries, no hate, no judgment&hellip; only love!&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Hogan&rsquo;s slideshow included a video of him and his wife, Sky Daily Hogan, submerging themselves in a pool of water and resurfacing with huge grins on their faces.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">They were both garbed with white clothing, with the former pro wrestler rocking his signature bandana and a gold cross necklace.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">A photo included at the end of the post appeared to show Hulk and Sky, plus others, bowing their heads in prayer.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The Indian Rocks Baptist Church took to its Instagram Story to celebrate the &ldquo;Hogan Knows Best&rdquo; alum&rsquo;s special moment.</span></p>]]></description>
   <author><![CDATA[Garrison Hardie]]></author>
   <enclosure url="https://app.dropwave.io/episode/41d0c2fb-09a1-4297-a656-c0aa16c2302b/daily-news-brief-for-friday-december-22nd-2023.mp3" length="854" type="audio/mp3"/>
   <guid isPermaLink="false"><![CDATA[41d0c2fb-09a1-4297-a656-c0aa16c2302b]]></guid>
   <pubDate>Fri, 22 Dec 2023 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
   <source url=""><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></source>
   <itunes:author><![CDATA[Garrison Hardie]]></itunes:author>
   <itunes:image href="https://assets-cdn2.dropwave.io/2ab40ac0-e99d-4f25-a6d2-541d2c9b290a/cover-art/mUK8zsnHkCK3vep7E1W6UgYb9dTnLenASAMEFha3.jpg"/>
   <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
   <itunes:duration>854</itunes:duration>
   <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
  
  </item><item>
   <title><![CDATA[Daily News Brief for Wednesday , December 20th, 2023 [Daily News Brief]]]></title>
   <link/>
   <description><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">This is Garrison Hardie with your CrossPolitic Daily News Brief for Wednesday , December 20th, 2023.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>Rowdy Christian Merch Plug:</strong></span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">If you&rsquo;re a fan of CrossPolitic, or the Fight Laugh Feast Network, then surely, you know we have a merch store right? Rowdy Christian Merch is your one-stop-shop for everything CrossPolitc merchandise. We&rsquo;ve got T-Shirts, hoodies, hats, but we&rsquo;ve also got specialty items like backpacks, mugs, coffee, even airpod cases! Visit Rowdy Christian Merch at rowdychristian.com, and buy that next gift, or a little something for yourself. Again, that&rsquo;s rowdychristian.com.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://thepostmillennial.com/kamala-harris-to-take-pro-abortion-reproductive-freedoms-tour-across-us?utm_campaign=64487"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://thepostmillennial.com/kamala-harris-to-take-pro-abortion-reproductive-freedoms-tour-across-us?utm_campaign=64487</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>Kamala Harris launches 'Reproductive Freedoms' pro-abortion tour across US</strong></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Vice President Kamala Harris announced Tuesday that she plans to travel around the United States in what she calls a "Reproductive Freedoms" tour. Harris announced that these trips will be taken "to organize, build community, and fight back" against what she calls a "full-on attack on a woman's fundamental freedom to make decisions about her own body" across the nation.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The pro-abortion tour will kick off in Wisconsin on Jan. 22, which marks the 51st anniversary of the now-overturned Roe v. Wade.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The White House promises that "Vice President Harris will also hold extremists accountable for proposing a national abortion ban," although it does not specify what those consequences may be.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://thenationalpulse.com/2023/12/18/britain-bans-prayer-near-abortion-clinics/"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://thenationalpulse.com/2023/12/18/britain-bans-prayer-near-abortion-clinics/</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>Britain BANS PRAYER Near Abortion Clinics.</strong></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">England&rsquo;s High Court has upheld a local government order establishing a so-called &ldquo;buffer zone&rdquo; against prayers being said near an abortion clinic. Livia Tossici-Bolt, who heads the pro-life group 40 Days for Life Bournemouth, and Christian Concern had attempted to overturn the ban, arguing it &ldquo;criminalized prayer and reading from the Bible&rdquo;.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Judges determined on Friday that the banning order &ldquo;lawfully followed the democratic and consultative procedures&rdquo;. They said any infringements of freedom of religion, speech, and the right to protest were &ldquo;justified by the legitimate aim of protecting the rights of women attending the clinic.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Christian Concern intends to appeal the decision. &ldquo;Peaceful witness near abortion centers are helpful to many women in crisis pregnancies, offering genuine choice by providing support,&rdquo; argued Christian Legal Centre chief executive Andrea Williams. British police are exceptionally rigid in enforcing &ldquo;buffer zones&rdquo; protecting abortionists. Lone Christians have in some cases been arrested or fined for praying silently inside their heads near clinics.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/policy/immigration/border-officials-encounter-14-509-illegal-immigrants-new-record"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/policy/immigration/border-officials-encounter-14-509-illegal-immigrants-new-record</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>Biden border crisis shatters record with 14,509 illegal immigrants encountered in one day</strong></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">U.S. border officials encountered the highest number of illegal immigrants at the U.S.-Mexico border on Monday than any day, upending all other records that the Biden administration has set over the past three years.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The Washington Examiner obtained internal U.S. Customs and Border Protection data Tuesday that revealed 14,509 immigrants were encountered by federal law enforcement at the southern border on Monday. The large majority of encounters were of immigrants who walked around the port of entry and crossed into the country illegally, while a small percentage tried to enter at the port of entry but were denied admission.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The most recent record of 12,000 was set last week, according to Fox News. If yesterday's rate of 14,509 arrests per day continued for a month, it would translate to more than 435,000 immigrant arrests.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Rep. Tony Gonzales (R-TX), whose district runs along 800 miles of the 2,000-mile border, described the situation in his region as "all very sad." Gonzales told the Washington Examiner in a text message Tuesday morning that he believes the situation in Eagle Pass, Texas, a border town where 2,500 immigrants were arrested on Sunday, will continue to decline but that the extent would depend on how the Biden administration responds.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">"Depends on how much pressure gets put on U.S. and Mexican officials," Gonzales wrote.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">House Homeland Security Committee Chairman Mark Green (R-TN) reacted to the new one-day record on X, formerly Twitter.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">"Another Record: Over 14,500 illegal immigrants have been encountered while entering our country," Green wrote. "This has been the single worst 24 hours for our Southwest border in our nation&rsquo;s history."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Border officials in the Eagle Pass-Del Rio region encountered 3,100 illegal immigrants Monday, while officials in the Tucson region of Arizona encountered 3,089 people.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Government numbers obtained Tuesday show 26,758 immigrants were in custody as of Tuesday morning, including 5,197 in Del Rio, Texas; 5,004 in Tucson, Arizona; 4,968 in the Rio Grande Valley of Texas; and 4,722 in El Paso, Texas.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Existing Border Patrol stations in the Eagle Pass area are too small to accommodate more than several hundred people, so immigrants are being processed at a large tent facility outside town known as "Firefly" for the road that it is located on. The tent facility was set up last year with the intent of holding up to 1,000 immigrants, but as of Tuesday, more than 3,000 immigrants were at the site &mdash; putting the facility three times over the legal limit.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Border Patrol is also busing immigrants to other regions for processing. One official at the tent facility told the Washington Examiner that it sends out 30 to 50 large buses of immigrants to other regions each day.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Border Patrol highway checkpoints, including the only one north of Eagle Pass, were shuttered this week as agents were pulled to transport and process migrants.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">President Joe Biden has yet to react to the situation.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The Department of Homeland Security did not respond to a request for comment.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://www.dailyfetched.com/germany-begins-deploying-troops-for-first-time-since-world-war-ii/"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.dailyfetched.com/germany-begins-deploying-troops-for-first-time-since-world-war-ii/</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>Germany Begins Deploying Troops for First Time since World War II</strong></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The announcement was made on Monday in Lithuania, where Defense Minister Arvydas Anusauskas met Boris Pistoriusto to outline a &ldquo;Roadmap Action Plan&rdquo; involving 4,800 permanently stationed German soldiers.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The new move was described as &ldquo;historical&rdquo; for both nations and NATO.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">German troops will be stationed in the Lithuanian cities of Kaunas and Vilnius in early 2024, with the majority of troops being deployed in 2025 and 2026 and full-operation capability expected by 2027.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Meanwhile, Lithuania committed to providing all necessary civilian and military infrastructure.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">&ldquo;The German commitment of permanently stationing a brigade in Lithuania is a historical step for both Germany and Lithuania,&rdquo; Anusauskas said Monday, according to a press release.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">&ldquo;We are turning over to a page of even deeper strategic partnership.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Pistorius noted the step as being positive for defense relations, considering the war between Ukraine and Russia,</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">We will ensure reliable deterrence, and we will be ready to [defend] NATO. We are sending a clear signal with this step to those who present a threat to peace and security in Europe.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Newsweek reported that experts within the two defense ministries formulated the plan:</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">&ldquo;Most of the German troops will be stationed in the territory of Rdninkai military training ground, while the rest will be deployed in the town of Rukla, where some 1,000 allied troops already reside.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Logistical hubs will cater to the new brigade, including three maneuver battalions and combat support and supply units formed by new and existing units.&ldquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">&ldquo;The 203rd Panzer Battalion, based in North Rhine-Westphalia, and the 122nd Armored Infantry Battalion, based in Bavaria, will be moved to Lithuania. Lithuania&rsquo;s enhanced Forward Presence Battalion Battle Group will be transformed into a multinational battalion to become &ldquo;an integral part of the brigade,&rdquo; the release said.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The head of the parliamentary National Security and Defense Committee, Laurynas Kasciunas, said the country would allocate 0.3 percent of its gross domestic product to help fund the deployment and to build housing.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Earlier this year, Germany faced pressure from the US to provide Leopard 2 tanks to Ukraine.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://pjmedia.com/vodkapundit/2023/12/18/americans-yawn-at-cdc-warnings-about-tripledemic-n4924835"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://pjmedia.com/vodkapundit/2023/12/18/americans-yawn-at-cdc-warnings-about-tripledemic-n4924835</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>Americans Yawn at CDC Warnings About 'Tripledemic'</strong></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">While America's public health officials issue one warning after another about this winter's "tripledemic" of COVID, flu, and RSV, the American public is responding with a collective yawn &mdash; if vaccination rates are anything to go by.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The CDC's most recent weekly vaccination update says that "receipt of the COVID-19 vaccine is low across all socio-demographic subgroups and has consistently varied by age, race and ethnicity, poverty status, health insurance status, and urbanicity." As of December 2, fewer than 18% of adults reported getting the updated COVID-19 vaccine since Sept. 14, and about another 15% of adults said they would "definitely" get vaccinated.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">RSV &mdash; respiratory syncytial virus infection &mdash; is another one of those bugs that poses its most serious risk to the 60-and-over crowd. Although a serious RSV infection might require hospitalization, the uptake rate among the eligible 60-plus cohort is just 16%.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Vaccinations for the ordinary flu are down a bit, too. "Adult vaccination rates for influenza reached their peak for the 2020-2021 cycle," the Washington Examiner reported on Monday, "with 50.2% of those over 18 getting vaccinated. For the 2022-2023 season, however, only 46.9% of the same population obtained their shot." Rates are expected to be about the same or lower for the current 2023-2024 flu season.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The drop isn't huge but the trendline is clear: Americans don't seem to be all that worried about the flu &mdash; and aren't concerned at all about COVID or RSV.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">That's not for any lack of effort on the part of our public health system.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The CDC began its big vaccination push more than two months ago, with this tragically hip tweet from CDC director Mandy Cohen.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Chicago health officials took a more traditional (and much less wince-inducing) approach on Monday, with Dr. Colleen Nash, associate professor of pediatrics in the division of infectious diseases at Rush University Medical Center, warning, "We&rsquo;ve now been lucky enough to kind of live with COVID but still enjoy normal life and activities and things. And that is directly attributable, at least in part, to vaccinations. So I would really encourage people to do that if they haven&rsquo;t already."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">While reports show that Illinois' hospitalization rate for COVID is "ticking up," the actual numbers aren't anything like 2020, with an additional 1,251 COVID hospital admissions this week statewide. And yet according to the Chicago Tribune, only about 11% of city residents are fully up to date on their COVID vaccinations.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The CDC tried on Twitter/X again on Saturday, reminding readers, "&lsquo;Tis the season for joy and family. Now is the time to get vaccinated against COVID-19 and flu before you see your loved ones again."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">"Visit vaccines.gov to find vaccines near you."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The ratio, as the kids like to say, is epic.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">While the replies were all over the place in tone, this one reasonable-sounding tweet captured the general sentiment.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">When vaccination rates are down even for the innocuous (and generally trusted) flu shot, it's clear that the CDC no longer enjoys the clout it used to with the American public.</span></p>]]></description>
   <author><![CDATA[Garrison Hardie]]></author>
   <enclosure url="https://app.dropwave.io/episode/9793ede3-9d1b-4806-a25e-46e929864bde/daily-news-brief-for-wednesday-december-20th-2023.mp3" length="729" type="audio/mp3"/>
   <guid isPermaLink="false"><![CDATA[9793ede3-9d1b-4806-a25e-46e929864bde]]></guid>
   <pubDate>Wed, 20 Dec 2023 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
   <source url=""><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></source>
   <itunes:author><![CDATA[Garrison Hardie]]></itunes:author>
   <itunes:image href="https://assets-cdn2.dropwave.io/2ab40ac0-e99d-4f25-a6d2-541d2c9b290a/cover-art/mUK8zsnHkCK3vep7E1W6UgYb9dTnLenASAMEFha3.jpg"/>
   <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
   <itunes:duration>729</itunes:duration>
   <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
  
  </item><item>
   <title><![CDATA[Daily News Brief for Tuesday, December 19th, 2023 [Daily News Brief]]]></title>
   <link/>
   <description><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">This is Garrison Hardie with your CrossPolitic Daily News Brief for Tuesday, December 19th, 2023.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Pub Membership Plug:</strong></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Public Houses, or Pubs, are not just places to drink beer, wine, cider or even something a little stronger. It is also a unique social centre, very often the focus of community life in villages, towns and cities throughout the length and breadth of the world. We here at CrossPolitic hope to emulate that for you and yours. That&rsquo;s why you should grab yourself a pub membership at fightlaughfeast.com&hellip; we need you on this ride with us. So pull up a chair, grab a pint, and join us on this ride at fightlaughfeast.com - that&rsquo;s fightlaughfeast.com.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://www.foxnews.com/media/navy-vet-defends-beheading-iowa-capitols-satanic-baphomet-statue-christian-civil-disobedience"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.foxnews.com/media/navy-vet-defends-beheading-iowa-capitols-satanic-baphomet-statue-christian-civil-disobedience</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Navy vet defends beheading Iowa capitol's satanic Baphomet statue: 'Christian civil disobedience'</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">A Mississippi Navy reserve pilot instructor who admitted to beheading a statue of the satanic half-man, half-goat Baphomet inside the Iowa State Capitol told Fox News he was simply engaging in "Christian civil disobedience."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Michael Cassidy said he decided "spur of the moment" to travel north to Des Moines and take action against the statue, which had been permitted to be erected not far from the rotunda's Nativity display for Christmas.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">He told "Jesse Watters Primetime" he wrecked the statue then went straight to Capitol security to tell them what he did.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">"I wasn't running away or anything like that. I told them what I did," he said, thanking law enforcement for their professionalism following the incident.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">He was cited for criminal mischief in the fourth degree and released.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">"I saw that this was going on, I was surprised that the legislature allowed it up and that they didn't do anything to take it down," Cassidy added.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">He said he wasn't sure what to expect when he came upon the Capitol, citing a prior incident in Springfield, Ill., where groups were chanting after a 2021 erection of a satanic statue in the Illinois State House.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">In a Tuesday statement, Iowa Republican Gov. Kim Reynolds said she found the statue "absolutely objectionable," but that the best response to objectionable speech is more speech and prayer.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">After he was charged, several conservative figures rallied to Cassidy's defense, including Florida Gov. Ron DeSantis and conservative commentator Matt Walsh.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">DeSantis promised to "chip in" for Cassidy's legal fees, writing on X, formerly Twitter, that "Satan has no place in our society and should not be recognized as a &lsquo;religion&rsquo; by the federal government." Walsh similarly tweeted he will contribute to Cassidy's defense.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Host Jesse Watters noted the contrast between reaction to Cassidy's act and the dozens of protests in recent years that featured left-wing activists tearing down statues of Confederate officers, former U.S. presidents and historical figures like Christopher Columbus.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">He pointed to then-Speaker Nancy Pelosi's, D-Calif., dismissal of the crowd in her home neighborhood of Little Italy, Baltimore, who leveled the Columbus statue and tossed it in the Patapsco River.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">"People will do what they do," Pelosi said at a July 2020 press conference.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The city of Richmond, Va., in recent years removed an entire street's worth of statuary dedicated to Confederate Gens. A. P. Hill, "Stonewall" Jackson and J. E. B. Stuart, all of which lined the former Confederate capital's "Monument Avenue" for decades.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Left-wing protesters notably failed to topple the statue of Andrew Jackson, the first Democratic president, near the White House in 2020 after being rebuffed by law enforcement.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">In that respect, Watters said there appears to be a dichotomy between what statuary destruction causes mainstream or left-wing outrage.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Cassidy's attorney, Davis Younts, said his client's case is a question of good versus evil, and that he and those who have come to his defense will continue to stand by him to make sure he gets equal protection under law.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">He also said there has not yet been a First Amendment suit in case law that has found Satanism to be considered a religion under the Constitution, and that anti-blasphemy laws still exist in the United States.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://www.breitbart.com/europe/2023/12/17/church-of-england-blesses-same-sex-couples-for-the-first-time/"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.breitbart.com/europe/2023/12/17/church-of-england-blesses-same-sex-couples-for-the-first-time/</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Church of England Blesses Same-Sex Couples For the First Time</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Church of England priests offered officially sanctioned blessings of same-sex partnerships for the first time on Sunday, though a ban on church weddings for gay couples remains in place amid deep divisions within global Anglicanism over marriage and sexuality.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">In one of the first ceremonies, the Rev. Catherine Bond and the Rev. Jane Pearce had their union blessed at St John the Baptist church, in Felixstowe, eastern England, where both are associate priests.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The couple knelt in front of Canon Andrew Dotchin, who held their heads as he gave &ldquo;thanks for Catherine and Jane, to the love and friendship they share, and their commitment to one another as they come before you on this day.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The church&acute;s national assembly voted in February to allow clergy to bless the unions of same-sex couples who have had civil weddings or partnerships. The words used for the blessings, known as prayers of love and faith, were approved by the church&acute;s House of Bishops on Tuesday and used for the first time on Sunday.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The compromise was struck following five years of discussions about the church&acute;s position on sexuality. Church leaders offered an apology for the church&acute;s failure to welcome LGBTQ people, but also endorsed the doctrine that marriage is the union of one man and one woman. Clergy won&acute;t be required to perform same-sex blessings if they disagree with them.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The blessings can be used in regular church services. The church&acute;s governing body has also drawn up a plan for separate &ldquo;services of prayer and dedication&rdquo; for same-sex couples that would resemble weddings, but it has not yet been formally approved.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Public opinion surveys consistently show that a majority of people in England support same-sex marriage, which has been legal since 2013. The church didn&acute;t alter its teaching on marriage when the law changed.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Archbishop of Canterbury Justin Welby has said he won&acute;t personally bless any same-sex couples because it&acute;s his job to unify the world&rsquo;s 85 million Anglicans. Welby is the spiritual leader of both the Church of England and the global Anglican Communion of which it is a member.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Several Anglican bishops from Africa, Asia, Latin America and the Pacific said after the February decision that they no longer recognize Welby as their leader.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://www.breitbart.com/politics/2023/12/18/poll-54-of-democrat-voters-want-to-replace-joe-biden-as-2024-nominee/"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.breitbart.com/politics/2023/12/18/poll-54-of-democrat-voters-want-to-replace-joe-biden-as-2024-nominee/</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Poll: 54% of Democrat Voters Want to Replace Joe Biden as 2024 Nominee</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Democrat party voters are unhappy President Joe Biden, 81, is the presumptive Democrat nominee to likely challenge former President Donald Trump, Fox News polling revealed Sunday.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The poll highlights the disconnect and discord inflicting the Democrat party after Biden refused to step aside and allow a different Democrat to lead the party.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The survey showed:</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">54 percent of Democrat primary voters prefer an alternative to Biden.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Just 43 percent of Democrat primary voters want to keep Biden.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The polling showed a slight uptick in negative sentiment against the president:</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">October: 53 percent prefer an alternative, while 45 want to keep Biden</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">March: 52 percent prefer an alternative, while 44 want to keep Biden</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Biden previously told reporters in December he must run for reelection after prominent Democrats implored him to reconsider a second bid against Trump. &ldquo;Would you be running if Trump wasn&rsquo;t running?&rdquo; a reporter asked Biden.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&ldquo;I expect so,&rdquo; Biden replied. &ldquo;But he is running, and &mdash; I just &mdash; I have to run.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Biden&rsquo;s comment came on the same day he told donors he probably would not run if Trump was not running. &ldquo;If Trump wasn&rsquo;t running, I&rsquo;m not sure I&rsquo;d be running,&rdquo; Biden said, adding that Democrats &ldquo;cannot let him [Trump] win.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">National and battleground state polling shows Biden losing to Trump:</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Morning Consult: Trump leads Biden in six of seven crucial swing states.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">NBC News: Trump leads Biden by two points.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Fox News: Trump trounces Biden by four points.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The poll surveyed 1,0007 registered voters from December 10-13 with a 4.5 point margin of error.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://thepostmillennial.com/eric-adams-admits-biden-admin-will-not-help-nyc-with-illegal-immigrant-crisis?utm_campaign=64487"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://thepostmillennial.com/eric-adams-admits-biden-admin-will-not-help-nyc-with-illegal-immigrant-crisis?utm_campaign=64487</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Eric Adams admits Biden admin will not help NYC with illegal immigrant crisis</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">On Sunday, New York City Mayor Eric Adams said that Democrats "underestimated" the impact that illegal immigration would have on their cities, and warned New Yorkers to brace for "extremely painful" budget cuts to pay back the debt created by it.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">In an interview with WPIX-TV, Adams said, that a low for the city in 2023 was "150,000 migrants and asylum seekers that put a real bump in the road of our recovery effort in the city."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://twitter.com/i/status/1736507664308277364"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://twitter.com/i/status/1736507664308277364</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> - Play Video&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://twitter.com/i/status/1736512831963430927"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://twitter.com/i/status/1736512831963430927</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> - Play Video </span><strong>Combine these videos</strong></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">After a meeting with the congressional leaders of the Biden administration earlier this month, Adams said he was not optimistic about getting help from the federal government to deal with the illegal immigrant crisis plaguing New York City.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Adams was forced to cut the budget for the New York City Police Department last month, taking the department below 30,000 personnel.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://www.foxnews.com/sports/aaron-rodgers-likely-cleared-return-ruptured-achilles-next-week-report"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.foxnews.com/sports/aaron-rodgers-likely-cleared-return-ruptured-achilles-next-week-report</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Aaron Rodgers likely to be cleared for return from ruptured Achilles next week</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Aaron Rodgers' bold prediction is apparently about to play out.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The four-time MVP ruptured his Achilles Sept. 11 on just his fourth snap as a New York Jet.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Four days later, he shocked the world when he said, "Give me your doubts,then watch what I do."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">At that time, Rodgers did not rule out a return this season, saying that "anything is possible." Most doubted, but it may actually become a reality.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">According to ESPN, the 40-year-old is likely to be medically cleared to return next week.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Rodgers returned to practice Nov. 29, roughly seven weeks since his injury. It was an unprecedented time frame to practice after such an injury.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">However, Rodgers said he underwent "innovative" surgery in his best effort to get back on the field this season.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Rodgers has said he wanted a return on Christmas Eve. The Jets have until Wednesday to decide whether to activate Rodgers from injured reserve. Otherwise, he would miss the rest of the season.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Rodgers has wowed just about everyone in the organization with how quickly he has progressed. Earlier this week, he even lined up as a linebacker for the scout team and made a one-handed interception.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">However, being cleared isn't exactly a guarantee Rodgers would play.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The quarterback and the Jets have said the team's playoff chances will play a role in whether he returns. He likely would not return if they are mathematically eliminated from the playoffs, which could happen this weekend.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Rodgers recently said there are hardly any risks in taking the field this season.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">"My thing is, what&rsquo;s the worst that can happen?" he told reporters shortly after returning to practice. "Something unfortunate again, and then you just slow the rehab down. I think by my own timetable that if you take the rehab slower and a little more deliberate &mdash; five months, six months max &mdash; is probably the length to get back to 100% if you really take it slow. So, in my opinion, there's not like a downside to coming back and reinjuring it."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The Jets face the Washington Commanders on Christmas Eve.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p><br /><br style="font-weight: 400;" /></p>]]></description>
   <author><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></author>
   <enclosure url="https://app.dropwave.io/episode/b5af4df7-c0f1-4993-b0fe-db46e54c830d/daily-news-brief-for-tuesday-december-19th-2023.mp3" length="746" type="audio/mp3"/>
   <guid isPermaLink="false"><![CDATA[b5af4df7-c0f1-4993-b0fe-db46e54c830d]]></guid>
   <pubDate>Tue, 19 Dec 2023 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
   <source url=""><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></source>
   <itunes:author><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></itunes:author>
   <itunes:image href="https://assets-cdn2.dropwave.io/2ab40ac0-e99d-4f25-a6d2-541d2c9b290a/cover-art/mUK8zsnHkCK3vep7E1W6UgYb9dTnLenASAMEFha3.jpg"/>
   <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
   <itunes:duration>746</itunes:duration>
   <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
  
  </item>
 </channel>
</rss>
