<?xml version="1.0"?>
<?xml-stylesheet href="/storage/feed-stylesheet.xsl" type="text/xsl"?>

<rss xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
 <channel>
  <title>FLF - Daily News Brief</title>
  <link>https://dropwave.io</link>
  <description><![CDATA[FIGHT LAUGH FEAST PRESENTS SHOWS PROCLAIMING THE LORDSHIP OF CHRIST OVER ALL OF LIFE.
]]></description>
  <language>en</language>
  <managingEditor><![CDATA[fightlaughfeast@gmail.com (FLF, LLC)]]></managingEditor>
  <webMaster><![CDATA[support@dropwave.io (DropWave Support)]]></webMaster>
  <pubDate>Tue, 09 May 2023 13:25:44 +0000</pubDate>
  <lastBuildDate>Tue, 09 May 2023 13:25:44 +0000</lastBuildDate>
  <image>
   <url>https://is4-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Podcasts113/v4/58/56/52/5856525c-2973-cf29-3db9-21faa8595391/mza_1144696925612154085.png/1200x1200bb.jpg</url>
   <link>https://dropwave.io</link>
   <title><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></title>
  </image>
  <itunes:author><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></itunes:author>
  <itunes:image href="https://is4-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Podcasts113/v4/58/56/52/5856525c-2973-cf29-3db9-21faa8595391/mza_1144696925612154085.png/1200x1200bb.jpg"/>
  <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
  <itunes:owner>
   <itunes:name><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></itunes:name>
   <itunes:email>fightlaughfeast@gmail.com</itunes:email>
  </itunes:owner>
  <itunes:category text="News"/>
  <item>
   <title><![CDATA[CrossPolitic Daily News Brief for Tuesday, May 9th, 2023. [Daily News Brief]]]></title>
   <link>https://app.dropwave.io/episode/eade695e-9ed3-47f9-a2e6-93f67f318e99/crosspolitic-daily-news-brief-for-tuesday-may-9th-2023.mp3</link>
   <description><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">This is Garrison Hardie with your CrossPolitic Daily News Brief for Tuesday, May 9th, 2023.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Samaritan Ministries:</strong></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Don&rsquo;t be limited by restrictive networks. There&rsquo;s another way. A Biblical way. Samaritan Ministries. Say you have a medical need. You don&rsquo;t have to check and see what hospital is in your network, or be concerned about the doctor being in-network, too. No. You go to the hospital you choose, and don&rsquo;t give a second thought as to what&rsquo;s in-network and what&rsquo;s not, because with Samaritan Ministries, you&rsquo;re in control of your health care. Afterwards, fellow members pray for you, and send money directly to you to help you pay your medical bills. And when they have a medical need, you&rsquo;ll do the same for them. That&rsquo;s what Biblical health care sharing looks like. Check it out today at samaritan ministries dot org slash cross politic</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">First, we start with the news of a coronation for our friends across the pond.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://www.cnn.com/2023/05/06/europe/coronation-king-charles-ckc-gbr-intl/index.html"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.cnn.com/2023/05/06/europe/coronation-king-charles-ckc-gbr-intl/index.html</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>King Charles III is crowned in once-in-a-generation ceremony</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Britain&rsquo;s King Charles III has been crowned in a once-in-a-generation royal event witnessed by hundreds of high-profile guests inside Westminster Abbey, as well as tens of thousands of well-wishers who gathered in central London despite the rain.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">While Charles became King on the death of his mother, Queen Elizabeth II last September, the coronation on Saturday was the formal crowning of the monarch.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The service was a profoundly religious affair, reflecting the fact that aside from being head of state of the United Kingdom and 14 other countries, Charles is also the Supreme Governor of the Church of England.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">In the most significant moment of the day, Archbishop of Canterbury Justin Welby placed the 360-year-old St. Edward&rsquo;s Crown on Charles&rsquo; head. The spiritual leader of the Anglican Church then declared: &ldquo;God Save the King.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The intricate service lasted just over two hours &ndash; about an hour shorter than Elizabeth II&rsquo;s coronation in 1953 &ndash; and followed a traditional template that has stayed much the same for more than 1,000 years.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">However, it has been modernized in certain key ways. The archbishop acknowledged the multiple faiths observed in the UK during the ceremony, saying the Church of England &ldquo;will seek to foster an environment in which people of all faiths may live freely.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The King took the Coronation Oath and became the first monarch to pray aloud at his coronation. In his prayer he asked to &ldquo;be a blessing&rdquo; to people &ldquo;of every faith and conviction.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">In what is considered the most sacred part of the ceremony, the King was anointed with holy oil by the Archbishop of Canterbury. He was also presented with the coronation regalia, including the royal Robe and Stole, in what is known as the investiture part of the service.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Then, for the first time in coronation history, the archbishop invited the British public, as well as those from &ldquo;other Realms,&rdquo; to recite a pledge of allegiance to the newly crowned monarch and his &ldquo;heirs and successors.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Ahead of the event, some parts of the British media and public interpreted the invitation as a command, reporting that people had been &ldquo;asked&rdquo; and &ldquo;called&rdquo; to swear allegiance to the King. In the face of such criticism, the Church of England revised the text of the liturgy so that members of the public would be given a choice between saying simply &ldquo;God save King Charles&rdquo; or reciting the full pledge of allegiance.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The ceremony also included a reading from the Bible by UK Prime Minister Rishi Sunak and, in another coronation first, gospel music.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Once the King was crowned, his wife, Queen Camilla, was crowned in her own, shorter ceremony with Queen Mary&rsquo;s Crown &ndash; marking the first time in recent history that a new crown wasn&rsquo;t made specifically for this occasion.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">After the ceremony, the newly crowned King and Queen rode back to Buckingham Palace in a much larger parade, featuring 4,000 members of the armed forces, 250 horses and 19 military bands.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The pomp and pageantry concluded with a royal salute and the customary balcony appearance by the King and family members. They and the crowds below watched a flypast of military aircraft, slimmed down because of the poor weather.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Despite the splendor of the occasion, it has not been without controversy. Some have objected to millions of pounds of taxpayers&rsquo; money being spent on a lavish ceremony at a time when millions of Britons are suffering a severe cost-of-living crisis.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Security is by far the most costly element of large events and the Met said ahead of time that Saturday would be the largest one-day policing operation in decades, with more than 11,500 officers on duty in London.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The coronation has also attracted anti-monarchy demonstrations, with a small number of protesters arrested in central London on Saturday morning before the event began.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Republic, a campaign group that calls for the abolition of the monarchy, said the idea of the &ldquo;homage of the people&rdquo; was &ldquo;offensive, tone deaf and a gesture that holds the people in contempt.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Some eyebrows were also raised earlier this week when a controversial and widely criticized UK public order bill came into force.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Since the death of Queen Elizabeth II last year, there have been a number of instances of anti-monarchists turning up at royal engagements to voice their grievances against the institution.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The new rules, signed into law by the King on Tuesday, just days before the coronation, empower the police to take stronger action against peaceful protesters.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://thepostmillennial.com/biden-to-veto-house-remain-in-mexico-bill?utm_campaign=64487"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://thepostmillennial.com/biden-to-veto-house-remain-in-mexico-bill?utm_campaign=64487</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Biden to veto House 'remain in Mexico' bill</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">On Monday, the White House announced that Joe Biden would veto an immigration bill coming out of the House of Representatives that would reinstitute several Trump-era policies including construction of the border wall and the remain in Mexico policy, which stated that anyone seeking asylum had to wait in Mexico as their claim was processed.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">According to the Associated Press, the White House Office of Management and Budget said in a statement, "While we welcome Congress' engagement on meaningful steps to address immigration and the challenges at the border, this bill would make things worse, not better. Because this bill does very little to actually increase border security while doing a great deal to trample on the nation&rsquo;s core values and international obligations, it should be rejected."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">On Thursday, the House is set to vote on the 213-page Secure the Border Act. Thursday also marks the expiration of Title 42, the Trump-era policy instituted under Covid that granted Border Patrol and Department of Homeland Security officials the ability to expel illegal immigrants over health concerns.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The Secure the Border Act would also require employers to verify a worker's immigration status for employment and institute the E-Verify system</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">House Majority Leader Steve Scalise said, "Joe Biden sent a message that America&rsquo;s border is open, and millions of people answered that call and started coming across our border illegally. We&rsquo;re going to show the president how to solve the problem."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The Daily Mail reports, the Secure the Border Act would limit federal funds for NGOs (non-governmental organizations) that aid illegal immigrants crossing the border, would end Biden's expedited entry policy for Nicaraguans, Venezuelans, Haitians, and Cubans, and grant more money for hiring additional border agents.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Joe Biden loosened restrictions along the southern border after he took office and HHS Secretary Alejandro Mayorkas made the announcement that migrants seeking asylum would be permitted entry into the US as would unaccompanied minors.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">US Border Patrol Chief Raul Ortiz said that over the weekend 26,382 apprehensions were made by border patrol and that 11 pounds of fentanyl and 83 pounds of meth were seized.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Mexican cartels have exploited Biden's border crisis, with 2,378,944 illegal immigrant encounters reported in the 2022 fiscal year and 1,659,206 reported in FY 2021, by trafficking humans and drugs, especially fentanyl across the border in record numbers.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://www.dailywire.com/news/airlines-may-soon-be-on-the-hook-for-delayed-and-canceled-flights-transportation-dept-says"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.dailywire.com/news/airlines-may-soon-be-on-the-hook-for-delayed-and-canceled-flights-transportation-dept-says</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Airlines May Soon Be On The Hook For Delayed And Canceled Flights, Transportation Dept Says</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Transportation Secretary Pete Boo-tuh-jeg announced on Monday that the agency introduced rules requiring airlines to reimburse customers who incur expenses due to certain delayed and canceled flights, a move which comes as the industry faces elevated demand and a constrained labor force.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The proposed rules, which would apply when an airline delays a flight for more than three hours or cancels a flight for a &ldquo;controllable&rdquo; reason, would mandate that the firms offer compensation for stranded passengers, as well as a meal or meal voucher, overnight accommodations, and ground transportation between the airport and hotel.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&ldquo;When an airline causes a flight cancellation or delay, passengers should not foot the bill,&rdquo; Buttigieg said in a statement, noting that the proposed reimbursement rules would be the first in American history.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The move comes after Southwest Airlines experienced holiday travel disruptions last year due to extreme winter weather conditions, staff shortages, and an outdated computer system. The carrier canceled thousands of flights days after other carriers had resumed normal operations. Buttigieg told the company, which has since promised to compensate passengers for all expenses incurred during that time, that the disruptions were &ldquo;unacceptable&rdquo; and promised that his agency would exercise &ldquo;the fullest extent of its investigative and enforcement powers&rdquo; to ensure customers are reimbursed.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The new proposals also occur as the sector faces a severely limited pool of available pilots and frontline staff. Carriers previously encouraged commercial pilots to retire as worldwide lockdowns caused demand for air travel to plummet in the spring of 2020, worsening a previous trend toward a lack of available pilots. Elevated prices for airline tickets and a rapid return in travel demand, however, are now prompting lawmakers to consider the problem.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Regional Airline Association CEO Faye Malarkey Black told members of the House Transportation and Infrastructure Committee last month that more than 50% of current pilots would be forced to retire within the next 15 years because of federal rules mandating that pilots exit their positions once they reach 65 years of age, even as only 8% of pilots are below 30 years of age due to the high cost of flight education. Buttigieg has opposed legislation that would increase the retirement threshold to 67 years of age, contending that &ldquo;the answer is to make sure we have as many and as good pilots ready to take their place, to have a stronger pipeline.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://www.nbcnews.com/health/health-news/fecal-transplant-pill-fda-approval-rcna81779"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.nbcnews.com/health/health-news/fecal-transplant-pill-fda-approval-rcna81779</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>FDA approves first pill for fecal transplants, made from healthy bacteria in human waste</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">U.S. health officials on Wednesday approved the first pill made from healthy bacteria found in human waste to fight dangerous gut infections &mdash; an easier way of performing so-called fecal transplants.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The new treatment from Seres Therapeutics provides a simpler, rigorously tested version of stool-based procedures that some medical specialists have used for more than a decade to help patients.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The Food and Drug Administration cleared the capsules for adults 18 and older who face risks from repeat infections with Clostridium difficile, a bacteria that can cause severe nausea, cramping and diarrhea.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<ol>
<li><span style="font-weight: 400;"> diff is particularly dangerous when it reoccurs, leading to between 15,000 and 30,000 deaths per year. It can be killed with antibiotics but they also destroy good bacteria that live in the gut, leaving it more susceptible to future infections. The new capsules are approved for patients who have already received antibiotic treatment.</span></li>
</ol>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">More than 10 years ago, some doctors began reporting success with fecal transplants &mdash; using stool from a healthy donor &mdash; to restore the gut&rsquo;s healthy balance and prevent reinfections.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The FDA approved the first pharmaceutical-grade version of the treatment last year from a rival drugmaker, Ferring Pharmaceuticals. But that company&rsquo;s product &mdash; like most of the original procedures &mdash; must be delivered via the rectum.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Cambridge, Mass.-based Seres will market its drug as a less invasive option. The treatment will be sold under the brand name Vowst and comes as a regimen of four daily capsules taken for three consecutive days.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Both of the recent FDA approvals are the product of years of pharmaceutical industry research into the microbiome, the community of bacteria, viruses and fungi that live in the gut.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Currently most fecal transplants are provided by a network of stool banks that have popped up at medical institutions and hospitals across the country.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">While the availability of new FDA-approved options is expected to decrease demand for donations from stool banks, some plan to stay open.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The FDA warned in its approval announcement that the drug &ldquo;may carry a risk of transmitting infectious agents. It is also possible for Vowst to contain food allergens,&rdquo; the agency noted.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The FDA approved the treatment based on a 180-patient study in which nearly 88% of patients taking the capsules did not experience reinfection after 8 weeks, compared with 60% of those who received dummy pills.</span></p>]]></description>
   <author><![CDATA[Garrison Hardie]]></author>
   <enclosure url="https://app.dropwave.io/episode/eade695e-9ed3-47f9-a2e6-93f67f318e99/crosspolitic-daily-news-brief-for-tuesday-may-9th-2023.mp3" length="778" type="audio/mp3"/>
   <guid isPermaLink="false"><![CDATA[eade695e-9ed3-47f9-a2e6-93f67f318e99]]></guid>
   <pubDate>Tue, 09 May 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
   <source url=""><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></source>
   <itunes:author><![CDATA[Garrison Hardie]]></itunes:author>
   <itunes:image href="https://assets-cdn2.dropwave.io/2ab40ac0-e99d-4f25-a6d2-541d2c9b290a/cover-art/hUZu1H9lrRY0wXg66WHC8eLwYBA3hbRNTAHQmHt2.png"/>
   <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
   <itunes:duration>778</itunes:duration>
   <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
  
  </item><item>
   <title><![CDATA[CrossPolitic Daily News Brief for Friday, May 5th, 2023 [Daily News Brief]]]></title>
   <link>https://app.dropwave.io/episode/11f6aeb4-42f0-4413-bf0f-675fb220e80a/crosspolitic-daily-news-brief-for-friday-may-5th-2023.mp3</link>
   <description><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">This is Garrison Hardie with your CrossPolitic Daily News Brief for Friday, May 5th, 2023. Watch out for the revenge of the 5th if you&rsquo;re into that&hellip; or cinco de mayo, take your pick.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://tvpworld.com/69620835/us-navy-deployed-drag-queen-influencer-to-boost-youth-recruitment"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://tvpworld.com/69620835/us-navy-deployed-drag-queen-influencer-to-boost-youth-recruitment</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>As part of a recruitment drive aimed at the country&rsquo;s youth, the U.S. Navy deployed a "drag queen influencer" to assist in boosting lagging numbers in the military.</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">In November of last year Joshua Kelley aka &ldquo;Harpy Daniels&rdquo;, who has over 1,300,000 likes on TikTok, revealed that he was to be the Navy&rsquo;s &lsquo;Digital Ambassador&rsquo;.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Whilst the U.S. Navy only recently revealed about approaching Kelley, the drag queen claims to have danced in drag in front of an audience of service officers on a number of occasions, even sharing one video from 2018 on his Instagram.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Kelley was part of a Digital Ambassador initiative that lasted from October 2022 to March 2023, &ldquo;designed to explore the digital environment to reach a wide range of potential candidates,&rdquo; a Navy spokesperson told Fox News. The spokesperson also said that the Navy is navigating &ldquo;the most challenging recruiting environment it has faced since the start of the all-volunteer force.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&ldquo;The Navy did not compensate YN2 Kelley or any others for being Navy Digital Ambassadors. The pilot has concluded and we are now evaluating the program and how it will exist in the future," the spokesperson added.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Regarding his role as Digital Ambassador, Kelley wrote on his Instagram page: &ldquo;Thank you to the Navy for giving me this opportunity! I don't speak for the Navy but simply sharing my experience in the Navy! Hoorah, and let's go Slay!&rdquo;.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Not only the Navy but more broadly the U.S. military face big problems in convincing young people to join. Only 13 pct of 18-29-year-olds are &ldquo;highly willing&rdquo; to join the military, whilst 25 pct declared themselves &ldquo;somewhat willing&rdquo; and 26 pct are &ldquo;not willing at all.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Gender ideology has become a hot topic in the Navy and all branches of the U.S. Armed Forces.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">In March, a group of House Democrats proposed legislation to prevent the Department of Defense from standing in the way of transgender people who want to serve in the military.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Some critics have argued that the purpose of the U.S. military is to provide security for the country, not to be a tool for gender ideology politics. Whilst others have suggested that in an unstable world, where a lot of military strategy is played out through bravado, such as with military drills, it is perhaps surprising that the U.S. would do the opposite of striking fear into their enemies.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">It&rsquo;s a good thing we have Joshua to scare off said enemies, which ties in nicely for this next story!</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://www.usnews.com/news/world/articles/2023-05-03/second-oil-tanker-in-a-week-seized-by-iran-in-gulf-u-s-navy"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.usnews.com/news/world/articles/2023-05-03/second-oil-tanker-in-a-week-seized-by-iran-in-gulf-u-s-navy</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Iran Seizes Second Oil Tanker in a Week in Gulf -U.S. Navy</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Iran seized a second oil tanker in a week on Wednesday in Gulf waters, and the U.S. State Department called for its release, in the latest escalation in a series of seizures or attacks on commercial vessels in Gulf waters since 2019.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The Baa-rain-based Fifth Fleet of the U.S. Navy said the Panama-flagged oil tanker Niovi was seized by Iran's Islamic Revolutionary Guard Corps Navy (IRGCN) at 6:20 a.m. (0220 GMT) while passing through the Strait of Hor-mooz.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">In Iran's first response, Tehran's prosecutor announced the oil tanker was seized on a judicial order following a complaint by a plaintiff, the judiciary's Mizan news agency said. No further details were provided.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The incident comes after Iran on Thursday seized a Marshall Islands-flagged oil tanker in the Gulf of Oman called the Advantage Sweet. That tanker is being held by Iranian authorities in Bandar Abbas, the Marshall Islands flag registry said on Tuesday.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Maritime security firm Ambrey has said it believed the Advantage Sweet's seizure was in response to a recent seizure via a court order by the United States of an oil cargo aboard the Marshall Islands tanker Suez Rajan.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The Niovi oil tanker seized on Wednesday had been travelling from Dubai toward the UAE's Fujairah port when it was forced by IRGCN boats to change course towards Iranian territorial waters, the Navy said.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The Niovi last reported its position at 0231 GMT on Wednesday off the coast of Oman in the Strait of Hormuz with the UAE as its destination, Refinitiv ship tracking data showed.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">According to the International Maritime Organization shipping database,, the Niovi's owner is Grand Financing Co, and the ship is managed by Greece-based Smart Tankers, which did not immediately respond to a request for comment.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Vedant Patel, a deputy spokesperson at the U.S. State Department, told reporters the Biden administration and the "international community" call on Iran and its Navy to release the ships and their crews. "Iran's harassment of vessels and interference with navigational rights in regional and international waters are contrary to international law and disruptive to regional stability and security," Patel said.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">About a fifth of the world's crude oil and oil products passes through the Strait of Hormuz, a choke point between Iran and Oman, according to data from analytics firm Vortexa.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Since 2019, there have been a series of attacks on shipping in the strategic Gulf waters at times of tension between the United States and Iran.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Indirect talks between Tehran and Washington to revive Iran's 2015 nuclear pact with world powers have stalled since September over a range of issues, including the Islamic Republic's violent crackdown on popular protests, Tehran's sale of drones to Russia and acceleration of its nuclear program.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://justthenews.com/nation/crime/alleged-texas-killer-captured-following-manhunt"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://justthenews.com/nation/crime/alleged-texas-killer-captured-following-manhunt</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Fugitive illegal alien accused of mass killing in Texas captured</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Authorities on Tuesday apprehended an individual suspected of killing five people in Cleveland, Texas, following a Friday evening altercation.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Authorities arrested Francisco Oropesa without incident on Tuesday evening, NBC News reported, citing the Montgomery County Sheriff's Office.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">His arrest marks an end to the manhunt that had baffled law enforcement for days. Authorities indicated earlier this week that they had "zero leads" as to his whereabouts.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">As of Monday, it was believed that Oropesa had slipped past a network of roadblocks in the Cleveland area, despite extensive efforts by law enforcement to contain him within a set perimeter.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">During the manhunt, reports emerged that the fugitive had been deported four times, twice in 2009, and again in 2012 and 2016.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The manhunt ensued following Oropesa's alleged killing of five of his neighbors after reportedly being asked to stop shooting his firearm. Authorities indicated that four adults were found dead at the scene while one child died at the hospital later.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://www.latimes.com/california/story/2023-05-03/gun-rights-advocates-renew-legal-fight-over-californias-10-day-wait-on-firearm-purchases"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.latimes.com/california/story/2023-05-03/gun-rights-advocates-renew-legal-fight-over-californias-10-day-wait-on-firearm-purchases</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Gun rights advocates renew legal fight over California&rsquo;s 10-day wait for firearm buyers</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Renewing a legal battle that some had considered settled, gun rights advocates filed a federal lawsuit this week challenging a California law that places a 10-day waiting period on most firearm purchases.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The law, which requires people to wait the prescribed &ldquo;cooling off&rdquo; period even if they&rsquo;ve passed a more immediate background check, is aimed in part at deterring people from rushing to harm themselves or others with newly purchased weapons during periods of sudden distress or anger.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Gun control advocates and state officials say the law reduces gun violence, including suicides, and the law has been upheld in the face of legal challenges before &mdash; including by the U.S. Supreme Court, which in 2018 declined to hear an appeal to a lower court decision upholding it.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">However, things have changed since the high court ruled last year &mdash; in New York State Rifle &amp; Pistol Assn. vs. Bruen &mdash; that restrictions on firearms violate the 2nd Amendment if they aren&rsquo;t deeply rooted in the nation&rsquo;s history or analogous to some historical rule.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">According to the San Diego gun owners and advocacy groups suing the state, the high court&rsquo;s 2018 decision allowing the waiting period law to stand was &ldquo;abrogated,&rdquo; or undone, by its more recent Bruen decision, and, therefore, the law is unconstitutional under the court&rsquo;s newer historical standard.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The plaintiffs argue enforcement of the law &ldquo;prevents law-abiding people from taking possession of lawfully acquired firearms for immediate self-defense and other lawful purposes &mdash; even after [state officials] know the individual is eligible to exercise their fundamental, constitutionally protected right to keep and bear arms.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The office of California Atty. Gen. Rob Bonta said it was reviewing the lawsuit Tuesday but could not otherwise comment. Bonta is the lead defendant in the lawsuit.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">According to legal experts, the revived challenge reflects how massively the legal landscape around gun laws has changed since President Trump shifted the Supreme Court to the right and the court issued its Bruen decision.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">It also reflects the increased confidence among gun rights advocates that the high court is ready and willing to overturn more gun laws, the experts said &mdash; even those it may have allowed to stand in the past.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Jake Charles, an associate professor at Pepperdine Caruso School of Law and an expert in firearms law, said he was &ldquo;surprised it took until May of this year&rdquo; for the waiting period law to be challenged again under Bruen &mdash; in part because it is obviously vulnerable.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Prior to Bruen, federal courts across the country judged gun laws not only through a historical lens, but by assessing whether they served a well-reasoned purpose of modern government.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">When the California-based U.S. 9th Circuit Court of Appeals upheld California&rsquo;s 10-day waiting period law in 2016, it did so based on such a review. Writing for the court, Circuit Judge Mary Schroeder found that the 10-day waiting period was &ldquo;a reasonable safety precaution,&rdquo; and therefore constitutional.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Now, however, Bruen has changed the relevant legal analysis and Schroeder&rsquo;s reasoning is now irrelevant, the plaintiffs argue.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The law&nbsp; rvive, they argue, because waiting period laws were not enacted in the country until 1923 &mdash; making them too recent to be considered part of the nation&rsquo;s tradition under Bruen.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Gun law experts said it&rsquo;s a strong argument.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Attorneys for California may still argue the law is similar enough to some historical law that didn&rsquo;t institute a waiting period for purchased weapons but restricted the purchase of them in some other way. The state has already argued that other modern gun laws being challenged &mdash; including its bans on assault-style weapons and high-capacity magazines &mdash; are similar enough to other historical laws to survive Bruen&rsquo;s test, even if they aren&rsquo;t exactly the same.</span></p>]]></description>
   <author><![CDATA[Garrison Hardie]]></author>
   <enclosure url="https://app.dropwave.io/episode/11f6aeb4-42f0-4413-bf0f-675fb220e80a/crosspolitic-daily-news-brief-for-friday-may-5th-2023.mp3" length="673" type="audio/mp3"/>
   <guid isPermaLink="false"><![CDATA[11f6aeb4-42f0-4413-bf0f-675fb220e80a]]></guid>
   <pubDate>Fri, 05 May 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
   <source url=""><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></source>
   <itunes:author><![CDATA[Garrison Hardie]]></itunes:author>
   <itunes:image href="https://assets-cdn2.dropwave.io/2ab40ac0-e99d-4f25-a6d2-541d2c9b290a/cover-art/hUZu1H9lrRY0wXg66WHC8eLwYBA3hbRNTAHQmHt2.png"/>
   <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
   <itunes:duration>673</itunes:duration>
   <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
  
  </item><item>
   <title><![CDATA[Daily News Brief for Thursday, May the 4th be with you, 2023.  [Daily News Brief]]]></title>
   <link>https://app.dropwave.io/episode/1251c2aa-1900-4260-a78b-0bfeda16c36d/daily-news-brief-for-thursday-may-the-4th-be-with-you-2023-1.mp3</link>
   <description><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">This is Garrison Hardie with your CrossPolitic Daily News Brief for Thursday, May the 4th be with you, 2023.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://youtu.be/-bzWSJG93P8"><span style="font-weight: 400;" data-rich-links="{&quot;fple-t&quot;:&quot;Star Wars- The Imperial March (Darth Vader's Theme)&quot;,&quot;fple-u&quot;:&quot;https://youtu.be/-bzWSJG93P8&quot;,&quot;fple-mt&quot;:null,&quot;type&quot;:&quot;first-party-link&quot;}">Star Wars- The Imperial March (Darth Vader's Theme)</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;">-Play 0:00-0:36</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Star Wars Day is an informal commemorative day observed annually on May 4 to celebrate the Star Wars media franchise created by founder, former chairman and CEO of Lucasfilm, George Lucas. Observance of the day spread quickly through media and grassroots celebrations since the franchise began in 1977.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The date originated from the pun "May the Fourth be with you", a variant of the popular Star Wars catchphrase "May the Force be with you". Even though the holiday was not created or declared by Lucasfilm, many Star Wars fans around the world have chosen to celebrate the holiday. It has since been embraced by Lucasfilm and parent company Disney as an annual celebration of Star Wars.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Additionally, the release date of the original Star Wars movie on May 25, 1977 is also celebrated as Geek Pride Day.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Olive Tree Biblical Software:</strong></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Discover why more than a million people use the free Olive Tree Bible App as their go-to for reading, studying, and listening to the God&rsquo;s Word.&nbsp;&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Download one of many free Bibles and start taking notes, highlighting verses, and bookmarking your favorite passages.&nbsp;&nbsp;</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Read at your own pace, or choose from a large selection of Reading Plans, including the Bible Reading Challenge.&nbsp;</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">When you are ready to go deeper into your studies, Olive Tree is right there with a large selection of study Bibles, commentaries, and other helpful study resources available for purchase.&nbsp;&nbsp;</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">An extensive bookstore allows you to build your digital library one book at a time.&nbsp;</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Olive Tree&rsquo;s sync technology lets you pick up where you left off on your tablet, pc or phone and get right to studying on another supported device.&nbsp;</span></li>
</ul>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://www.cnn.com/2023/05/03/europe/ukraine-drone-attack-putin-kremlin-intl/index.html"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.cnn.com/2023/05/03/europe/ukraine-drone-attack-putin-kremlin-intl/index.html</span></a></p>
<p><strong>Kyiv denies involvement in alleged Kremlin drone attack</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Russia claimed Ukraine launched an attempt to kill Russian President Vladimir Putin with a drone strike on the Kremlin overnight on Wednesday, an extraordinary allegation that was met with forceful denials in Kyiv.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The Kremlin said the attack was foiled and the alleged drones destroyed. Video that appeared on social media shows a bright flash and a puff of smoke over a part of the Kremlin, the official residence of the Russian president and the most potent symbol of power in Moscow.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">In a statement, the Kremlin said it regarded the alleged attack as terrorism and a deliberate attempt on Putin&rsquo;s life. &ldquo;Russia reserves the right to take retaliatory measures where and when it sees fit,&rdquo; it added.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Ukraine denied involvement in the alleged strike.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">US officials said they were still assessing the incident, and had no information about who might have been responsible. Whatever the truth, any admission of a security breach at the heart of the Kremlin is remarkable.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Moscow said the alleged attack took place in the early hours of Wednesday. The Russian president was not in the building at the time, Kremlin spokesperson Dmitry Peskov said.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">analysis of video showing the incident support the Kremlin&rsquo;s claim that two drones were flown above the Kremlin early Wednesday, but did not show evidence of Ukrainian involvement:</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">A video that appeared to show smoke rising from the Kremlin surfaced on a local neighborhood channel on social media platform Telegram at 2:37 a.m. local time Wednesday. The first reports of the incident citing the Kremlin came via Russian state media TASS and RIA around 2:33 p.m. local time &ndash; around 12 hours later.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Shortly after the first media reports, another video appearing to show the moment a drone exploded above the Kremlin began circulating widely on social media. In the video, the drone appears to fly towards the building&rsquo;s domed roof, followed by what looks like a small explosion.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">In this video, two people appear to be climbing on the dome holding flashlights, and can be seen ducking down just before the moment of the explosion. The people climbing the dome are not present in the first of these videos, but appear in the second, suggesting they were responding to the fire caused by the first drone at the time the subsequent drone appeared.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The Kremlin Press Service has called the purported drone attack an &ldquo;attempt on the President&rsquo;s life,&rdquo; said it was an &ldquo;act of terrorism&rdquo; and blamed Ukraine.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://www.outkick.com/audrey-hale-nashville-police-release-update-litigation/"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.outkick.com/audrey-hale-nashville-police-release-update-litigation/</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>POLICE ANNOUNCE MANIFESTO OF NASHVILLE TRANSGENDER MASS KILLER WON&rsquo;T BE RELEASED SOON</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The release of transgender mass killer Audrey Hale&rsquo;s manifesto has been put on hold.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The Nashville Police Department had previously told Fox News Digital last week the manifesto was being revealed and would be released. People are interested to see what drove Hale to murder six innocent people, including three children, at the Covenant School in late March.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Now, it appears that the process has hit a roadblock.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Metro Nashville PD announced Wednesday afternoon that &ldquo;Due to pending litigation filed this week, the Metropolitan Nashville Police Department has been advised by counsel to hold in abeyance the release of records related to the shooting at The Covenant School pending orders or direction of the court.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The update is in response to a lawsuit filed by former Hamilton County Sheriff Jim Hammond and the Tennessee Firearms Association against the Nashville city government and the police to release the manifesto, according to TimeFreePress.com.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">As of early May, the public still doesn&rsquo;t have any idea what is in the manifesto.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">It&rsquo;s been more than a month since Audrey Hale walked into the Covenant School to unleash her rampage of terror against children and staffers.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Despite the significant time that has passed, government officials have seemingly dragged their feet to make sure the manifesto doesn&rsquo;t come out. For most of the time, it appeared that Hale&rsquo;s writings would never be released.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Metro Nashville Council Member Courtney Johnston previously told the New York Post, &ldquo;What I was told is, her manifesto was a blueprint on total destruction, and it was so, so detailed at the level of what she had planned &hellip; That document in the wrong person&rsquo;s hands would be astronomically dangerous.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2023/05/03/fed-rate-decision-may-2023-.html"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.cnbc.com/2023/05/03/fed-rate-decision-may-2023-.html</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Fed increases rates a quarter point and signals a potential end to hikes</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The Federal Reserve on Wednesday approved its 10th interest rate increase in just a little over a year and dropped a tentative hint that the current tightening cycle is at an end.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">In a unanimous decision widely expected by markets, the central bank&rsquo;s Federal Open Market Committee raised its benchmark borrowing rate by 0.25 percentage point. The rate sets what banks charge each other for overnight lending but feeds through to many consumer debt products such as mortgages, auto loans and credit cards.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The increase takes the fed funds rate to a target range of 5%-5.25%, the highest since August 2007.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Markets, though, are more focused on whether the Fed will pause here, particularly with lingering concerns over economic growth and a banking crisis that has rattled nerves on Wall Street. Stocks rose slightly and Treasury yields were mostly lower immediately following the Fed news, but stocks struggled to hold on to the gains.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">During Wednesday&rsquo;s news conference, Chairman Jerome Powell said &ldquo;a decision on a pause was not made today&rdquo; but noted the change in the statement language around future policy firming was &ldquo;meaningful.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The post-meeting statement had only offered some clarity on the future pace of rate hikes &mdash; and not by what it said but what it didn&rsquo;t say. The document omitted a sentence present in the previous statement saying that &ldquo;the Committee anticipates that some additional policy firming may be appropriate&rdquo; for the Fed to achieve its 2% inflation goal.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The statement also tweaked language to outline the conditions under which &ldquo;additional policy firming may be appropriate.&rdquo; Previously, the FOMC had framed the forward guidance around how it would determine &ldquo;the extent of future increases in the target range.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The statement reiterated that the Fed &ldquo;will take into account the cumulative tightening of monetary policy, the lags with which monetary policy affects economic activity and inflation, and economic and financial developments.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Taken together, the moves are at least a tenuous nod that while tight policy could remain in effect, the path ahead is less clear for actual interest rate hikes as policymakers assess incoming data and financial conditions.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Wednesday&rsquo;s decision comes amid U.S. economic fragility and over the objections of prominent Democratic lawmakers, who urged the Fed this week to stop rate hikes that they insisted could cause a recession and excessive loss of jobs.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">However, the labor market has remained strong since the increases started in March 2022. At the same time, inflation is still well above the 2% target that policymakers consider optimum. Multiple officials have said rates probably will need to stay elevated even if the hikes are put on hold.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://www.theepochtimes.com/irs-spent-10-million-on-weapons-since-covid-19-pandemic-began-watchdog_5238319.html?utm_source=partner&amp;utm_campaign=BonginoReport"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.theepochtimes.com/irs-spent-10-million-on-weapons-since-covid-19-pandemic-began-watchdog_5238319.html?utm_source=partner&amp;utm_campaign=BonginoReport</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>IRS Spent $10 Million on Weapons Since COVID-19 Pandemic Began: Watchdog</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The Internal Revenue Service (IRS) has been splashing out millions stocking up on guns, ammunition, and combat gear since 2020, according to the findings of Open The Books, a watchdog group that tracks government spending.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">A report by the watchdog, published on April 27, found that the agency has spent a total of $10 million on weaponry and gear since the COVID-19 pandemic began, including $2.3 million on duty ammunition, $1.2 million on ballistic shields, and another $1.3 million on &ldquo;various other gear for criminal investigation agents.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Additionally, the agency has spent $474,000 on Smith &amp; Wesson rifles, $463,000 on Beretta 1301 tactical shotguns, and $243,000 on body armor vests since 2020.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Another $467,000 was reportedly spent on duty tactical lighting, $354,000 on tactical gear bags, and $267,000 on ballistic helmets in the same time.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The report, called &ldquo;The Militarization of Federal Bureaucracy,&rdquo; contains updated data through the end of March 2023.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Since 2006, the IRS has splashed out $35.2 million (adjusted for inflation) on guns, ammunition, and military-style equipment. The report found that 2020 and 2021 saw them spend increased amounts.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">In a statement to Open The Books in 2021, an IRS spokesperson said IRS Criminal Investigation special agents &ldquo;have been using weapons throughout their history as they have consistently found themselves investigating the most dangerous criminals involved in organized crime, drugs, and gangs.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The IRS Careers website for criminal investigation special agents states that applicants must be willing to &ldquo;carry a firearm, must be prepared to protect him/herself or others from physical attacks at any time and without warning and use firearms in life-threatening situations; must be willing to use force up to and including the use of deadly force.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://www.dailyfetched.com/san-francisco-loses-another-retail-giant-as-shops-continue-to-close-due-to-crime/"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.dailyfetched.com/san-francisco-loses-another-retail-giant-as-shops-continue-to-close-due-to-crime/</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>San Francisco Loses Another Retail Giant as Shops Continue To Close Due to Crime</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">According to a memo from Chief Stores Officer Jamie Nordstrom to employees, the company has decided not to renew its leases for its San Francisco Centre Nordstrom store and the Market Street Rack store.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&ldquo;We&rsquo;ve spent more than 35 years serving customers in downtown San Francisco, building relationships with them and investing in the local community,&rdquo; Nordstrom wrote.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&ldquo;But as many of you know, the dynamics of the downtown San Francisco market have changed dramatically over the past several years, impacting customer foot traffic to our stores and our ability to operate successfully.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The San Francisco Centre location will close at the end of August, and the Market Street Rack will close on July 1.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">the owner of the Westfield mall, told the San Francisco Standard that such closures &ldquo;underscores the deteriorating situation in Downtown San Francisco.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">A spokesperson for the mall added:</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&ldquo;A growing number of retailers and businesses are leaving the area due to the unsafe conditions for customers, retailers, and employees, coupled with the fact that these significant issues are preventing an economic recovery of the area.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The statement continued:</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">[Unibail-Rodamco-Westfield] has actively engaged with city leaders for many years to express our serious concerns, which are shared by our customers and retailers. We have urged the city to find solutions to the key issues and lack of enforcement again.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The news comes not long after San Francisco flagship Whole Foods retail store closed after just a year due to 568 emergency calls over 13 months amid soaring crime in the city.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Incidents included vagrants starting fights, throwing food, and defecating on the floor.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Twenty retailers have closed stores in the Union Square area since 2020, The Standard reports.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Last month, CashApp founder Bob Lee was fatally stabbed in the streets of San Fransisco, while former fire commissioner Don Carmignani was recently beaten over the head with a pipe by a vagrant.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Last October, The Daily Fetched reported that commuters were resorting to arming themselves with baseball bats and stun guns due to droves of violent drug addicts.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Residents of the SoMa, in northeast San Francisco, said the recent opening of the SoMa RISE drug sobering center, which opened in June, has plagued the neighborhood, making it unsafe.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Residents say the center, which aims to temper drug usage, has done nothing but draw heavy users to the neighborhood.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Residents said the influx of drug users had brought soaring crime, making the neighborhood more dangerous, Fox News reported.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">San Francisco Mayor London Breed touted the center as a safe haven for addicts looking to rebuild their lives.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">But according to SoMa resident and business owner Mark Sackett, the reality of the center in the neighborhood is much different.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://www.dailyfetched.com/joe-biden-offers-500k-grant-for-teachers-in-pakistan-to-help-transgender-youth/"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.dailyfetched.com/joe-biden-offers-500k-grant-for-teachers-in-pakistan-to-help-transgender-youth/</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Joe Biden Offers $500K Grant for Teachers in Pakistan to Help Transgender Youth</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">According to the State Department grant, it will teach English language skills to Pakistani transgender youth so they &ldquo;better participate in the global community and prepare them for success in the workplace.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The grant report aims to focus on three components:</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">(1) Professional Development for English Language Teachers from Non-Mainstream Institutions</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">(2) Professional Development for novice Pakistani English language teachers</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">(3) Professional Development for Transgender Youth and for Afghan Teachers, Students, and Young Professionals Residing in Pakistan.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The program component that includes a focus on transgender youth accepts proposals from applicants &ldquo;for a minimum of $25,000 and a maximum of $75,000 to implement: (1) intensive professional development courses for Pakistani transgender youth from the ages of 13-25, and (2) and intensive professional development courses for Afghan teachers, students, and young professionals residing in Pakistan.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The components aim to improve English language communication skills and connect trainees to a professional alumni network.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Applicants to the Biden grant program are encouraged to address, &ldquo;What is the most effective way to reach the greatest number of Pakistani transgender youth and Afghan teachers, students, and young professionals from diverse locations across Pakistan?&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">A spokesperson for the State Department said the education project from the agency focuses on transgender youth like it does with other &ldquo;marginalized communities.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">However, the spokesperson added that the grant funds won&rsquo;t be used for gender transitions.</span></p>]]></description>
   <author><![CDATA[Garrison Hardie]]></author>
   <enclosure url="https://app.dropwave.io/episode/1251c2aa-1900-4260-a78b-0bfeda16c36d/daily-news-brief-for-thursday-may-the-4th-be-with-you-2023-1.mp3" length="951" type="audio/mp3"/>
   <guid isPermaLink="false"><![CDATA[1251c2aa-1900-4260-a78b-0bfeda16c36d]]></guid>
   <pubDate>Thu, 04 May 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
   <source url=""><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></source>
   <itunes:author><![CDATA[Garrison Hardie]]></itunes:author>
   <itunes:image href="https://assets-cdn2.dropwave.io/2ab40ac0-e99d-4f25-a6d2-541d2c9b290a/cover-art/hUZu1H9lrRY0wXg66WHC8eLwYBA3hbRNTAHQmHt2.png"/>
   <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
   <itunes:duration>951</itunes:duration>
   <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
  
  </item><item>
   <title><![CDATA[Daily News Brief for Thursday, May the 4th be with you, 2023.  [Daily News Brief]]]></title>
   <link>https://app.dropwave.io/episode/6b4e5a42-92bd-4e73-8198-9fc7232a40c6/daily-news-brief-for-thursday-may-the-4th-be-with-you-2023.mp3</link>
   <description><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">This is Garrison Hardie with your CrossPolitic Daily News Brief for Thursday, May the 4th be with you, 2023.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://youtu.be/-bzWSJG93P8"><span style="font-weight: 400;" data-rich-links="{&quot;fple-t&quot;:&quot;Star Wars- The Imperial March (Darth Vader's Theme)&quot;,&quot;fple-u&quot;:&quot;https://youtu.be/-bzWSJG93P8&quot;,&quot;fple-mt&quot;:null,&quot;type&quot;:&quot;first-party-link&quot;}">Star Wars- The Imperial March (Darth Vader's Theme)</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;">-Play 0:00-0:36</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Star Wars Day is an informal commemorative day observed annually on May 4 to celebrate the Star Wars media franchise created by founder, former chairman and CEO of Lucasfilm, George Lucas. Observance of the day spread quickly through media and grassroots celebrations since the franchise began in 1977.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The date originated from the pun "May the Fourth be with you", a variant of the popular Star Wars catchphrase "May the Force be with you". Even though the holiday was not created or declared by Lucasfilm, many Star Wars fans around the world have chosen to celebrate the holiday. It has since been embraced by Lucasfilm and parent company Disney as an annual celebration of Star Wars.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Additionally, the release date of the original Star Wars movie on May 25, 1977 is also celebrated as Geek Pride Day.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Olive Tree Biblical Software:</strong></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Discover why more than a million people use the free Olive Tree Bible App as their go-to for reading, studying, and listening to the God&rsquo;s Word.&nbsp;&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Download one of many free Bibles and start taking notes, highlighting verses, and bookmarking your favorite passages.&nbsp;&nbsp;</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Read at your own pace, or choose from a large selection of Reading Plans, including the Bible Reading Challenge.&nbsp;</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">When you are ready to go deeper into your studies, Olive Tree is right there with a large selection of study Bibles, commentaries, and other helpful study resources available for purchase.&nbsp;&nbsp;</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">An extensive bookstore allows you to build your digital library one book at a time.&nbsp;</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Olive Tree&rsquo;s sync technology lets you pick up where you left off on your tablet, pc or phone and get right to studying on another supported device.&nbsp;</span></li>
</ul>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://www.cnn.com/2023/05/03/europe/ukraine-drone-attack-putin-kremlin-intl/index.html"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.cnn.com/2023/05/03/europe/ukraine-drone-attack-putin-kremlin-intl/index.html</span></a></p>
<p><strong>Kyiv denies involvement in alleged Kremlin drone attack</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Russia claimed Ukraine launched an attempt to kill Russian President Vladimir Putin with a drone strike on the Kremlin overnight on Wednesday, an extraordinary allegation that was met with forceful denials in Kyiv.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The Kremlin said the attack was foiled and the alleged drones destroyed. Video that appeared on social media shows a bright flash and a puff of smoke over a part of the Kremlin, the official residence of the Russian president and the most potent symbol of power in Moscow.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">In a statement, the Kremlin said it regarded the alleged attack as terrorism and a deliberate attempt on Putin&rsquo;s life. &ldquo;Russia reserves the right to take retaliatory measures where and when it sees fit,&rdquo; it added.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Ukraine denied involvement in the alleged strike.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">US officials said they were still assessing the incident, and had no information about who might have been responsible. Whatever the truth, any admission of a security breach at the heart of the Kremlin is remarkable.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Moscow said the alleged attack took place in the early hours of Wednesday. The Russian president was not in the building at the time, Kremlin spokesperson Dmitry Peskov said.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">analysis of video showing the incident support the Kremlin&rsquo;s claim that two drones were flown above the Kremlin early Wednesday, but did not show evidence of Ukrainian involvement:</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">A video that appeared to show smoke rising from the Kremlin surfaced on a local neighborhood channel on social media platform Telegram at 2:37 a.m. local time Wednesday. The first reports of the incident citing the Kremlin came via Russian state media TASS and RIA around 2:33 p.m. local time &ndash; around 12 hours later.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Shortly after the first media reports, another video appearing to show the moment a drone exploded above the Kremlin began circulating widely on social media. In the video, the drone appears to fly towards the building&rsquo;s domed roof, followed by what looks like a small explosion.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">In this video, two people appear to be climbing on the dome holding flashlights, and can be seen ducking down just before the moment of the explosion. The people climbing the dome are not present in the first of these videos, but appear in the second, suggesting they were responding to the fire caused by the first drone at the time the subsequent drone appeared.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The Kremlin Press Service has called the purported drone attack an &ldquo;attempt on the President&rsquo;s life,&rdquo; said it was an &ldquo;act of terrorism&rdquo; and blamed Ukraine.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://www.outkick.com/audrey-hale-nashville-police-release-update-litigation/"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.outkick.com/audrey-hale-nashville-police-release-update-litigation/</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>POLICE ANNOUNCE MANIFESTO OF NASHVILLE TRANSGENDER MASS KILLER WON&rsquo;T BE RELEASED SOON</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The release of transgender mass killer Audrey Hale&rsquo;s manifesto has been put on hold.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The Nashville Police Department had previously told Fox News Digital last week the manifesto was being revealed and would be released. People are interested to see what drove Hale to murder six innocent people, including three children, at the Covenant School in late March.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Now, it appears that the process has hit a roadblock.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Metro Nashville PD announced Wednesday afternoon that &ldquo;Due to pending litigation filed this week, the Metropolitan Nashville Police Department has been advised by counsel to hold in abeyance the release of records related to the shooting at The Covenant School pending orders or direction of the court.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The update is in response to a lawsuit filed by former Hamilton County Sheriff Jim Hammond and the Tennessee Firearms Association against the Nashville city government and the police to release the manifesto, according to TimeFreePress.com.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">As of early May, the public still doesn&rsquo;t have any idea what is in the manifesto.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">It&rsquo;s been more than a month since Audrey Hale walked into the Covenant School to unleash her rampage of terror against children and staffers.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Despite the significant time that has passed, government officials have seemingly dragged their feet to make sure the manifesto doesn&rsquo;t come out. For most of the time, it appeared that Hale&rsquo;s writings would never be released.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Metro Nashville Council Member Courtney Johnston previously told the New York Post, &ldquo;What I was told is, her manifesto was a blueprint on total destruction, and it was so, so detailed at the level of what she had planned &hellip; That document in the wrong person&rsquo;s hands would be astronomically dangerous.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2023/05/03/fed-rate-decision-may-2023-.html"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.cnbc.com/2023/05/03/fed-rate-decision-may-2023-.html</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Fed increases rates a quarter point and signals a potential end to hikes</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The Federal Reserve on Wednesday approved its 10th interest rate increase in just a little over a year and dropped a tentative hint that the current tightening cycle is at an end.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">In a unanimous decision widely expected by markets, the central bank&rsquo;s Federal Open Market Committee raised its benchmark borrowing rate by 0.25 percentage point. The rate sets what banks charge each other for overnight lending but feeds through to many consumer debt products such as mortgages, auto loans and credit cards.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The increase takes the fed funds rate to a target range of 5%-5.25%, the highest since August 2007.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Markets, though, are more focused on whether the Fed will pause here, particularly with lingering concerns over economic growth and a banking crisis that has rattled nerves on Wall Street. Stocks rose slightly and Treasury yields were mostly lower immediately following the Fed news, but stocks struggled to hold on to the gains.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">During Wednesday&rsquo;s news conference, Chairman Jerome Powell said &ldquo;a decision on a pause was not made today&rdquo; but noted the change in the statement language around future policy firming was &ldquo;meaningful.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The post-meeting statement had only offered some clarity on the future pace of rate hikes &mdash; and not by what it said but what it didn&rsquo;t say. The document omitted a sentence present in the previous statement saying that &ldquo;the Committee anticipates that some additional policy firming may be appropriate&rdquo; for the Fed to achieve its 2% inflation goal.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The statement also tweaked language to outline the conditions under which &ldquo;additional policy firming may be appropriate.&rdquo; Previously, the FOMC had framed the forward guidance around how it would determine &ldquo;the extent of future increases in the target range.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The statement reiterated that the Fed &ldquo;will take into account the cumulative tightening of monetary policy, the lags with which monetary policy affects economic activity and inflation, and economic and financial developments.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Taken together, the moves are at least a tenuous nod that while tight policy could remain in effect, the path ahead is less clear for actual interest rate hikes as policymakers assess incoming data and financial conditions.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Wednesday&rsquo;s decision comes amid U.S. economic fragility and over the objections of prominent Democratic lawmakers, who urged the Fed this week to stop rate hikes that they insisted could cause a recession and excessive loss of jobs.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">However, the labor market has remained strong since the increases started in March 2022. At the same time, inflation is still well above the 2% target that policymakers consider optimum. Multiple officials have said rates probably will need to stay elevated even if the hikes are put on hold.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://www.theepochtimes.com/irs-spent-10-million-on-weapons-since-covid-19-pandemic-began-watchdog_5238319.html?utm_source=partner&amp;utm_campaign=BonginoReport"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.theepochtimes.com/irs-spent-10-million-on-weapons-since-covid-19-pandemic-began-watchdog_5238319.html?utm_source=partner&amp;utm_campaign=BonginoReport</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>IRS Spent $10 Million on Weapons Since COVID-19 Pandemic Began: Watchdog</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The Internal Revenue Service (IRS) has been splashing out millions stocking up on guns, ammunition, and combat gear since 2020, according to the findings of Open The Books, a watchdog group that tracks government spending.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">A report by the watchdog, published on April 27, found that the agency has spent a total of $10 million on weaponry and gear since the COVID-19 pandemic began, including $2.3 million on duty ammunition, $1.2 million on ballistic shields, and another $1.3 million on &ldquo;various other gear for criminal investigation agents.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Additionally, the agency has spent $474,000 on Smith &amp; Wesson rifles, $463,000 on Beretta 1301 tactical shotguns, and $243,000 on body armor vests since 2020.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Another $467,000 was reportedly spent on duty tactical lighting, $354,000 on tactical gear bags, and $267,000 on ballistic helmets in the same time.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The report, called &ldquo;The Militarization of Federal Bureaucracy,&rdquo; contains updated data through the end of March 2023.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Since 2006, the IRS has splashed out $35.2 million (adjusted for inflation) on guns, ammunition, and military-style equipment. The report found that 2020 and 2021 saw them spend increased amounts.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">In a statement to Open The Books in 2021, an IRS spokesperson said IRS Criminal Investigation special agents &ldquo;have been using weapons throughout their history as they have consistently found themselves investigating the most dangerous criminals involved in organized crime, drugs, and gangs.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The IRS Careers website for criminal investigation special agents states that applicants must be willing to &ldquo;carry a firearm, must be prepared to protect him/herself or others from physical attacks at any time and without warning and use firearms in life-threatening situations; must be willing to use force up to and including the use of deadly force.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://www.dailyfetched.com/san-francisco-loses-another-retail-giant-as-shops-continue-to-close-due-to-crime/"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.dailyfetched.com/san-francisco-loses-another-retail-giant-as-shops-continue-to-close-due-to-crime/</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>San Francisco Loses Another Retail Giant as Shops Continue To Close Due to Crime</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">According to a memo from Chief Stores Officer Jamie Nordstrom to employees, the company has decided not to renew its leases for its San Francisco Centre Nordstrom store and the Market Street Rack store.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&ldquo;We&rsquo;ve spent more than 35 years serving customers in downtown San Francisco, building relationships with them and investing in the local community,&rdquo; Nordstrom wrote.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&ldquo;But as many of you know, the dynamics of the downtown San Francisco market have changed dramatically over the past several years, impacting customer foot traffic to our stores and our ability to operate successfully.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The San Francisco Centre location will close at the end of August, and the Market Street Rack will close on July 1.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">the owner of the Westfield mall, told the San Francisco Standard that such closures &ldquo;underscores the deteriorating situation in Downtown San Francisco.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">A spokesperson for the mall added:</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&ldquo;A growing number of retailers and businesses are leaving the area due to the unsafe conditions for customers, retailers, and employees, coupled with the fact that these significant issues are preventing an economic recovery of the area.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The statement continued:</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">[Unibail-Rodamco-Westfield] has actively engaged with city leaders for many years to express our serious concerns, which are shared by our customers and retailers. We have urged the city to find solutions to the key issues and lack of enforcement again.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The news comes not long after San Francisco flagship Whole Foods retail store closed after just a year due to 568 emergency calls over 13 months amid soaring crime in the city.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Incidents included vagrants starting fights, throwing food, and defecating on the floor.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Twenty retailers have closed stores in the Union Square area since 2020, The Standard reports.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Last month, CashApp founder Bob Lee was fatally stabbed in the streets of San Fransisco, while former fire commissioner Don Carmignani was recently beaten over the head with a pipe by a vagrant.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Last October, The Daily Fetched reported that commuters were resorting to arming themselves with baseball bats and stun guns due to droves of violent drug addicts.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Residents of the SoMa, in northeast San Francisco, said the recent opening of the SoMa RISE drug sobering center, which opened in June, has plagued the neighborhood, making it unsafe.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Residents say the center, which aims to temper drug usage, has done nothing but draw heavy users to the neighborhood.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Residents said the influx of drug users had brought soaring crime, making the neighborhood more dangerous, Fox News reported.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">San Francisco Mayor London Breed touted the center as a safe haven for addicts looking to rebuild their lives.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">But according to SoMa resident and business owner Mark Sackett, the reality of the center in the neighborhood is much different.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://www.dailyfetched.com/joe-biden-offers-500k-grant-for-teachers-in-pakistan-to-help-transgender-youth/"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.dailyfetched.com/joe-biden-offers-500k-grant-for-teachers-in-pakistan-to-help-transgender-youth/</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Joe Biden Offers $500K Grant for Teachers in Pakistan to Help Transgender Youth</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">According to the State Department grant, it will teach English language skills to Pakistani transgender youth so they &ldquo;better participate in the global community and prepare them for success in the workplace.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The grant report aims to focus on three components:</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">(1) Professional Development for English Language Teachers from Non-Mainstream Institutions</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">(2) Professional Development for novice Pakistani English language teachers</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">(3) Professional Development for Transgender Youth and for Afghan Teachers, Students, and Young Professionals Residing in Pakistan.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The program component that includes a focus on transgender youth accepts proposals from applicants &ldquo;for a minimum of $25,000 and a maximum of $75,000 to implement: (1) intensive professional development courses for Pakistani transgender youth from the ages of 13-25, and (2) and intensive professional development courses for Afghan teachers, students, and young professionals residing in Pakistan.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The components aim to improve English language communication skills and connect trainees to a professional alumni network.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Applicants to the Biden grant program are encouraged to address, &ldquo;What is the most effective way to reach the greatest number of Pakistani transgender youth and Afghan teachers, students, and young professionals from diverse locations across Pakistan?&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">A spokesperson for the State Department said the education project from the agency focuses on transgender youth like it does with other &ldquo;marginalized communities.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">However, the spokesperson added that the grant funds won&rsquo;t be used for gender transitions.</span></p>]]></description>
   <author><![CDATA[Garrison Hardie]]></author>
   <enclosure url="https://app.dropwave.io/episode/6b4e5a42-92bd-4e73-8198-9fc7232a40c6/daily-news-brief-for-thursday-may-the-4th-be-with-you-2023.mp3" length="951" type="audio/mp3"/>
   <guid isPermaLink="false"><![CDATA[6b4e5a42-92bd-4e73-8198-9fc7232a40c6]]></guid>
   <pubDate>Thu, 04 May 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
   <source url=""><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></source>
   <itunes:author><![CDATA[Garrison Hardie]]></itunes:author>
   <itunes:image href="https://assets-cdn2.dropwave.io/2ab40ac0-e99d-4f25-a6d2-541d2c9b290a/cover-art/hUZu1H9lrRY0wXg66WHC8eLwYBA3hbRNTAHQmHt2.png"/>
   <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
   <itunes:duration>951</itunes:duration>
   <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
  
  </item><item>
   <title><![CDATA[Daily News Brief for Wednesday, May 3rd, 2023 [Daily News Brief]]]></title>
   <link>https://app.dropwave.io/episode/256dace2-7236-464e-8409-7180184ea69d/daily-news-brief-for-wednesday-may-3rd-2023.mp3</link>
   <description><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">This is Garrison Hardie with your CrossPolitic Daily News Brief for Wednesday, May 3rd, 2023.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>Club Membership Plug: (1/9)</strong></span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Ladies and gentleman, it&rsquo;s never been a better time to become a club member at CrossPolitic. This year, CrossPolitic will be dropping exclusive content into our club portal for club members ONLY. Some of this content will include a pilot TV Show called This America, a Bible study series with Pastor Toby, a special with New Saint Andrew&rsquo;s President, Ben Merkle, our backstage content, and our conference talks! You can grab a club membership for 10 bucks per month&hellip; that&rsquo;s two cups of coffee. So again, head on over to fightlaughfeast.com to get signed up today! That&rsquo;s fightlaughfeast.com.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://thefederalist.com/2023/05/02/in-reynosa-mexico-15000-haitian-immigrants-wait-for-key-biden-policy-to-end/"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://thefederalist.com/2023/05/02/in-reynosa-mexico-15000-haitian-immigrants-wait-for-key-biden-policy-to-end/</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>In Reynosa, Mexico, 15,000 Haitian Immigrants Wait For New Chaotic Biden Policy To Kick In</strong></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">An estimated 15,000 mostly Haitian immigrants have packed into every crevice of this northern Mexican city on the Rio Grande across from McAllen, Texas, and won&rsquo;t leave. At least not until after 11:59 p.m. on May 11.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">That&rsquo;s the moment when the pandemic-era &ldquo;Title 42&rdquo; rapid expulsion policy finally expires and is replaced by a new, untested Biden administration plan for keeping them in Reynosa as well as the &ldquo;volatile logjam,&rdquo; as The New York Times recently termed them, of tens of thousands of other immigrants now waiting for the policy change all over Mexico.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">But because of a powerful deterrent of Title 42 fairly unique to them, the 15,000 Haitians in Reynosa make for a good bellwether for if the administration&rsquo;s replacement strategy will hold them back as Title 42 has, or will invite the most chaotic rush on the U.S. southern border yet in this third long year of the most voluminous mass migration event in recorded American history.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The reason to watch Reynosa after May 12 is that most of its Haitians, long ago overflowing migrant camps all over town, will not dare cross the river while Title 42 is in effect, unlike other nationalities who have already disregarded it by crossing in large numbers. The Haitians of Reynosa won&rsquo;t go even as they enviously witness large numbers of Venezuelans nearby illegally cross in an overwhelming new surge despite Title 42 and see the American government admit them into the country.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Title 42&rsquo;s impact on them is why its ending makes Reynosa and its reticent population of Haitians almost the perfect bellwether to know if the Biden administration&rsquo;s plan for May 12 is going to work as sold. Either way, many hundreds of thousands, turning into millions by the end of the Biden term, will enter.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The question is whether it will be an orderly flow no one can see &mdash; or a schizophrenic rush that overflows border management preparations into towns and cities across the country, hurts the country, and poses a political liability for Democrats thinking about 2024 elections.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://time.com/6276438/biden-troops-border-title42/"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://time.com/6276438/biden-troops-border-title42/</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>Biden Sending 1,500 Troops to Southern Border Ahead of Expected Migration Surge</strong></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The Biden Administration will send 1,500 troops to the southern border of the U.S. to support immigration authorities facing tens of thousands of migrants expected to surge into the country once COVID-19 restrictions are lifted, U.S. officials said.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">At the request of the Department of Homeland Security (DHS), the U.S. service members will be sent on a 90-day temporary deployment assisting Customs and Border Patrol (CBP), the Pentagon announced on Tuesday. The troops will not carry out law enforcement work, but instead perform support duties that will free up CBP agents to detain and process migrants.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Homeland Security Secretary Alejandro Mayorkas said Sunday the government is bracing for a record tide of migration across the southwest border when pandemic restrictions, known as Title 42, end on May 11. The Trump-era authorities prevented migrants from requesting asylum and allowed U.S. border agents to quickly expel migrants out of public-health concerns.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Mayorkas emphasized the immigration system was stretched thin on resources and made a public case for federal relief.&ldquo;I just want to be clear that we are working within significant constraints,&rdquo; he said Sunday on &ldquo;Meet the Press.&rdquo; &ldquo;We need people. We need technology. We need facilities. We need transportation resources&mdash;all of the elements of addressing the needs of a large population of people arriving irregularly at our southern border.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Customs and Border Patrol (CBP) Commissioner Troy Miller told Congress last month his agency is preparing for about 10,000 migrant crossings every day once Title 42 ends. President Joe Biden signed an executive order April 27 to call-up active-duty troops to combat international drug trafficking, officials said. The DHS then formally asked for the Pentagon&rsquo;s support, which Defense Secretary Lloyd Austin approved on Tuesday.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Currently, there are about 2,500 troops&mdash;members of the National Guard on active-duty orders&mdash;deployed along the 2,000-mile-long southwest border supporting CBP&rsquo;s efforts. For years, U.S. forces have monitored &ldquo;Mobile Surveillance Cameras&rdquo; in all nine border sectors in each of the four states bordering Mexico. The devices are armed with infrared cameras, enabling service members to watch for illegal border crossings day or night.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://thepostmillennial.com/breaking-jay-inslee-will-not-seek-4th-term-as-washingtons-governor-in-2024?utm_campaign=64487"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://thepostmillennial.com/breaking-jay-inslee-will-not-seek-4th-term-as-washingtons-governor-in-2024?utm_campaign=64487</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>Jay Inslee will not seek 4th term as Washington's governor in 2024</strong></span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Washington state Governor Jay Inslee (D) announced Monday that he will not seek re-election in 2024.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">In a statement, Inslee said:</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">"Today I announced I will not be running for a fourth term. We've made Washington a beacon for progress, and now it's time to pass the torch," Gov Inslee said on Twitter. "I'm proud of the progress we've made on so many fronts: climate, financial aid, paid family leave, legal justice system reforms, gun safety, reproductive freedom... Now is the time to intensely focus on all we can accomplish in the next year and a half. I intend to do just that.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Inslee's announcement follows the conclusion of an "intense" and "controversial" legislative session where the democrat-controlled House and Senate voted to ban semi-automatic firearms, make Washington a sanctuary state for minors seeking gender affirming care and abortions, and legalized possession of illicit drugs, to name a few.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Governor Inslee became the second governor in state history to serve three consecutive terms after he was re-elected in 2020, and in his announcement Inslee called his tenure a "dynamic success."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Under Inslee's governance, Washington state has succumbed to criminal lawlessness as well as an existential homeless crisis rippling throug the evergreen state. Immediately following the announcement, critics of the governor took to social media to praise Inslee's decision to step down from his post, saying "good riddance."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://thenationalpulse.com/2023/05/01/carjackings-in-washington-dc-skyrocketing/"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://thenationalpulse.com/2023/05/01/carjackings-in-washington-dc-skyrocketing/</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>How Many Carjackings in Washington, D.C. in 2023? Here Are The Staggering Numbers&hellip;</strong></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Carjackings in Washington D.C. continue to skyrocket in line with a five-year trend that has the local police chief Robert Contee lamenting that crimes are happing &ldquo;at a pace that I have not seen in my 30-plus year career here with the Metropolitan Police Department.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Since the beginning of the year, there have been a staggering 228 carjackings in the District, 78 of which occurred in April alone, with 23 in the last week, according to the Washington D.C. Metropolitical Police Department (MPD). Despite 74 percent of this year&rsquo;s carjackings featuring a firearm, less than 35 percent of carjacking offenses are prosecuted.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">In 2018, there were 148 carjackings in D.C., and 152 in 2019. However, following the death of George Floyd, the D.C. city council announced its intention to slash $15 million from the MPD&rsquo;s annual budget. This resulted in an explosion in carjackings, amongst other crimes.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">In 2020, there were 360 carjackings, followed by 425 in 2021, and 485 last year. If carjackings continue to occur at the current rate, there may be as many as 600 by the end of 2023.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Republicans from the U.S. House of Representatives were forced to intervene earlier this year after the D.C. council wanted to reduce penalties for violent crimes such as carjacking and gun possession.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The D.C. council thought it better to lower the maximum jail time for carjackings, and eliminate most mandatory minimum sentences for crimes in the capitol than addressing the problem as the MPD demanded. The Criminal Code Act of 2022 was, however, blocked by the U.S. Congress from coming into force, with 33 Democrat Senators even voting against the bill.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Andrew Clyde, a House Representative from Georgia&rsquo;s 9th District, led the charge against the Criminal Code Act, arguing that Congress had to &ldquo;stop this insanity in its tracks.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The Democrat Mayor of Washington D.C., Muriel Bowser, has also promised free steering wheel locks for some cars after suggesting one of the reasons why carjackings are so common had something to do with a &ldquo;recent social media challenge.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">These actions, however, do not meet the demands of the local police force. A representative of the MPD Carjacking Task Force, Valkyrie Barnes, argues, &ldquo;It&rsquo;s ridiculous&hellip; unless there is some kind of deterrent to this, it&rsquo;s not going to stop&hellip; we need more [detectives].&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The District of Columbia and many of its residents currently support the notion of adding D.C. as a fully-fledged state, arguing that residents are taxed as citizens, but do not receive commensurate representation as a result. Opponents of this cause point out that D.C. residents often have far more political sway than ordinary voters around the country, and that the purpose of the District, per the nation&rsquo;s founders, was to be separate from the Congress and its machinations. Many of the latter group believe that much of D.C. should be given back to Virginia and Maryland as a means to create a compromise over representation.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/americas/vice-media-bankruptcy-journalism-layoffs-b2330554.html"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/americas/vice-media-bankruptcy-journalism-layoffs-b2330554.html</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>Vice heading for bankruptcy after once being worth $5.7bn, reports say</strong></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Vice, once heralded as the insurgent leader of a new generation of media companies, is heading for bankruptcy, according to The New York Times.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Two people familiar with Vice operations told the paper the media company is looking for a buyer. Otherwise, the company will have to file for bankruptcy, the unnamed sources said.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">&ldquo;Vice Media Group has been engaged in a comprehensive evaluation of strategic alternatives and planning,&rdquo; Vice said in a statement on Monday to the Times. &ldquo;The company, its board and stakeholders continue to be focused on finding the best path for the company.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The media company, which got its start as a Canadian alternative publication, eventually became a digital powerhouse known for its in-your-face, youth-focused stories about politics, music, and culture, told across a constellation of websites, films, podcasts, TV shows, the flagship magazine, and eventually a standalone TV network.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Vice News reporters filed memorable documentaries like a report from the Charlottesville &ldquo;Unite the Right&rdquo; rally in 2017, as well as reporting gonzo tales like chronicling NBA legend Dennis Rodman&rsquo;s visit to North Korea.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">A 2017 investment round led by TPG once valued the company at $5.7bn. More recently, the company was thought to be worth less than $1bn, according to reports earlier this year about the company&rsquo;s potential search for a buyer.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Despite receiving acclaim for its unique style of storytelling, as well investments from marquee names like Disney and Fox, the company has continued to struggle financially.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Last week, the company announced it would cancel its flagship &ldquo;Vice News Tonight&rdquo; show and lay off dozens of employees amid a larger corporate restructuring, the latest in a bruising season of media layoffs that saw cuts at Insider, NPR, Paper magazine, and the demise of Buzzfeed News.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">That follows reports that the Vice got an emergency $30m in financing to pay off a growing number of debts.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">In February, Vice Media chief executive Nancy Dubuc left the company.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The company fell short of a 2022 revenue goal by more than $100m, The Wall Street Journal reported in December.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The previous year, the company scuttled plans to go public through a special purpose acquisition company.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">In addition to its financial woes, Vice has been plagued by scandals, with critics charging the company&rsquo;s anti-establishment ethos at times covered up a corporate culture rife with abuse.</span></p>
<p><br /><br /><br /></p>]]></description>
   <author><![CDATA[Garrison Hardie]]></author>
   <enclosure url="https://app.dropwave.io/episode/256dace2-7236-464e-8409-7180184ea69d/daily-news-brief-for-wednesday-may-3rd-2023.mp3" length="780" type="audio/mp3"/>
   <guid isPermaLink="false"><![CDATA[256dace2-7236-464e-8409-7180184ea69d]]></guid>
   <pubDate>Wed, 03 May 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
   <source url=""><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></source>
   <itunes:author><![CDATA[Garrison Hardie]]></itunes:author>
   <itunes:image href="https://assets-cdn2.dropwave.io/2ab40ac0-e99d-4f25-a6d2-541d2c9b290a/cover-art/hUZu1H9lrRY0wXg66WHC8eLwYBA3hbRNTAHQmHt2.png"/>
   <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
   <itunes:duration>780</itunes:duration>
   <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
  
  </item><item>
   <title><![CDATA[Daily News Brief for Tuesday, May 2nd, 2023 [Daily News Brief]]]></title>
   <link>https://app.dropwave.io/episode/2ddf19b8-8538-4187-bf36-9aa48b978c3b/daily-news-brief-for-tuesday-may-2nd-2023.mp3</link>
   <description><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">This is Garrison Hardie with your CrossPolitic Daily News Brief for Tuesday, May 2nd, 2023.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Fight Laugh Feast Conference - Ark Encounter</strong></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">This year, our Fight Laugh Feast Conference is at the Ark Encounter in Kentucky on The Politics of Six Day Creation. The politics of six day creation is the difference between a fixed standard of justice and a careening standard of justice, the difference between the corrosive relativism that creates mobs and anarchy and the freedom of objectivity, truth, and due process. The politics of six day creation establishes the authority and sufficiency of God&rsquo;s Word for all of life: from what is a man or a woman, when does human life begin, and how is human society best organized?</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Come hear Ken Ham, Pastor Doug Wilson, Dr. Ben Merkle, Dr. Gordon Wilson, me and more, and of course a live CrossPolitic show! Mark your calendars for October 11th-14th, as we fight, laugh, and feast, with beer &amp; psalms, our amazing lineup of speakers, our Rowdy Christian Merch, and a Sabbath Feast to wrap up the occasion. Maybe an infant baptism while we&rsquo;re at it! Visit fightlaughfeast.com for more information!</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://www.financialexpress.com/world-news/us-says-chinese-coast-guard-harassing-philippine-vessels/3069316/"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.financialexpress.com/world-news/us-says-chinese-coast-guard-harassing-philippine-vessels/3069316/</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>US says Chinese coast guard harassing Philippine vessels</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The United States urged China on Saturday to stop harassing Philippine vessels in the South China Sea, pledging to stand with the Philippines after another maritime confrontation between the two Asian countries.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&ldquo;We call upon Beijing to desist from its provocative and unsafe conduct,&rdquo; the U.S. State Department said in a statement.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The Philippines on Friday accused China&rsquo;s coast guard of &ldquo;aggressive tactics&rdquo; following an incident during a Philippine coast guard patrol close to the Philippines-held Second Thomas Shoal, a flashpoint for previous altercations located 105 nautical miles (195 km) off its coast.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">China on Sunday said it was willing to handle maritime differences with countries of concern in the South China Sea through friendly consultations and warned the United States against interference.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&ldquo;The U.S., as a country outside of the region, must not interfere with the South China Sea matter or use the South China Sea matter to sow discord among regional countries,&rdquo; a Chinese foreign ministry spokesperson said in a written statement.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The Second Thomas Shoal is home to a small military contingent aboard a rusty World War Two-era U.S. ship that was intentionally grounded in 1999 to reinforce the Philippines&rsquo; territorial claims. In February, the Philippines said a Chinese ship had directed a &ldquo;military-grade laser&rdquo; at one of its resupply vessels.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">China claims sovereignty over almost the entire South China Sea, with a &ldquo;nine-dash line&rdquo; on maps that stretches more than 1,500 km off its mainland and cuts into the exclusive economic zones of Vietnam, the Philippines, Malaysia, Brunei and Indonesia. An international arbitral ruling in 2016 dismissed that line as having no legal basis.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">China&rsquo;s foreign ministry on Friday said the Philippine vessels had intruded into Chinese waters and made deliberate provocative moves.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The State Department said Washington &ldquo;stands with our Philippine allies in upholding the rules-based international maritime order.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2023/05/01/us/politics/debt-limit-date-janet-yellen.html#:~:text=WASHINGTON%20%E2%80%94%20Treasury%20Secretary%20Janet%20L,defaulting%20on%20the%20nation's%20debt"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.nytimes.com/2023/05/01/us/politics/debt-limit-date-janet-yellen.html#:~:text=WASHINGTON%20%E2%80%94%20Treasury%20Secretary%20Janet%20L,defaulting%20on%20the%20nation's%20debt</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;">.&rsquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>U.S. Could Run Out of Cash by June 1, Yellen Warns</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Treasury Secretary Janet L. Yellen said on Monday that the United States could run out of money to pay its bills by June 1 if Congress does not raise or suspend the debt limit, putting pressure on President Biden and lawmakers to reach a swift agreement to avoid defaulting on the nation&rsquo;s debt.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The more precise warning over when the United States could hit the so-called X-date dramatically reduces the projected amount of time lawmakers have to reach a deal before the government runs out of money to pay all of its bills on time. The new timeline could force a flurry of negotiations between the House, Senate and Mr. Biden over government spending &mdash; or a high-stakes standoff between the president and the House Republicans who have refused to raise the limit without deep spending cuts attached.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Economists have warned that failure to raise the debt limit, which caps the total amount of money the United States can borrow, threatens to rock financial markets and throw the global economy into a financial crisis.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Because the United States runs a budget deficit &mdash; meaning it spends more money than it takes in &mdash; it must borrow huge sums of money to pay its bills. In addition to paying Social Security benefits, along with salaries for the military and government workers, the United States is also required to make interest and other payments to the bondholders who own its debt.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">White House officials had not expected the date of possible default to arrive so soon, and the accelerated timetable could scramble the president&rsquo;s approach to the potential crisis.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The newly compressed calendar leaves little time for the president and congressional leaders to find agreement on raising the limit. Mr. McCarthy is traveling in the Middle East this week. Later this month, Mr. Biden is scheduled to attend the Group of 7 nations leaders&rsquo; summit in Japan, then travel on to Australia for a summit with the leaders of Japan, India and Australia.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">House Republicans passed legislation in April that would raise the debt limit in exchange for deep spending cuts and roll back recent climate legislation that Democrats passed along party lines. Mr. Biden has blasted that bill, saying it would hurt working families while benefiting the oil and gas industry, and he has accused Republicans of putting America&rsquo;s economy on the line.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">On Monday, the president called on Republicans &ldquo;to make sure the threat by the Speaker of the House to default on the national debt is off the table.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Mr. Biden has said he will meet with Mr. McCarthy to discuss government spending and the budget. But he has insisted that raising the debt limit is not negotiable and has urged Republicans to lift the borrowing cap without strings attached.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://www.usnews.com/news/health-news/articles/2023-05-01/biden-administration-to-end-many-covid-19-vaccine-mandates-next-week#:~:text=The%20Biden%20administration%20will%20also%20end%20the%20controversial%20Title%2019%20travel%20restrictions.&amp;text=May%201%2C%202023%2C%20at%205%3A43%20p.m.&amp;text=The%20Biden%20administration%20on%20Monday,international%20air%20travelers%20next%20week"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.usnews.com/news/health-news/articles/2023-05-01/biden-administration-to-end-many-covid-19-vaccine-mandates-next-week#:~:text=The%20Biden%20administration%20will%20also%20end%20the%20controversial%20Title%2019%20travel%20restrictions.&amp;text=May%201%2C%202023%2C%20at%205%3A43%20p.m.&amp;text=The%20Biden%20administration%20on%20Monday,international%20air%20travelers%20next%20week</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;">.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Biden Administration to End Many COVID-19 Vaccine Requirements Next Week</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The Biden administration on Monday announced that it will end its COVID-19 vaccine requirements for federal workers, federal contractors and international air travelers next week.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&ldquo;While vaccination remains one of the most important tools in advancing the health and safety of employees and promoting the efficiency of workplaces, we are now in a different phase of our response when these measures are no longer necessary,&rdquo; the White House said in a statement.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The mandates will end May 11, the same day the COVID-19 public health emergency declaration is set to expire.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The Biden administration will also begin the process to end coronavirus vaccine requirements for &ldquo;Head Start educators, CMS-certified healthcare facilities, and certain noncitizens at the land border.&rdquo; Additional details on the process will be available in the coming days, according to the White House.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Additionally, the Department of Homeland Security on Monday said it would end its Title 19 travel restrictions on May 12. The agency will &ldquo;no longer require non-U.S. travelers entering the United States via land ports of entry and ferry terminals to be fully vaccinated against COVID-19 and provide related proof of vaccination upon request.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Coronavirus vaccine requirements were among the most controversial decisions from the Biden administration during the pandemic. As coronavirus cases, deaths and hospitalizations have declined, the administration rolled back nearly all of its COVID-19 mitigation measures. The Pentagon in January dropped its COVID-19 vaccine mandate for troops after President Joe Biden signed into law a massive defense spending bill that required the measure&rsquo;s termination, bringing a close to the contentious issue that drew considerable ire from Republicans.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://www.theepochtimes.com/bernie-sanders-calls-for-confiscation-of-wealth-above-999-million_5232590.html?utm_source=partner&amp;utm_campaign=BonginoReport"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.theepochtimes.com/bernie-sanders-calls-for-confiscation-of-wealth-above-999-million_5232590.html?utm_source=partner&amp;utm_campaign=BonginoReport</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Bernie Sanders Calls for Confiscation of Wealth Above $999 Million</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Senator Bernie Sanders (I-Vt.) called for the U.S. government to confiscate assets over $999 million, and also announced his support for President Joe Biden.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The senator spoke with CNN anchor Chris Wallace last week for an interview when he declared that billionaires should not exist.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Sanders said he believes that the government should seize personal assets over his suggested limit before any American could become a billionaire.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">He appeared on Wallace&rsquo;s show to talk about his new book, &ldquo;It&rsquo;s OK to Be Angry About Capitalism.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">A former Democratic party presidential candidate, in 2016 and 2020, the senator amassed huge support in the primaries and raised large amounts of money, but failed to secure the nomination each time.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The CNN host questioned Sanders about a statement in his book that called for the government to prevent the creation of new billionaires.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&ldquo;So are you basically saying that once you get to $999 million, that the government should confiscate all the rest?&rdquo; Wallace asked.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&ldquo;Yeah, I think people can make it on $999 million,&rdquo; Bernie responded.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&ldquo;Which would mean that all these billion dollars, basically, it all goes to the government,&rdquo; said Wallace.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Sanders recently got into an exchange during a contentious Senate hearing over Starbuck&rsquo;s labor practices, with a not too subtle remark on the billionaire status of the company&rsquo;s former CEO, Howard Schultz.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Bernie, who is himself worth $3 million, according to GoBankingRates, previously criticized both millionaires and billionaires, but now only opposes those worth over a billion dollars.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The Vermont senator said that a return to the 90 percent top marginal tax rate of the Eisenhower administration was a way to accomplish that.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The proposed legislation calls for wealthy heirs to pay more on their inheritances by expanding the estate tax to 45 percent on estates worth at least $3.5 million.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">It will also impose a 65 percent tax&mdash;a so-called &ldquo;billionaire&rsquo;s tax&rdquo;&mdash;on estates worth over $1 billion.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The amount of inheritances exempt from the estate tax has gradually increased over the last two decades, according to the Tax Policy Center.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">As of 2023, the estate tax exemption stands at just under $13 million, a rise from around $12 million the previous year.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The bill also targets loopholes that the very wealthy can exploit to shield their assets from taxation such as trusts that do not incur estate or gift taxes when money is doled out from an inherited trust.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">However, any legislation to hike tax rates would be dead on arrival due to the Republican-controlled House.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://www.foxnews.com/us/new-mexico-mom-sentenced-18-years-tossing-baby-trash-bin"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.foxnews.com/us/new-mexico-mom-sentenced-18-years-tossing-baby-trash-bin</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>New Mexico mom sentenced to 18 years for tossing baby in trash bin</strong></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">A New Mexico teenage mother was sentenced Monday to a mandatory 18 years in prison for tossing her newborn son into a trash bin behind a shopping center, but a state district judge cited mental health concerns and the defendant's age in suspending two years of the punishment.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Jurors convicted Alexis Avila, 19, of child abuse involving great bodily harm following a days-long trial last month in which her public defender argued her actions were not premeditated and that a previously undiagnosed mental health disorder played a role.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Judge William Shoobridge told Avila that had it not been for luck and the grace of God he would have been deliberating a sentence in a murder case as there was a high probability the child would have died had it not been found by three people looking through the dumpster that winter day in Hobbs, near the Texas border.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">He ordered that Avila continue with treatment, medication and her higher education while serving her sentence.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Avila told the judge she wants to learn how to deal with stress and anxiety so she can handle her emotions in a healthier way. She also said she regrets missing out on her son's first milestones and that she denied him motherly love.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Police said a group of people were looking through the dumpster when they heard what they thought was a dog or kitten. They moved a trash bag and found a baby inside, wrapped in a towel with its umbilical cord still attached. They tried to keep the boy warm until police and paramedics arrived.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Prosecutors argued during trial that Avila made a choice to ignore her pregnancy and place her newborn son into two trash bags, secure them with a hair tie and toss the boy into the bin. They told jurors the boy had been in the cold for over six hours.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The judge told Avila that she had the opportunity to correct her actions within in that time but did not.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Her Public defender disputed that Avila made a premeditated attempt to kill her baby. He said while Avila's actions were wrong, they were the result of her bipolar disorder and that she was disassociated and detached from her feelings.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Her defender told the judge Avila did not pose a threat to the public, has made progress with her therapy and does not take lightly what she did to her child.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://www.latimes.com/entertainment-arts/business/story/2023-04-26/fox-news-ratings-plummet-without-tucker-carlson"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.latimes.com/entertainment-arts/business/story/2023-04-26/fox-news-ratings-plummet-without-tucker-carlson</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Fox News prime-time ratings plummet after Tucker Carlson firing as Newsmax sees boost</strong></p>
<p><br /><br /></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Fox News is feeling the effects of life without Tucker Carlson.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&ldquo;Fox News Tonight&rdquo; &mdash; the program temporarily filling the slot long occupied by Carlson &mdash; pulled in 1.7 million viewers with &ldquo;Fox &amp; Friends&rdquo; host Brian Kilmeade, according to Nielsen data.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The number is 47% below what &ldquo;Tucker Carlson Tonight&rdquo; delivered in the 8 p.m. Eastern hour a week earlier on April 16. Carlson averaged 3.2 million viewers in the first quarter of 2023.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Fox News now is faced with replacing a top-rated prime-time star, a situation it has dealt with successfully in the past. But in the short term, the network may be in for a rocky ride from a ratings standpoint.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">CNN&rsquo;s Anderson Cooper won the hour in the demo with 163,000 viewers, with MSNBC&rsquo;s &ldquo;All in With Chris Hayes&rdquo; close behind at 162,000. Kilmeade scored 149,000 in the category. The ratings indicate Kilmeade won&rsquo;t be giving up the morning shift anytime soon.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Without the tentpole that Carlson&rsquo;s program provided, the ratings for other Fox News shows were down as well. &ldquo;Hannity&rdquo; averaged 2 million viewers, a decline of 20% from the previous week. &ldquo;The Ingraham Angle&rdquo; scored 1.56 million, down 12%.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Fox News will be tested again, as the sharp decline in Tuesday&rsquo;s ratings is a clear sign that the audience is upset. One possible fix is moving Fox News fan favorite Jesse Watters into Carlson&rsquo;s time slot while auditioning hosts an hour earlier.</span></p>]]></description>
   <author><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></author>
   <enclosure url="https://app.dropwave.io/episode/2ddf19b8-8538-4187-bf36-9aa48b978c3b/daily-news-brief-for-tuesday-may-2nd-2023.mp3" length="868" type="audio/mp3"/>
   <guid isPermaLink="false"><![CDATA[2ddf19b8-8538-4187-bf36-9aa48b978c3b]]></guid>
   <pubDate>Tue, 02 May 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
   <source url=""><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></source>
   <itunes:author><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></itunes:author>
   <itunes:image href="https://assets-cdn2.dropwave.io/2ab40ac0-e99d-4f25-a6d2-541d2c9b290a/cover-art/hUZu1H9lrRY0wXg66WHC8eLwYBA3hbRNTAHQmHt2.png"/>
   <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
   <itunes:duration>868</itunes:duration>
   <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
  
  </item><item>
   <title><![CDATA[Daily News Brief for Friday, April 28th, 2023 [Daily News Brief]]]></title>
   <link>https://app.dropwave.io/episode/4dbee7a4-0428-4cf2-aeb0-40bf35f52577/daily-news-brief-for-friday-april-28th-2023.mp3</link>
   <description><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">This is Garrison Hardie with your CrossPolitic Daily News Brief for Friday, April 28th, 2023.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://www.breitbart.com/politics/2023/04/27/argentina-shuns-u-s-dollar-will-pay-for-china-imports-in-yuan/"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.breitbart.com/politics/2023/04/27/argentina-shuns-u-s-dollar-will-pay-for-china-imports-in-yuan/</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>Argentina Shuns U.S. Dollar: Will Pay for China Imports in Yuan</strong></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Argentina struck a deal with Beijing on Wednesday to stop using U.S. dollars to pay for Chinese imports and embrace the yuan instead.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The measure, driven by Argentina&rsquo;s leftist President Alberto Fern&aacute;ndez, is designed to relieve the South American country&rsquo;s dwindling dollar reserves, AP reports.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The deal further enhances China&rsquo;s rise on the world stage and the diminished role of the U.S. on a host of fronts under President Joe Biden.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">After reaching the agreement with various companies, Argentina will use the yuan for imports from China worth about U.S.$1.04 billion from next month, accelerating trade with China as Beijing seeks to gain a further foothold in South America.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">In November last year Argentina expanded a currency swap with China by $5 billion in an effort to increase its yuan reserves.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">That agreement allowed Argentina &ldquo;to work on the possibility&rdquo; of advancing the rate of imports with yuan-denominated import orders being authorized in 90 days rather than the standard 180 days.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The decision comes as Argentina battles critical levels in its dollar reserves amid a sharp drop in agricultural exports caused by a historic drought, as well as political uncertainty ahead of elections this year.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">It has also been working hard to build a relationship with Beijing after having officially joined China&rsquo;s infrastructure-building Belt and Road Initiative (BRI) last year.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Argentina&rsquo;s government finalized a deal with Beijing soon after to construct a nuclear plant based on Chinese technology near Buenos Aires, Argentina&rsquo;s national capital, in the near future.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The Chinese Communist Party will reportedly provide $8 billion in financing toward the project&rsquo;s $12 billion total budget.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">As Breitbart News reported, Argentina currently owes the International Monetary Fund (IMF) $44 billion.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The international organization is in talks with Argentine authorities to finalize a fourth review of its program that includes a flexibilization of the proposed foreign exchange reserve accumulation as Argentina, whose foreign reserves are now at a $5 billion deficit, cannot comply with the current goals.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://www.foxnews.com/world/singapore-executes-man-conspired-traffic-2-pounds-cannabis"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.foxnews.com/world/singapore-executes-man-conspired-traffic-2-pounds-cannabis</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>Singapore executes man who allegedly conspired to traffic 2 pounds of cannabis</strong></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Singapore on Wednesday executed a man accused of coordinating a cannabis delivery, despite pleas for clemency from his family and protests from activists that he was convicted on weak evidence.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Tangaraju Suppiah, 46, was sentenced to death in 2018 for abetting the trafficking of 2.2 pounds of cannabis. Under Singapore laws, trafficking more than 500 grams of cannabis may result in the death penalty.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Tangaraju was hanged Wednesday morning and his family was given the death certificate, according to a tweet from activist Kirsten Han of the Transformative Justice Collective, which advocates for abolishing the death penalty in Singapore.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Although Tangaraju was not caught with the cannabis, prosecutors said phone numbers traced him as the person responsible for coordinating the delivery of the drugs. Tangaraju had maintained that he was not the one communicating with the others connected to the case.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">At a United Nations Human Rights briefing Tuesday, a spokesperson called on the Singapore government to adopt a "formal moratorium" on executions for drug-related offenses.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">"Imposing the death penalty for drug offences is incompatible with international norms and standards," said the spokesperson, who added that increasing evidence shows the death penalty is ineffective as a deterrent.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Singapore authorities say there is a deterrent effect, citing studies that traffickers carry amounts below the threshold that would bring a death penalty.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The island-state's imposition of the death penalty for drugs is in contrast with its neighbors. In Thailand, cannabis has essentially been legalized, and Malaysia has ended the mandatory death penalty for serious crimes.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Singapore executed 11 people last year for drug offenses. One case that spurred international concern involved a Malaysian man whose lawyers said he was mentally disabled.</span></p>
<p><br /><br /></p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://dailycaller.com/2023/04/26/red-state-bill-religious-institutions-state-funding/"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://dailycaller.com/2023/04/26/red-state-bill-religious-institutions-state-funding/</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>Red State Passes Bill Allowing Religious Institutions Access To State Funding</strong></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The Oklahoma House of Representatives passed a bill Tuesday protecting religious institutions from being denied access to state funding.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The Oklahoma Religious Freedom Act was introduced by Republican state Sen. Shane Jett and Republican state Sen. Julie Daniels to further reinforce the First Amendment by preventing the state from denying faith-based groups access to taxpayer dollars, according to the bill. The legislature passed the act Tuesday by a 64 to 27 vote, officially sending the act to Republican Gov. Kevin Stitt&rsquo;s desk to be signed into law.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The bill makes way for religious institutions to access state funding by barring the state from denying applications for funding &ldquo;based solely on the religious character or affiliation of the person or entity.&rdquo; The act adds to religious protections the state passed in 2021 preventing the government from declaring church activities non-essential, as was often the case during the COVID-19 pandemic.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">However, some Democrats argued that the bill was an unnecessary addition to the First Amendment, according to KFOR.com, a local media outlet. One Democratic state representative warned that the bill could lead to government funding of religious activities at religious schools.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Republican state Rep. John Echols, who co-authored the bill, disagreed with his colleague&rsquo;s assessment, according to KFOR.com.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Oklahoma has been at the center of this discussion for some time. Earlier this month, Gov. Stitt and state Attorney General Gentner Drummond clashed over a Catholic charter school application that would have created the first state-funded religious charter school in the nation. The application was temporarily denied by the state&rsquo;s virtual charter board but will be voted on again in the coming weeks. Stitt told the Daily Caller News Foundation that he was disappointed by the the attorney general&rsquo;s response to the charter and continued to hope that Oklahoma would host the nation&rsquo;s first state-funded religious charter school, providing more options for parents.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Stitt, Jett, Daniels and Echols did not immediately respond to the Daily Caller News Foundation&rsquo;s request for comment.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://thepostmillennial.com/breaking-ex-producer-suing-tucker-carlson-has-never-even-met-him?utm_campaign=64487"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://thepostmillennial.com/breaking-ex-producer-suing-tucker-carlson-has-never-even-met-him?utm_campaign=64487</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>Ex-producer suing Tucker Carlson has never even met him</strong></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Tucker Carlson Tonight producer Abby Grossberg is suing Carlson and the Fox Network over sexual behavior in the workplace, despite never having met Carlson in person.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The Spectator reports that lawyers for Grossberg have confirmed that she never actually met Carlson. "Like many on the [Tucker Carlson Tonight] staff, Abby never met Tucker Carlson in person because he taped the show from his personal studios in Maine and Florida, and he did not visit Fox's NY HQ during her time there," said one of Grossberg's attorneys Kimberly A. Catala.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Grossberg was the head of booking from July 2022 until she was recently placed on leave in March. She "alleges that Carlson encouraged a hostile and sexist workplace environment among his employees. Grossberg says she was subjected to bullying, antisemitic comments and sexism by staff while working out of Fox&rsquo;s Manhattan office," Spectator reports.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Despite never having met Carlson, Grossberg told rival network MSNBC that "Tucker and his executive producer Justin Wells, who was also fired, really were responsible for breaking me and making my life a living hell."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">"Since Tucker did not come to the Fox office, he relied on Justin Wells, his executive producer, and others like Alexander McCaskill, senior producer, who were present in the office every day to be his eyes, ears and mouthpiece, and to convey his &lsquo;tone,&rsquo; as they threateningly reminded Ms. Grossberg," Catala said.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The allegation per Grossberg's attorneys is that Carlson directed the "sexist" environment from afar. Apparently, the attorneys posited that Carlson had staff work as his "eyes" and "ears" in the New York office while he worked away in Maine.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Carlson and Fox parted ways on Monday morning, though promos for the evening's show were already airing as the press release from Fox went out. It is unclear as to why Fox dismissed the insanely popular news anchor, though speculation abounds, including that Fox owner Rupert Murdoch took issue with Carlson's Christian beliefs.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Carlson has been seen in Florida enjoying time with his wife, and laughing about finally being able to dine together on weeknights. His show has been on the air for 7 years, and in that time he amassed a loyal following. In the hours following his departure from the network, "RIP Fox News" was trending on Twitter as many viewers found they had no reason to tune in once Carlson was no longer on the air.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The end of the Tucker Carlson Tonight era was celebrated by AOC, who had called for federal regulation of Fox and Carlson, which routinely took aim at her and her shenanigans.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2023/04/26/us/colorado-rock-throwing-arrests.html"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.nytimes.com/2023/04/26/us/colorado-rock-throwing-arrests.html</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>3 Teens Charged With Murder in Rock-Throwing Spree That Killed Colorado Driver</strong></span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Three teenagers have been charged with first-degree murder in connection with a rock-throwing spree on Colorado roads last week that led to the death of one driver, the authorities said.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The three suspects, all 18 and identified as Joseph Koenig, Nicholas Karol-Chik and Zachary Kwak, were arrested on Tuesday evening at their homes in Arvada, Colo., for taking part in a series of rock-throwing episodes on April 19 that fatally wounded Alexa Bartell, 20, who was killed when one of the rocks smashed through her windshield and struck her, the Jefferson County Sheriff&rsquo;s Office announced on Wednesday.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">In addition to murder, the three men are charged with extreme indifference; other charges to be determined by the First Judicial District Attorney&rsquo;s Office are expected.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">It was not immediately clear if the three, who are seniors from different high schools, had lawyers on Wednesday.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The rock-throwing spree began shortly after 10 p.m. on April 19 in Westminster, Colo., which is a city of about 114,000 residents north of Denver, the authorities said.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">During that hour, the authorities said, the three drove a pickup truck around the county and threw large landscaping rocks at six vehicles, including a minivan and an S.U.V., hitting their windshields and driver&rsquo;s side windows. Those drivers had minor or no injuries.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Around 10:45 p.m., Ms. Bartell was driving north on Indiana Street when her Chevrolet Spark, a subcompact, became the last vehicle struck during the spree, the authorities said.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Moments before she was killed, Ms. Bartell was on her phone talking to a friend &ldquo;when the phone went silent,&rdquo; according to the sheriff&rsquo;s office.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Her friend tracked her phone and drove to the location on Indiana Street where she found Ms. Bartell &ldquo;fatally wounded inside her car, which was off the roadway in a field.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">It was unclear which of the men were driving but &ldquo;all three are suspected of throwing rocks,&rdquo; the sheriff&rsquo;s office said. They were believed to be in a black 2016 Chevrolet Silverado pickup truck.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">&ldquo;Ultimately, mobile device forensics and supporting information from the public helped lead to the identification and arrest of the suspects,&rdquo; according to the sheriff&rsquo;s office, which did not release additional details.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The men, who were booked into the jail at the Jefferson County Sheriff&rsquo;s Office, are scheduled to appear in court on Thursday.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Before we end today&hellip; how about some good news?!</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://www.goodnewsnetwork.org/mom-wins-lottery-with-ticket-she-bought-celebrating-daughters-victory-over-cancer/"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.goodnewsnetwork.org/mom-wins-lottery-with-ticket-she-bought-celebrating-daughters-victory-over-cancer/</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>Mom Wins Lottery with Ticket She Bought Celebrating Daughter&rsquo;s Victory Over Cancer</strong></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">After shelling out her life savings to pay for her daughter&rsquo;s breast cancer treatment, a Florida grandmother got a nod from the universe.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Buying the last available scratch-off from her preferred lottery game at the store, she landed a $2 million jackpot.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Geraldine Gimblet of Lakeland was celebrating the moment that her daughter, Lawrencia Jackson, rang a bell at the local hospital signifying she had finished her breast cancer treatment.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">A long-time lottery player, Gimblet, 74, spent $10 on the last scratch-off card at the store, and it happened to be a winner.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">&ldquo;I just didn&rsquo;t know,&rdquo; Gimblet told Good Morning America regarding her reaction,, &lsquo;Are you sure, would you check this on your phone?&rsquo; And, I won!&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Daughter Jackson, who accompanied Gimblet to the Tallahassee lottery offices to accept a lump sum of $1.6 million, described it as a &ldquo;blessing.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Gimblet didn&rsquo;t hesitate to finance the cancer treatment, saying she just &ldquo;did what I had to do,&rdquo; with Jackson adding that she would &ldquo;just have to keep loving her,&rdquo; as a means to try and repay the kindness.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">+-</span></p>]]></description>
   <author><![CDATA[Garrison Hardie]]></author>
   <enclosure url="https://app.dropwave.io/episode/4dbee7a4-0428-4cf2-aeb0-40bf35f52577/daily-news-brief-for-friday-april-28th-2023.mp3" length="760" type="audio/mp3"/>
   <guid isPermaLink="false"><![CDATA[4dbee7a4-0428-4cf2-aeb0-40bf35f52577]]></guid>
   <pubDate>Fri, 28 Apr 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
   <source url=""><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></source>
   <itunes:author><![CDATA[Garrison Hardie]]></itunes:author>
   <itunes:image href="https://assets-cdn2.dropwave.io/2ab40ac0-e99d-4f25-a6d2-541d2c9b290a/cover-art/hUZu1H9lrRY0wXg66WHC8eLwYBA3hbRNTAHQmHt2.png"/>
   <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
   <itunes:duration>760</itunes:duration>
   <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
  
  </item><item>
   <title><![CDATA[Daily News Brief for Thursday, April 27th, 2023 [Daily News Brief]]]></title>
   <link>https://app.dropwave.io/episode/b0ae4f18-e5ad-48c5-8f38-9355608404b3/daily-news-brief-for-thursday-april-27th-2023.mp3</link>
   <description><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">This is Garrison Hardie with your CrossPolitic Daily News Brief for Thursday, April 27th, 2023.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://theconversation.com/ukraine-war-pentagon-leaks-paint-gloomy-picture-of-long-war-that-cant-be-won-but-must-not-be-lost-203698"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://theconversation.com/ukraine-war-pentagon-leaks-paint-gloomy-picture-of-long-war-that-cant-be-won-but-must-not-be-lost-203698</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Ukraine war: Pentagon leaks paint gloomy picture of long war that can&rsquo;t be won but must not be lost</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Classified Pentagon documents leaked last week paint a grim picture of the trajectory of the war in Ukraine. While it may well be the most significant national security breach since the Snowden leaks of US National Security Agency material a decade ago, the fact that the leak occurred is almost certainly more significant than what was revealed about Ukraine.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The leak reveals how apparently easy it was for a low-level employee on a US military base to obtain and then share highly sensitive US government information. By comparison, the contents of the documents on Ukraine leaked are far less explosive in nature &ndash; they mostly confirm existing battlefield assessments that cast doubt, in the eyes of US intelligence officials, on any major breakthroughs in a widely expected Ukrainian spring offensive.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The key shortfalls on the Ukrainian side &ndash; artillery pieces and munitions, as well as air defences &ndash; have been well known for some time. What has also been obvious for some time, and was reconfirmed in some of the leaked documents, is that Ukraine has been mostly relying on Soviet-era artillery equipment and stocks of ammunition have begun to run dry.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">At the same time, western equipment has been slow to be delivered and training of Ukrainian forces has taken time. And the western capacity to produce shells in excess of current Ukrainian consumption has yet to be built.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Add to that delays in training and equipping the troops needed for a counter-offensive and the likelihood of well-entrenched Russian defences. The low expectations of at best modest territorial gains in a Ukrainian spring offensive do not come as a surprise.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The equally limited gains that Russia has made over the past several months of its offensive, including around the still contested city of Bakhmut should serve as an indication of what is and is not possible after more than a year of war. Similarly, the protracted battle over Soledar back in January this year already gave a glimpse at how costly even minimal and strategically insignificant gains in this war have become.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The flipside of the US assessment that any Ukrainian counter-offensive is unlikely to constitute a turning point in the war is that the fighting is likely to continue beyond this year. In some estimates it could last well beyond that.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">There are no signs that either side is willing to give up. US estimates of casualties &ndash; among the leaks from the Pentagon &ndash; indicate more than 40,000 Russian soldiers killed in action over the past year and an additional 180,000 wounded. On the Ukrainian side, the figures are lower &ndash; with 17,500 likely dead and 113,500 wounded troops &ndash; but still significant. Both countries now have tightened conscription rules and procedures in another sign that they are readying themselves for intensifying battles.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Equally important from a Ukrainian perspective is continuing support from its western partners. Despite the logistical difficulties of ramping up defence industry outputs and deliveries to Ukraine, there is no indication that supplies will fall critically short and expose Ukraine to the risk of major battlefield defeats. This is partly because Moscow also cannot muster the superior military capabilities that would be needed for inflicting such defeats on Kyiv.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Ultimately, both sides are likely to match each other&rsquo;s increases in capability over time and the current stalemate will continue, albeit at a higher level of mutual attrition. And each increase in capability, however slight, will boost the conviction that this war remains winnable.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The Pentagon leaks have cast doubt on such assumptions, but also confirmed that neither Washington nor Kyiv are contemplating losing the war on the battlefield or the negotiation table. Time will tell whether this is a sustainable objective &ndash; and at what cost.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/policy/courts/disney-sues-desantis-alleged-campaign-weaponize-government-power-against-company"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/policy/courts/disney-sues-desantis-alleged-campaign-weaponize-government-power-against-company</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Disney sues DeSantis over alleged 'campaign to weaponize government power' against company</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Disney has filed a lawsuit against Gov. Ron DeSantis (R-FL) and members of the new Central Florida Tourism Oversight District alleging government power has been weaponized against them.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">In the lawsuit filed in the U.S. District Court for the Northern District of Florida, the company alleges a "relentless campaign to weaponize government power against Disney in retaliation for expressing a political viewpoint unpopular with certain State officials."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Disney argues the state and DeSantis have violated its First Amendment right to speech by working to strip control of the special taxing district encompassing the Walt Disney World Resort from the company after Disney spoke out against Florida's Parental Rights in Education bill.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The lawsuit was filed shortly after the Central Florida Tourism Oversight District unanimously approved a resolution to declare an agreement designed to undercut the new board's power as void. Disney cites the action as the "latest strike" in the state's string of "retaliatory" and "unconstitutional" actions.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The lawsuit also argues the state violated the contract clause in the U.S. Constitution by working to void an agreement Disney made with the previous board, which undercut the power of the new DeSantis-appointed district board. Lawyers for Disney also say the state violated the takings clause in the U.S. Constitution by allegedly taking property rights from the company "without payment of just compensation."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The fifth cause of action Disney makes in the lawsuit accuses the state of violating the due process clause of the 14th Amendment by arbitrating "the Contracts without any rational basis and for only impermissible reasons."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The board had cited violations of necessary procedures outlined in the state's sunshine laws as reason to declare the agreement as void.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Disney is seeking to have the two laws restructuring the former Reedy Creek Improvement District declared as "unlawful and unenforceable," along with legally upholding the agreement between Disney and the former district made on Feb. 8, which stripped the new district of most of its power.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The entertainment giant had maintained full autonomy over the district since its creation in 1967, but legislation signed into law in February gave the state power over the district.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://justthenews.com/politics-policy/nebraska-becomes-27th-state-pass-constitutional-carry"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://justthenews.com/politics-policy/nebraska-becomes-27th-state-pass-constitutional-carry</span></a></p>
<p><strong>Nebraska becomes 27th state to pass constitutional carry</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Nebraska Gov. Jim Pillen signed constitutional carry into law on Tuesday, making it the 27th state to add to the constitutional carry majority.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The law allows law-abiding Nebraskans who are 21 and up to be able to carry a concealed handgun without a permit.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">It will go into effect 90 days after the end of the legislative session, which is scheduled for June 9.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The bill is backed by the NRA.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">"Today, Nebraska joined 26 other states whose constituents and leaders recognize that law-abiding Americans should not have to ask for special government permission and pay additional fees in order to exercise their rights outside of the home,"&nbsp; Randy Kozuch, executive director of the NRA's legislative lobby arm told Fox News in a statement.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://www.dailyfetched.com/satanic-church-founder-sentenced-to-18-months-in-prison-for-operating-unlicensed-money-transmitting-business/"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.dailyfetched.com/satanic-church-founder-sentenced-to-18-months-in-prison-for-operating-unlicensed-money-transmitting-business/</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Satanic Church Founder Sentenced to 18 Months in Prison for Operating Unlicensed Money-Transmitting Business</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Self-described satanist Aria DiMezzo, 35, was also ordered to pay a fine of $5,000 and to forfeit more than $14,000 along with 1.93 bitcoins.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">According to investigators, between June 2020 and January 2021, DiMezzo charged a fee to exchange mostly U.S. dollars for Bitcoin, recruiting customers on websites.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Customers sent DiMezzo money through bank accounts to the Reformed Satanic Church.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">DiMezzo sold more than $3 million worth of virtual currency but did not register the operation as a money-transmitting business, failing to comply with mandatory regulations.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">According to investigators, DiMezzo failed to file currency transaction reports for exchanges of over $10,000 or suspicious activity reports for transactions over $2,000.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Prosecutors said DiMezzo worked with a man named Ian Freeman to sell virtual currency to customers, paying Freeman a percentage of the profits.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Freeman was found guilty of operating an unlicensed money-transmitting business, laundering over $10 million in proceeds of romance scams, and tax evasion.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">In 2020, Republicans in one New Hampshire county nominated DiMezzo for sheriff, whose campaign slogan disparaged the police.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">At the time, DiMezzo said, as law enforcement, any of his deputies &ldquo;would be fired on the spot, and perhaps charged with crimes, for any brutality or misconduct.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">DiMezzo serves as the high priest and founder of the Reformed Satanic Church.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The church doesn&rsquo;t believe Satan exists, DiMezzo claimed, but instead &ldquo;stands for individualism and voluntarism, and opposes the god of the day,&rdquo; which he described as the state.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://www.theblaze.com/news/let-s-go-lawsuit-students-sue-after-school-forces-them-to-remove-let-s-go-brandon-sweatshirts"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.theblaze.com/news/let-s-go-lawsuit-students-sue-after-school-forces-them-to-remove-let-s-go-brandon-sweatshirts</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>'Let's go, lawsuit':&nbsp; Students sue after school forces them to remove 'Let's Go Brandon' sweatshirts</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Two students are suing a Michigan school district for viewpoint discrimination after school employees forbade them wearing sweatshirts opposing President Biden, the students' legal team announced in a statement Tuesday.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">"These students should not only be allowed to express their political beliefs, but should be encouraged to do so," FIRE attorney Harrison Rosenthal said in the statement.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">"America&rsquo;s students must be free to exercise their constitutional rights, not just learn about them."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The case stems from multiple incidents in February 2022 and May 2022 at Tri County Middle School in Howard City, Michigan. School employees ordered two students to "remove 'Let's Go Brandon' sweatshirts despite allowing students to wear apparel with other political and social messages," the complaint alleges.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">FIRE attorneys representing the students say the incidents are "part of a pattern of political favoritism by the school district." They add that during a field day, an administrator ordered a student to stop wearing a Trump flag as a cape, but permitted students to wear gay pride flags in the same manner.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Though the phrase originated as a means for mimicking a "f*** Joe Biden" chant, the phrase "let's go Brandon" contains no profane language. Therefore, FIRE attorneys reason, the school's dress code barring profane clothing does not apply.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Howard City is in west central Michigan about 35 miles from Grand Rapids. It has a population of approximately 1,967.</span></p>]]></description>
   <author><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></author>
   <enclosure url="https://app.dropwave.io/episode/b0ae4f18-e5ad-48c5-8f38-9355608404b3/daily-news-brief-for-thursday-april-27th-2023.mp3" length="619" type="audio/mp3"/>
   <guid isPermaLink="false"><![CDATA[b0ae4f18-e5ad-48c5-8f38-9355608404b3]]></guid>
   <pubDate>Thu, 27 Apr 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
   <source url=""><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></source>
   <itunes:author><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></itunes:author>
   <itunes:image href="https://assets-cdn2.dropwave.io/2ab40ac0-e99d-4f25-a6d2-541d2c9b290a/cover-art/hUZu1H9lrRY0wXg66WHC8eLwYBA3hbRNTAHQmHt2.png"/>
   <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
   <itunes:duration>619</itunes:duration>
   <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
  
  </item>
 </channel>
</rss>
