<?xml version="1.0"?>
<?xml-stylesheet href="/storage/feed-stylesheet.xsl" type="text/xsl"?>

<rss xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
 <channel>
  <title>FLF - Daily News Brief</title>
  <link>https://dropwave.io</link>
  <description><![CDATA[FIGHT LAUGH FEAST PRESENTS SHOWS PROCLAIMING THE LORDSHIP OF CHRIST OVER ALL OF LIFE.
]]></description>
  <language>en</language>
  <managingEditor><![CDATA[fightlaughfeast@gmail.com (FLF, LLC)]]></managingEditor>
  <webMaster><![CDATA[support@dropwave.io (DropWave Support)]]></webMaster>
  <pubDate>Fri, 26 May 2023 01:25:45 +0000</pubDate>
  <lastBuildDate>Fri, 26 May 2023 01:25:45 +0000</lastBuildDate>
  <image>
   <url>https://is4-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Podcasts113/v4/58/56/52/5856525c-2973-cf29-3db9-21faa8595391/mza_1144696925612154085.png/1200x1200bb.jpg</url>
   <link>https://dropwave.io</link>
   <title><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></title>
  </image>
  <itunes:author><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></itunes:author>
  <itunes:image href="https://is4-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Podcasts113/v4/58/56/52/5856525c-2973-cf29-3db9-21faa8595391/mza_1144696925612154085.png/1200x1200bb.jpg"/>
  <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
  <itunes:owner>
   <itunes:name><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></itunes:name>
   <itunes:email>fightlaughfeast@gmail.com</itunes:email>
  </itunes:owner>
  <itunes:category text="News"/>
  <item>
   <title><![CDATA[Daily News Brief for Wednesday, May 24th, 2023 [Daily News Brief]]]></title>
   <link>https://app.dropwave.io/episode/3bff24f1-e7d1-4e75-9545-7e5687844fd5/daily-news-brief-for-wednesday-may-24th-2023.mp3</link>
   <description><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">This is Garrison Hardie with your CrossPolitic Daily News Brief for Wednesday, May 24th, 2023.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://www.zerohedge.com/covid-19/who-warns-unusual-surge-severe-myocarditis-babies"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.zerohedge.com/covid-19/who-warns-unusual-surge-severe-myocarditis-babies</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>WHO Warns Of 'Unusual' Surge in Severe Myocarditis in Babies</strong></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">On Tuesday, the WHO issued an alert that there had been a rise in &ldquo;severe myocarditis&rdquo; in newborns and infants between June 2022 and March 2023 in Wales and England.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">It said that this was associated with the enterovirus infection, which rarely affects the heart.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">A UK Health Security Agency (UKHSA) spokesperson confirmed to The Epoch Times that 10 babies have been diagnosed in Wales and five have been diagnosed in England.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The WHO said that &ldquo;although enterovirus infections are common in neonates and young infants, the reported increase in myocarditis with severe outcomes in neonates and infants associated with enterovirus infection is unusual.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">It said that in the same hospital (covering the South Wales region) over the previous six years, &ldquo;only one other similar case has been identified.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">WHO assessed the public health risk as low, but added that in certain situations, it &ldquo;may be advisable to close child-care facilities and schools to reduce the intensity of transmission.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">However, the WHO took down the alert on Wednesday. The Epoch Times understands that this could be because some of the numbers were not correct.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The WHO did not respond to The Epoch Times&rsquo; request for comment.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Dr. Shamez Ladhani, Consultant Paediatrician at UKHSA, told The Epoch Times by email that &ldquo;given a higher than average number of cases in Wales in the autumn/winter months in very young babies, UKHSA is investigating the situation in England to see if any similar cases have been observed here and whether there are any factors driving the increase in cases.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The UKHSA did not respond to questions about ruling out any links to the effects of the COVID-19 vaccine.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Public Health Wales at the start of May announced that it was investigating a cluster of severe enterovirus infections with myocarditis occurring in very young babies from the South Wales region.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The cases occurred from June 2022 with a peak in November 2022 involving babies under 28 days old.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Ten babies have developed myocarditis within this cluster. One baby remains in hospital, eight are being managed as outpatients, and one baby has died.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Consultant pathologist and HART member Dr. Clare Craig told The Epoch Times that there&rsquo;s &ldquo;a massive question about whether or not these babies or the mums are vaccinated.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">HART is an organisation that was set up to share concerns about policy and guidance recommendations relating to the COVID-19 pandemic.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/restoring-america/community-family/nebraska-governor-signs-ban-abortion-and-child-transitions"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/restoring-america/community-family/nebraska-governor-signs-ban-abortion-and-child-transitions</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>Nebraska governor signs ban on abortion and child transitions</strong></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Nebraska became the latest state to enact bans on abortion and child gender transitions as Gov. Jim Pillen (R-NE) signed a dual measure Monday afternoon.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Nebraska 's legislature passed the measure Friday, which will prohibit abortion at 12 weeks of pregnancy and ban genital and nongenital mutilation surgeries on children. The bill also gives the state's chief medical officer, Dr. Timothy Tesmer, the authority to determine restrictions on puberty blockers and cross-sex hormones.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Pillen called child gender transitions "Lucifer at its finest" at the signing ceremony.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">"All children deserve a chance to grow and live happy, fruitful lives," Pillen said in a press release before the signing. "This includes pre-born boys and girls, and it includes children struggling with their gender identity. These kids deserve the opportunity to grow and explore who they are and want to be, and they can do so without making irreversible decisions that should be made when they are fully grown."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">While the abortion ban goes into effect immediately upon Pillen's signature, the ban on transgender procedures will go into effect on Oct. 1.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The abortion ban includes exceptions for rape, incest, and instances in which the life of the mother is at risk. Eighty-six percent of abortions in Nebraska occur before 12 weeks, according to state statistics.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Primary sponsor state Sen. Joni Albrecht, fighting through tears, said, "I look forward to the day when every child is protected from elective abortions in our state."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Nebraska joins a growing list of states that have passed abortion restrictions since the overturn of Roe v. Wade. Twenty-seven states have attempted to pass such laws, but some states have been either held up by courts or hindered by a divided government.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Last week, North Carolina and South Carolina took action to restrict abortion.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">From Nebraska to Texas we go&hellip;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://townhall.com/tipsheet/madelineleesman/2023/05/23/texas-bans-diversity-offices-at-colleges-n2623589"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://townhall.com/tipsheet/madelineleesman/2023/05/23/texas-bans-diversity-offices-at-colleges-n2623589</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>Texas Moves a Step Closer to Banning Diversity Programs in Higher Education</strong></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">On Monday, Texas lawmakers passed a bill to end Diversity, Equity and Inclusion (DEI) programs at state colleges and universities. If the bill were to become law, it would be the second state in the nation with such legislation, following Florida.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">According to The Hill, the measure requires the governors of each state university to ensure that there is no DEI office at the school and that preferential treatment is not given for &ldquo;diversity hires.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Rep. John Kuempel, a Republican, said that &ldquo;DEI is present in some form in almost every Texas campus&rdquo; and that schools &ldquo;must recruit the best people in every field regardless of race and gender,&rdquo; according to the Dallas Morning News. The Texas House voted 83-60 in support of S.B. 17. The legislation heads back to the Senate, where it will decide to accept or deny changes made by members of the House.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Last month, when the Senate passed its version of the bill, Lt. Gov. Dan Patrick described the legislation as the &ldquo;strongest pushback on woke policies in higher education.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">&ldquo;For far too long, academia has been poisoned by woke policies and faculty seeking to indoctrinate our students. Professors did not believe we would push back on their advances, but they were wrong. Students should be taught how to think critically, not what to think," Patrick said in a statement.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://freebeacon.com/energy/majority-of-united-states-faces-elevated-risk-of-summer-power-blackouts-amid-green-energy-push/"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://freebeacon.com/energy/majority-of-united-states-faces-elevated-risk-of-summer-power-blackouts-amid-green-energy-push/</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>Majority of United States Faces 'Elevated Risk' of Summer Power Blackouts Amid Green Energy Push</strong></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">America's increased reliance on green energy in favor of coal and gas has a majority of the United States facing an "elevated risk" of summer power blackouts, according to a leading grid reliability watchdog.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The North American Electric Reliability Corporation (NERC) last week published its 2023 summer reliability assessment, which found that two-thirds of North America could face power shortages this summer during periods of extreme heat. That vulnerability, the watchdog group said, stems from America's increase in green power generation and decrease in fossil fuel power plants. While coal and natural gas plants can be turned on and off at the flip of a switch, green alternatives such as wind and solar rely on favorable weather conditions to operate at full capacity. If those conditions aren't met, power demand can outpace supply.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">"The system is closer to the edge," NERC director of reliability assessment and performance analysis John Moura said last week. "More needs to be done."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Moura is far from the only expert sounding the alarm on America's unreliable power grid. Both state and federal officials in recent weeks have warned that high summer temperatures, combined with low nightly winds, could bring power blackouts across the country. "I'm afraid to say it, but I think the United States is heading towards a catastrophic situation," Federal Energy Regulatory Commission member Mark Christie said during a May Senate hearing.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Despite those warnings, President Joe Biden has moved forward with plans to accelerate U.S. coal plant retirements. With nearly half of America's coal power already set to disappear by 2030, Biden's Environmental Protection Agency earlier this month unveiled new standards that force coal and gas power plants to slash their carbon emissions by a whopping 90 percent between 2035 and 2040. In order to meet the near-impossible standards, those plants will have to spend big on infrastructure upgrades&mdash;costs that may prompt the plants to shut down rather than comply.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">"Coal is more than five times as dependable as wind and more than twice as dependable as solar when electricity demand is greatest," America's Power CEO Michelle Bloodworth said in a statement, "yet bad public policy and EPA regulations are forcing the closure of coal plants."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">In addition to his far-reaching fossil fuel regulations, Biden has spent hundreds of billions of dollars on tax breaks and subsidies aimed at increasing electric car use. And in April, Biden's Environmental Protection Agency announced a new rule that imposes strict tailpipe emission limits on vehicles sold&mdash;so strict that it effectively forces automakers to ensure that two-thirds of the cars they sell are electric by 2032.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Those moves could also put strain on the nation's power grid. As more Americans plug in their cars instead of filling them up with gasoline, grids across the country will need to put out more power to keep up. The issue has already plagued some U.S. states&mdash;in September, for example, California urged electric car drivers to stop charging their vehicles due to power grid strain. Still, the ordeal did not stop state officials from moving full steam ahead with plans to outlaw gas-powered vehicles and eradicate fossil fuel power plants.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/news/house/mccarthy-warns-nowhere-near-deal-on-debt-ceiling"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/news/house/mccarthy-warns-nowhere-near-deal-on-debt-ceiling</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>McCarthy warns White House and GOP &lsquo;nowhere near a deal&rsquo; on debt ceiling</strong></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">House Speaker Kevin McCarthy (R-CA) warned Republican lawmakers that his team is &ldquo;nowhere near a deal&rdquo; with the White House on the debt ceiling, ramping up pressure on President Joe Biden just nine days before the default deadline.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">In a closed-door meeting with GOP lawmakers on Tuesday, McCarthy told members a compromise on the debt ceiling was still far off, reiterating his position that he would not increase spending or raise the debt ceiling without conditions. Republicans emerged from the meeting wary of negotiators&rsquo; progress, telling reporters the talks are not going well so far.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">As part of the negotiations, the White House proposed late last week to limit next year&rsquo;s spending to 2023 levels &mdash; an idea that was rejected by Republicans, who wish to return to 2022 levels. McHenry and Rep. Garret Graves (R-LA), the top negotiators for McCarthy, emphasized that stance on Tuesday by calling on the White House to agree to cut spending.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Meanwhile, some Republicans remain skeptical of Treasury Secretary Janet Yellen&rsquo;s warnings that the country could default on its payments as soon as June 1, calling that date a manufactured deadline set by the Biden administration to accelerate a deal.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Gaetz argued the United States is not at risk of missing its payments, noting the country has strong revenue that will continue coming in over the next few weeks. Instead, the Florida Republican said Yellen should appear before Congress to present &ldquo;receipts and deposits&rdquo; that prove the country is on track to default.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">McCarthy&rsquo;s warning comes after the speaker met with Biden on Monday evening, marking the third meeting the two have held since restarting negotiations earlier this month. McCarthy called the meeting &ldquo;productive&rdquo; but noted the two are still far apart on finalizing a deal.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Now for the rundown&hellip;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://thepostmillennial.com/breaking-suspect-in-custody-after-allegedly-crashing-u-haul-truck-into-barriers-near-white-house?utm_campaign=64487"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://thepostmillennial.com/breaking-suspect-in-custody-after-allegedly-crashing-u-haul-truck-into-barriers-near-white-house?utm_campaign=64487</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">On Monday night, the driver of a U-Haul truck was taken into custody after allegedly slamming into security barriers near the White House. According to Secret Service spokesperson Anthony Guglielmi, the truck crashed on the northern side of Lafayette Square at around 10 pm.</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Guglielmi said in a statement, "Shortly before 10:00 p.m. Monday, Secret Service Uniformed Division officers detained the driver of a box truck after the vehicle collided with security barriers on the north side of Lafayette Square at 16th Street."</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">He added that there were no injuries to any Secret Service or White House personnel and that the crash is under investigation but that the preliminary investigation reveals the driver may have intentionally crashed into the barriers.</span></li>
</ul>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://thepostmillennial.com/uc-berkeley-holds-segregated-graduation-ceremony-for-black-students-only?utm_campaign=64487"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://thepostmillennial.com/uc-berkeley-holds-segregated-graduation-ceremony-for-black-students-only?utm_campaign=64487</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The University of California Berkeley hosted a black-only graduation ceremony for its non-white students at Zellerbach Hall on Saturday. In March, UC Berkeley&rsquo;s African American Studies Department announced they would be holding their annual &ldquo;Black Graduation&rdquo; ceremony for students in May.</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">According to the announcement, &ldquo;The Department of African American Studies plans on hosting our annual Black Graduation ceremony, which is open to all majors and degree programs across the campus."</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://twitter.com/i/status/1660362211636969473"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://twitter.com/i/status/1660362211636969473</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> - Play Video&nbsp;</span></span></li>
</ul>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://redstate.com/mike_miller/2023/05/22/super-woke-target-partners-on-its-new-gay-pride-line-with-designer-who-insists-satan-loves-you-n749804"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://redstate.com/mike_miller/2023/05/22/super-woke-target-partners-on-its-new-gay-pride-line-with-designer-who-insists-satan-loves-you-n749804</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">So let&rsquo;s check them off. By &ldquo;them,&rdquo; I mean just the latest corporations to put their &ldquo;woke&rdquo; beliefs ahead of customer loyalty, profits, and shareholders: Disney, Nike, Bud Light, BlackRock, Ford, and Miller Lite. The complete list is long &mdash; and it just got longer with the addition of the super-woke Target Corporation.</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Target has partnered with UK-based Satanist designer Abprallen on its new &ldquo;Pride&rdquo; collection, which features a &ldquo;Cure Transphobia&rdquo; sweatshirt, which bears the message &ldquo;Cure transphobia, not trans people,&rdquo; and other related items. Did I mention that Abprallen insists &ldquo;Satan loves you,&rdquo; &ldquo;Satan respects pronouns,&rdquo; and other uplifting [sarc] trash for your shopping pleasure? As reported by Breitbart, Abprallen mixes its affinity for satanism with its pro-LGBT activism, boasting on its Instagram page: &ldquo;Satan loves you and respects who you are; you&rsquo;re important and valuable in this world and you deserve to treat yourself with love and respect.&rdquo;</span></li>
</ul>]]></description>
   <author><![CDATA[Garrison Hardie]]></author>
   <enclosure url="https://app.dropwave.io/episode/3bff24f1-e7d1-4e75-9545-7e5687844fd5/daily-news-brief-for-wednesday-may-24th-2023.mp3" length="890" type="audio/mp3"/>
   <guid isPermaLink="false"><![CDATA[3bff24f1-e7d1-4e75-9545-7e5687844fd5]]></guid>
   <pubDate>Wed, 24 May 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
   <source url=""><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></source>
   <itunes:author><![CDATA[Garrison Hardie]]></itunes:author>
   <itunes:image href="https://assets-cdn2.dropwave.io/2ab40ac0-e99d-4f25-a6d2-541d2c9b290a/cover-art/hUZu1H9lrRY0wXg66WHC8eLwYBA3hbRNTAHQmHt2.png"/>
   <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
   <itunes:duration>890</itunes:duration>
   <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
  
  </item><item>
   <title><![CDATA[Daily News Brief for Tuesday, May 23rd, 2023 [Daily News Brief]]]></title>
   <link>https://app.dropwave.io/episode/bc3a25a3-61d5-4dad-9435-49fcc84f03dc/daily-news-brief-for-tuesday-may-23rd-2023.mp3</link>
   <description><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">This is Garrison Hardie with your CrossPolitic Daily News Brief for Tuesday, May 23rd, 2023.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>Concordis Education Partners:</strong></span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Classical Christian education has reminded us to aim education at truth, but the trivium has been used as a formula rather than a way of training students in discernment.&nbsp;&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">To teach well, you must coach.&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">&nbsp;</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Concordis Foundation is offering their third annual BOOT CAMP &ndash; a faculty summit &ndash; July 11-13th in Moscow, Idaho.&nbsp; This is a three-day intensive teaching training where you learn to coach students, using the trivium, so that you can meet students at all learning levels.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">&nbsp;</span></p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Learn more at</span><a href="https://concordispartners.com/"><span style="font-weight: 400;"> </span><span style="font-weight: 400;">concordispartners.com</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;">&nbsp;&nbsp;</span></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://www.westernjournal.com/two-women-told-broken-law-criticizing-male-attempting-breastfeed-child-report/"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.westernjournal.com/two-women-told-broken-law-criticizing-male-attempting-breastfeed-child-report/</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>Two Women Are Told They've Broken the Law by Criticizing Male Attempting to Breastfeed a Child: Report</strong></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Two Australian women were reportedly given notices informing them that they committed a crime by criticizing a male, who identifies as a woman, that was trying to breastfeed a baby.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The news was first reported by the &ldquo;Pro-Woman, Pro-Child Safeguarding, Anti-Bullsh*t,&rdquo; media outlet Reduxx.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">According to the outlet, Twitter contacted the two women &mdash; Jasmine Sussex and Leah Whiston &mdash; on May 16, notifying them that they had violated Australian law in several of their tweets.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The platform told the two that a &ldquo;government entity or law enforcement agency&rdquo; had informed them of their alleged crime, and that the platform had been forced to hide the content from Australian users.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The posts in question had been critical of Jennifer Buckley, a female-identified male.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Buckley had previously announced online that, after two years of transitioning, he had induced lactation and had begun breastfeeding his newborn son, who his wife had given birth to.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Sussex was heavily critical of this, telling the U.K.&rsquo;s Daily Mail that &ldquo;men shouldn&rsquo;t breastfeed because breastfeeding [is] for the baby,&rdquo; and that &ldquo;there is no evidence that any male-induced milk is equivalent to mother&rsquo;s milk.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">&ldquo;We have no idea if the substance is even milk. It&rsquo;s absolutely a human experiment on babies,&rdquo; she told the outlet.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">As a volunteer breastfeeding counselor, Sussex was reportedly fired from her job in 2021 for failing to comply with the adoption of &ldquo;gender neutral&rdquo; language in breastfeeding care &mdash; a claim which the ABA denied to the Daily Mail.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">A year after, she was removed from the Australian Breastfeeding Association (ABA), Reduxx reported.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">&ldquo;I was sacked for. &hellip; &lsquo;Engaging in Sectarian Controversy&rsquo; in breach of the ABA constitution,&rdquo; she told Reduxx. &ldquo;In other words, continuing to talk about the dangers of gender identity ideology for mothers and babies, including how men were forcing their way into the breastfeeding relationship by attempting to induce lactation.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Whiston, meanwhile, is the representative for the Standing for Women Queensland (SFWQ) page.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">She had posted a Twitter thread on the page, revealing that an LGBT lobby group had allegedly given the ABA $20,000 for them to create an educational booklet about &ldquo;chest feeding.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://www.dailysignal.com/2023/05/22/exclusive-leaked-policy-exposes-fox-news-stances-on-woke-ideology/?fbclid=IwAR36KJiUko85jY6nRrQSX4DH2XOZAwUdyaTl-iEhQIfZe9w-ZPnsTY3cAnA"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.dailysignal.com/2023/05/22/exclusive-leaked-policy-exposes-fox-news-stances-on-woke-ideology/?fbclid=IwAR36KJiUko85jY6nRrQSX4DH2XOZAwUdyaTl-iEhQIfZe9w-ZPnsTY3cAnA</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>Leaked Policy Exposes Fox News Stances on Woke Ideology</strong></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Fox News employees are allowed to use bathrooms that align with their gender identity, rather than their biological sex, and permitted to dress in alignment with their preferred gender. They must also be addressed by their preferred name and pronouns in the workplace.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">These are just a few of the policies outlined in the company handbook, dated January 2021, a copy of which was shared with The Daily Signal. Fox also offers to help employees come up with a &ldquo;Workplace Transition Plan&rdquo; to ease their gender transition at work.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The revelations comes amid conservative consternation at Fox Digital&rsquo;s use of activist language like &ldquo;gender affirming care&rdquo; in stories on its website, as well as the site&rsquo;s consistent use of female pronouns for biological males like TikTok celebrity Dylan Mulvaney and swimmer Lia Thomas (formerly known as Will Thomas).</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Fox also drew strong backlash for a June 2022 on-air segment praising a child&rsquo;s gender transition as an &ldquo;inspiration to others.&rdquo; That segment briefly depicted California state Sen. Scott Weiner, a far-left Democrat who led the move to soften sex offender registry requirements for sodomy with minors, and highlighted the activist claim that a child might commit suicide if he or she is not permitted to transition.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Carlson&rsquo;s show was canceled April 24, days after he delivered a viral speech at The Heritage Foundation&rsquo;s 50th anniversary gala. Fox News Media has not given a reason, simply stating that the two parties &ldquo;agreed to part ways.&rdquo;&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">A source who still works at Fox News told The Daily Signal that after Carlson&rsquo;s show was canceled in April, producers for the new 8 p.m. &ldquo;Fox News Tonight&rdquo; program were told not to bash Mulvaney. That directive came from high-level executives, the source said.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Fox News did not respond to The Daily Signal&rsquo;s multiple requests for comment.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Under the category &ldquo;Gender Transition,&rdquo; Fox&rsquo;s employee handbook promises that the company is dedicated to &ldquo;expanding and strengthening&rdquo; efforts to &ldquo;sustain a more inclusive work environment.&rdquo; The Fox employee handbook is posted on Workday, where employees can see company guidelines or policies, a former employee told The Daily Signal.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">&ldquo;Employees who are transitioning their gender have the right to be open about their transition if they so choose, and to work in an environment free of harassment, discrimination, or retaliation, and without fear of consequences or transphobia for living openly,&rdquo; the policy says.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Citing the Human Rights Campaign, one of the most prominent LGBTQ organization in the country, the Fox handbook defines a slew of LGBTQ terms, including cisgender, gender expression, gender-fluid, gender identity, gender non-conforming, gender transition, LGBTQ, non-binary, and transgender.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">For the past several years, Fox received a perfect score on the Human Rights Campaign&rsquo;s Corporate Equality Index, &ldquo;the nation&rsquo;s foremost benchmarking survey and report measuring corporate policies and practices related to LGBTQ+ workplace equality.&rdquo; A former Fox News employee told The Daily Signal that the company frequently mentions this perfect score in employee training materials.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">&ldquo;Fox News devotes hours of programming to attacking &lsquo;woke companies,&rsquo; but ironically Fox is as woke as the rest of them,&rdquo; another former Fox News employee told The Daily Signal, emphasizing that Fox viewers would be &ldquo;astonished to find out what the company is like.&rdquo;&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Fox&rsquo;s policies appear to be aligned with the legal requirements in New York City, where the company is headquartered, as well as California, where a large number of its employees work.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The handbook explicitly states that any employee &ldquo;may access the restroom corresponding to their gender identity.&rdquo;&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">&ldquo;If a transitioning employee expresses a desire for increased privacy they will be provided access to a single occupancy restroom where available,&rdquo; the handbook says. &ldquo;However, no employee shall be required to use a single occupancy restroom if they do not wish to do so.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">When trans-identifying TikTok star Mulvaney was first gaining prominence last year, producers for &ldquo;Tucker Carlson Tonight&rdquo; had to fight to be able to refer to Mulvaney with male pronouns in the show&rsquo;s chyrons, the former &ldquo;Tucker Carlson Tonight&rdquo; producer told The Daily Signal.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Carlson&rsquo;s team also fought to be able to host The Daily Wire&rsquo;s Matt Walsh on trans issues, the producer said, but the team was repeatedly met with resistance from Fox on this due to Walsh&rsquo;s frank condemnation of transgender ideology. This may have also been due in part to Fox&rsquo;s view of The Daily Wire as a competitor, the former producer suggested.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://www.based-politics.com/2023/05/22/this-public-college-is-giving-out-paid-internships-that-openly-exclude-white-people/"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.based-politics.com/2023/05/22/this-public-college-is-giving-out-paid-internships-that-openly-exclude-white-people/</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>This public college is giving out paid internships that openly exclude white people</strong></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Martin Luther King Jr. famously dreamed of a day when Americans would be judged not by the color of their skin but by the content of their character. Well, keep dreaming, MLK, because segregation and open race discrimination are making a comeback&mdash;this time, in progressive bastions like our higher education system and in the name of &ldquo;Diversity, Equity, and Inclusion.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The University of Minnesota just got hit with a federal civil rights complaint because it&rsquo;s openly conditioning a paid internship program on the basis of race. Their &ldquo;Multicultural Summer Research Opportunities Program&rdquo; is &ldquo;an intensive 10 week summer program in which undergraduate students of color work full-time with a faculty mentor on a research project.&rdquo; It aims to help in &ldquo;preparing students for graduate school and developing research skills,&rdquo; and pays students a $6,000 stipend. A condition of the program is that it is only open to students who &ldquo;identify&rdquo; as &ldquo;a student of color or Native American.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">This program&rsquo;s legality is being challenged by the Legal Insurrection Foundation&rsquo;s Equal Protection Project (EPP), which &ldquo;seeks to ensure equal protection under the law and non-discrimination by the government&rdquo; and &ldquo;opposes racial discrimination in any form.&rdquo; They just filed a complaint with the&nbsp; Office of Civil Rights of the U.S. Department of Education arguing that this internship program violates the Civil Rights Act and the Equal Protection clause of the Constitution.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">&ldquo;The U. Minnesota segregated summer program is inexcusable, and it&rsquo;s shocking that a major university would so openly make educational opportunities open only to students of a certain skin color,&rdquo; EPP President Bill told Fox News Digital. &ldquo;There is no good form of racial discrimination. Depriving white students of educational opportunities does not promote racial or any other form of justice.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://www.breitbart.com/politics/2023/05/21/census-new-york-city-loses-nearly-half-a-million-residents-in-two-years/"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.breitbart.com/politics/2023/05/21/census-new-york-city-loses-nearly-half-a-million-residents-in-two-years/</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>New York City Loses Nearly Half a Million Residents in Two Years</strong></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">New York City has lost nearly half a million residents over the course of just two years, newly released United States Census Bureau data reveals.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The Census Bureau data, which shows population estimates for mid-2022, finds that fewer than 8.4 million residents remain living in New York City &mdash; still making the Big Apple the nation&rsquo;s most populous city by several million.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">In April 2020, the very start of the Chinese coronavirus pandemic, more than 8.8 million residents lived in New York City. This figure indicates a population loss of more than five percent from April 2020 to July 2022 with almost half a million residents leaving the city.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Americans moving out of deep blue cities is widespread, the Census Bureau data shows.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The second largest city, Los Angeles, California, and the third largest city, Chicago, Illinois, also lost residents over the course of two years. In Los Angeles, for instance, about 3.8 million residents remain in the city as of July 2022 compared to about 3.9 million residents in April 2020, a loss of about 100,000 residents.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Similarly, Chicago had about 2.67 million residents as of July 2022 but in April 2020, the city had about three percent more residents. Over the two years, about 85,000 residents left Chicago.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">And now for the rundown&hellip;&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://andmagazine.substack.com/p/china-is-building-killer-robots-using"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://andmagazine.substack.com/p/china-is-building-killer-robots-using</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Many of us have seen The Terminator, a 1984 film starring Arnold Schwarzenegger. It depicts an almost unstoppable robot sent back in time from 2029 to 1984. Its mission was to kill a woman whose unborn son will save humanity from Skynet, a 2029 artificial intelligence system that had become self-aware and then decided to destroy all of mankind because humans were interfering in their plans and programs.</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The Chinese Communist Party, the CCP, is now creating their version of the Terminator -- an army of battlefield killer robots that will not be managed by humans in any way and, instead, will be controlled by an artificial intelligence (AI) system. The Chinese plan for building such lethal autonomous robots was revealed by Zeng Yi, an executive in a Chinese government-owned company named Norinco. He said, &ldquo;In future battlegrounds, there will be no people fighting,&rdquo; adding that autonomous AI platforms are &ldquo;inevitable.&rdquo;</span></li>
</ul>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/news/washington-secrets/explosion-of-ap-climate-change-stories-following-8m-enviro-grant"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/news/washington-secrets/explosion-of-ap-climate-change-stories-following-8m-enviro-grant</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">In the year following a grant of more than $8 million to the Associated Press from key climate change advocates, the news service has poured out at least 64 stories warning of environmental calamity, according to a new media study.Media Research Center Business charted the stories and language used following the multimillion-dollar grant and found that AP also used over 500 environmental extremism buzzwords in the stories.</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The media giant, which feeds news outlets worldwide, received grants totaling $8 million from the William and Flora Hewlett Foundation, the Howard Hughes Medical Institute, Quadrivium, the Rockefeller Foundation, and the Walton Family Foundation in February 2022. AP said it would hire 20 new environmental writers with the money to create a climate swat team to &ldquo;enhance the global understanding of climate change and its impact across the world.&rdquo;</span></li>
</ul>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://www.outkick.com/trans-high-school-track-runner-robs-female-athlete-of-state-championship-bid/"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.outkick.com/trans-high-school-track-runner-robs-female-athlete-of-state-championship-bid/</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Another day, another biological male taking opportunities from deserving females.Athena Ryan took second place Saturday in the high school women&rsquo;s 1600 meter race at the North Coast Meet of Champions in California. The top three athletes advance to the CIF State Track &amp; Field Championships next week. So the fourth-place finisher, Adeline Johnson, missed her chance to compete in State by just one spot. A spot taken by a boy.</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Ryan, a junior at Sonoma Academy, competed on the men&rsquo;s team in 2021. But he&rsquo;s been running in women&rsquo;s events for the past two seasons. In Saturday&rsquo;s meet, he clocked a season-record 4:55:91 in the 1600m finals. He would have finished last in the male category. The slowest male time in the preliminaries was 4:46:54. The slowest male time in the finals was 4:35:12.</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">A group of advocates held a banner at the event that simply read, &ldquo;Protect Female Sports.&rdquo; They were eventually asked to leave and then escorted off the premises. But not before they had an interesting exchange with an angry passerby.</span></li>
</ul>
<p><br /><br /></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">How about we end with some cool news&hellip;</span></p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://www.dailyfetched.com/soldier-who-lost-both-legs-in-afghanistan-does-the-unimaginable-and-climbs-everest-anything-is-possible/"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.dailyfetched.com/soldier-who-lost-both-legs-in-afghanistan-does-the-unimaginable-and-climbs-everest-anything-is-possible/</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">British army soldier Gurkha veteran Hari Budha Magar, who lost both his legs while serving in Afghanistan, has successfully climbed to the top of the world&rsquo;s tallest mountain, Mount Everest.</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Magar, a father of three, served as a corporal in the Gurkha regiment in the British Army. After Magar lost his legs to an improvised explosive device in 2010, he thought his life was &ldquo;completely finished.&rdquo;</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The veteran, who now lives in Canterbury, England, battled depression and alcoholism following the explosion.</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">But Magar persevered. The veteran helped strike down a ban on both double amputees and blind people climbing Everest, ensuring he would have a chance at overcoming both nature and his injuries. According to the BBC, Magar hoped to &ldquo;inspire others&rdquo; and &ldquo;change perceptions on disability&rdquo; and set off with a team of Nepalese climbers to combat Everest. He&rdquo; set off on May 6 with a team of Nepalese climbers led by Krish Thapa, a fellow Gurkha veteran and British special forces mountain troop leader. Magar announced he &ldquo;stood victorious&rdquo; atop Everest around 3 p.m. on May 19, noting, &ldquo;Disability is no barrier to reaching the 8,849-metre peak.&rdquo;</span></li>
</ul>]]></description>
   <author><![CDATA[Garrison Hardie]]></author>
   <enclosure url="https://app.dropwave.io/episode/bc3a25a3-61d5-4dad-9435-49fcc84f03dc/daily-news-brief-for-tuesday-may-23rd-2023.mp3" length="937" type="audio/mp3"/>
   <guid isPermaLink="false"><![CDATA[bc3a25a3-61d5-4dad-9435-49fcc84f03dc]]></guid>
   <pubDate>Tue, 23 May 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
   <source url=""><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></source>
   <itunes:author><![CDATA[Garrison Hardie]]></itunes:author>
   <itunes:image href="https://assets-cdn2.dropwave.io/2ab40ac0-e99d-4f25-a6d2-541d2c9b290a/cover-art/hUZu1H9lrRY0wXg66WHC8eLwYBA3hbRNTAHQmHt2.png"/>
   <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
   <itunes:duration>937</itunes:duration>
   <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
  
  </item><item>
   <title><![CDATA[Daily News Brief for Friday, May 19th, 2023 [Daily News Brief]]]></title>
   <link>https://app.dropwave.io/episode/5a4c60b3-4f2f-47eb-9fb1-ef16be82746f/daily-news-brief-for-friday-may-19th-2023.mp3</link>
   <description><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">This is Garrison Hardie with your CrossPolitic Daily News Brief for Friday, May 19th, 2023.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>Concordis Education Partners:</strong></span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Classical Christian education has reminded us to aim education at truth, but the trivium has been used as a formula rather than a way of training students in discernment.&nbsp;&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">To teach well, you must coach.&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">&nbsp;</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Concordis Foundation is offering their third annual BOOT CAMP &ndash; a faculty summit &ndash; July 11-13th in Moscow, Idaho.&nbsp; This is a three-day intensive teaching training where you learn to coach students, using the trivium, so that you can meet students at all learning levels.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">&nbsp;</span></p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Learn more at</span><a href="https://concordispartners.com/"><span style="font-weight: 400;"> </span><span style="font-weight: 400;">concordispartners.com</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;">&nbsp;&nbsp;</span></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://hotair.com/john-s-2/2023/05/17/bryan-kohberger-indicted-by-grand-jury-in-killing-of-college-students-n551466"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://hotair.com/john-s-2/2023/05/17/bryan-kohberger-indicted-by-grand-jury-in-killing-of-college-students-n551466</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>Bryan Kohberger indicted by grand jury in killing of college students</strong></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">In order to continue to hold Kohberger prosecutors had two choices. They could go through a preliminary hearing where lawyers for both sides would spell out some of the evidence in the case or they could bring and indictment through a grand jury. Kohberger had been scheduled for a preliminary hearing in June but it appears prosecutors decided to take the other path and make the case to a grand jury in secret.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The prosecutors&rsquo; decision to impanel a grand jury, however, was not anticipated and allows the state to avoid the week-long preliminary hearing that would have required it to present evidence before a judge as well as permit the defense counsel to cross-examine witnesses.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Since January, lawyers, police and other officials have refrained from making statements after Latah County Magistrate Judge Megan Marshall issued a gag order, which is being challenged by a coalition of news organizations&hellip;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Kohberger has yet to enter a plea, but is expected to do so at an arraignment Monday.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Kohberger will plead not guilty. He&rsquo;s potentially facing the death penalty and, possibly because he was a grad student studying criminology, may believe he can beat the system. However, there seems to be significant evidence linking him to the murders. The knife used in the murders has never been found but a sheath for what authorities believe was the murder weapon was left behind at the crime scene.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">&ldquo;The sheath was later processed and had &lsquo;Ka-Bar&rsquo; &lsquo;USMC&rsquo; and the United States Marine Corps eagle globe and anchor insignia stamped on the outside of it,&rdquo; Payne wrote. &ldquo;The Idaho state lab later located a single source of male DNA (suspect Profile) left on the button snap of the knife sheath.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">While police were investigation, Kohberger was driving home to Pennsylvania for winter break. Police got a DNA sample from the trash of the family home.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">On Dec. 27, police collected garbage from outside the Kohberger home.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The evidence was sent to the Idaho State Lab for testing and a DNA profile was compared with DNA discovered on the knife sheath.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">According to the affidavit, the DNA retrieved from the trash indicated a high probability it is from the biological father of the person who left DNA on the knife sheath at the crime scene in Moscow.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The other major evidence in the case is the cell phone data. It shows that Kohberger had been in the vicinity of the house where the murders took place at least 12 times in the months before the attack. It also showed that on the night of the killing, Kohberger left his home in Washington after midnight headed toward Idaho. Then his phone was switched off during the time of the killings. Then it was switched back on after the killings and showed him driving back from Idaho to Washington. And he made one more trip.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">A few hours later, after 9 a.m. on Nov. 13, Kohberger traveled from Pullman to an area close to the crime scene and quickly returned home.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">On top of all of that, one of the roommates saw the suspect leaving the house the night of the murders.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">D.M. stated she opened her door for the third time after she heard the crying and saw a figure clad in black clothing and a mask that covered the person&rsquo;s mouth and nose walking towards her. D.M. described the figure as 5&prime; 10&Prime; or taller, male, not very muscular, but athletically built with bushy eyebrows. The male walked past D.M. as she stood in a &ldquo;frozen shock phase.&rdquo; The male walked towards the back sliding glass door. D.M. locked herself in her room after seeing the male. D.M. did not state that she recognized the male. This leads investigators to believe that the murderer left the scene.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">What the case is lacking, at least so far, is any clear motive. It&rsquo;s still not clear whether Kohberger knew any of the victims or why though we do know that investigators have requested the social media information on the three female victims.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Search warrants recently executed by Idaho authorities demanded TikTok and Google hand over the user history dating back to January 2021 of three of the four victims: Madison Mogen, 21, Kaylee Goncalves, 21, and Xana Kernodle, 20&hellip;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Retired FBI agent Jennifer Coffindaffer said the warrants suggest police could be searching for a connection between Kohberger, 28, and his alleged victims that far pre-dates the murders.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">We&rsquo;ll have to wait and see what those searches turned up. If Kohberger is arraigned Monday the judge will likely set his trial date at that time.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://www.dailywire.com/news/ex-biden-nuclear-official-sam-brinton-arrested-as-fugitive-from-justice"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.dailywire.com/news/ex-biden-nuclear-official-sam-brinton-arrested-as-fugitive-from-justice</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>Ex-Biden Nuclear Official Sam Brinton Arrested As &lsquo;Fugitive From Justice&rsquo;</strong></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Sam Brinton, the &ldquo;nonbinary&rdquo; activist tapped by Joe Biden for a key nuclear role before he was fired for repeatedly stealing women&rsquo;s clothes, was arrested Wednesday night as a &ldquo;fugitive from justice,&rdquo; The Daily Wire has learned.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Montgomery County, Maryland, police arrested him at his home on Wednesday, police logs show. He is currently in jail and being held without bond.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">A neighbor told The Daily Wire that &ldquo;four unmarked police showed up last night, they would not let his spouse Kevin leave. After about an hour Sam Brinton was escorted out in handcuffs.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Brinton is set to appear for a hearing before Judge Victor Del Pino on Thursday afternoon.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">This is a breaking news story and will be updated.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://www.theblaze.com/news/radical-us-rep-cori-bush-proposes-14-trillion-in-federal-reparations"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.theblaze.com/news/radical-us-rep-cori-bush-proposes-14-trillion-in-federal-reparations</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>Radical US Rep. Cori Bush proposes $14 trillion in federal reparations, says America has 'moral and legal obligation' to pay up 'for the enslavement of Africans</strong></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Far-left U.S. Rep. Cori Bush proposed $14 trillion in federal reparations Wednesday, saying America has a "moral and legal obligation" to pay up "for the enslavement of Africans."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">National Public Radio characterized the Missouri Democrat's push as an "effort to see the federal government atone for the practice of chattel slavery and hundreds of years of racist policies that followed."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://twitter.com/i/status/1659175389887864832"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://twitter.com/i/status/1659175389887864832</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> - Play Video&nbsp;</span></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">She added that "America must provide reparations if we desire a prosperous future for all," the outlet added.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">"We know that we continue to live under slavery's vestiges. We know how slavery has perpetuated Jim Crow. We know how slavery's impacts live on today," Bush added, according to NPR, which also said she cited the racial wealth gap, voter suppression, infant mortality rates, and other negative health outcomes for black people.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">More from NPR:</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">About three-quarters or more of white adults oppose reparations, and so do a majority of Latinos and Asian Americans.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Black Americans overwhelmingly support the proposal, and young people in general are more likely to support cash payments to the descendants of enslaved people than their older counterparts.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">But more than 90 percent of Republicans say they oppose it, while Democrats are split nearly 50/50 on whether descendants should receive compensation.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Bush has been hard at work of late pushing leftist perspectives and policies:</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">She and U.S. Rep. Rashida Tlaib (D-Mich.) were the only two lawmakers who voted against a resolution Monday to honor law enforcement; this week is "Police Week."</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Last month Bush suggested in a tweet that Republicans run on a platform that includes "white supremacy" and "gun violence."</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">In January, she angrily lashed out at black Republican Rep. Byron Donalds of Florida, calling him a "prop" for the GOP and and accusing him of backing a "policy agenda intent on upholding and perpetuating white supremacy."</span></li>
</ul>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://www.breitbart.com/health/2023/05/17/poll-28-of-canadians-approve-of-assisted-suicide-for-homelessness/"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.breitbart.com/health/2023/05/17/poll-28-of-canadians-approve-of-assisted-suicide-for-homelessness/</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>Poll: 28% of Canadians Approve of &lsquo;Assisted Suicide&rsquo; for Homelessness</strong></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Canada&rsquo;s National Post on Tuesday published the results of a poll that show nearly a third of Canadians believe assisted suicide should be offered to homeless people who are weary of their lives.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">A fifth of the respondents said Medical Assistance in Dying (MAID) should be offered as an option to anyone, regardless of medical or psychological condition.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The poll, conducted by a public opinion firm called Research Co. founded by noted Canadian pollster Mario Canseco, looks like the rapidly approaching bottom of a slippery slope that began when Canada became one of the few countries to legalize assisted suicide for non-medical reasons in 2021.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">A larger number of countries have legalized euthanasia and assisted suicide &mdash; similar but not identical procedures that vary based on how deeply a doctor is involved in the process &mdash; for people suffering from severe chronic pain or terminal illnesses. There is constant pressure to &ldquo;liberalize&rdquo; the procedure further with arguments that adults of sound mind should be able to request humane medically assisted death for any reason they see fit.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">In some countries, the requirements for &ldquo;sound mind&rdquo; and even &ldquo;adult&rdquo; have been challenged. Belgium, for example, allows children of any age to request euthanasia if they have a terminal illness. In February, a Canadian parliamentary committee recommended expanding MAID to allow &ldquo;mature minors&rdquo; to request the procedure.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Canada lifted the requirement for adults to be suffering from a terminal illness in 2021, and in March 2023 it formally authorized euthanasia for people suffering from mental illnesses, although implementation of that change was pushed back to 2024 at the last minute.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Critics of the practice pointed to an explosion of suicides among Canadians as MAID was first destigmatized, and then actively promoted by doctors trained to bring euthanasia up in conversation with patients, rather than waiting for them to make the fateful request.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The ensuing surge of assisted suicides was remarkable, as the National Post reported: &ldquo;While only 2,838 Canadians opted for assisted suicide in the first full year of legalized MAID, as of last count in 2021 that had risen to 10,064 &ndash; an increase of 32.4 per cent over just the year before.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">When MAID was authorized for people with mental illness, skeptics predicted health officials would see it as a cost-effective method for cleaning out overcrowded clinics. Last August, a Canadian armed forces veteran suffering from post-traumatic stress disorder said he was offered medically assisted suicide by an employee from the Department of Veterans&rsquo; Affairs even though he had never expressed any interest in dying.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">MAID in Canada does not even require supervision by medical doctors, only nurse practitioners, and it is offered to prisoners, a measure even toddler-suicide Belgium balked at.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">According to the Research Co. poll, 73 percent of Canadians are comfortable with the current state of MAID, and only 16 percent want to put restrictions back in place. The National Post noted a growing number of Canadians across all demographic lines believe assisted suicide should be liberalized even further:</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Perhaps most strikingly, half of the poll respondents said they were untroubled by reports that people with severe illness are choosing MAID because they cannot obtain the medical treatment they need from Canada&rsquo;s overstressed socialized medical system. Over half, 51 percent, said they endorsed &ldquo;inability to receive medical treatment&rdquo; as a reason for requesting assisted suicide, which will come as grim news to MAID critics who thought killing patients because Canada is running out of medicine would be the last straw.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The only place Canada&rsquo;s enthusiasm for euthanasia appears to falter is the plan to offer MAID to people with mental illness, perhaps because securing legitimate consent from people who are not of sound mind is problematic.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Canadian Justice Minister David Lametti said MAID eligibility for the mentally ill was pushed back to March 2024 in order to &ldquo;provide sufficient time to ensure our health care system fully protects those who may be vulnerable and supports autonomy and freedom of choice.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">And now for the run down:</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://townhall.com/tipsheet/spencerbrown/2023/05/17/biden-considering-ban-on-chocolate-milk-in-schools-n2623260"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://townhall.com/tipsheet/spencerbrown/2023/05/17/biden-considering-ban-on-chocolate-milk-in-schools-n2623260</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">As if President Joe Biden and his administration haven't already done enough to make life more difficult and usher in more hardship for the American people, his band of merry muck-ups are now setting their sights on school lunches and toying around with a ban on chocolate milk &mdash; as well as strawberry milk and other flavor alternatives &mdash; over concerns about added sugars.</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Yes, the same administration that called it "outrageous" and "immoral" to prevent children from taking life-altering hormones to prevent puberty for the purpose of "transitioning" is worried that milk provided at school might have ill effects on their health.</span></li>
</ul>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://townhall.com/tipsheet/rebeccadowns/2023/05/18/marjorie-taylor-greene-files-impeachment-articles-against-joe-biden-and-more-n2623423"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://townhall.com/tipsheet/rebeccadowns/2023/05/18/marjorie-taylor-greene-files-impeachment-articles-against-joe-biden-and-more-n2623423</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Republicans are putting their money with their mouth is when it comes to holding President Joe Biden and his Cabinet accountable. On Thursday morning, Rep. Marjorie Taylor Greene (R-GA) announced that she was filing articles of impeachment against the president, but he's not the only one. She's also filed impeachment articles against FBI Director Christopher Wray, Attorney General Merrick Garland, Department of Homeland Security Secretary Alejandro Mayorkas, and U.S. Attorney Matthew, as part of what she is calling Impeachment Week.</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">During her press conference, the congresswoman referred to the Biden administration as "America last" and argued that it "has been working since January 20, 2021, to systemically destroy this country," specifically when it comes to how his handling of illegal immigration.</span></li>
</ul>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://townhall.com/tipsheet/rebeccadowns/2023/05/17/nc-legislature-overrides-governors-veto-making-12-week-abortion-ban-law-n2623365"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://townhall.com/tipsheet/rebeccadowns/2023/05/17/nc-legislature-overrides-governors-veto-making-12-week-abortion-ban-law-n2623365</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">NC Legislature Overrides Gov. Cooper's Veto, Making 12-Week Abortion Ban the Law</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">In a post-Dobbs v. Jackson world, states are considering abortion legislation at an increasing rate. The latest includes North Carolina, where the state legislature on Tuesday night overrode a veto on a 12-week abortion ban from Gov. Roy Cooper (D-NC). North Carolina is a particularly interesting case as the state "experienced a greater spike in abortions than any other state" in the first two months after Dobbs fell, according to The Washington Post.</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The new law, S.B. 20, the Care for Women, Children, and Families Act, also provides funding of foster care programs, as well as paid family leave and pregnancy resource centers. It's set to go into effect on July 1, 2023.</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">It was previously covered how the state legislature passed the bill earlier this month. While Cooper was expected to veto the bill, overriding his veto was likely but not necessarily certain. Republicans could only afford to lose one member. The bill was able to become law, though, thanks to members who refused to budge, including Rep. Tricia Cotham, who last month switched from the Democratic Party to the GOP, as Madeline also highlighted.</span></li>
</ul>]]></description>
   <author><![CDATA[Garrison Hardie]]></author>
   <enclosure url="https://app.dropwave.io/episode/5a4c60b3-4f2f-47eb-9fb1-ef16be82746f/daily-news-brief-for-friday-may-19th-2023.mp3" length="932" type="audio/mp3"/>
   <guid isPermaLink="false"><![CDATA[5a4c60b3-4f2f-47eb-9fb1-ef16be82746f]]></guid>
   <pubDate>Fri, 19 May 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
   <source url=""><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></source>
   <itunes:author><![CDATA[Garrison Hardie]]></itunes:author>
   <itunes:image href="https://assets-cdn2.dropwave.io/2ab40ac0-e99d-4f25-a6d2-541d2c9b290a/cover-art/hUZu1H9lrRY0wXg66WHC8eLwYBA3hbRNTAHQmHt2.png"/>
   <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
   <itunes:duration>932</itunes:duration>
   <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
  
  </item><item>
   <title><![CDATA[Daily News Brief for Thursday, May 18th, 2023 [Daily News Brief]]]></title>
   <link>https://app.dropwave.io/episode/a9c74cf5-2b00-4120-84e7-2d047951d4d6/daily-news-brief-for-thursday-may-18th-2023.mp3</link>
   <description><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">This is Garrison Hardie with your CrossPolitic Daily News Brief for Thursday, May 18th, 2023.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>PUB MEMBERSHIP PLUG:</strong></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">We have ourselves an exciting summer coming up here at CrossPolitic, and we want you to join us on this ride&hellip; First, we&rsquo;re no longer calling it the Fight Laugh Feast club&hellip; it&rsquo;s now called the Pub! Second, we are launching a new line of content, focused on family entertainment. Some of this content includes a new TV Show called This America, a cooking show, a hunting show, live streaming of our conferences, and our past conference talks, all bundled within our new polished Fight Laugh Feast App, dropping on June 1st. Head on over to fightlaughfeast.com, and join the Pub today&hellip; that&rsquo;s fightlaughfeast.com.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://www.dailywire.com/news/house-chairman-demands-irs-chief-answer-for-alleged-hunter-biden-probe-shakeup"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.dailywire.com/news/house-chairman-demands-irs-chief-answer-for-alleged-hunter-biden-probe-shakeup</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>House Chairman Demands IRS Chief Answer For Alleged Hunter Biden Probe Shakeup</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">A top House Republican wants the Internal Revenue Service (IRS) to clarify what is happening with the criminal investigation into Hunter Biden after lawyers for a whistleblower within the agency claimed his team got removed from the case.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Ways and Means Chairman Jason Smith (R-MO) is requesting an &ldquo;urgent briefing&rdquo; from IRS Commissioner Daniel Werfel&rsquo;s office to address concerns about possible retaliation.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&ldquo;These allegations are extremely serious. Such retaliation not only discourages whistleblowers from coming forward to Congress but can also constitute an illegal violation of statutory protections for whistleblowers,&rdquo; Smith wrote in a letter to Werfel on Tuesday. The letter was published by Just the News.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Lawyers for an IRS criminal supervisory special agent wrote to Congress on Monday to say their client had just been told that &ldquo;he and his entire investigative team are being removed&rdquo; from the Hunter Biden probe and was &ldquo;informed the change was at the request of the Department of Justice.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The &ldquo;move is clearly retaliatory and may also constitute obstruction of a congressional inquiry,&rdquo; lawyers Mark Lytle and Tristan Leavitt wrote.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The IRS agent, who has not been publicly identified, has sought to make protected whistleblower disclosures to Congress while raising concerns about lies and politics corrupting the criminal inquiry into Hunter Biden.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">After Biden&rsquo;s lawyers met with Department of Justice officials late last month, sources told The Washington Post that potential charges for tax- and gun-related crimes may soon follow from Delaware&rsquo;s U.S. Attorney David Weiss. Hunter Biden has said he expects to be cleared of wrongdoing, and his father, President Joe Biden, told MSNBC this month that his son has &ldquo;done nothing wrong.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The IRS and Justice Department have so far refused to respond directly to the claim that the IRS supervisor and his entire team had been pulled from the case.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The Justice Department has deferred to Weiss, whose office is so far not speaking out on the matter.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Smith requested a briefing from Werfel&rsquo;s office by 5 p.m. on Thursday. &ldquo;Failure to provide forthcoming and transparent information regarding the actions taken against this employee by your agency will necessitate additional Committee action,&rdquo; he warned.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://www.foxnews.com/politics/supreme-court-allows-illinois-assault-weapons-ban-take-effect"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.foxnews.com/politics/supreme-court-allows-illinois-assault-weapons-ban-take-effect</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Supreme Court allows Illinois 'assault weapons' ban to take effect</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The U.S. Supreme Court allowed Illinois' ban on "assault weapons" to take effect temporarily on Wednesday.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The ruling allows the Illinois law to remain in effect while lower courts deliberate on its constitutional status. Wednesday's ruling comes after a gun shop owner in Illinois requested an injunction against the ban.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The Illinois law bans the sale and new possession of semi-automatic "assault weapons." Those who already legally own such weapons would not have to turn them in. The law also bans the sale of large capacity magazines.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The court did not offer an explanation for its Wednesday decision, and there were no noted dissents.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The National Foundation for Gun Rights (NFGR) a legal group associated with the gun store that requested an injunction, expressed disappointment with Wednesday's ruling. The group remains committed to fighting Illinois' ban, however.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">"Any action the Supreme Court would have taken at this point would only have been temporary and not on the merits of the case itself. Clearly, the Supreme Court is watching the issue closely and we look forward to appealing very soon on the merits if the 7th Circuit rules against us &ndash; as the signs currently point to," said Hannah Hill, Executive Director of the NFGR.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The U.S. Court of Appeals for the 7th Circuit is currently considering the case. The request for an injunction went to Justice Amy Coney Barrett.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Illinois passed the Protect Illinois Communities Act on Jan. 10, banning the sale, purchase, manufacture, delivery and importation of "assault weapons" and large capacity magazines, with exceptions for law enforcement, military members and certain other professionals with firearm training. The legislation specifically names the AR-15 and AK-47 rifles and requires lawful owners of semi-automatic rifles to register their ownership with state police.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The 7th Circuit has yet to issue a final ruling on the Illinois law, but its decision is likely to be appealed to the Supreme Court.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Judge Stephen Patrick McGlynn, a Trump appointee in Illinois' Southern District, had initially granted the injunction earlier in May. Appellate Judge Frank Easterbrook then reversed McGlynn's ruling, a decision that has now been supported by both the 7th Circuit and the Supreme Court.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">McGlynn's ruling had argued that Illinois' law infringed on the right to self-defense and, in some cases, "completely obliterated that right by criminalizing the purchase and the sale of more than 190 'arms.'"</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://mynorthwest.com/3889164/rantz-pedophile-ish-adult-woman-identifies-15-year-old-boy-per-police-report/"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://mynorthwest.com/3889164/rantz-pedophile-ish-adult-woman-identifies-15-year-old-boy-per-police-report/</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>&lsquo;Pedophile-ish&rsquo; adult woman identifies as 15-year-old boy, per police report</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Police arrested a 35-year-old woman, who identifies as a 15-year-old boy, for harboring a teen runaway. Shouldn&rsquo;t Washington Progressives defend this woman for being mis-aged?</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The police allege Amanda Dorrough was involved in a host of inappropriate behavior with juveniles, including getting naked in front of them, inappropriately touching one, and providing marijuana. One of her alleged victims characterized her as &ldquo;pedophile-ish,&rdquo; according to a police incident report, which doesn&rsquo;t list the individual ages of the alleged victims.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">This incident highlights the dangers of identifying as something you&rsquo;re not. But it also shows the left-wing hypocrisy on issues of identity.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The vice principal at Port Angeles High School reported to police that two students reported that eight of their classmates were planning to run away to Seattle with Amanda Dorrough, according to the police report. It said there had been &ldquo;several recent reports of Amanda Dorrough having runaway youth in her apartment.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">An officer located several teen minors at the gully behind Dorrough&rsquo;s apartment complex on May 4, 2023. Several of them were identified by the school as planning to run away, and Dorrough was allegedly aware that one was listed as a runaway, giving the officer probable cause to arrest her for Unlawful Harboring of a Minor. In addition to the minors, police found two empty condom packets and a bra at the gully.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&ldquo;While at the Clallam County Jail, Amanda told the staff that she identifies as a teenage boy,&rdquo; the incident report states. &ldquo;The previous week, she told [an officer] that she identifies as a teenage boy. The previous week she told [the officer] that she feels like teenagers &lsquo;understand&rsquo; her better and that she &lsquo;identifies&rsquo; better with teenage kids. Amanda is a 35-year-old woman.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">An alleged juvenile victim, identified only as T.A., told authorities that he found Dorrough to be &ldquo;pedophile-ish,&rdquo; according to the incident report. It says T.A. reports that Amanda told him that she liked him and when he didn&rsquo;t reciprocate the feeling, she got upset and &ldquo;almost killed herself.&rdquo; He alleged she touched him inappropriately and has been completely nude in front of him.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">T.A. also alleged that Dorrough provided him and other juveniles with marijuana. The Clallam County Prosecuting Attorney&rsquo;s Office charged her with one count of distributing a controlled substance (marijuana/cannabis) to a minor. She posted bail on May 14.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">This is not the first contact police have had with an adult pretending to be a minor. Since April 11, 2023, the police said they received 11 calls concerning Dorrough&rsquo;s alleged conduct.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Now it&rsquo;s time for my new segment, the rundown&hellip;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://www.theblaze.com/news/church-that-runs-nashville-christian-school-where-mass-killing-occurred-moves-to-block-public-release-of-trans-shooters-manifesto"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.theblaze.com/news/church-that-runs-nashville-christian-school-where-mass-killing-occurred-moves-to-block-public-release-of-trans-shooters-manifesto</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Over the weekend, the Covenant Presbyterian Church and associated Covenant School filed a motion to block the public release of the manifesto of the transgender shooter who attacked the school, court documents revealed.</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Monday court filings revealed that the Covenant Church requested that the court prevent the documents from being released to the public, citing privacy concerns.</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">The motion, filed against the Tennessee Firearms Association, and another filed against the Nashville Police Association stated that the manifesto "may include and/or relate to information owned by Covenant Church," such as "schematics of church facilities and confidential information" regarding employees.</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">The church claimed the manifesto's release could "impair or impede its ability to protect its interests and the privacy of its employees."</span></li>
</ul>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://justthenews.com/nation/states/center-square/24-republican-governors-commit-help-texas-defend-its-border"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://justthenews.com/nation/states/center-square/24-republican-governors-commit-help-texas-defend-its-border</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Twenty-four Republican governors have responded to Texas Gov. Greg Abbott&rsquo;s call for help to secure its border with Mexico.</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">This is after at least more than 7 million people have been apprehended or reported evading capture by law enforcement since President Joe Biden&rsquo;s been in office.</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Within the past few days, groups of tens of thousands of foreign nationals arrived in the Rio Grande Valley and in other areas of Texas, overwhelming Border Patrol agents, officials said. Abbott has already sent more than 10,000 Texas National Guard troops to the border as border communities continue to declare emergencies.</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">The governors pledging support in addition to Florida Gov. Ron DeSantis, who is deploying troops and resources in the next 24 hours, include those of Alabama, Alaska, Arkansas, Georgia, Idaho, Indiana, Iowa, Missouri, Mississippi, Montana, Nebraska, North Dakota, New Hampshire, Nevada, Ohio, Oklahoma, South Carolina, South Dakota, Tennessee, Utah, Virginia, West Virginia, and Wyoming.</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">They pledged their support within hours of Abbott&rsquo;s request for help Tuesday afternoon.</span></li>
</ul>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://www.dailyfetched.com/netflix-series-which-incorrectly-featured-cleopatra-as-black-woman-gets-worst-audience-score-in-tv-history/"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.dailyfetched.com/netflix-series-which-incorrectly-featured-cleopatra-as-black-woman-gets-worst-audience-score-in-tv-history/</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Netflix Series Which Incorrectly Featured Cleopatra as Black Woman Gets Worst Audience Score in TV History</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">As The Daily Fetched reported last month, the government of Egypt has slammed Netflix for the portrayal, accusing them of falsely rating history for politics. The secretary-general of the Supreme Council of Antiquities, Mostafa Waziri, said the Netflix show wrongly Featuring Cleopatra was a black woman represents a &ldquo;falsification of Egyptian history and a blatant historical fallacy.&rdquo;</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">the show has done something I didn&rsquo;t think was even possible. It has not just the lowest audience score in Netflix history; it has essentially the lowest audience score possible on Rotten Tomatoes, a 1%. Not a 10%, a 1%. (Update: It just ticked up to 2%. Still an unprecedented low)</span></li>
</ul>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://www.boundingintosports.com/2023/05/west-virginia-coach-bob-huggins-hit-with-massive-fine-suspension-for-anti-gay-slur/"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.boundingintosports.com/2023/05/west-virginia-coach-bob-huggins-hit-with-massive-fine-suspension-for-anti-gay-slur/</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">West Virginia Coach Bob Huggins Hit With Massive Fine, Suspension For Anti-Gay Slur</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">While appearing on the May 8, 2023, episode of The Bill Cunningham Show, he used a homophobic slur and expressed anti-Catholic sentiments on more than one occasion.</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Following the interview&rsquo;s airing, Bob Huggins subsequently issued an apology for what he had said, calling it &ldquo;completely insensitive and abhorrent&rdquo; and promised to accept any consequences.</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Amidst calls for Bob Huggins to be fired, the administration in Morgantown was faced with a tough decision. The comments were easily a terminable offense, but the school chose to blow the whistle on their head coach in a different manner. And while Huggy Bear will return to the bench next year, he&rsquo;ll have a lot lighter wallet to sit on when he does.</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Huggins has agreed to a million-dollar salary reduction, a three-game suspension, and sensitivity training. Huggins&rsquo; suspension will take place during his team&rsquo;s first three regular-season games.</span></li>
</ul>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://www.boundingintosports.com/2023/05/former-raiders-wide-receiver-henry-ruggs-pleads-guilty-to-driving-drunk-156-mph-in-fatal-crash/"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.boundingintosports.com/2023/05/former-raiders-wide-receiver-henry-ruggs-pleads-guilty-to-driving-drunk-156-mph-in-fatal-crash/</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Former Raiders Wide Receiver Henry Ruggs Pleads Guilty To Driving Drunk 156 MPH In Fatal Crash</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Tina Tintor, 23, and her pet dog were killed in the crash. Following the accident, Ruggs registered a blood alcohol content twice Nevada&rsquo;s legal limit.</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">On May 10, the Raiders&rsquo; 2020 first-round NFL draft pick will avoid trial and is expected to be sentenced Aug. 9 to three to 10 years in state prison under terms of his plea deal with prosecutors. The minimum three-year sentence cannot be reduced by converting the year-and-a-half that he has already spent on house arrest applied as time already served.</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">That means the once-promising wide receiver will go to prison and won&rsquo;t be able to appeal his conviction or sentence. It&rsquo;s a strict punishment, designed to hit first-time offenders harder than most traffic felonies. However, due to the events leading up to the incident, Clark County District Attorney Steve Wolfson pushed for the maximum repercussions.</span></li>
</ul>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://boundingintocomics.com/2023/05/16/arnold-schwarzenegger-says-hes-done-with-terminator-admits-genisys-and-dark-fate-were-just-not-well-written/"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://boundingintocomics.com/2023/05/16/arnold-schwarzenegger-says-hes-done-with-terminator-admits-genisys-and-dark-fate-were-just-not-well-written/</span></a></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">In entertainment news&hellip;&nbsp;</span></p>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Terminator actor Arnold Schwarzenegger bluntly stated he&rsquo;s done with the Terminator franchise moving forward while also admitting that both Genisys and Dark Fate &ldquo;were just not well written.&rdquo;</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Schwarzenegger conducted a wide-ranging interview with The Hollywood Reporter discussing everything from the media slaughtering Last Action Hero due to his politics, his own personal growth and belief in God, his divorce, and his upcoming Netflix series FUBAR.</span></li>
</ul>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://dailycaller.com/2023/05/16/sports-illustrated-transgender-male-swimsuit-edition-magazine-cover/"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://dailycaller.com/2023/05/16/sports-illustrated-transgender-male-swimsuit-edition-magazine-cover/</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Sports Illustrated Swimsuit Edition has put biological male Kim Petras in a two-piece swimsuit on its Swimsuit Edition magazine cover that was released Monday.</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Petras is a singer and songwriter who identifies as transgender. The grammy award winner was among the &ldquo;28 incredible women&rdquo; which Sports Illustrated celebrated in its recent Swimsuit Edition of the magazine.</span></li>
</ul>]]></description>
   <author><![CDATA[Garrison Hardie]]></author>
   <enclosure url="https://app.dropwave.io/episode/a9c74cf5-2b00-4120-84e7-2d047951d4d6/daily-news-brief-for-thursday-may-18th-2023.mp3" length="858" type="audio/mp3"/>
   <guid isPermaLink="false"><![CDATA[a9c74cf5-2b00-4120-84e7-2d047951d4d6]]></guid>
   <pubDate>Thu, 18 May 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
   <source url=""><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></source>
   <itunes:author><![CDATA[Garrison Hardie]]></itunes:author>
   <itunes:image href="https://assets-cdn2.dropwave.io/2ab40ac0-e99d-4f25-a6d2-541d2c9b290a/cover-art/hUZu1H9lrRY0wXg66WHC8eLwYBA3hbRNTAHQmHt2.png"/>
   <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
   <itunes:duration>858</itunes:duration>
   <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
  
  </item><item>
   <title><![CDATA[Daily News Brief for Wednesday, May 17th, 2023 [Daily News Brief]]]></title>
   <link>https://app.dropwave.io/episode/515357cd-71c9-4fc0-aaea-5417e2094989/daily-news-brief-for-wednesday-may-17th-2023.mp3</link>
   <description><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">This is Garrison Hardie with your CrossPolitic Daily News Brief for Wednesday, May 17th, 2023.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Concordis Education Partners:</strong></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Classical Christian education has reminded us to aim education at truth, but the trivium has been used as a formula rather than a way of training students in discernment.&nbsp;&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">To teach well, you must coach.&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&nbsp;</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Concordis Foundation is offering their third annual BOOT CAMP &ndash; a faculty summit &ndash; July 11-13th in Moscow, Idaho.&nbsp; This is a three-day intensive teaching training where you learn to coach students, using the trivium, so that you can meet students at all learning levels.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&nbsp;</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Learn more at</span><a href="https://concordispartners.com/"><span style="font-weight: 400;"> </span><span style="font-weight: 400;">concordispartners.com</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;">&nbsp;&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://www.dailywire.com/news/tsa-rolls-out-facial-recognition-technology-test-at-several-major-airports"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.dailywire.com/news/tsa-rolls-out-facial-recognition-technology-test-at-several-major-airports</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>TSA Rolls Out Facial Recognition Technology Test At Several Major Airports</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The Transportation Security Administration is testing the use of facial recognition technology at airports across the nation, a move that the federal agency claims will help employees more easily identify travelers.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Passengers may soon find themselves in a security screening line where they are asked to place their identification into a slot and look into a camera, after which a small screen will take their picture and flash the words &ldquo;photo complete,&rdquo; permitting the traveler to continue through the security process without handing their identification to an employee.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The technology is currently in use at 16 airports throughout the country, such as those in Atlanta, Boston, Dallas, Detroit, Los Angeles, Miami, Orlando, Phoenix, and Salt Lake City, according to a report from the Associated Press. Passengers are allowed to opt out of the pilot program conducted by the TSA, which is a branch of the Department of Homeland Security.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">TSA employees in the security lines with the technology, which examines whether the identification is real and whether the identification belongs to the traveler, will nevertheless be present to ensure that the system reaches correct conclusions.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The test of the technology comes despite a February letter from five members of the Senate, including Sen. Bernie Sanders (I-VT) and Sen. Jeff Merkley (D-OR), who expressed concern over reports that the system could be implemented across the United States as soon as this year if deemed successful. The lawmakers contended that facial recognition technology &ldquo;represents a risk to civil liberties and privacy rights.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Federal entities already leverage facial recognition technology in various capacities despite the privacy and security concerns: a report published last year by the Government Accountability Office found that 18 out of 24 agencies reported using facial recognition systems in fiscal year 2020, largely for computer access and law enforcement activities, while 14 out of 42 agencies that employ law enforcement officers reported using the technology in criminal investigations.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Americans broadly support the &ldquo;widespread use of facial recognition technology&rdquo; by police officers who utilize the systems for law enforcement purposes, according to a survey from Pew Research Center, in which 27% of respondents said the policy was a &ldquo;bad idea&rdquo; and 46% said the policy was a &ldquo;good idea.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Other state and local governments have indeed banned biometric recognition technology. Texas Attorney General Ken Paxton filed suit last year against Google and Meta for breaches of state laws which prohibit technology firms from using data such as iris scans, fingerprints, voiceprints, or records of hand and face geometry for commercial purposes without permission.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://www.theepochtimes.com/anheuser-busch-announces-changes-company-amid-bud-light-boycott_5266255.html?utm_source=partner&amp;utm_campaign=BonginoReport"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.theepochtimes.com/anheuser-busch-announces-changes-company-amid-bud-light-boycott_5266255.html?utm_source=partner&amp;utm_campaign=BonginoReport</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Anheuser-Busch Makes Changes to Company Amid Bud Light Boycott</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Anheuser-Busch revealed that it is making attempts to change its marketing structure in the midst of a backlash after Bud Light produced a can featuring a transgender activist&rsquo;s face for a social media promotion.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">While the firm did not make mention of the controversy and boycott, a spokesperson for the brewing giant told Fox2Now in St. Louis that it held a meeting in the city and that &ldquo;we have communicated some next steps with our internal teams and wholesaler partners.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&ldquo;First, we made it clear that the safety and welfare of our employees and our partners is our top priority,&rdquo; the company spokesperson said before adding that a new executive was tapped to head a marketing division.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&ldquo;Todd Allen was appointed Vice President of Bud Light added the spokesperson. &ldquo;Third, we made some adjustments to streamline the structure of our marketing function to reduce layers so that our most senior marketers are more closely connected to every aspect of our brands activities. These steps will help us maintain focus on the things we do best: brewing great beer for all consumers, while always making a positive impact in our communities and on our country.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">For the past month and a half, Bud Light&rsquo;s sales have taken a nosedive after transgender influencer Dylan Mulvaney posted a video with the namesake can on social media, writing &ldquo;#budlightpartner&rdquo; in the caption. That led many to believe the light beer was officially partnering with Mulvaney and would launch a campaign with the activist, who is a biological male.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Anheuser-Busch executive Brendan Whitworth said in an April 14 news release that the beverage firm had had no intention of sparking division or wading into a political debate. However, Whitworth made no mention of Mulvaney or the backlash.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Weeks later, Anheuser-Busch InBev CEO Michel Doukeris told investors in a call that there was no partnership with Mulvaney and that only &ldquo;one can&rdquo; was produced with Mulvaney&rsquo;s face. In a subsequent Financial Times interview, Doukeris claimed that the slumping Bud Light sales were sparked by social media-driven &ldquo;misinformation.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Continuing, the CEO said that people believed it was a campaign. &ldquo;It was not: it was one post. It was not an advertisement,&rdquo; he remarked, contradicting the #budlightpartner hashtag that Mulvaney had written.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Sales of the product dropped 26 percent year-over-year in the week ending April 22, according to Bump Williams Consulting based on Nielsen IQ data. Meanwhile, sales of rival beers Coors Light and Miller Light both saw their sales rise by about 10 percent each, according to the data.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">In the midst of the backlash, two Bud Light executives&mdash;Alissa Heinerscheid and Daniel Blake&mdash;took a leave of absence, the company said. &ldquo;Given the circumstances, Alissa has decided to take a leave of absence which we support. Daniel has also decided to take a leave of absence,&rdquo; the company said last month.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://thepostmillennial.com/seattle-to-pay-out-2-3-million-to-whistleblowers-who-revealed-mayor-engaged-in-chaz-cover-up-by-deleting-texts?utm_campaign=64487"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://thepostmillennial.com/seattle-to-pay-out-2-3-million-to-whistleblowers-who-revealed-mayor-engaged-in-chaz-cover-up-by-deleting-texts?utm_campaign=64487</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Seattle to pay out $2.3 MILLION to whistleblowers who revealed mayor engaged in CHAZ cover-up by deleting texts</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The city of Seattle will be forced to pay $2.3 million to settle a lawsuit brought by city employees who were mistreated after they helped reveal that thousands of then-Mayor Jenny Durkan&rsquo;s text messages had been deleted during the violent riots that rocked the city and the deadly Capitol Hill Autonomous Zone in the summer of 2020.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">A whistleblower complaint by the employees helped to reveal that the texts of Durkan, former Police Chief Carmen Best, Fire Chief Harold Scoggins, and other top officials from the summer of 2020 were intentionally deleted.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Though the King County Superior Court case was resolved last month, the terms of Seattle&rsquo;s settlement with Stacy Irwin and Kimberly Ferreiro weren&rsquo;t finalized until this week and the details were released to The Seattle Times through a public disclosure request on Friday.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The $2.3 million payout is in addition to over $770,000, as of April, spent by the city on attorneys to defend the case, the outlet reported.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">According to the suit, Irwin and Ferreiro claimed that they resigned as public-records officers in Durkan&rsquo;s office due to hostile conditions and retaliation. The pair claimed they were &ldquo;subjected to scorn, ridicule, abuse, and hostility &hellip; and the demand to perform illegal acts.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The pair sounded the alarm in 2021 when they complained to the Seattle Ethics and Elections Commission that the mayor&rsquo;s office was mishandling records requests.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">An investigation by the SEEC determined that the mayor&rsquo;s legal counsel, Michelle Chen, had violated the state Public Records Act by using narrow interpretations of certain requests to exclude Durkan&rsquo;s missing texts and diverged from best practices by not informing requesters the texts were missing.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Under state law, texts and other communications about public businesses by local elected officials must be kept for at least two years and anyone who willfully destroys a public record that&rsquo;s supposed to be preserved is guilty of a felony, punishable by up to five years in prison.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The settlement agreement includes $25,000 in lost wages each to Irwin and Ferreiro, while the remainder of the $2.3 million is for general damages and attorneys&rsquo; fees.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">As part of the settlement, the plaintiffs are required to drop the case, destroy city documents in their possession, and never pursue jobs in the city again. Additionally, both parties are barred from talking publicly about the settlement amount.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Irwin told the Times that records disappeared and yet, &ldquo;There&rsquo;s been no accountability. These officials basically got away with it and the taxpayers are paying.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Ferreiro said, &ldquo;It&rsquo;s still a loss for the citizens of Seattle,&rdquo; because some questions about the actions of city officials &ldquo;will never be answered.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">In August 2022, then-King County Prosecutor Dan Satterberg requested that Sheriff Patti Cole-Tindall investigate the city officials&rsquo; deleted texts, but Cole-Tindall&rsquo;s office has yet to announce the results.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Durkan&rsquo;s office previously claimed that an &ldquo;unknown technology issue&rdquo; caused the texts to go missing but a city-commissioned forensic report found that Durkan&rsquo;s phone was changed in July 2020 to delete texts automatically after 30 days as well as texts stored in the cloud.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Durkan also previously claimed that she dropped her phone in a tide pool on the July 4 weekend of that year.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">A subsequent forensic report commissioned by business owners and residents suing the city over the deadly autonomous zone revealed that Durkan texts were manually deleted.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">In February, the city settled that lawsuit for $3.65 million, including $600,000 in penalties for the deleted texts.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The settlement came swiftly after a judge sanctioned the city for destroying evidence and noted that Durkan&rsquo;s excuses &ldquo;strained credibility.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Over 27,000 texts were deleted from Best&rsquo;s phone and the most recent forensic reports show that phones used by Scoggins and others were reset in October 2020.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">In 2022, Seattle paid nearly $200,000 and pledged to improve its public records processes to settle a lawsuit brought by The Seattle Times that alleged the city had mishandled requests from reporters who asked for the messages between city officials.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">In February, the owner of a Korean restaurant filed a federal lawsuit against the city for the loss of business and expenses incurred during the notorious autonomous zone.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Litigation against the city as a result of the zone has already cost Seattle over $11 million.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/policy/defense-national-security/bipartisan-bill-pentagon-mexican-drug-cartels-pushing-fentanyl"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/policy/defense-national-security/bipartisan-bill-pentagon-mexican-drug-cartels-pushing-fentanyl</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Bipartisan bill would empower Pentagon to take down Mexican drug cartels pushing fentanyl</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Democrats and Republicans from the House and Senate will debut legislation that would declare fentanyl a national security threat and allow the Pentagon to take new action targeting Mexican drug cartels.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Senate Armed Services Committee members Joni Ernst (R-IA) and Tim Kaine (D-VA) shared exclusively with the Washington Examiner Tuesday morning their forthcoming bipartisan, bicameral bill to use their oversight authority of the Department of Defense to force the federal government to take stronger actions against Mexican transnational criminal organizations.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">"The amount of lives lost in Iowa and across the country due to this deadly drug has far surpassed the federal government&rsquo;s response, and we must scale immediately to combat this national security threat," Ernst said in a statement provided to the Washington Examiner. "This bipartisan work will engage Mexico as an active partner to counter fentanyl trafficking and put the Pentagon&rsquo;s tools to use to save American lives.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The Disrupt Fentanyl Trafficking Act would require the Pentagon to develop a fentanyl-specific counterdrug strategy, including how to work directly with the Mexican military and to increase security operations with Mexico.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Fentanyl is largely moved into the U.S. from Mexico, and the ingredients to make the powerful drug originate in China and are then shipped to producers in Mexico.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Ernst and Kaine maintained that enlisting the Mexican government as an equal partner in the war on fentanyl is critical, given the southern neighbor has failed to get a hold of the problem over the past five years.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Between 2017 and 2021, fentanyl seizures at the U.S. border increased by 950% &mdash; most of which occurred under Mexican President Andres Manuel Lopez Obrador.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Fentanyl has become the leading cause of death in U.S. adults between 18 and 45. President Joe Biden, in his State of the Union address earlier this year, vowed to do more to tackle the epidemic.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Now before we end today, it&rsquo;s time for a new segment I like to call the rundown:</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2023/05/15/microsoft-activision-deal-eu-approves-takeover-of-call-of-duty-maker.html"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.cnbc.com/2023/05/15/microsoft-activision-deal-eu-approves-takeover-of-call-of-duty-maker.html</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">European Union regulators on Monday approved Microsoft&rsquo;s proposed $69 billion acquisition of gaming firm Activision Blizzard, subject to remedies offered by the U.S. tech giant.</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">The European Commission, the EU&rsquo;s executive arm, said that Microsoft offered remedies in the nascent area of cloud gaming that have staved off antitrust concerns. These remedies centered on allowing users to stream Activision games they purchase on any cloud streaming platform.</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Europe&rsquo;s green light is a huge win for Microsoft, after the U.K.&rsquo;s top competition authority last month blocked the deal.</span></li>
</ul>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://www.military.com/daily-news/2023/05/15/china-sentences-78-year-old-us-citizen-life-prison-spying-charges.html"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.military.com/daily-news/2023/05/15/china-sentences-78-year-old-us-citizen-life-prison-spying-charges.html</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">China sentenced a 78-year-old United States citizen to life in prison Monday on spying charges, in a case that could exacerbate the deterioration in ties between Beijing and Washington over recent years.</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Details of the charges against John Shing-Wan Leung, who also holds permanent residency in Hong Kong, have not been publicly released.</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Such investigations and trials are held behind closed doors and little information is generally released other than vague accusations of infiltration, gathering secrets and threatening state security.</span></li>
</ul>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://www.breitbart.com/entertainment/2023/05/15/81-year-old-martha-stewart-poses-for-sports-illustrated-swimsuit/"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.breitbart.com/entertainment/2023/05/15/81-year-old-martha-stewart-poses-for-sports-illustrated-swimsuit/</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Martha Stewart, who is 81-years-old, posed for the cover of Sports Illustrated Swimsuit, making her the oldest cover model in SI swimsuit issue history.</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">That&rsquo;s it&hellip;&nbsp; that&rsquo;s all there is with that story.&nbsp;</span></li>
</ul>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://www.foxnews.com/sports/horse-euthanized-churchill-downs-broken-leg-becomes-8th-thoroughbred-die-track-last-2-weeks"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.foxnews.com/sports/horse-euthanized-churchill-downs-broken-leg-becomes-8th-thoroughbred-die-track-last-2-weeks</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Another horse is dead after running at Churchill Downs, the site of the annual Kentucky Derby.</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Rio Moon broke his leg on Sunday near the finish line and had to be euthanized.</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">The horse became the eighth to die in the last two weeks at the racetrack - seven died of multiple causes in the days, and hours, leading up to the May 6 Derby.</span></li>
</ul>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://www.cbssports.com/nba/news/ja-morant-could-face-significant-suspension-to-start-2023-24-nba-season-over-latest-controversy-per-report/"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.cbssports.com/nba/news/ja-morant-could-face-significant-suspension-to-start-2023-24-nba-season-over-latest-controversy-per-report/</span></a></p>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">In NBA news&hellip; The Memphis Grizzlies could start next season without their best player for a period of time. After an Instagram Live video circulated online that showed Grizzlies superstar Ja Morant holding what appeared to be a gun in a car, the All-Star guard was suspended by Memphis from all team activities.&nbsp;</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">But that's not the only suspension Morant could be facing. The franchise centerpiece could be facing a "significant suspension" from the league, according to Adrian Wojnarowski.</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">The video in question was from an Instagram Live on Saturday, and it shows Morant in a car with friends and for a brief second as the camera pans to him it appears that he is holding a gun. After the video made the rounds on social media, the Grizzlies suspended their star guard. The league then announced it was launching an investigation into the situation.</span></li>
</ul>]]></description>
   <author><![CDATA[Garrison Hardie]]></author>
   <enclosure url="https://app.dropwave.io/episode/515357cd-71c9-4fc0-aaea-5417e2094989/daily-news-brief-for-wednesday-may-17th-2023.mp3" length="949" type="audio/mp3"/>
   <guid isPermaLink="false"><![CDATA[515357cd-71c9-4fc0-aaea-5417e2094989]]></guid>
   <pubDate>Wed, 17 May 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
   <source url=""><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></source>
   <itunes:author><![CDATA[Garrison Hardie]]></itunes:author>
   <itunes:image href="https://assets-cdn2.dropwave.io/2ab40ac0-e99d-4f25-a6d2-541d2c9b290a/cover-art/hUZu1H9lrRY0wXg66WHC8eLwYBA3hbRNTAHQmHt2.png"/>
   <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
   <itunes:duration>949</itunes:duration>
   <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
  
  </item><item>
   <title><![CDATA[CrossPolitic Daily News Brief for Tuesday, May 16th, 2023 [Daily News Brief]]]></title>
   <link>https://app.dropwave.io/episode/eb2cc10c-b7a7-4c24-aeeb-4154e3fab6b7/crosspolitic-daily-news-brief-for-tuesday-may-16th-2023.mp3</link>
   <description><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">This is Garrison Hardie with your CrossPolitic Daily News Brief for Tuesday, May 16th, 2023.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Concordis Education Partners:</strong></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Classical Christian education has reminded us to aim education at truth, but the trivium has been used as a formula rather than a way of training students in discernment.&nbsp;&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">To teach well, you must coach.&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&nbsp;</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Concordis Foundation is offering their third annual BOOT CAMP &ndash; a faculty summit &ndash; July 11-13th in Moscow, Idaho.&nbsp; This is a three-day intensive teaching training where you learn to coach students, using the trivium, so that you can meet students at all learning levels.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&nbsp;</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Learn more at</span><a href="https://concordispartners.com/"><span style="font-weight: 400;"> </span><span style="font-weight: 400;">concordispartners.com</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;">&nbsp;&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://www.19fortyfive.com/2023/05/the-u-s-navy-is-no-longer-the-largest-on-earth-it-might-not-matter/"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.19fortyfive.com/2023/05/the-u-s-navy-is-no-longer-the-largest-on-earth-it-might-not-matter/</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>The U.S. Navy Is No Longer The Largest On Earth</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">China now operates the world&rsquo;s largest Navy and has for several years exceeded the U.S. Navy in terms of sheer size, a fact that raises the much-considered question as to whether the People&rsquo;s Liberation Army &ndash; Navy (PLAN) can outmatch or simply might be superior to the U.S. Navy.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">In terms of sheer numbers of ships, the PLA-Navy surpassed the U.S. Navy several years ago, but how impactful are pure numbers when it comes to maritime warfare superiority? Can today&rsquo;s Chinese Navy outperform or even destroy the U.S. Navy? However unlikely this may be, it is certain to be a possibility being closely studied at the Pentagon.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Do sheer numbers equate to or parallel technological sophistication? Certainly &ldquo;mass still matters,&rdquo; to reference the famous concept expressed by Sun Tzu, yet several critical modern variables such as sensor and weapons range, multi-domain networking, and the effective use of unmanned systems could definitely offset or even counter any numerical advantage.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The U.S. Navy, for example, operates 11 aircraft carriers, is fast adding a new fleet of unmanned surface and undersea vessels, and is arming its warships with a wide range of advanced technologies including laser weapons, next-generation electronic warfare (EW), and an unprecedented ability to launch and control a small fleet of unmanned systems. The U.S. Navy has also demonstrated breakthrough technologies with multi-domain networking, AI-enabled autonomous platforms, and course-adjusting weapons such as the Tactical Tomahawk, which can re-route as needed in-fight to hit moving targets at sea.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The specifics of China&rsquo;s technological sophistication may be tough to fully assess, yet there is little doubt that the PLA-Navy is trying to challenge and ultimately surpass the U.S. Navy in terms of both size and capability.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">China&rsquo;s shipbuilding ambitions and pace of construction may be difficult for the U.S. to match. For instance, multiple reports say China is on pace to double its fleet of destroyers within just the next five years. The concern, however, is by no means restricted to pure numbers but also grounded in uncertainties related to the relative sophistication and capability of China&rsquo;s new destroyers. Having more destroyers does not necessarily equate to maritime superiority if they cannot compete with the range, precision, networking, and overall capability of U.S. destroyers. The U.S. Navy does have as many as 10 DDG Flight III destroyers under contract and is moving quickly to modernize its sensors, radar systems, computing, and ship-integrated weapons.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://thepostmillennial.com/eric-adams-wants-to-revoke-nycs-sanctuary-city-status-amid-massive-migrant-influx?utm_campaign=64487"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://thepostmillennial.com/eric-adams-wants-to-revoke-nycs-sanctuary-city-status-amid-massive-migrant-influx?utm_campaign=64487</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Eric Adams wants to revoke NYC's 'sanctuary city' status amid massive migrant influx</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">As New York City deals with a massive influx of illegal immigrants, Mayor Eric Adams on Thursday said he was asking a judge to revisit the city&rsquo;s sanctuary city law.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">"The law of sanctuary city was in place long before I became mayor. I&rsquo;m following the law. As a law enforcement person, you know, we follow the law," Adams said. "We are now in court now, today, asking the judge to revisit this law to deal with this humanitarian crisis because, even when they decided to put in place that law, no one thought they would be dealing with a humanitarian crisis of this proportion."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The statement comes as hotels in Upstate New York have canceled pre-booked hotel rooms and booted homeless veterans to make space for Adams&rsquo; migrants.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The Crossroads Hotel in Newburgh, New York abruptly canceled a Florida couple&rsquo;s 30-room reservation made for their wedding, made a few months ago to accommodate traveling guests.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">35-year-old Deanna Mifsud and 37-year-old Gary Moretti intend to get married on June 24 in upstate Wallkill, New York, and made the reservation at the hotel because it was 20 minutes away. Their reservation was canceled, with no help from the hotel staff.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Another pair to be married from Queens said Crossroads also canceled their May 20 reservation.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Also in Newburgh, homeless veterans staying in multiple hotels were told by staff that their temporary housing would not be extended and they would have to leave immediately.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The city of Newburgh, which is roughly 60 miles north of New York City, has become the staging ground for illegal immigrants in the state as Mayor Eric Adams continues to transport them into the county from New York City.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Adams signed an emergency declaration on Wednesday, ahead of Title 42&rsquo;s expiration,&nbsp; suspending the city&rsquo;s right-to-shelter rules that find private rooms for illegal immigrants immediately, according to CBS News.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Regarding the emergency declaration, Adams said on Thursday, "this was a hard decision, but it's the right decision, that this is just wrong what is happening to New York City. It's wrong and no one seems to care, but I care. And it was a challenging thing to do, but we're doing the right thing. No one thought about a humanitarian crisis when they first took this court case of right-to-shelter."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://www.foxnews.com/politics/durham-doj-fbi-failed-uphold-mission-strict-fidelity-law-trump-russia-probe"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.foxnews.com/politics/durham-doj-fbi-failed-uphold-mission-strict-fidelity-law-trump-russia-probe</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Durham finds DOJ, FBI 'failed to uphold' mission of 'strict fidelity to the law' in Trump-Russia probe</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Special Counsel John Durham found that the Department of Justice and FBI "failed to uphold their mission of strict fidelity to the law" when it launched the Trump-Russia investigation.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Fox News Digital obtained Durham&rsquo;s report Monday afternoon after his years-long investigation into the origins of the FBI&rsquo;s original investigation, known as "Crossfire Hurricane." That investigation looked into whether the Trump campaign coordinated with Russia to influence the 2016 presidential election.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Durham gave his final report to the Justice Department, which released it Monday afternoon. The report spans more than 300 pages.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Durham said his investigation also revealed that "senior FBI personnel displayed a serious lack of analytical rigor towards the information that they received, especially information received from politically-affiliated persons and entities."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Durham is referring to past FBI leadership in his report &ndash; specifically former FBI Director James Comey and former FBI Deputy Director Andrew McCabe.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Reacting to the report, the FBI said in a statement: "The conduct in 2016 and 2017 that Special Counsel Durham examined was the reason that current FBI leadership already implemented dozens of corrective actions, which have now been in place for some time. Had those reforms been in place in 2016, the missteps identified in the report could have been prevented. This report reinforces the importance of ensuring the FBI continues to do its work with the rigor, objectivity, and professionalism the American people deserve and rightly expect."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Still, Durham said there is a "continuing need for the FBI and the Department to recognize that lack of analytical rigor, apparent confirmation bias, and an over-willigness to rely on information from individuals connected to political opponents caused investigators to fail to adequately consider alternative hypotheses and to act without appropriate objectivity or restraint in pursuing allegations of collusion or conspiracy between a U.S. political campaign and a foreign power."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Special Counsel Robert Mueller completed his investigation into a possible Trump-Russia connection in April 2019, which yielded no evidence of criminal conspiracy or coordination between the Trump campaign and Russia to influence the 2016 election.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Durham indicted three people as part of his investigation: former Clinton attorney Michael Sussmann in September 2021, Igor Danchenko in November 2021 and Kevin Clinesmith in August 2020.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">And now this!!!</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://www.conservativereview.com/netflix-s-woke-queen-cleopatra-bombs-gets-2-average-audience-score-2660240969.html"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.conservativereview.com/netflix-s-woke-queen-cleopatra-bombs-gets-2-average-audience-score-2660240969.html</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Netflix's woke 'Queen Cleopatra' bombs, gets 2% average audience score</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Cleopatra, the last ruler of Ptolemaic Egypt, is said to have killed herself with poison. Netflix's new series about the historic figure similarly did itself in, albeit by other means.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The series, which debuted on May 10 and is #6 in Netflix's Top 10 list, presently has a 2% average audience score on Rotten Tomatoes and an average critic score of 11%.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The show did not fare better with reviewers on IMDB, where it has a 1.1 out of 10 rating. As of the time of publication, 94.2% (around 37,000) of the approximately 39,000 ratings the show received gave it the lowest possible review.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Forbes noted, "Fans usually rate things higher than critics, even bad shows, and the point being, a 1% audience score seems borderline mathematically impossible, even with the controversy the film has attracted."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">While Adele James may be a talented dramatist, the decision to cast the black actress in the role and the show's corresponding ahistorical framing have proven contentious in recent months.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">TheBlaze previously reported that after the trailer for the show was released, the project was widely lambasted on social media for portraying the historical figure as black. Cleopatra was of Macedonian Greek descent.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">"From Executive Producer Jada Pinkett Smith comes a new documentary series exploring the lives of prominent and iconic African Queens," reads the description of the movie from the Netflix YouTube account.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">A voiceover in the trailer says, "I remember my grandmother saying to me, 'I don&rsquo;t care what they tell you in school. Cleopatra was black.'"</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The casting decision was widely criticized, especially in light of the claim that the series would be a documentary &mdash; and therefore correspond in some way with historical reality.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">One popular response to the announcement read, "Egypt is diverse in skin colors, there&rsquo;s no one Egyptian look so you could do a documentary about black Egyptian rulers but Cleopatra was of Greek ancestry and presenting her story as a battle between native Egyptians and the oppressive Roman tyrants is extremely anachronistic."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The BBC reported that Zahi Hawass, a prominent Egyptologist and former antiquities minister, spoke out against the show, saying, "This is completely fake. Cleopatra was Greek, meaning that she was light-skinned, not black."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">"Netflix is trying to provoke confusion by spreading false and deceptive facts that the origin of the Egyptian civilisation is black," added Hawass, who indicated that the only known black rulers of Egypt were the Kushite kings of the 26th Dynasty (747-656 B.C.).</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Others accused the streaming service of cultural appropriation and historical revisionism.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">While some argued that any actor could play the role, Jada Pinkett Smith, an executive producer and narrator on the project, said of the casting decision, "We don't often get to see or hear stories about black queens, and that was really important for me."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Tina Gharvi, the show's director, made clear ahead of time that her intentions were ideological.</span></p>]]></description>
   <author><![CDATA[Garrison Hardie]]></author>
   <enclosure url="https://app.dropwave.io/episode/eb2cc10c-b7a7-4c24-aeeb-4154e3fab6b7/crosspolitic-daily-news-brief-for-tuesday-may-16th-2023.mp3" length="719" type="audio/mp3"/>
   <guid isPermaLink="false"><![CDATA[eb2cc10c-b7a7-4c24-aeeb-4154e3fab6b7]]></guid>
   <pubDate>Tue, 16 May 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
   <source url=""><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></source>
   <itunes:author><![CDATA[Garrison Hardie]]></itunes:author>
   <itunes:image href="https://assets-cdn2.dropwave.io/2ab40ac0-e99d-4f25-a6d2-541d2c9b290a/cover-art/hUZu1H9lrRY0wXg66WHC8eLwYBA3hbRNTAHQmHt2.png"/>
   <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
   <itunes:duration>719</itunes:duration>
   <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
  
  </item><item>
   <title><![CDATA[CrossPolitic Daily News Brief for Friday, May 12th, 2023 [Daily News Brief]]]></title>
   <link>https://app.dropwave.io/episode/dd8d4133-255d-4445-a0b4-aade324fe060/crosspolitic-daily-news-brief-for-friday-may-12th-2023-1.mp3</link>
   <description><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">This is Garrison Hardie with your CrossPolitic Daily News Brief for Friday, May 12th, 2023.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>Concordis Education Partners:</strong></span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Classical Christian education has reminded us to aim education at truth, but the trivium has been used as a formula rather than a way of training students in discernment.&nbsp;&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">To teach well, you must coach.&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">&nbsp;</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Concordis Foundation is offering their third annual BOOT CAMP &ndash; a faculty summit &ndash; July 11-13th in Moscow, Idaho.&nbsp; This is a three-day intensive teaching training where you learn to coach students, using the trivium, so that you can meet students at all learning levels.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">&nbsp;</span></p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Learn more at</span><a href="https://concordispartners.com/"><span style="font-weight: 400;"> </span><span style="font-weight: 400;">concordispartners.com</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;">&nbsp;&nbsp;</span></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://www.foxnews.com/politics/border-patrol-chief-authorizes-release-migrants-us-without-court-dates-title-42-ends"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.foxnews.com/politics/border-patrol-chief-authorizes-release-migrants-us-without-court-dates-title-42-ends</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>Border Patrol chief authorizes release of migrants into US without court dates as Title 42 ends</strong></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The head of U.S. Border Patrol has sent out a memo authorizing the release of illegal migrants into the U.S. without court dates if agents face overcrowding as the Biden administration scrambles to deal with a historic surge in migration at the border ahead of the end of Title 42.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The memo says that migrants can be allowed into the country on parole &mdash; a process typically reserved for "urgent humanitarian reasons or significant public benefit" &mdash; if Customs and Border Protection (CBP) faces overcrowding. The memo calls the practice "parole with conditions" as migrants are required to make an appointment with Immigration and Customs Enforcement (ICE) or request a Notice to Appear by mail.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Under a parole release, migrants are rapidly released into the country, do not get an alien registration number and do not receive a court date.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The use of parole is being authorized if a sector capacity goes above 125%, if agents apprehend 7,000 a day over 72 hours or if average time in custody goes above 60 hours.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Agents have been encountering over 10,000 migrants a day since Monday, and there are no signs of that slowing down with the looming end of Title 42, which is expected to bring an even bigger wave with it.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The memo noted the enormous numbers agents are encountering.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">"For the past 7 days, USBP has averaged over 8,750 encounters per day. This is over double the average daily encounters of 4,284 in May of 2019, the highest month of the 2019 surge. Even with significant personnel along the SWB, a significant detention capacity, and interagency resources supporting the effort, this situation requires urgent action," the memo states.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The public health order has been used since March 2020 to expel over two million migrants due to the COVID-19 pandemic. The Biden administration has told migrants that it will not be easier to enter the U.S. once the order drops as there will be stiffer penalties until Title 8. Parole is not a Title 8 authority.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The use of parole is legally questionable, with critics arguing it is not supposed to be used to wave in thousands of migrants. The state of Florida successfully sued the Biden administration in March to block a similar policy, "Parole + ATD."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">On Thursday, Fox Digital reported that Florida sued this week over the latest plan to release migrants into the U.S. interior, saying it is "materially identical" to the policy that the federal court enjoined.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">"Florida seeks a temporary restraining order to preserve the status quo until the parties can brief motions for a preliminary injunction or to postpone the effective date of the new policy," the lawsuit states. "The Biden Administration&rsquo;s behavior, if left unchecked, makes a mockery of our system of justice and our Constitution."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The judge has given the Biden administration a 4 p.m. deadline Thursday to respond to the request for a temporary restraining order, adding that it appears the administration is "preparing to flout" the court&rsquo;s order.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">A Department of Homeland Security (DHS) spokesperson this week claimed that the releases are similar to those conducted by prior administrations.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://thepostmillennial.com/breaking-house-votes-yes-on-measure-to-secure-us-mexico-border?utm_campaign=64487"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://thepostmillennial.com/breaking-house-votes-yes-on-measure-to-secure-us-mexico-border?utm_campaign=64487</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>House votes YES on Secure Border Act in 219-213 vote, includes e-Verify requirement, with 2 Republicans joining Democrats to vote against border security</strong></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">On Thursday, House Representatives debated the Secure the Border Act of 2023 as Title 42 expired at the southern border, which lays out sweeping new requirements and restrictions for securing the southern border.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The bill passed 219-213. Two Republicans, Reps. Thomas Massie and John Duarte voted along side all Democrat members against the bill.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The bill was introduced to the House of Representatives on May 2 in anticipation of the flood of illegal immigrants expected in the wake of Title 42, which allowed expulsions due to the pandemic emergency.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The bill calls for the "immediate resumption of border wall construction" no later than seven days after the bill is enacted, using previously set aside funds and materials for its construction.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">No later than 180 days after the bill is enacted, a report shall be submitted to congressional committees that outlines a strategic 5-year technology investment plan for border security, including potential upgrades in security technology, communications equipment, screening equipment, incorporating in input from the private sector.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">In an effort to retain Border Patrol personnel, the bill will authorize up to $100,000,000 in appropriated funds for the Commissioner of the US Customs and Border Protection to give to front-line agents who hold a position equal to or below level GS-12, has been with Border Patrol for five years or longer, and commits two additional years of service with Border Patrol upon acceptance of the bonus.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The bill also requires that the Commissioner hire and train enough Border Patrol agents to maintain an active duty presence of no less than 22,000 full-time agents.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The bill also includes a provision prohibiting the requirement to take a Covid-19 vaccine or adverse actions taken against a Department of Homeland Security employee.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The Secretary of Homeland Security would be required to send a report no later than 60 days after the bill is enacted on whether Mexican drug cartels meet the criteria for being designated as a foreign terrorist organization.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The bill amends the Immigration and Nationality Act, stating that those found not to be eligible for parole shall be deported from the country.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The bill also increases penalties for illegal entry or presence in the country from $50-$250 up to $500-$1000.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Illegal immigrants who overstay a visa are subject to imprisonment of no more than six months and/or a fine for the first offense, and a fine and/or no more than two years of imprisonment for subsequent offenses.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The bill also mandates the use of e-Verify, a system used to check if a person is authorized to work in the United States.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/policy/education/connecticut-wesleyan-pay-for-students-abortions"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/policy/education/connecticut-wesleyan-pay-for-students-abortions</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>Connecticut liberal arts college says it will pay for students to get abortions</strong></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">A liberal arts university in Connecticut says it will now cover the costs of any student who wishes to get an abortion or a Plan B contraceptive, regardless of their insurance status.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Wesleyan University announced last week that, following a pressure campaign from the university's Young Democratic Socialists of America chapter, the school would now pay for any student to get an abortion or emergency contraceptives. The school has also committed to footing the bill for any transportation costs incurred by students seeking abortions.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">&ldquo;Consistent with the health center&rsquo;s mission to provide education and support in the decision-making process, students will be able to access emergency contraceptives by consulting with a nurse at Davison Health Center," the university told NBC Connecticut in a statement.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The decision comes after the Young Democratic Socialists of America chapter at Wesleyan collected over 700 signatures on a petition that urged the school to "ensure all students are able to overcome financial burdens to and lack of transportation for abortion procedures."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">"This victory comes in the wake of landmark efforts by Barnard College students to secure abortion pills on campus as well as a broader movement for reproductive justice nationwide," the student organization said in a press release. "Wesleyan now plays a pioneering role in reproductive healthcare among private liberal arts colleges by committing to cover the entire cost of abortion after insurance for all students."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">After the Supreme Court issued a ruling that overturned Roe v. Wade last year, the availability of abortion for college students has gained increased attention, as numerous states with widely recognized state universities have banned abortion altogether. Students have increasingly reported that access to abortion has become a factor in their college decision-making process.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Democratic-controlled states, meanwhile, have taken steps to make abortion as available to college students as a flu shot.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The entire University of California and California State University systems are required by law to provide abortion pills to students at their respective university health centers, and last year, the University of Massachusetts Amherst announced it would be providing abortion pills on campus as well.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://www.foxnews.com/us/marine-veteran-charged-manhattan-da-jordan-neely-subway-chokehold-death"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.foxnews.com/us/marine-veteran-charged-manhattan-da-jordan-neely-subway-chokehold-death</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>Marine veteran to be charged by Manhattan DA in Jordan Neely subway chokehold death</strong></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">A New York City subway rider accused of choking a homeless man to death is expected to turn himself in to police on Friday morning to face a manslaughter charge.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">"We can confirm that Daniel Penny will be arrested on a charge of Manslaughter in the Second Degree," a spokesperson for the Manhattan District Attorney's Office said. "We cannot provide any additional information until he has been arraigned in Manhattan Criminal Court, which we expect to take place tomorrow."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">On May 1, Penny, a 24-year-old Marine veteran and college student, put 30-year-old Jordan Neely in a fatal chokehold after what police described as an altercation on a northbound F train.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Neely was allegedly threatening passengers on the subway and having a mental episode. He was yelling and pacing back and forth, when Penny interjected, tackled him to the ground and put him in a chokehold, witnesses and police said.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The incident sparked protests and violent clashes last week after the Marine veteran was taken into custody and released.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">And now for my favorite topic&hellip; sports!</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://www.boundingintosports.com/2023/05/prosecutors-confirm-former-buffalo-bills-punter-matt-araiza-was-not-present-when-alleged-gang-rape-occurred/"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.boundingintosports.com/2023/05/prosecutors-confirm-former-buffalo-bills-punter-matt-araiza-was-not-present-when-alleged-gang-rape-occurred/</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>Prosecutors Confirm Former Buffalo Bills Punter Matt Araiza Was Not Present When Alleged Gang Rape Occurred</strong></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">After having the criminal charges against him dropped, former Buffalo Bills punter Matt Araiza now has to undergo a stressful process of fighting the civil lawsuit against him for an alleged gang rape at a college party that occurred when Arazia and the plaintiff were attending San Diego State University at the same time.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">However, based on new information, that might be over soon, and potentially in Araiza&rsquo;s favor.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">During a nearly year long investigation by San Diego police and detailed review by prosecutors, they have come to the conclusion that the alleged gang rape that the female plaintiff accused Araiza of being part of stands in question since evidence shows that Arazia, then a college student at the time when the plaintiff was 17-years-old, was not even present during the alleged crime.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Yahoo Sports has obtained a 200-plus page transcript, covering a meeting in which a San Diego deputy district attorney broke the back of the case.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">According Yahoo Sports&rsquo; summary, &ldquo;Araiza couldn&rsquo;t have led the girl into the alleged gang rape because he had &lsquo;left&rsquo; the home at about 12:30 a.m., an hour prior to when evidence suggested the alleged gang rape would have occurred.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Deputy district attorney Trisha Amador stated that &ldquo;He wasn&rsquo;t even at the party anymore. All I know is that at that point, suspect Araiza is gone from the party.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Prosecutors additionally told the plaintiff that the recordings that were made of the situation &ldquo;made it impossible&rdquo; to identify Araiza or any other potential suspects since their faces and voices aren&rsquo;t clear enough to make a prosecution.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Further, there are questions as to whether a rape occurred at all as the plaintiff claimed, and not a consensual sexual situation.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">&ldquo;In looking at the videos on the sex tape, I absolutely cannot prove any forceable sexual assault based upon what happened,&rdquo; said Deputy DA Amador.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Because of this lawsuit, then-rookie Araiza was cut from the Bills team, crippling his rookie season so he could &ldquo;take care of this situation,&rdquo; according to Buffalo general manager Brandon Beane.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">But Araiza isn&rsquo;t out of the woods yet, despite the prosecutors themselves admitting he wasn&rsquo;t present at the event &ndash; civil suits have a much lower standard of proof than criminal cases do.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">As news broke of the developments in the civil suit, online figures in sports and media began to defend Arazia, including Daily Wire columnist Matt Walsh and Outkick.com founder Clay Travis.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">&ldquo;False rape accusers should receive the same penalty that we give to rapists,&rdquo; Walsh posted to Twitter. &ldquo;Instead, in a vast majority of cases, they receive no penalty at all and are free to move on like nothing happened.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">&ldquo;The Bills released punter Matt Araiza for an allegation of sexual assault that police proved was 100% a lie,&rdquo; tweeted Travis. &ldquo;Why shouldn&rsquo;t his accuser face criminal charges for lying? He&rsquo;s lost a year of his career &amp; his good name. She has zero consequences. Not right.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Thanks to all the legal trouble, Araiza is still a free agent. We&rsquo;ve seen plenty of comebacks from legal trouble in the National Felon League. Araiza could be the next to move on to a respectable career.</span></p>]]></description>
   <author><![CDATA[Garrison Hardie]]></author>
   <enclosure url="https://app.dropwave.io/episode/dd8d4133-255d-4445-a0b4-aade324fe060/crosspolitic-daily-news-brief-for-friday-may-12th-2023-1.mp3" length="813" type="audio/mp3"/>
   <guid isPermaLink="false"><![CDATA[dd8d4133-255d-4445-a0b4-aade324fe060]]></guid>
   <pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
   <source url=""><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></source>
   <itunes:author><![CDATA[Garrison Hardie]]></itunes:author>
   <itunes:image href="https://assets-cdn2.dropwave.io/2ab40ac0-e99d-4f25-a6d2-541d2c9b290a/cover-art/hUZu1H9lrRY0wXg66WHC8eLwYBA3hbRNTAHQmHt2.png"/>
   <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
   <itunes:duration>813</itunes:duration>
   <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
  </item>
 </channel>
</rss>
