<?xml version="1.0"?>
<?xml-stylesheet href="/storage/feed-stylesheet.xsl" type="text/xsl"?>

<rss xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
 <channel>
  <title>FLF - Daily News Brief</title>
  <link>https://dropwave.io</link>
  <description><![CDATA[FIGHT LAUGH FEAST PRESENTS SHOWS PROCLAIMING THE LORDSHIP OF CHRIST OVER ALL OF LIFE.
]]></description>
  <language>en</language>
  <managingEditor><![CDATA[fightlaughfeast@gmail.com (FLF, LLC)]]></managingEditor>
  <webMaster><![CDATA[support@dropwave.io (DropWave Support)]]></webMaster>
  <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2023 07:25:47 +0000</pubDate>
  <lastBuildDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2023 07:25:47 +0000</lastBuildDate>
  <image>
   <url>https://is4-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Podcasts113/v4/58/56/52/5856525c-2973-cf29-3db9-21faa8595391/mza_1144696925612154085.png/1200x1200bb.jpg</url>
   <link>https://dropwave.io</link>
   <title><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></title>
  </image>
  <itunes:author><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></itunes:author>
  <itunes:image href="https://is4-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Podcasts113/v4/58/56/52/5856525c-2973-cf29-3db9-21faa8595391/mza_1144696925612154085.png/1200x1200bb.jpg"/>
  <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
  <itunes:owner>
   <itunes:name><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></itunes:name>
   <itunes:email>fightlaughfeast@gmail.com</itunes:email>
  </itunes:owner>
  <itunes:category text="News"/>
  <item>
   <title><![CDATA[CrossPolitic Daily News Brief for Thursday, July 27th, 2023 [Daily News Brief]]]></title>
   <link>https://app.dropwave.io/episode/4b15b356-ce83-4852-969e-37f76652a1fe/crosspolitic-daily-news-brief-for-thursday-july-27th-2023.mp3</link>
   <description><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">This is Garrison Hardie with your CrossPolitic Daily News Brief for Thursday, July 27th, 2023.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>Olive Tree Biblical Software:</strong></span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Discover why more than a million people use the free Olive Tree Bible App as their go-to for reading, studying, and listening to the God&rsquo;s Word.&nbsp;&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Start by downloading one of many free Bibles and start taking notes, highlighting verses, and bookmarking your favorite passages. You can read at your own pace, or choose from a large selection of Reading Plans, including the Bible Reading Challenge. When you are ready to go deeper into your studies, Olive Tree is right there with a large selection of study Bibles, commentaries, and other helpful study resources available for purchase. There&rsquo;s also an extensive bookstore allows you to build your digital library one book at a time and Olive Tree&rsquo;s sync technology lets you pick up where you left off on your tablet, pc or phone and get right to studying on another supported device.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">&nbsp;</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Now here's the best part &ndash; You can start with the Olive Tree Essentials Bundle for FREE. Visit www.olivetree.com/FLF and download it today! </span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://apnews.com/article/ufos-uaps-congress-whistleblower-spy-aliens-ba8a8cfba353d7b9de29c3d906a69ba7"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://apnews.com/article/ufos-uaps-congress-whistleblower-spy-aliens-ba8a8cfba353d7b9de29c3d906a69ba7</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>Whistleblower tells Congress the US is concealing &lsquo;multi-decade&rsquo; program that captures UFOs</strong></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The U.S. is concealing a longstanding program that retrieves and reverse engineers unidentified flying objects, a former Air Force intelligence officer testified Wednesday to Congress. The Pentagon has denied his claims.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Retired Maj. David Grusch&rsquo;s highly anticipated testimony before a House Oversight subcommittee was Congress&rsquo; latest foray into the world of UAPs &mdash; or &ldquo;unidentified aerial phenomena,&rdquo; which is the official term the U.S. government uses instead of UFOs. While the study of mysterious aircraft or objects often evokes talk of aliens and &ldquo;little green men,&rdquo; Democrats and Republicans in recent years have pushed for more research as a national security matter due to concerns that sightings observed by pilots may be tied to U.S. adversaries.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Grusch said he was asked in 2019 by the head of a government task force on UAPs to identify all highly classified programs relating to the task force&rsquo;s mission. At the time, Grusch was detailed to the National Reconnaissance Office, the agency that operates U.S. spy satellites.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">&ldquo;I was informed in the course of my official duties of a multi-decade UAP crash retrieval and reverse engineering program to which I was denied access,&rdquo; he said.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Asked whether the U.S. government had information about extraterrestrial life, Grusch said the U.S. likely has been aware of &ldquo;non-human&rdquo; activity since the 1930s.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The Pentagon has denied Grusch&rsquo;s claims of a coverup. In a statement, Defense Department spokeswoman Sue Gough said investigators have not discovered &ldquo;any verifiable information to substantiate claims that any programs regarding the possession or reverse-engineering of extraterrestrial materials have existed in the past or exist currently.&rdquo; The statement did not address UFOs that are not suspected of being extraterrestrial objects.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Grusch says he became a government whistleblower after his discovery and has faced retaliation for coming forward. He declined to be more specific about the retaliatory tactics, citing an ongoing investigation.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://hotair.com/david-strom/2023/07/26/swiss-study-heart-injuries-from-covid-vaccine-3000x-higher-than-thought-n567151"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://hotair.com/david-strom/2023/07/26/swiss-study-heart-injuries-from-covid-vaccine-3000x-higher-than-thought-n567151</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>Swiss study: heart injuries from COVID vaccine 3000x higher than thought</strong></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">It is a small study, but a very disturbing one.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">In fact, in a study with only 777 participants with a median age of 37--all medical professionals getting the COVID vaccine&ndash;the incidence of elevated cardiac enzymes 3 days after injection was pretty substantial, at almost 3%.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The CDC did a study and from that, they claimed the rate was 0.001%, or one out of 100,000.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">2.8% is a lot higher than 0.001%. Another 0.3% had &ldquo;probable myocarditis,&rdquo; putting the total at over 3%. That is 3000 times higher than the US government claimed.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">In this small study, nobody had serious complications, but with a myocarditis complication rate of 3%, you would have to expect that giving out hundreds of millions of doses is a pretty risky proposition.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">I think we all knew that already, but this study seems to put the nail in the coffin of &ldquo;vaccine injuries are super rare&rdquo; from COVID-19 shots.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">One oddity was that the rate of myocarditis among the participants was heavily weighted toward women, not men. That could be an artifact of the sample, or it could indicate that women are more likely to get a complication, but the complications are more likely to be serious among men.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">One reason the researchers posit for the vast difference between their results&ndash;which are based upon blood tests looking for cardiac enzymes in all participants&ndash;and the commonly asserted claim that vaccine-induced myocarditis is rare is that the only cases that are diagnosed without looking specifically for it are severe.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">In other words, most people don&rsquo;t go to the doctor until there is a serious problem, so many people suffer from myocarditis without ever getting diagnosed.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">This suggests that there is a very large group of people who were afflicted but never treated. This in most cases would not be a huge problem, as the inflammation resolves on its own, but in some cases, actual damage to the heart was done without it ever being caught.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">In any case, this study sheds quite a light on just how deceptive the CDC, the FDA, and NIAID have been about vaccine safety. And also how intentionally ignorant they have chosen to be. This was not a complicated study to do. The researchers chose a cohort easy to recruit, tested them both before and after vaccination to create a baseline and comparison, and analyzed the data.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://www.foxnews.com/politics/hunter-biden-plea-deal-appears-fall-apart-first-court-appearance"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.foxnews.com/politics/hunter-biden-plea-deal-appears-fall-apart-first-court-appearance</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>Hunter Biden pleads 'not guilty' as plea deal falls apart during Delaware court appearance</strong></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Hunter Biden's plea deal fell apart during his first court appearance Wednesday morning and pleaded "not guilty" as federal prosecutors confirmed the president's son is still under federal investigation.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The president's son was expected to plead guilty to two misdemeanor tax counts of willful failure to pay federal income tax, as part of plea deal to avoid jail time on a felony gun charge.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">But Judge Maryellen Noreika did not accept the plea agreement, questioning the constitutionality--specifically the diversion clause and the immunity Hunter Biden would receive.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Hunter Biden was also expected to enter into a pretrial diversion agreement regarding a separate felony charge of possession of a firearm by a person who is an unlawful user of or addicted to a controlled substance.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">House Ways &amp; Means Committee Chairman Jason Smith filed an amicus brief to the court, requesting that testimony be considered ahead of accepting the planned plea deal, saying Hunter Biden "appears to have benefited from political interference which calls into question the propriety of the investigation of the U.S. Attorney&rsquo;s Office."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">"In the interest of full transparency and fairness for all citizens, it is critical for the Court to have this relevant information when evaluating the Plea Agreement," Smith wrote in the brief.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Meanwhile, on the eve of the court appearance, the judge threatened to sanction Hunter Biden's legal team after one of his attorneys allegedly lied about who she was while asking to remove IRS whistleblower testimony from the court docket.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The defense, though, denied the allegations and called the incident "an unfortunate and unintentional miscommunication."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/news/new-york-city-crane-falls-engulfed-flames"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/news/new-york-city-crane-falls-engulfed-flames</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>New York City crane collapse: Construction equipment tumbles to ground as it is engulfed in flames</strong></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">A crane fell near the Hell's Kitchen neighborhood of Manhattan on Wednesday after a fire broke out on the construction equipment, but officials say it could have been much worse.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The crane was engulfed in flames before part of it fell to the ground, hitting a nearby building in the process. The New York City Fire Department said that six people, including two firefighters, have injuries. The injuries to the two firefighters are "non-life threatening," while the four civilian injuries are "minor," according to the department.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">"As you see from the debris on the street, this could have been much worse. We are extremely fortunate, No. 1, that [it was] not during the busy time of the day &mdash; as you know, the Port Authority is here. Many of the buses move through here. We were extremely fortunate," New York City Mayor Eric Adams said at a press conference.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The first report of the fire to FDNY came at 7:25 a.m. local time, with officials saying the fire started in the engine compartment of the crane. The top part of the crane and a 16-ton load collapsed as firefighters were arriving at the scene. One of the injuries was described as "chest pains" for one of the firefighters.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">At a news conference Wednesday morning, fire officials said the fire had been mostly extinguished but that operations are still ongoing. Fifty units, totaling 220 fire personnel, responded to the scene of the fire, according to FDNY.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">New York City Department of Buildings Commissioner Jimmy Oddo said the building where the crane fire occurred was an under-construction 54-story mixed-use building, which had all proper permits filed. Oddo said the only previous incident at the site was when construction workers hit a vault during excavation for the building.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">City officials also said the crane operator had attempted to put out the fire when he noticed it, but when he was unable to do so safely, he evacuated from the crane and is OK.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://thenationalpulse.com/2023/07/25/accept-deadly-blackouts-to-fight-climate-change-says-paper/"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://thenationalpulse.com/2023/07/25/accept-deadly-blackouts-to-fight-climate-change-says-paper/</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>Accept Deadly Blackouts to Fight &lsquo;Climate Change&rsquo;, Says Paper</strong></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The Los Angeles Times says that blackouts have to increase in order to combat climate change, while stunningly acknowledging the policy may cost people&rsquo;s lives. The newspaper has asked its dwindling audience to consider &ldquo;a larger conversation&rdquo; in which people become more accustomed to changing their expectations, including the idea of living without electricity for large parts of their lives so as to prevent &ldquo;climate catastrophe.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The piece also insists that &ldquo;fossil-funded lies,&rdquo; apparently spread by Republicans &ndash; such as the overall uselessness of solar farms and wind turbines &ndash; should not be considered within the discussion on how to address climate change. Instead, the conversation must be orientated towards adding &ldquo;solar panels, wind turbines and all kinds of energy storage to the grid as fast as possible.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The newspaper also recognizes the risk of such a policy as it reports that someone dies every time there is a blackout, and includes a quote from the director of reliability assessment and performance analysis at the North American Electric Reliability Corp, John Moura, that &ldquo;it&rsquo;s not really about keeping the lights on. It&rsquo;s about keeping people alive.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Accepting increased blackouts is yet another extreme measure being suggested to tackle climate change. One recent study suggested changing working hours from 9 am to 5 am to 6 am to 2 pm.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Speaking of climate change&hellip;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://www.theblaze.com/news/npr-ridiculed-for-regurgitating-claim-that-the-movement-to-push-bug-food-on-the-masses-is-a-racist-conspiracy-theory"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.theblaze.com/news/npr-ridiculed-for-regurgitating-claim-that-the-movement-to-push-bug-food-on-the-masses-is-a-racist-conspiracy-theory</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>NPR ridiculed for regurgitating claim that the movement to push bug food on the masses is a 'racist' conspiracy theory</strong></span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">NPR's race-obsessed and taxpayer-subsidized show "Code Switch" recently peddled the notion that it is conspiratorial thinking to take proponents of the bug-food movement at their word.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">What's more, host Gene Demby's guest on the July 19 episode, entitled "This right wing conspiracy theory about eating bugs is about as racist as you think," has intimated that criticism both of bug food and of those technocrats who seek to alter consumer behavior may be racist.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">NPR has since been met with ridicule by those aware that the desire to supplement or replace normal food with bugs is not a conspiracy theory but rather a real initiative with substantial momentum, which has been long detailed and defended in academic journals, trusted publications, and even on NPR.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">NPR reporter Huo Jingnan joined "Code Switch" host Gene Demby on last week's episode to regurgitate talking points from his April NPR article, wherein he simultaneously held that the claim that "elites want people to eat bugs" was a right-wing conspiracy theory while also acknowledging the inclusion of bugs in human food was "an emerging, but still marginal, idea among climate scientists and food security experts."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Jingnan hinted both in his article and on Demby's show there must also be a racial component to the growing concerns about the bug-food movement and the motivations driving it.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">While Demby appeared keen to write off the bug-food movement as "not that big a deal," and Jingnan intimated that it might just the MAGA crowd who are paying attention, critics have pointed that NPR's publication history suggests otherwise.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Here are the titles of just a few NPR features in recent months and years:</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">"These Pictures Might Tempt You To Eat Bugs" &mdash; July 18, 2013;</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">"Making Food From Flies (It's Not That Icky)" &mdash; Sept. 19, 2013;</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">"Even Neil DeGrasse Tyson Is Now Munching On Bugs" &mdash; March 23, 2015;</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">"Street Food No More: Bug Snacks Move To Store Shelves In Thailand" &mdash; April 15, 2015;</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">"Are Insects The Future Of Food?" &mdash; Nov. 17, 2016;</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">"At Bug-Eating Festival, Kids Crunch Down On The Food Of The Future" &mdash; Sept. 14, 2017;</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">"Your Ancestors Probably Ate Insects. So What's Bugging You?" &mdash; July 16, 2018;</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">"VIDEO: 4 Ways That Wild Edibles, Including Insects, Will Wow You" &mdash; Dec. 20, 2018; and</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">"Should Hyping Edible Bugs Focus On The Experience Instead Of The Environment?" &mdash; Jan. 10, 2019.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The food of the future indeed&hellip;&nbsp;</span></p>]]></description>
   <author><![CDATA[Garrison Hardie]]></author>
   <enclosure url="https://app.dropwave.io/episode/4b15b356-ce83-4852-969e-37f76652a1fe/crosspolitic-daily-news-brief-for-thursday-july-27th-2023.mp3" length="842" type="audio/mp3"/>
   <guid isPermaLink="false"><![CDATA[4b15b356-ce83-4852-969e-37f76652a1fe]]></guid>
   <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
   <source url=""><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></source>
   <itunes:author><![CDATA[Garrison Hardie]]></itunes:author>
   <itunes:image href="https://assets-cdn2.dropwave.io/2ab40ac0-e99d-4f25-a6d2-541d2c9b290a/cover-art/mUK8zsnHkCK3vep7E1W6UgYb9dTnLenASAMEFha3.jpg"/>
   <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
   <itunes:duration>842</itunes:duration>
   <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
  
  </item><item>
   <title><![CDATA[Daily News Brief for Wednesday, July 26th, 2023 [Daily News Brief]]]></title>
   <link>https://app.dropwave.io/episode/ae0c9ac6-2363-4677-853c-3b4d38a04c77/daily-news-brief-for-wednesday-july-26th-2023.mp3</link>
   <description><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">This is Garrison Hardie with your CrossPolitic Daily News Brief for Wednesday, July 26th, 2023.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>PUB MEMBERSHIP PLUG:</strong></span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Summer has been great here at CrossPolitic, and we want you to join us on this ride&hellip; First, we&rsquo;re no longer calling it the Fight Laugh Feast club&hellip; it&rsquo;s now called the Pub! Second, we are launching a new line of content, focused on family entertainment. We will have our new show &ldquo;This America&rdquo; and our exciting new &ldquo;Rowdy Christian Guides&rdquo; highlighting the practical guides to fun and godly life! Additionally, we will have the live streaming of our conferences, and our past conference talks, all bundled within our new polished Fight Laugh Feast App. Sign up today! Head on over to fightlaughfeast.com, and join the Pub! that&rsquo;s fightlaughfeast.com.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://thepostmillennial.com/breaking-biden-admin-launches-permanent-pandemic-preparedness-office?utm_campaign=64487"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://thepostmillennial.com/breaking-biden-admin-launches-permanent-pandemic-preparedness-office?utm_campaign=64487</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>Biden admin launches PERMANENT pandemic preparedness office</strong></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">President Joe Biden has created a permanent office for pandemic response. Called the Office of Pandemic Preparedness and Response Policy, the new office within the executive branch replaces the Covid-19 response team that Biden ushered in during his first days in the White House.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">This new office will ensure that the Biden administration can continue to implement so-called pandemic mitigation strategies for any new communicable disease that comes down the pike.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">"This will be a permanent office in the Executive Office of the President (EOP)," the White House offers in a briefing, "charged with leading, coordinating, and implementing actions related to preparedness for, and response to, known and unknown biological threats or pathogens that could lead to a pandemic or to significant public health-related disruptions in the United States."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">This office replaces those set up for both Covid and the oddly named Mpox, so called because its original name, Monkey Pox, was deemed to be racist by Democrats who believe that in some way "monkey" is racist against black people.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The new team, led by retired Major General Paul Friedrichs, will "continue to coordinate and develop policies and priorities related to pandemic preparedness and response."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">This office will be primarily responsible to the executive branch, and will "drive and coordinate federal science and technology efforts related to pandemic preparedness." What this entails in specific is the overseeing of "efforts to develop, manufacture, and procure the next generation of medical countermeasures, including leveraging emerging technologies and working with HHS on next generation vaccines and treatments for COVID-19 and other public health threats."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The administration also took the opportunity to tout its efforts during the Covid pandemic, which began when a virus created through gain-of-function research leaked from a Wuhan, China lab that was funded in part by the National Institutes of Health.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">It was also during the Biden administration's pandemic response that Americans were encouraged to not leave their homes, to shut down churches and schools while leaving casinos, liquor stores, and Walmarts open, and to mandate the wearing of face coverings that later studies revealed were steeped with bacteria. Under Biden's watch, newly-created vaccines were mandated both for federal employees and the employees of companies that contracted with the federal government.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">This is the kind of pandemic response the new Office of Pandemic Preparedness and Response Policy will be ready to implement as soon as the next potential pandemic comes along.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://www.theguardian.com/environment/2023/jul/24/greta-thunberg-fined-for-disobeying-swedish-police-at-climate-protest"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.theguardian.com/environment/2023/jul/24/greta-thunberg-fined-for-disobeying-swedish-police-at-climate-protest</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>Greta Thunberg fined for disobeying Swedish police at climate protest</strong></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Greta Thunberg has been fined by a Swedish court after she was found guilty of disobeying a police order to leave a climate protest.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The 20-year-old climate activist, who from 2018 became the face of the youth climate movement, had admitted taking part in the protest in Malm&ouml; in June, but pleaded not guilty on the grounds she had acted out of necessity.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">&ldquo;My actions are justifiable,&rdquo; Thunberg told the court in Malm&ouml;, according to local media. &ldquo;I believe that we are in an emergency that threatens life, health and property. Countless people and communities are at risk both in the short term and in the long term.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Five years ago, Thunberg, then 15, began skipping school each Friday and staging solo climate protests outside the Swedish parliament in Stockholm, holding up a sign reading: &ldquo;Skolstrejk f&ouml;r klimatet&rdquo; (school strike for climate).</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Her weekly demonstrations snowballed into a global wave of youth climate protest, as she gained fame for her youth and her blunt speaking on the dire future faced by young people staring down the barrel of the climate crisis.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Although the school strikes movement lost some of its momentum with the outbreak of the coronavirus pandemic, Thunberg has continued to travel the world joining climate protests and speaking at international summits, urging world leaders to act on the climate crisis.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">It is believed that Monday&rsquo;s trial is her first conviction for climate protest.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Thunberg was part of a group of protesters that blocked the road for oil trucks in Malm&ouml; harbour. She was charged for failing to leave when ordered to do so by police.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The fine will be based on Thunberg&rsquo;s reported income and it was not immediately clear how much she would have to pay, Reuters reported.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://newsbusters.org/blogs/nb/tim-graham/2023/07/24/solvency-dies-darkness-washington-post-pace-lose-100-million-year"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://newsbusters.org/blogs/nb/tim-graham/2023/07/24/solvency-dies-darkness-washington-post-pace-lose-100-million-year</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>Washington Post On Pace to Lose $100 Million This Year</strong></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The New York Times buried the lede in a story about Amazon billionaire Jeff Bezos owning The Washington Post. It isn't quite profitable, you learn in the eighth paragraph: "The Post is on a pace to lose about $100 million in 2023, according to two people with knowledge of the company&rsquo;s finances."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The headline doesn't include that eye-grabbing detail. It's just this:</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">A Decade Ago, Jeff Bezos Bought a Newspaper. Now He&rsquo;s Paying Attention to It Again.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The Amazon founder, who purchased The Washington Post for $250 million in 2013, has taken a more active role in the paper&rsquo;s operations this year.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Yes, you can imagine he'd take a "more active role" with this nagging problem. Post employees were delighted a liberal billionaire bought the paper, so they didn't have to be too worried about profits. "Prestige journalism" for the liberals isn't working out right now, even as the paper extends its Trump obsession forward.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://www.newsmax.com/world/globaltalk/russia-lgbtq-transgender-procedures-banned/2023/07/24/id/1128275/"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.newsmax.com/world/globaltalk/russia-lgbtq-transgender-procedures-banned/2023/07/24/id/1128275/</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>Russian President Signs Legislation Marking the Final Step Outlawing Gender-affirming Procedures</strong></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Russian President Vladimir Putin signed new legislation Monday which marked the final step in outlawing gender-affirming procedures, a crippling blow to Russia&rsquo;s already embattled LGBTQ+ community.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The bill, which was approved unanimously by both houses of parliament, bans any &ldquo;medical interventions aimed at changing the sex of a person,&rdquo; as well as changing one&rsquo;s gender in official documents and public records. The only exception will be medical intervention to treat congenital anomalies.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">It also annuls marriages in which one person has &ldquo;changed gender&rdquo; and bars transgender people from becoming foster or adoptive parents.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The ban is said to stem from the Kremlin&rsquo;s crusade to protect what it views as the country&rsquo;s &ldquo;traditional values.&rdquo; Lawmakers say the legislation is to safeguard Russia against &ldquo;Western anti-family ideology,&rdquo; with some describing gender transitioning as &ldquo;pure satanism.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Russia&rsquo;s crackdown on LGBTQ+ people started a decade ago when Putin first proclaimed a focus on &ldquo;traditional family values,&rdquo; supported by the Russian Orthodox Church.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">In 2013, the Kremlin adopted legislation that banned any public endorsement of &ldquo;nontraditional sexual relations&rdquo; among minors. In 2020, Putin pushed through constitutional reform that outlawed same-sex marriage, and last year signed a law banning &ldquo;propaganda of nontraditional sexual relations&rdquo; among adults as well.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://www.breitbart.com/latin-america/2023/07/24/brazil-lula-limits-gun-rights-by-decree-hoping-for-disarmed-country/"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.breitbart.com/latin-america/2023/07/24/brazil-lula-limits-gun-rights-by-decree-hoping-for-disarmed-country/</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>Brazil: Lula Limits Gun Rights by Decree, Hoping for a &lsquo;Disarmed Country&rsquo;</strong></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Brazilian radical leftist President Luiz In&aacute;cio Lula da Silva signed a &ldquo;Responsible Gun Control&rdquo; decree this weekend to further restrict civilian access to firearms, rolling back policies implemented by former President Jair Bolsonaro.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The executive order, signed on Friday at the presidential Planalto Palace, forbids civilians from having access to certain types of firearms, reduces the total legal number of firearms a citizen may own, greatly reduces the annual amount of ammunition that civilians can legally buy, and imposes restrictions on shooting clubs and firearms for hunters, marksmen, and collectors.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The decree also establishes guidelines to transfer authority over the regulation and inspection of civilian firearms from the Brazilian army to the federal police, which will now exercise exclusive power over civilian activities involving weapons and ammunition in cooperation with the nation&rsquo;s Justice and Public Security Ministry.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">In a speech announcing the new regulations, Lula said, &ldquo;we cannot allow there to be arsenals of weapons in the hands of people.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">&ldquo;That is why we will continue to fight for a disarmed country,&rdquo; Lula said. &ldquo;It is the Brazilian police who have to be well armed, it is the Brazilian armed forces who have to be well armed. What we need to lower is the prices of books, and the price of access to cultural things that our children do not have access to.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Brazil&rsquo;s Minister of Justice Fl&aacute;vio Dino said that the new set of rules ends &ldquo;irresponsible armamentism&rdquo; as a result of Bolsonaro&rsquo;s gun rights reforms.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Civilians are now only allowed to purchase up to two firearms for self-defense, down from four, and must comply with a series of requirements to demonstrate proof of self-defense use. The total amount of ammunition that Brazilian citizens can buy per year has been reduced from 200 to 50 bullets.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The decree rolled back reforms Bolsonaro implemented that allowed civilians to purchase 9mm, .40, and .45 Automatic Colt Pistols (ACP), as well as semi-automatic smoothbore firearms. Brazilian citizens can no longer legally obtain these types of firearms.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The decree also reduces the duration of firearm registry permits from ten years to three to five years depending on the firearm&rsquo;s intended use. Active members of Brazil&rsquo;s police and other government security officials, meanwhile, no longer have to abide by any time limit on their permits.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Lula further imposed restrictions on firearms for hunters, marksmen, and collectors, reducing the total number of firearms and ammunition permitted in each category, introducing new required authorization permits for hunters, establishing new sub-categories for sports shooters, and reducing the number of firearms legally allowed for collectors from five of each model down to one weapon of each model, type, brand, variant, caliber, and origin.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">While the decree &ldquo;guarantees&rdquo; legal possession of these types of firearms if previously obtained and properly registered, the Brazilian government announced that it will implement a buyback program for these firearms this year.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The decree also imposes restrictions on sport shooting clubs, prohibiting 24-hour establishments and limiting operating hours from 6 a.m. to 10 p.m. Shooting clubs and instructional businesses must now be located at least one kilometer away from public or private schools, giving existing locations an 18-month grace period to comply with the new ruling.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The new gun control decree is the first part of a broader &ldquo;Security Action Program&rdquo; launched by Lula&rsquo;s administration on Friday. In addition to gun control, the Security Action Program, according to the Brazilian government, seeks to combat school violence, protect the Amazon region, and change regional public fund financing.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The program will also greatly increase penalties for crimes &ldquo;committed against the democratic rule of law,&rdquo; including longer prison sentences for those who organize, finance, or lead &ldquo;anti-democratic movements.&rdquo; It will also reportedly provide for the blocking of bank accounts and seizure of assets of people in whose cases law enforcement finds &ldquo;sufficient evidence of authorship or financing of crimes against the democratic state of law.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Now, to my favorite topic, sports!</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://thepostmillennial.com/breaking-lebron-james-18-year-old-son-suffers-heart-attack-on-basketball-court?utm_campaign=64487"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://thepostmillennial.com/breaking-lebron-james-18-year-old-son-suffers-heart-attack-on-basketball-court?utm_campaign=64487</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>Lebron James' 18-year-old son suffers heart attack on basketball court</strong></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">During a basketball workout at the University of Southern California, basketball legend Lebron James&rsquo; son, Bronny, was rushed to the hospital after suffering cardiac arrest.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">A family spokesperson told TMZ Sports, "Yesterday while practicing Bronny James suffered a cardiac arrest. Medical staff was able to treat Bronny and take him to the hospital. He is now in stable condition and no longer in ICU. We ask for respect and privacy for the James family and we will update media when there is more information."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">"LeBron and Savannah wish to publicly send their deepest thanks and appreciation to the USC medical and athletic staff for their incredible work and dedication to the safety of their athletes," the spokesperson added.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Sources with direct knowledge told the outlet that a 911 call was made at 9:26 am on Monday morning from USC&rsquo;s Galen Center, where the 18-year-old had fallen unconscious. He was taken by ambulance to a nearby hospital.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Sources said that it was a Code 3, in which first responders use lights and sirens during transport, indicating the seriousness of the incident.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Bronny had recently committed to the USC Trojans and is expected to play for the NBA like his father.</span></p>]]></description>
   <author><![CDATA[Garrison Hardie]]></author>
   <enclosure url="https://app.dropwave.io/episode/ae0c9ac6-2363-4677-853c-3b4d38a04c77/daily-news-brief-for-wednesday-july-26th-2023.mp3" length="806" type="audio/mp3"/>
   <guid isPermaLink="false"><![CDATA[ae0c9ac6-2363-4677-853c-3b4d38a04c77]]></guid>
   <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jul 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
   <source url=""><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></source>
   <itunes:author><![CDATA[Garrison Hardie]]></itunes:author>
   <itunes:image href="https://assets-cdn2.dropwave.io/2ab40ac0-e99d-4f25-a6d2-541d2c9b290a/cover-art/mUK8zsnHkCK3vep7E1W6UgYb9dTnLenASAMEFha3.jpg"/>
   <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
   <itunes:duration>806</itunes:duration>
   <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
  
  </item><item>
   <title><![CDATA[Daily News Brief for Tuesday, July 25th, 2023 [Daily News Brief]]]></title>
   <link>https://app.dropwave.io/episode/f11f99ea-3d1c-4fc3-856e-9b547a683666/daily-news-brief-for-tuesday-july-25th-2023.mp3</link>
   <description><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">This is Garrison Hardie with your CrossPolitic Daily News Brief for Tuesday, July 25th, 2023.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>Fight Laugh Feast Conference - Ark Encounter</strong></span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">This year, our Fight Laugh Feast Conference is at the Ark Encounter in Kentucky on The Politics of Six Day Creation. The politics of six day creation is the difference between a fixed standard of justice and a careening standard of justice, the difference between the corrosive relativism that creates mobs and anarchy and the freedom of objectivity, truth, and due process. The politics of six day creation establishes the authority and sufficiency of God&rsquo;s Word for all of life: from what is a man or a woman, when does human life begin, and how is human society best organized?</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Come hear Ken Ham, Pastor Doug Wilson, Dr. Ben Merkle, Dr. Gordon Wilson, me and more, and of course a live CrossPolitic show! Mark your calendars for October 11th-14th, as we fight, laugh, and feast, with beer &amp; psalms, our amazing lineup of speakers, our Rowdy Christian Merch, and a Sabbath Feast to wrap up the occasion. Maybe an infant baptism while we&rsquo;re at it! Visit fightlaughfeast.com for more information!</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">We start today at the southern border&hellip;&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://justthenews.com/government/security/biden-has-border-terrorism-problem-encounters-flagged-aliens-explode-nine-fold"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://justthenews.com/government/security/biden-has-border-terrorism-problem-encounters-flagged-aliens-explode-nine-fold</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>Biden has a border terrorism problem as encounters with flagged aliens explode ninefold</strong></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The number of foreigners on the U.S. terrorist screening list who have tried illegally crossing into the United States has exploded ninefold since President Joe Biden took office, an alarming increase that experts say puts national security at risk.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">So far in fiscal 2023, 140 people on the terror list have been apprehended between ports of entry, already crushing last year&rsquo;s record of 98.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">There were only three such crossings in the last year of Donald Trump&rsquo;s presidency, and 16 in Biden&rsquo;s first year.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The rapid growth in crossings by illegal aliens with terror ties is a warning sign that countries with bad intent may be trying to sneak potential terror cells into the United States, experts told Just the News.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Added Mark Morgan, the former acting commissioner of the Customs Border Protection agency: &ldquo;We literally could have the next terrorist sleeper cell in United States planning a terrorist attack, and we would have no idea.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The pattern also has alarmed Congress, which began an investigation earlier this summer. Lawmakers said they are particularly concerned that there have been 1.5 million gotaways who have never been encountered illegally crossing the border, raising the possibility there are many more potential terrorists already in the country.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">&ldquo;These &lsquo;known gotaways&rsquo; do not provide biometric or biographic information to USBP agents and continue their journey into the interior of the country without background checks against law enforcement databases,&rdquo; Reps. Jim Jordan, James Comer and Mark Green wrote in a recent letter to Homeland Security Secretary Alejandro Mayorkas.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Jordan, Comer and Green chair three of the most powerful committees in Congress: Judiciary, Oversight and Homeland Security.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">&nbsp;</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The lawmakers also cited a recent change in language by the Homeland Security Department, raising concerns that some illegal aliens with terror ties may not have been deported.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Concerns have been exacerbated by the recent revelation the Biden released an illegal alien with known terrorism ties, and it took two weeks to apprehend him.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://justthenews.com/politics-policy/coronavirus/china-publishes-then-deletes-official-covid-data-indicating-over-1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://justthenews.com/politics-policy/coronavirus/china-publishes-then-deletes-official-covid-data-indicating-over-1</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>China publishes then deletes official COVID data indicating over 1 million more deaths than reported</strong></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">While Beijing has claimed about 83,700 people have died in China since the start of the COVID-19 pandemic, the Zhejiang provincial government published and quickly deleted official data indicating the true death toll is significantly higher.&nbsp;&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The Zhejiang government deleted the data last week just days after it was published, but epidemiologists who reviewed the information said it was the latest indication that China's official death toll is vastly undercounted, according to The New York Times.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Provincial data shows that the number of cremations rose to 171,000 in the first quarter of 2023, which is 72,000 more cremations than the same period last year when China's stringent COVID mandates were still in place.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">China has only acknowledged about 83,700 deaths in total.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">An analysis earlier this year from the New York paper estimated that China's most recent wave of COVID, which started late last year, may have resulted in between one million and 1.5 million deaths.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Experts say the data from Zhejiang, which has a population of 65.8 million people, when extrapolated to China's population of 1.4 billion, is consistent with earlier mortality estimates.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">"I&rsquo;m not sure the impact would have been exactly the same in every province, but I think it would be useful for a rough extrapolation," University of Hong Kong epidemiologist Ben Cowling said. "It&rsquo;s consistent with the estimates of around 1.5 million."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Over to Portland we go&hellip;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://thepostmillennial.com/former-kmart-in-portland-that-became-a-homeless-squat-burns-down-in-huge-fire?utm_campaign=64487"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://thepostmillennial.com/former-kmart-in-portland-that-became-a-homeless-squat-burns-down-in-huge-fire?utm_campaign=64487</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>Former Kmart in Portland that became a homeless squat burns down in huge fire</strong></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">An abandoned Kmart store that homeless vagrants have been using as their temporary home in Portland, Oregon was riddled by a massive fire on Wednesday, authorities say.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Portland Fire Bureau spokesperson Rick Graves told The Oregonian that it was only a matter of time before the site was set ablaze.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">"We know this structure," Graves asserted. "We've known this has been vacant for some time &hellip; [with] people gaining occupancy and using it as their home."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Several complaints from nearby residents have recently been made towards the city over the building's accessibility and draw for homeless individuals, trash, and debris. The most recent complaint, filed on July 6, prompted a city inspection, which is currently ongoing.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">It is unknown at this moment if anyone was trapped inside the structure when the fire broke out on Wednesday morning. No known injuries exist, authorities say.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Firefighters were able to gain control of the blaze on Wednesday morning, with Graves explaining that the "major challenge" in controlling the fire was a lack of water supply due to a lack of water hydrants in the area, according to the outlet.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">A nearby resident, 67-year-old Laurel McAfee, told reporters that huge bunches of ash were scattered throughout the yard of her home.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">McAfee said the initial "boom" was so loud she had "thought maybe a car had hit a building or something."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The cause of Wednesday&rsquo;s fire has not yet been identified.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">So while Portland is continuing it&rsquo;s decent into Mordor status, Disney does the same!</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://notthebee.com/article/disneys-new-snow-white-its-not-1937-shes-not-gonna-be-saved-by-the-prince-and-shes-not-going-to-be-dreaming-about-true-love-shes-dreaming-about-becoming-the-leader-she-knows-she-can-be?fbclid=IwAR1-Lnh2oHRUkC7B62wlOx4v6tQukl3sn81zXp26vGDGzM5Ct6Uazpd4UJg"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://notthebee.com/article/disneys-new-snow-white-its-not-1937-shes-not-gonna-be-saved-by-the-prince-and-shes-not-going-to-be-dreaming-about-true-love-shes-dreaming-about-becoming-the-leader-she-knows-she-can-be?fbclid=IwAR1-Lnh2oHRUkC7B62wlOx4v6tQukl3sn81zXp26vGDGzM5Ct6Uazpd4UJg</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>Disney's new Snow White: "It's not 1937. She&rsquo;s not gonna be saved by the prince and she&rsquo;s not going to be dreaming about true love. She&rsquo;s dreaming about becoming the leader she knows she can be."</strong></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Another remake that's here to smash the patriarchy.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://twitter.com/i/status/1683121280390660097"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://twitter.com/i/status/1683121280390660097</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> - Play Video&nbsp;</span></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">How many billions will this Snow White remake cost Disney?</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Good luck with that Disney! In other entertainment news&hellip;&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://www.breitbart.com/entertainment/2023/07/20/nolte-sound-of-freedom-crosses-100-million-mark/"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.breitbart.com/entertainment/2023/07/20/nolte-sound-of-freedom-crosses-100-million-mark/</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>&lsquo;Sound of Freedom&rsquo; Crosses $100 Million Mark</strong></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Thanks to a Wednesday haul of another $4.5 million, Angel Studios&rsquo; Sound of Freedom has crossed the magic $100 million mark at the domestic box office.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">&ldquo;Angel Studios, the platform empowering filmmakers with full creative control to crowdfund and create, has reached a new theatrical milestone,&rdquo; the studio said in a statement released Thursday. &ldquo;Its independent summer hit, SOUND of FREEDOM. has now sold over 8.9 million tickets, and the film has now passed $100M in box office revenue.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">&ldquo;Since the films&rsquo; July 4 release, SOUND of FREEDOM has never left the top 3 positions on the charts[.]&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">On Wednesday, after 16 days of release, Sound of Freedom also managed to nearly top Mission: Impossible &mdash; Dead Reckoning Part One once again, which is only in its eighth day of release &mdash; $4.37 million for Dead Reckoning&rsquo;s Wednesday haul compared to Sound of Freedom&rsquo;s $4.5 million.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">As Breitbart News reported Tuesday, Tom Cruise&rsquo;s seventh outing as Ethan Hunt enjoys the advantage of playing in 1,000+ more screens&mdash;4,327 to 3,265. So, as far as packing in the crowds on a per-screen average, Jim Caviezel&rsquo;s $14.5 million movie is beating Tom Cruise&rsquo;s $250 to $300 million blockbuster, and doing so after being in wide release a week longer.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Currently, Sound of Freedom is the second most popular movie in the country and there are no signs it will slow down. Barbie and Oppenheimer open this weekend, but just as we saw with Dead Reckoning the previous weekend, Sound of Freedom is operating in a lane all of its own. The anti-child trafficking movie (a topic the pro-grooming left finds offensive and controversial) is bringing normal people back to movie theaters. all kinds of people who long ago divorced mainstream Hollywood and have or intend to see Sound of Freedom. Top Gun: Maverick did the same last year.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Normal people are craving normal entertainment. No gay sex. No smug lectures about the patriarchy. No deconstructing our heroes. No Mary Sues. Normal people want good stories created around interesting and complicated characters. Hollywood did this without breaking a sweat for a hundred years. Now a normal movie is an exception in an ocean of woketardery, shaming, and the normalization of destructive perversions.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">By all accounts, Sound of Freedom is a quality movie about an important subject that&rsquo;s making a fortune and driving the left-wing establishment crazy.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">It doesn&rsquo;t get any better than that.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">I suspect Disney will soon produce a remake where the sex traffickers are the heroes rescuing children from their traditional parents. Yes, the liberation of gay sex to unshackle the suffocating tenets of the Christian Faith. Coming soon to an empty theater near you.</span></p>]]></description>
   <author><![CDATA[Garrison Hardie]]></author>
   <enclosure url="https://app.dropwave.io/episode/f11f99ea-3d1c-4fc3-856e-9b547a683666/daily-news-brief-for-tuesday-july-25th-2023.mp3" length="699" type="audio/mp3"/>
   <guid isPermaLink="false"><![CDATA[f11f99ea-3d1c-4fc3-856e-9b547a683666]]></guid>
   <pubDate>Tue, 25 Jul 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
   <source url=""><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></source>
   <itunes:author><![CDATA[Garrison Hardie]]></itunes:author>
   <itunes:image href="https://assets-cdn2.dropwave.io/2ab40ac0-e99d-4f25-a6d2-541d2c9b290a/cover-art/mUK8zsnHkCK3vep7E1W6UgYb9dTnLenASAMEFha3.jpg"/>
   <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
   <itunes:duration>699</itunes:duration>
   <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
  
  </item>
 </channel>
</rss>
