<?xml version="1.0"?>
<?xml-stylesheet href="/storage/feed-stylesheet.xsl" type="text/xsl"?>

<rss xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
 <channel>
  <title>FLF - Daily News Brief</title>
  <link>https://dropwave.io</link>
  <description><![CDATA[FIGHT LAUGH FEAST PRESENTS SHOWS PROCLAIMING THE LORDSHIP OF CHRIST OVER ALL OF LIFE.
]]></description>
  <language>en</language>
  <managingEditor><![CDATA[fightlaughfeast@gmail.com (FLF, LLC)]]></managingEditor>
  <webMaster><![CDATA[support@dropwave.io (DropWave Support)]]></webMaster>
  <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jul 2023 01:25:46 +0000</pubDate>
  <lastBuildDate>Wed, 26 Jul 2023 01:25:46 +0000</lastBuildDate>
  <image>
   <url>https://is4-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Podcasts113/v4/58/56/52/5856525c-2973-cf29-3db9-21faa8595391/mza_1144696925612154085.png/1200x1200bb.jpg</url>
   <link>https://dropwave.io</link>
   <title><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></title>
  </image>
  <itunes:author><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></itunes:author>
  <itunes:image href="https://is4-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Podcasts113/v4/58/56/52/5856525c-2973-cf29-3db9-21faa8595391/mza_1144696925612154085.png/1200x1200bb.jpg"/>
  <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
  <itunes:owner>
   <itunes:name><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></itunes:name>
   <itunes:email>fightlaughfeast@gmail.com</itunes:email>
  </itunes:owner>
  <itunes:category text="News"/>
  <item>
   <title><![CDATA[Daily News Brief for Tuesday, July 25th, 2023 [Daily News Brief]]]></title>
   <link>https://app.dropwave.io/episode/f11f99ea-3d1c-4fc3-856e-9b547a683666/daily-news-brief-for-tuesday-july-25th-2023.mp3</link>
   <description><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">This is Garrison Hardie with your CrossPolitic Daily News Brief for Tuesday, July 25th, 2023.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>Fight Laugh Feast Conference - Ark Encounter</strong></span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">This year, our Fight Laugh Feast Conference is at the Ark Encounter in Kentucky on The Politics of Six Day Creation. The politics of six day creation is the difference between a fixed standard of justice and a careening standard of justice, the difference between the corrosive relativism that creates mobs and anarchy and the freedom of objectivity, truth, and due process. The politics of six day creation establishes the authority and sufficiency of God&rsquo;s Word for all of life: from what is a man or a woman, when does human life begin, and how is human society best organized?</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Come hear Ken Ham, Pastor Doug Wilson, Dr. Ben Merkle, Dr. Gordon Wilson, me and more, and of course a live CrossPolitic show! Mark your calendars for October 11th-14th, as we fight, laugh, and feast, with beer &amp; psalms, our amazing lineup of speakers, our Rowdy Christian Merch, and a Sabbath Feast to wrap up the occasion. Maybe an infant baptism while we&rsquo;re at it! Visit fightlaughfeast.com for more information!</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">We start today at the southern border&hellip;&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://justthenews.com/government/security/biden-has-border-terrorism-problem-encounters-flagged-aliens-explode-nine-fold"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://justthenews.com/government/security/biden-has-border-terrorism-problem-encounters-flagged-aliens-explode-nine-fold</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>Biden has a border terrorism problem as encounters with flagged aliens explode ninefold</strong></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The number of foreigners on the U.S. terrorist screening list who have tried illegally crossing into the United States has exploded ninefold since President Joe Biden took office, an alarming increase that experts say puts national security at risk.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">So far in fiscal 2023, 140 people on the terror list have been apprehended between ports of entry, already crushing last year&rsquo;s record of 98.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">There were only three such crossings in the last year of Donald Trump&rsquo;s presidency, and 16 in Biden&rsquo;s first year.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The rapid growth in crossings by illegal aliens with terror ties is a warning sign that countries with bad intent may be trying to sneak potential terror cells into the United States, experts told Just the News.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Added Mark Morgan, the former acting commissioner of the Customs Border Protection agency: &ldquo;We literally could have the next terrorist sleeper cell in United States planning a terrorist attack, and we would have no idea.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The pattern also has alarmed Congress, which began an investigation earlier this summer. Lawmakers said they are particularly concerned that there have been 1.5 million gotaways who have never been encountered illegally crossing the border, raising the possibility there are many more potential terrorists already in the country.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">&ldquo;These &lsquo;known gotaways&rsquo; do not provide biometric or biographic information to USBP agents and continue their journey into the interior of the country without background checks against law enforcement databases,&rdquo; Reps. Jim Jordan, James Comer and Mark Green wrote in a recent letter to Homeland Security Secretary Alejandro Mayorkas.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Jordan, Comer and Green chair three of the most powerful committees in Congress: Judiciary, Oversight and Homeland Security.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">&nbsp;</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The lawmakers also cited a recent change in language by the Homeland Security Department, raising concerns that some illegal aliens with terror ties may not have been deported.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Concerns have been exacerbated by the recent revelation the Biden released an illegal alien with known terrorism ties, and it took two weeks to apprehend him.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://justthenews.com/politics-policy/coronavirus/china-publishes-then-deletes-official-covid-data-indicating-over-1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://justthenews.com/politics-policy/coronavirus/china-publishes-then-deletes-official-covid-data-indicating-over-1</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>China publishes then deletes official COVID data indicating over 1 million more deaths than reported</strong></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">While Beijing has claimed about 83,700 people have died in China since the start of the COVID-19 pandemic, the Zhejiang provincial government published and quickly deleted official data indicating the true death toll is significantly higher.&nbsp;&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The Zhejiang government deleted the data last week just days after it was published, but epidemiologists who reviewed the information said it was the latest indication that China's official death toll is vastly undercounted, according to The New York Times.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Provincial data shows that the number of cremations rose to 171,000 in the first quarter of 2023, which is 72,000 more cremations than the same period last year when China's stringent COVID mandates were still in place.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">China has only acknowledged about 83,700 deaths in total.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">An analysis earlier this year from the New York paper estimated that China's most recent wave of COVID, which started late last year, may have resulted in between one million and 1.5 million deaths.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Experts say the data from Zhejiang, which has a population of 65.8 million people, when extrapolated to China's population of 1.4 billion, is consistent with earlier mortality estimates.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">"I&rsquo;m not sure the impact would have been exactly the same in every province, but I think it would be useful for a rough extrapolation," University of Hong Kong epidemiologist Ben Cowling said. "It&rsquo;s consistent with the estimates of around 1.5 million."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Over to Portland we go&hellip;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://thepostmillennial.com/former-kmart-in-portland-that-became-a-homeless-squat-burns-down-in-huge-fire?utm_campaign=64487"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://thepostmillennial.com/former-kmart-in-portland-that-became-a-homeless-squat-burns-down-in-huge-fire?utm_campaign=64487</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>Former Kmart in Portland that became a homeless squat burns down in huge fire</strong></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">An abandoned Kmart store that homeless vagrants have been using as their temporary home in Portland, Oregon was riddled by a massive fire on Wednesday, authorities say.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Portland Fire Bureau spokesperson Rick Graves told The Oregonian that it was only a matter of time before the site was set ablaze.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">"We know this structure," Graves asserted. "We've known this has been vacant for some time &hellip; [with] people gaining occupancy and using it as their home."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Several complaints from nearby residents have recently been made towards the city over the building's accessibility and draw for homeless individuals, trash, and debris. The most recent complaint, filed on July 6, prompted a city inspection, which is currently ongoing.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">It is unknown at this moment if anyone was trapped inside the structure when the fire broke out on Wednesday morning. No known injuries exist, authorities say.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Firefighters were able to gain control of the blaze on Wednesday morning, with Graves explaining that the "major challenge" in controlling the fire was a lack of water supply due to a lack of water hydrants in the area, according to the outlet.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">A nearby resident, 67-year-old Laurel McAfee, told reporters that huge bunches of ash were scattered throughout the yard of her home.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">McAfee said the initial "boom" was so loud she had "thought maybe a car had hit a building or something."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The cause of Wednesday&rsquo;s fire has not yet been identified.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">So while Portland is continuing it&rsquo;s decent into Mordor status, Disney does the same!</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://notthebee.com/article/disneys-new-snow-white-its-not-1937-shes-not-gonna-be-saved-by-the-prince-and-shes-not-going-to-be-dreaming-about-true-love-shes-dreaming-about-becoming-the-leader-she-knows-she-can-be?fbclid=IwAR1-Lnh2oHRUkC7B62wlOx4v6tQukl3sn81zXp26vGDGzM5Ct6Uazpd4UJg"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://notthebee.com/article/disneys-new-snow-white-its-not-1937-shes-not-gonna-be-saved-by-the-prince-and-shes-not-going-to-be-dreaming-about-true-love-shes-dreaming-about-becoming-the-leader-she-knows-she-can-be?fbclid=IwAR1-Lnh2oHRUkC7B62wlOx4v6tQukl3sn81zXp26vGDGzM5Ct6Uazpd4UJg</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>Disney's new Snow White: "It's not 1937. She&rsquo;s not gonna be saved by the prince and she&rsquo;s not going to be dreaming about true love. She&rsquo;s dreaming about becoming the leader she knows she can be."</strong></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Another remake that's here to smash the patriarchy.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://twitter.com/i/status/1683121280390660097"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://twitter.com/i/status/1683121280390660097</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> - Play Video&nbsp;</span></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">How many billions will this Snow White remake cost Disney?</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Good luck with that Disney! In other entertainment news&hellip;&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://www.breitbart.com/entertainment/2023/07/20/nolte-sound-of-freedom-crosses-100-million-mark/"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.breitbart.com/entertainment/2023/07/20/nolte-sound-of-freedom-crosses-100-million-mark/</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>&lsquo;Sound of Freedom&rsquo; Crosses $100 Million Mark</strong></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Thanks to a Wednesday haul of another $4.5 million, Angel Studios&rsquo; Sound of Freedom has crossed the magic $100 million mark at the domestic box office.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">&ldquo;Angel Studios, the platform empowering filmmakers with full creative control to crowdfund and create, has reached a new theatrical milestone,&rdquo; the studio said in a statement released Thursday. &ldquo;Its independent summer hit, SOUND of FREEDOM. has now sold over 8.9 million tickets, and the film has now passed $100M in box office revenue.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">&ldquo;Since the films&rsquo; July 4 release, SOUND of FREEDOM has never left the top 3 positions on the charts[.]&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">On Wednesday, after 16 days of release, Sound of Freedom also managed to nearly top Mission: Impossible &mdash; Dead Reckoning Part One once again, which is only in its eighth day of release &mdash; $4.37 million for Dead Reckoning&rsquo;s Wednesday haul compared to Sound of Freedom&rsquo;s $4.5 million.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">As Breitbart News reported Tuesday, Tom Cruise&rsquo;s seventh outing as Ethan Hunt enjoys the advantage of playing in 1,000+ more screens&mdash;4,327 to 3,265. So, as far as packing in the crowds on a per-screen average, Jim Caviezel&rsquo;s $14.5 million movie is beating Tom Cruise&rsquo;s $250 to $300 million blockbuster, and doing so after being in wide release a week longer.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Currently, Sound of Freedom is the second most popular movie in the country and there are no signs it will slow down. Barbie and Oppenheimer open this weekend, but just as we saw with Dead Reckoning the previous weekend, Sound of Freedom is operating in a lane all of its own. The anti-child trafficking movie (a topic the pro-grooming left finds offensive and controversial) is bringing normal people back to movie theaters. all kinds of people who long ago divorced mainstream Hollywood and have or intend to see Sound of Freedom. Top Gun: Maverick did the same last year.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Normal people are craving normal entertainment. No gay sex. No smug lectures about the patriarchy. No deconstructing our heroes. No Mary Sues. Normal people want good stories created around interesting and complicated characters. Hollywood did this without breaking a sweat for a hundred years. Now a normal movie is an exception in an ocean of woketardery, shaming, and the normalization of destructive perversions.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">By all accounts, Sound of Freedom is a quality movie about an important subject that&rsquo;s making a fortune and driving the left-wing establishment crazy.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">It doesn&rsquo;t get any better than that.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">I suspect Disney will soon produce a remake where the sex traffickers are the heroes rescuing children from their traditional parents. Yes, the liberation of gay sex to unshackle the suffocating tenets of the Christian Faith. Coming soon to an empty theater near you.</span></p>]]></description>
   <author><![CDATA[Garrison Hardie]]></author>
   <enclosure url="https://app.dropwave.io/episode/f11f99ea-3d1c-4fc3-856e-9b547a683666/daily-news-brief-for-tuesday-july-25th-2023.mp3" length="699" type="audio/mp3"/>
   <guid isPermaLink="false"><![CDATA[f11f99ea-3d1c-4fc3-856e-9b547a683666]]></guid>
   <pubDate>Tue, 25 Jul 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
   <source url=""><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></source>
   <itunes:author><![CDATA[Garrison Hardie]]></itunes:author>
   <itunes:image href="https://assets-cdn2.dropwave.io/2ab40ac0-e99d-4f25-a6d2-541d2c9b290a/cover-art/mUK8zsnHkCK3vep7E1W6UgYb9dTnLenASAMEFha3.jpg"/>
   <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
   <itunes:duration>699</itunes:duration>
   <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
  
  </item><item>
   <title><![CDATA[Daily News Brief for Friday, July 14th, 2023 [Daily News Brief]]]></title>
   <link>https://app.dropwave.io/episode/65fa24ef-b909-4541-8760-9bae78c03604/daily-news-brief-for-friday-july-14th-2023.mp3</link>
   <description><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">This is Garrison Hardie with your CrossPolitic Daily News Brief for Friday, July 14th, 2023.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Redballoon</strong></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Not so long ago, the American dream was alive and well. Employees who worked hard were rewarded, and employers looked for people who could do the job, not for people who had the right political views.&nbsp; RedBalloon.work is a job site designed to get us back to what made American businesses successful: free speech, hard work, and having fun.&nbsp; If you are a free speech employer who wants to hire employees who focus on their work and not identity politics, then post a job on RedBalloon.&nbsp; If you are an employee who is being censored at work or is being forced to comply with the current zeitgeist, post your resume on RedBalloon and look for a new job. redballoon.work, the job site where free speech is still alive!</span></p>
<p><a href="http://www.redballoon.work/"><span style="font-weight: 400;">www.redballoon.work</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/policy/energy-environment/how-farmers-angry-about-green-rules-helped-spur-dutch-governments-collapse"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/policy/energy-environment/how-farmers-angry-about-green-rules-helped-spur-dutch-governments-collapse</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>How farmers angry about green rules helped spur Dutch government's collapse</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Nitrogen emissions reduction targets have divided the Dutch population, ushering in an upstart political party and playing a primary role in the ouster of Prime Minister Mark Rutte just days after the shocking collapse of his coalition government.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Rutte, the longest-serving Dutch prime minister and a sharp tactician who has presided over four different governing coalitions, does not appear to have an immediate successor lined up.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Rutte&rsquo;s looming vacancy and the waning popularity of his People's Party for Freedom and Democracy could also clear the way for him to be replaced by someone on the far Right, as growing controversies over migration, farming, and nitrogen emissions reduction targets continue to sow deep divisions among voters.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The Dutch government agreed last summer to comply with the European Union&rsquo;s nitrate directive, a mandate that requires the country to slash 50% of its nitrogen emissions by 2030 &mdash; and which it plans to do primarily by reducing nitrogen-heavy fertilizer deposits on its many livestock farms.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">That agreement touched off a massive protest by tens of thousands of Dutch farmers, who massed in the streets to protest the decision, which they decried as unrealistic and unfair, given the country's status as a farming and agriculture powerhouse.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Roughly 40,000 people took part in the demonstrations, gathering outside government buildings, setting fire to bales of hay, and using their many tractors to block Dutch highways, canals, and warehouses.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The protests all but forced the country&rsquo;s economy to a standstill &mdash; and may have also played a role in reshaping the country's political tide.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Just months after the summer protests, the Farmers Citizens Movement, a populist, pro-farmer party known by its Dutch acronym of BBB, swept to power in the country&rsquo;s provincial elections, ultimately gaining enough seats in parliament to put it on par with the left-of-center Labor Party and the Green Party in the Senate.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Leaders of BBB, a party formed only three years earlier, made a name for themselves largely by appealing to the anger of farmers and others who work in the Dutch agriculture sector and campaigned on the promise of fighting the EU&rsquo;s mandated nitrogen emissions targets.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">This week's news of Rutte&rsquo;s departure, coupled with the rise of BBB, is widely expected to exacerbate existing deep-seated divisions over the future of agriculture and farming in the Netherlands.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">It also makes it far less likely that the splintered parties will be able to strike a compromise on key politically fraught issues, including nitrate emissions.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">In the near term, the Dutch government will effectively be held at a standstill, since Rutte will remain in his position through November to oversee a so-called &ldquo;caretaker&rdquo; government.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Leading a caretaker government means that Rutte and the holdover group of officials are unable to approve new and important policy decisions until a new government is formed later this year.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Until then, action will be suspended for months on key issues &mdash; including the country's ability to pass important policies on migration or climate, including taking further action on the EU&rsquo;s nitrate directive.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">In May, the European Commission approved the Dutch government&rsquo;s plan to buy out some of its most heavily polluting farms at roughly 120% of their value. The plan, estimated to cost around $1.65 billion, was aimed at helping the government deliver on its nitrogen emissions reduction commitments without sparking the deep unrest seen last summer.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">In announcing the effort, it warned the buyouts could become compulsory if farmers do not comply.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&ldquo;There is no better offer coming,&rdquo; Dutch Nitrogen Minister Christianne van der Wal told members of parliament.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The Netherlands is the EU&rsquo;s largest emitter of nitrogen oxide and ammonia and was ordered by the European Court of Justice in 2018 to address the problem. It also has a nitrogen balance nearly twice the European average &mdash; the majority of which comes from farming.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">And if it hopes to deliver on its 50% nitrogen reduction target by 2030, the Dutch government must act quickly &mdash; it has estimated that to meet its goal, 11,200 farms in the country will have to close. Roughly 17,600 others will have to significantly reduce their livestock numbers.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">But that has not gone over smoothly in the Netherlands, a farming and agriculture powerhouse where disagreements over nitrogen pollution reductions have sparked bitter protest and disagreement.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Despite its size of just 16,158 square miles &mdash; an area only slightly larger than the state of Maryland &mdash; the Netherlands is home to more than 110 million livestock and 54,000 agricultural businesses. It is the most intensively farmed country in all of Europe, and the world&rsquo;s second-largest exporter of agricultural goods, behind only the United States.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Farm and agriculture groups in the Netherlands have slammed the Dutch government&rsquo;s plans as &ldquo;unrealistic," according to the farming group LTO, and argued that the country's farmers have been unfairly targeted compared to other industries, which they argue remain comparably unscathed.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Others point to the massive amount of revenue generated by agriculture exports, which totaled roughly 105 billion euros in 2021 alone.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">"This is not going to work," LTO Netherland Chairman Sjaak van der Tak, whose organization represents 35,000 farmers, said in response to the government targets.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Others fear these divisions in the Netherlands could portend a larger trend in Europe and the Western world as environmental targets grow more ambitious.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://thepostmillennial.com/breaking-secret-service-says-no-suspect-in-white-house-cocaine-scandal?utm_campaign=64487"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://thepostmillennial.com/breaking-secret-service-says-no-suspect-in-white-house-cocaine-scandal?utm_campaign=64487</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Secret Service says 'no suspect' in White House cocaine scandal</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The Secret Service has reportedly concluded its investigation into the bag of cocaine that was discovered in the White House. But no suspect has been identified, according to two sources, per CNN.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The Secret Service looked through visitor logs and surveillance footage of those who came into the West Wing in the days leading up to the discovery, but they came up short.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Investigators weren't even able to identify a specific moment or day when the baggie was left inside the White House. One source said the prevailing theory is that the baggie was left behind by one of the hundreds of visitors who entered the West Wing for tours.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The cubbies where the small bag of cocaine was apparently found were in a blind spot for surveillance cameras, per the report. This has made it difficult to pin down who may have been responsible.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Representative Tim Burchett posted a video on Twitter about the investigation: </span><a href="https://twitter.com/i/status/1679502198374277120"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://twitter.com/i/status/1679502198374277120</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> - Play Video&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">A so-called powdery substance was discovered at the beginning of July, and speculation has since swirled as to who it may have belonged to. By July 5, officials had confirmed that the powdery substance was, in fact, cocaine.</span><span style="font-weight: 400;"><br /><br /></span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">According to Politico, an unidentified source familiar with the case said that it's "gonna be very difficult for us to do that because of where it was," noting that the baggie was discovered in a blind spot that wasn't picked up by the surveillance cameras.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Though the substance was discovered in the heavily trafficked West Wing, White House Press Secretary Karine Jean-Pierre said the Biden family was not at the White House when the substance was discovered on Sunday. Joe, Jill, and Hunter had dashed to Camp David on the previous Friday, and they returned to the White House on Tuesday for Independence Day.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://twitter.com/i/status/1676673509819404301"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://twitter.com/i/status/1676673509819404301</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> - Play Video</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">However, there has been speculation as to whether the cocaine belonged to Hunter Biden, who has openly spoke about his drug problems. Hunter was reportedly at the White House in the days before the cocaine was discovered. But there has been no evidence to directly connect the baggie of cocaine to the president's son.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Jean-Pierre had previously been asked whether the Biden administration would seek out prosecution if the culprit was found, but she evaded the question by saying she was "not going to get into hypotheticals."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Now for my facvorite topic&hellip; sports!</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://sports.yahoo.com/nba-approves-rule-change-to-make-flopping-a-technical-foul-004257997.html?guccounter=1&amp;guce_referrer=aHR0cHM6Ly9ib25naW5vcmVwb3J0LmNvbS8&amp;guce_referrer_sig=AQAAAN0ALfDif8Ng24K_3S2Ldit0ZVhgHi-1UlF8Oc4HwFsLIlnWOVxGDUGyyGt6mRUl9rvX7lOMcziNxuIR2MVOu3p0V1oFnM9cqfB2g67sMCNkkgSbKJDRlV_p41MwrLokuFaZYn3P6LqYZq5qZ8ReSTaWkxnzioOmW0Mb_lpxUeXG"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://sports.yahoo.com/nba-approves-rule-change-to-make-flopping-a-technical-foul-004257997.html?guccounter=1&amp;guce_referrer=aHR0cHM6Ly9ib25naW5vcmVwb3J0LmNvbS8&amp;guce_referrer_sig=AQAAAN0ALfDif8Ng24K_3S2Ldit0ZVhgHi-1UlF8Oc4HwFsLIlnWOVxGDUGyyGt6mRUl9rvX7lOMcziNxuIR2MVOu3p0V1oFnM9cqfB2g67sMCNkkgSbKJDRlV_p41MwrLokuFaZYn3P6LqYZq5qZ8ReSTaWkxnzioOmW0Mb_lpxUeXG</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>NBA approves rule change to make flopping a technical foul</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Look out [insert your least favorite NBA player here], flopping is about to come at a real cost.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The NBA Board of Governors approved a rule change that will make flopping a technical foul for the 2023-24 season, the league announced Tuesday, the result of increasing frustrations from fans and teams toward players who go out of their way to sell contact.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The change will come on a one-year trial basis.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Specifically, when a game official calls a flop, defined by the NBA as "a physical act that reasonably appears to be intended to cause the officials to call a foul on another player," the offending player will be charged with a non-unsportsmanlike technical foul and give the other team one free-throw attempt.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Because of the nature of the technical foul, a player will not be ejected from a game due to flopping violations. Refs will also not have to interrupt play to call a flop, as they can wait until the next stoppage to hit a player with the penalty.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The NBA specifically notes it's possible for the officials to call both a foul and a flop on the same play.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The league also instituted a change that will give coaches a second challenge if their first challenge is successful.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Flopping was previously punished with a warning, then fines escalating from $5,000 to $30,000. Such punishments were rare. The fines will change now that flopping is a tech, as it will be rolled into the existing fines for technical fouls instead.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The NBA was already trying out this system in the Summer League. Lester Quinones of the Golden State Warriors was the first player to feel the effect, getting called for a flop during a break in play.</span></p>
<p><br /><br /><br /><br /></p>]]></description>
   <author><![CDATA[Garrison Hardie]]></author>
   <enclosure url="https://app.dropwave.io/episode/65fa24ef-b909-4541-8760-9bae78c03604/daily-news-brief-for-friday-july-14th-2023.mp3" length="724" type="audio/mp3"/>
   <guid isPermaLink="false"><![CDATA[65fa24ef-b909-4541-8760-9bae78c03604]]></guid>
   <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jul 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
   <source url=""><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></source>
   <itunes:author><![CDATA[Garrison Hardie]]></itunes:author>
   <itunes:image href="https://assets-cdn2.dropwave.io/2ab40ac0-e99d-4f25-a6d2-541d2c9b290a/cover-art/mUK8zsnHkCK3vep7E1W6UgYb9dTnLenASAMEFha3.jpg"/>
   <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
   <itunes:duration>724</itunes:duration>
   <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
  
  </item><item>
   <title><![CDATA[Daily News Brief for Wednesday, July 12th, 2023 [Daily News Brief]]]></title>
   <link>https://app.dropwave.io/episode/07dab912-07c7-452d-b50c-fdbe65f8169d/daily-news-brief-for-wednesday-july-12th-2023.mp3</link>
   <description><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">This is Garrison Hardie with your CrossPolitic Daily News Brief for Wednesday, July 12th, 2023.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Olive Tree Biblical Software:</strong></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Discover why more than a million people use the free Olive Tree Bible App as their go-to for reading, studying, and listening to the God&rsquo;s Word.&nbsp;&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Start by downloading one of many free Bibles and start taking notes, highlighting verses, and bookmarking your favorite passages. You can read at your own pace, or choose from a large selection of Reading Plans, including the Bible Reading Challenge. When you are ready to go deeper into your studies, Olive Tree is right there with a large selection of study Bibles, commentaries, and other helpful study resources available for purchase. There&rsquo;s also an extensive bookstore allows you to build your digital library one book at a time and Olive Tree&rsquo;s sync technology lets you pick up where you left off on your tablet, pc or phone and get right to studying on another supported device.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&nbsp;</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Now here's the best part &ndash; You can start with the Olive Tree Essentials Bundle for FREE. Visit www.olivetree.com/FLF and download it today! </span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">We start things off in China!&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://dailycaller.com/2023/07/10/chinese-military-kindergarteners-war-bootcamps/"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://dailycaller.com/2023/07/10/chinese-military-kindergarteners-war-bootcamps/</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>The Chinese Military Is Training Kindergarteners For War In Bootcamps Across The Country</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The Chinese military is training kindergarteners to handle firearms and fight like soldiers in boot camps across China this summer, according to dozens of school social media accounts.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The boot camps feature combat training for boys and girls with a wide variety of toy weapons including knives, grenades, rifles and shoulder-fired missiles, and require the children to adopt military behavior, such as saluting, the schools&rsquo; social media posts show. The rise in the militarization of China&rsquo;s youth appears to follow a 2019 Chinese Communist Party (CCP) Central Committee push for increased &ldquo;National Defense Education&rdquo; and a related effort directing schools to hold National Defense Education activities in 2022, according to government documents.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Uniformed People&rsquo;s Liberation Army (PLA) soldiers oversaw all of the kindergarten boot camps. The boot camps were located in major Chinese cities, such as Beijing, Nanjing and Shenzhen, and were also run in more than half a dozen provinces.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The programs featured roughly the same sequence of activities, according to a DCNF review of posts from the participating kindergartens.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The boot camps generally began with basic military etiquette and proceeded to teach various military skills ranging from combat to emergency medical training. Additionally, a number of these programs also taught the children about famous PLA heroes and martyrs, according to the schools&rsquo; accounts.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">In May 2023, faculty members and more than 80 children of numerous provinces assembled on the playground for the opening ceremony of their school&rsquo;s week-long National Defense Education camp, all wearing matching camouflage fatigues.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&ldquo;INHERIT THE RED GENE, CARRY FORWARD PATRIOTIC FEELINGS, LOVE CHINA, LITTLE SOLDIER,&rdquo; declared a large PLA banner, which partially hid the kindergarten&rsquo;s playset.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Uniformed PLA soldiers then performed a flag-raising ceremony, with all attendants singing the Chinese national anthem, the social media post stated.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&ldquo;We solemnly swear to love the motherland from now on, to dedicate our hearts to working together to build the dream of a powerful country,&rdquo; the children then pledged, according to the social media post. &ldquo;Even if I fall to the ground I will continue onward!&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">PLA soldiers then taught the kindergarten recruits how to groom themselves and make their beds in accordance with military standards, before drilling them in how to stand at attention, stand at ease and salute.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Experts say recent efforts to militarize China&rsquo;s youth are part of the CCP&rsquo;s ideological goals.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Now compare that to the U.S., where students are regularly pushed into ideologies that despise everything the Founding Father&rsquo;s did.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://notthebee.com/article/just-unfathomable-disney-world-is-just-about-empty-during-summer-vacation-season?fbclid=IwAR2ZgkovaL7WZCwrL8WVQuUm3MNqIpPK8z9WvOLKpsRIph9epbgE0Xknj4E"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://notthebee.com/article/just-unfathomable-disney-world-is-just-about-empty-during-summer-vacation-season?fbclid=IwAR2ZgkovaL7WZCwrL8WVQuUm3MNqIpPK8z9WvOLKpsRIph9epbgE0Xknj4E</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>"Just unfathomable": Disney World is "just about empty" during summer vacation season</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">It takes real skill to drive this many customers away.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The July 4th weekend was a 10-year-low for the massive company's Disney World amusement park in Orlando, but all the parks have been suffering recently.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">According to the Wall Street Journal, Park visitors in recent weeks have had significantly lower wait times to get on rides, according to data from Touring Plans, a company that tracks wait times at major amusement parks, including Disney World and Disneyland in California. Industry analysts say shorter wait times generally correlate with smaller crowds.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The average posted wait time at the Magic Kingdom park in Florida &mdash; which has a special fireworks display on July 4 &mdash; was 27 minutes this year for the holiday, down from 31 minutes in 2022 and 47 minutes in 2019, the Touring Plans analysis shows.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">"It's something that nobody would have predicted &mdash; just unfathomable," says Len Testa, a computer scientist who runs Touring Plans. Testa says wait times rose in the following days.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The Journal offers an assortment of potential reasons for the lull: Cruises and European vacations are back after the pandemic, Disney isn't offering much new, and Disney wants to slim down the crowds for richer guests anyway.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">But unlike the journalist class, most of America understands the two primary reasons:</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Your wallet is hurting</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Disney went woke</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://thehill.com/blogs/blog-briefing-room/4085828-a-record-share-of-americans-are-living-alone/"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://thehill.com/blogs/blog-briefing-room/4085828-a-record-share-of-americans-are-living-alone/</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>A record share of Americans is living alone</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Nearly 30 percent of American households comprise a single person, a record high.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Scholars say living alone is not a trend so much as a transformation: Across much of the world, large numbers of people are living alone for the first time in recorded history.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&ldquo;It&rsquo;s just a stunning social change,&rdquo; said Eric Klinenberg, a sociologist at New York University and author of the book &ldquo;Going Solo.&rdquo; &ldquo;I came to see it as the biggest demographic change in the last century that we failed to recognize and take seriously.&rdquo;&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Homo sapiens is a social animal. Historians tapped ancient census rolls to show that our species has lived in groups for as long as such records have existed, stretching back at least to 1600.&nbsp;&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The U.S. Census shows that &ldquo;solitaries&rdquo; made up 8 percent of all households in 1940. The share of solo households doubled to 18 percent in 1970 and more than tripled, to an estimated 29 percent, by 2022.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The solo-living movement intersects with several other societal trends. Americans are marrying later, if at all. The nation is aging. The national birthrate is falling. People are living longer &mdash; or they were, until the pandemic arrived.&nbsp;&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">More than anything, perhaps, the rise of single-person households is about women entering the workforce and achieving economic self-sufficiency. The share of adult women participating in the labor force reached 50 percent around 1980.&nbsp;&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Historically speaking, &ldquo;you don&rsquo;t really see people living alone until women have control of their own lives and their own bodies,&rdquo; Klinenberg said.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Researchers see a marked downside to living alone, especially for older Americans, for people who live outside thickly settled cities and for pretty much anyone who is not alone by choice.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">A New York Times report on aging solitaries concluded that, &ldquo;while many people in their 50s and 60s thrive living solo, research is unequivocal that people aging alone experience worse physical and mental health outcomes and shorter life spans.&rdquo;&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The nation&rsquo;s declining birth rate and aging population portend a time when America doesn&rsquo;t have enough working-age citizens to sustain the national economy or to support the spiraling health care needs of its oldest citizens. The rise of single-person households can be seen as both a cause and effect of those challenges.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&ldquo;I think it&rsquo;s something we should be worried about,&rdquo; said Wendy Wang, director of research at the Institute for Family Studies, a conservative thinktank. &ldquo;If we have fewer and fewer children, that means we have fewer people to work, to be consumers, to pay taxes.&rdquo;&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Wang notes that low fertility rates are a global problem. Indeed, solo households are far more common across much of Europe than in the United States. According to United Nations data, solitaries make up 39 percent of households in Denmark, 45 percent in Finland, 42 percent in Germany, 38 percent in the Netherlands, 39 percent in Norway and 40 percent in Sweden.&nbsp;&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Even now, living alone is not quite so common in the United States as the data suggest. While nearly 30 percent of households comprise a single person, far fewer than 30 percent of Americans live in them.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Roughly 13 percent of American adults live alone, research shows. Breaking down that figure by age groups, the population of solitaries rises from 4 percent of adults at ages 18-24 to 9 percent at 25-34, dips to 8 percent at 35-44, then rises again, to 12 percent at 45-54, 17 percent at 55-64 and 26 percent at 65 and up.&nbsp;&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Living alone is much more common in large cities. Singles now make up more than 40 percent of households in Atlanta, Seattle, San Francisco, Minneapolis and Denver, according to a paper by the British historian Keith Snell. Half of all Manhattan dwellings are one-person residences. Snell identified a Midtown Census tract where 94 percent of households comprised a single person.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">At younger ages, men outnumber women in one-person households. Young men are far more likely than young women to be single, and they tend to marry later.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The gender gap in solitary living closes with age. In the retirement years, women are more likely than men to live alone.&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">That statistic is partly about women outliving husbands, and partly about &ldquo;grey divorce,&rdquo; the rising rate of marriages that dissolve after age 50. The grey divorce rate has doubled since 1990.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&ldquo;It used to be that if people were married for 30 years and they entered their 60s, basically, they were going to stay married,&rdquo; said Barbara Risman, a distinguished professor of sociology at the University of Illinois Chicago. &ldquo;You would pass the risk of divorce. No one is ever past the risk of divorce anymore.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Through much of the 20th century, marriage was so universal that the very act of living alone carried a stigma.&nbsp;&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The share of Americans who had not married by age 40 hovered below 10 percent from 1950 through 1980, according to a Pew Research analysis. The figure has soared in recent decades, reaching 25 percent in 2021, a record high.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The share of Americans in prime marriage years who are actually married has dwindled from about two-thirds to around half since 1990, Pew data show. Nearly two-fifths of Americans are &ldquo;unpartnered,&rdquo; neither married nor cohabiting.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Researchers consider living alone a risk factor for loneliness and social isolation, conditions associated with a host of physical and mental maladies, from heart disease to obesity to anxiety and depression.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Men tend to fare less well than women in single-person households, said Louise Hawkley, a researcher at the NORC thinktank who studies loneliness and social isolation. - Perhaps because we&rsquo;re meant to be taking dominion &amp; building families&hellip;&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Now for my favorite topic&hellip; sports!</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://www.foxnews.com/sports/us-soccer-star-megan-rapinoe-support-trans-athlete-uswnt-roster-i-see-trans-women-as-real-women"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.foxnews.com/sports/us-soccer-star-megan-rapinoe-support-trans-athlete-uswnt-roster-i-see-trans-women-as-real-women</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>US soccer star Megan Rapinoe would support trans athlete on USWNT roster: 'I see trans women as real women'</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">U.S. women&rsquo;s soccer icon Megan Rapinoe has been a public advocate for the inclusion of transgender athletes in women&rsquo;s sports, and ahead of what will be her final World Cup appearance before retiring, the one-time Golden Boot winner said she would "absolutely" support having a trans woman on the USWNT roster.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Even if that meant replacing a biological female.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">In an interview with Time published Monday, Rapinoe recalled highlights from her lengthy career, including her battles both on and off the pitch. She was asked specifically about her push to defend transgender athletes&rsquo; participation in women&rsquo;s sports.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">"We as a country are trying to legislate away people&rsquo;s full humanity," she told the outlet.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Rapinoe was one of 40 professional athletes to co-sign a letter to House lawmakers in April in opposition of the Protection of Girls and Women in Sports Act, arguing that the bill would exclude women and girls from getting "mental and physical health benefits."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">"It&rsquo;s particularly frustrating when women&rsquo;s sports is weaponized," Rapinoe said in the interview. "Oh, now we care about fairness? Now we care about women&rsquo;s sports? That&rsquo;s total bulls---. And show me all the trans people who are nefariously taking advantage of being trans in sports. It&rsquo;s just not happening."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Rapinoe was asked specifically if she would support a trans woman playing on the United States Women&rsquo;s National Team, even if it meant replacing a biological female. The OL Reign star said she would, but added that she did not view the act as "taking a &lsquo;real&rsquo; woman&rsquo;s place."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">"Absolutely," she told Time. "&lsquo;You&rsquo;re taking a &lsquo;real&rsquo; woman&rsquo;s place,&rsquo; that&rsquo;s the part of the argument that&rsquo;s still extremely transphobic. I see trans women as real women. What you&rsquo;re saying automatically in the argument&mdash;you&rsquo;re sort of telling on yourself already&mdash;is you don&rsquo;t believe these people are women. Therefore, they&rsquo;re taking the other spot. I don&rsquo;t feel that way."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Rapinoe will make her final World Cup appearance this month as the United States Women&rsquo;s National Team heads to Australia and New Zealand with the hopes of making history: becoming the first women&rsquo;s or men&rsquo;s team to win a three-peat.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The 38-year-old soccer star announced over the weekend her plans to retire at the conclusion of the 2023 National Women&rsquo;s Soccer League season.</span></p>]]></description>
   <author><![CDATA[Garrison Hardie]]></author>
   <enclosure url="https://app.dropwave.io/episode/07dab912-07c7-452d-b50c-fdbe65f8169d/daily-news-brief-for-wednesday-july-12th-2023.mp3" length="869" type="audio/mp3"/>
   <guid isPermaLink="false"><![CDATA[07dab912-07c7-452d-b50c-fdbe65f8169d]]></guid>
   <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
   <source url=""><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></source>
   <itunes:author><![CDATA[Garrison Hardie]]></itunes:author>
   <itunes:image href="https://assets-cdn2.dropwave.io/2ab40ac0-e99d-4f25-a6d2-541d2c9b290a/cover-art/mUK8zsnHkCK3vep7E1W6UgYb9dTnLenASAMEFha3.jpg"/>
   <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
   <itunes:duration>869</itunes:duration>
   <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
  
  </item>
 </channel>
</rss>
