<?xml version="1.0"?>
<?xml-stylesheet href="/storage/feed-stylesheet.xsl" type="text/xsl"?>

<rss xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
 <channel>
  <title>FLF - Daily News Brief</title>
  <link>https://dropwave.io</link>
  <description><![CDATA[FIGHT LAUGH FEAST PRESENTS SHOWS PROCLAIMING THE LORDSHIP OF CHRIST OVER ALL OF LIFE.
]]></description>
  <language>en</language>
  <managingEditor><![CDATA[fightlaughfeast@gmail.com (FLF, LLC)]]></managingEditor>
  <webMaster><![CDATA[support@dropwave.io (DropWave Support)]]></webMaster>
  <pubDate>Sat, 21 Oct 2023 07:25:49 +0000</pubDate>
  <lastBuildDate>Sat, 21 Oct 2023 07:25:49 +0000</lastBuildDate>
  <image>
   <url>https://is4-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Podcasts113/v4/58/56/52/5856525c-2973-cf29-3db9-21faa8595391/mza_1144696925612154085.png/1200x1200bb.jpg</url>
   <link>https://dropwave.io</link>
   <title><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></title>
  </image>
  <itunes:author><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></itunes:author>
  <itunes:image href="https://is4-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Podcasts113/v4/58/56/52/5856525c-2973-cf29-3db9-21faa8595391/mza_1144696925612154085.png/1200x1200bb.jpg"/>
  <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
  <itunes:owner>
   <itunes:name><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></itunes:name>
   <itunes:email>fightlaughfeast@gmail.com</itunes:email>
  </itunes:owner>
  <itunes:category text="News"/>
  <item>
   <title><![CDATA[Daily News Brief for Friday, October 20th, 2023 [Daily News Brief]]]></title>
   <link/>
   <description><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">This is Garrison Hardie with your CrossPolitic Daily News Brief for Friday, October 20th, 2023.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>PUB MEMBERSHIP PLUG:</strong></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Summer has been great here at CrossPolitic, and we want you to join us on this ride&hellip; First, we&rsquo;re no longer calling it the Fight Laugh Feast club&hellip; it&rsquo;s now called the Pub! Second, we&rsquo;ve launched a new line of content, focused on family entertainment. We will have our new show &ldquo;This America&rdquo; and our exciting new &ldquo;Rowdy Christian Guides&rdquo; highlighting the practical guides to fun and godly life! Additionally, we will have the live streaming of our conferences, and our past conference talks, all bundled within our new polished Fight Laugh Feast App. Sign up today! Head on over to fightlaughfeast.com, and join the Pub! that&rsquo;s fightlaughfeast.com.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://www.breitbart.com/middle-east/2023/10/18/watch-pro-palestinian-protesters-stage-insurrection-in-u-s-capitol-office-building-cannon/"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.breitbart.com/middle-east/2023/10/18/watch-pro-palestinian-protesters-stage-insurrection-in-u-s-capitol-office-building-cannon/</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Pro-Palestinian Protesters Stage &lsquo;Insurrection&rsquo; in U.S. Capitol Office Building</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Pro-Palestinian protesters, who want a ceasefire that would benefit the Hamas terrorist organization in Gaza, stormed the U.S. Capitol on Wednesday and staged a protest inside the Cannon Rotunda that one observer likened to an &ldquo;insurrection.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The Cannon Rotunda is part of the Cannon House Office Building. It is separate from the iconic Capitol building but is considered part of the Capitol complex. It is the oldest congressional office building on Capitol Hill.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Rep. Rashida Tlaib (D-MI), who falsely accused Israel of bombing a Gaza hospital Tuesday, addressed the protesters.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Fox 5 in Washington, DC, reported:</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">A large group of pro-Palestinian protesters are demonstrating inside the Cannon Rotunda on Capitol Hill.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The Cannon House Office Building holds the House Committee offices.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">U.S. Capitol Police say demonstrations are not allowed inside Congressional Buildings and are working to clear the crowd. Police have already detained some individuals as chants of &ldquo;ceasefire&rdquo; are echoing around the building.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Left-wing protesters have staged demonstrations inside the Capitol before, but none have been treated the way participants in the January 6, 2021 protesters have been treated, many of whom were detained and given harsh sentences for non-violent offenses.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The U.S. has seen anti-Israel protests in major cities and on college campuses since a Hamas terror attack Oct. 7 killed 1,400 Israelis and wounded roughly 4,400 more. About 200 people &mdash; including some Americans &mdash; were taken to Gaza as hostages.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">FBI Director Christopher Wray called the Capitol riot &ldquo;domestic terrorism.&rdquo; In this case, the pro-Palestinian protest is supporting terrorism against Israelis and Americans; a ceasefire would allow Hamas to escape without consequences for its atrocities.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/policy/education/israel-war-harvard-columbia-students-lose-job-offer-law-firm"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/policy/education/israel-war-harvard-columbia-students-lose-job-offer-law-firm</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Harvard and Columbia students lose law firm job offer for anti-Israel stance</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">A major law firm has rescinded its offer of employment to three students at Harvard and Columbia law schools who endorsed statements that blamed Israel for a series of terrorist attacks by Hamas.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The law firm Davis Polk notified employees in an internal email that the firm had withdrawn job offers to three students from Harvard and Columbia who had signed statements that blamed the Israeli government for the attacks by Hamas. The Columbia statement went further and said the attacks were justified acts of resistance. The attacks and the subsequent military response by Israel have claimed the lives of more than 4,000 people.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&ldquo;These statements are simply contrary to our firm&rsquo;s values and we thus concluded that rescinding these offers was appropriate in upholding our responsibility to provide a safe and inclusive work environment for all Davis Polk employees,&rdquo; the firm said in the email to employees.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The firm's action is the latest example of students losing employment offers because of their support for the statement.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Ryna Workman, a law student at New York University and the president of the student bar association, lost an employment offer from the law firm Winston &amp; Strawn after supporting a statement that said: &ldquo;Israel bears full responsibility for this tremendous loss of life.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">In addition to withdrawn job offers, other prominent figures have urged that the students be named publicly and face professional consequences. A number of the 31 student groups who signed the Harvard statement have since withdrawn their support for the statement.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Billionaire Bill Ackman, a Harvard alum, asked that the names of the students who signed the statement be publicly released "so as to ensure that none of us inadvertently hire any of their members."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Sweetgreen CEO Jonathan Neman echoed Ackman, saying, "I would like to know so I know never to hire these people."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://www.theblaze.com/news/sen-vances-new-bill-would-protect-mothers-who-exit-the-workforce-to-care-for-their-babies-from-undue-healthcare-costs"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.theblaze.com/news/sen-vances-new-bill-would-protect-mothers-who-exit-the-workforce-to-care-for-their-babies-from-undue-healthcare-costs</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Sen. Vance's new bill would protect mothers who exit the workforce to care for their babies from undue health care costs</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Republican Sens. J.D. Vance (Ohio) and Marco Rubio (Fla.) introduced legislation Tuesday that would ensure that mothers "who choose to prioritize their child's early development and recover rather than return to work" after giving birth won't be retroactively stripped of their health care premiums for having done so.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Currently, the Family and Medical Leave Act of 1993 requires covered companies with over 50 employees to give their workers 12 weeks of unpaid medical leave in a 12-month period for the birth of a child as well as in cases of adoption. Furthermore, it requires the "continuation of their group health benefits under the same conditions as if they had not taken leave."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The bill, entitled "Fairness for Stay-At-Home Parents Act," would amend the FMLA to "prohibit an employer from recovering any health care premium paid by the employer for an employee if the employee fails to return to work due to the birth of a child, and for other purposes."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">In addition to preventing clawbacks, the legislation would have employers continue their health premium contributions for the duration of the 12-week leave.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">"Our laws should not penalize new parents who choose to stay home to care for their newborn babies," Vance said in a statement. "We should celebrate and promote young families, not punish them. This legislation would relieve a serious financial burden for working families all over America and steer Washington in a more pro-family direction."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">America appears to be in dire need of a "pro-family direction."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The U.S. Census Bureau revealed in November 2022 that less than 24% of children under the age of 15 living in normal families had a stay-at-home mother. Only 1% had a stay-at-home father.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The Pew Research Center indicated that as of 2021, 26% of mothers stayed home with their children and 7% of fathers stayed home with their children.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">According to the Mayo Clinic, over half of women return to work after their maternity leave.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Not only are fewer people staying home to raise their children, but fewer Americans are having children.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The Centers for Disease Control and Prevention indicated in a June report that the provisional number of births in the U.S. for 2022 was just over 3.6 million, a decline from the previous year. The fertility rate was 56.1 per 1,000 women ages 15-44. This figure is roughly half of what the rate was in the 1960s and more or less on par with the rate in 2020, which was the lowest rate on record.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The New York Times noted in 2018 that one of the key drivers behind Americans having fewer or no children is financial insecurity.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">A poll conducted by USA Today last year confirmed that was still the case. About 46% of respondents suggested their personal financial situation influenced their planned or current childlessness; 40% indicated work-life balance was at least partly to blame.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The Washington Examiner noted that financial struggles hit parents straight out the gate. The national average cost of child delivery in a hospital exceeds $18,000, or $3,000 out of pocket for those with insurance.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The 12-week reprieve that some parents might find as a result of Vance's bill could go a long way.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">"The Fairness for Stay-At-Home Parents Act supports mothers' and parents' invaluable role in raising the next generation," said Rubio, the original co-sponsor of Vance's bill. "This legislation stops employers from imposing harsh financial penalties if a parent decides not to return to work after unpaid leave, and it empowers families to make choices that prioritize the well-being of their children."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Rubio, like Vance, appears keen on bolstering the family. Following the Supreme Court's Dobbs ruling, Rubio released a pro-family framework, stressing the "need to adopt pro-life policies that support families, rather than destroy them."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Among the proposals in the Florida senator's framework were an expansion to the child tax credit; an allowance for new parents to pull forward up to three months of their Social Security benefits to finance paid parental leave; tax relief for adoptive parents; expanded support for pro-life crisis pregnancy centers; and the establishment of a grant program funding integrated mentoring services for poor mothers.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Following the overturning of Roe v. Wade, the Manhattan Institute's Brian Riedl prophesied to the Washington Post that Republicans would likely take a stronger lead on bolstering the family beyond just sparing the unborn from mass extermination.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">"I could see if Republicans decide that abortion politics are working against them, there could be a push for child-care benefits, more maternal health care, and better adoption services to make it easy and more affordable for more mothers to carry the babies to term," said Riedl. "It would put their money where their mouth is when challenged on making it easier for mothers to afford their children and get their health care."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://www.outkick.com/conor-mcgregor-no-charges-nba-finals-heat-sexual-assault-allegation/"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.outkick.com/conor-mcgregor-no-charges-nba-finals-heat-sexual-assault-allegation/</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>CONOR MCGREGOR WON&rsquo;T FACE CHARGES AFTER BEING ACCUSED OF SEXUAL ASSAULT DURING NBA FINALS</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Conor McGregor won&rsquo;t face charges stemming from allegations he sexually assaulted a woman during the NBA Finals.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">McGregor was accused by a woman of sexually assaulting her in the bathroom of Kaseya Center during a Heat/Nuggets NBA Finals game, and the UFC star always maintained he didn&rsquo;t do anything wrong.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Prosecutors have now decided there is &ldquo;insufficient evidence&rdquo; to pursue the situation further, according to TMZ. Authorities also cited &ldquo;contradicting and/or no corroborating witnesses&rdquo; as another reason for why no charges will be brought.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&ldquo;In light of the above facts and circumstances, the State would not be able to satisfy its burden of proof beyond a reasonable doubt,&rdquo; prosecutors wrote in a closeout memo, according to the same TMZ report.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The woman initially claimed security separated her from her friends to get her in a bathroom with McGregor, but video of the situation told a very different story.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">She was filmed entering the bathroom with McGregor on her own freewill, and nobody was forcing her to go anywhere.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">TMZ also reported she was seen at a club with McGregor AFTER they left the bathroom together where she alleged she was assaulted.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">An attendant outside the bathroom told authorities they &ldquo;did not hear any signs of distress or sounds that would corroborate that whatever was occurring was not consensual.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">McGregor&rsquo;s attorney told TMZ, &ldquo;After a thorough investigation, including a review of videos and interviews with eyewitnesses, the authorities have concluded that there is no case to pursue against my client, Conor McGregor. On behalf of my client, his family and his fans we are pleased this is now over.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The situation is now behind McGregor, and that means he can focus on getting back in the octagon.</span></p>]]></description>
   <author><![CDATA[Garrison Hardie]]></author>
   <enclosure url="https://app.dropwave.io/episode/e1200639-2ca7-43a6-aaaf-c166eafbb362/daily-news-brief-for-friday-october-20th-2023.mp3" length="687" type="audio/mp3"/>
   <guid isPermaLink="false"><![CDATA[e1200639-2ca7-43a6-aaaf-c166eafbb362]]></guid>
   <pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2023 21:04:00 +0000</pubDate>
   <source url=""><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></source>
   <itunes:author><![CDATA[Garrison Hardie]]></itunes:author>
   <itunes:image href="https://assets-cdn2.dropwave.io/2ab40ac0-e99d-4f25-a6d2-541d2c9b290a/cover-art/mUK8zsnHkCK3vep7E1W6UgYb9dTnLenASAMEFha3.jpg"/>
   <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
   <itunes:duration>687</itunes:duration>
   <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
  
  </item><item>
   <title><![CDATA[Daily News Brief for Tuesday, October 10th, 2023 [Daily News Brief]]]></title>
   <link/>
   <description><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">This is Garrison Hardie with your CrossPolitic Daily News Brief for Tuesday, October 10th, 2023.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Gravity Jack:</strong></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Gravity Jack is a full service digital agency specializing in the development of Virtual &amp; Augmented Reality experiences, mobile apps, blockchain and Web3 projects. Founded in 2009 as the first American agency to offer augmented reality, they even patented it; Gravity Jack's digital experiences have been a source of innovation for small business, Fortune 500 Companies, and the US Military. Get your vision in motion at </span><a href="http://www.gravityjack.com/"><span style="font-weight: 400;">gravityjack.com</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://townhall.com/tipsheet/mattvespa/2023/10/08/100000-israeli-troops-mobilized-for-first-declared-war-since-1973-n2629547"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://townhall.com/tipsheet/mattvespa/2023/10/08/100000-israeli-troops-mobilized-for-first-declared-war-since-1973-n2629547</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Israel Mobilizes 100,000 Troops for Gaza Incursion</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">It might be the worst intelligence failure since the 1973 Yom Kippur War, a conflict that almost destroyed Israel after a surprise attack from Syria and Egypt. Israel was on the brink as Syrian forces reclaimed the Golan Heights, and it was by sheer luck that this invading force didn&rsquo;t move further to capture the key bridges along the Jordan River. Israel&rsquo;s heartland would&rsquo;ve been wide open. The game could&rsquo;ve been over, so Israel continues to respond forcefully against incursion by terrorists and its Arab neighbors since it&rsquo;s a nation with no strategic depth. How Jerusalem was caught sleeping amid this latest assault by Hamas on October 7 must be investigated since Shin Bet and Mossad are some of the most capable agencies in the world.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">This attack occurred on the 50th anniversary of the Yom Kippur War, and like that last war, the assault began during a Jewish holiday. Hamas launched thousands of rockets as cover for a land, sea, and air assault that could only have been made possible with outside help, considering its sophisticated nature. Iran has admitted they helped plan the assault.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The death toll has risen to 700, with reports of kidnappings, rapes, and murder of Israeli citizens caught in the fighting. Hamas operatives paraglided into Southern Israel, with other terrorists attacking over two dozen areas along the Gaza border. Some Americans were also kidnapped and murdered by these terrorists.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The footprint from Hamas was around 1,000 terrorists who stormed the infiltrated Israeli territory. Border Police and other forces are still fighting to restore order to the security situation in the area, but tanks and troops are being mobilized for a ground assault. Around 100,000 Israeli troops are ready to go into Gaza, with more reservists expected to be called up as Israel expects this to erupt into a multi-front war. Hezbollah has already launched rocket and mortar attacks in the northern Israel (via Associated Press):</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">More than 24 hours after Hamas launched its unprecedented incursion out of Gaza, Israeli forces were still battling with militants holed up in several locations Monday morning. At least 700 people have reportedly been killed in Israel &mdash; a staggering toll on a scale the country has not experienced in decades &mdash; and more than 400 have been killed in Gaza.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Israel said it brought in special forces to try to wrest control of four sites from Hamas fighters, including two points that militants entered earlier in their attacks.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Meanwhile, Hamas and the smaller Islamic Jihad group claimed to have taken captive more than 130 people from inside Israel and brought them into Gaza, saying they would be traded for the release of thousands of Palestinians imprisoned by Israel. The announcement, though unconfirmed, was the first sign of the scope of abductions.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The captives are known to include soldiers and civilians, including women, children and older adults &mdash; mostly Israelis but also some people of other nationalities. The Israeli military said only that the number of captives is &ldquo;significant.&rdquo;&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">As many as 1,000 Hamas fighters were involved in Saturday morning&rsquo;s assault, U.S. Secretary of State Antony Blinken said, speaking on ABC&rsquo;s &ldquo;This Week.&rdquo; The high figure underscored the extent of planning by the militant group ruling Gaza, which has said it launched the attack in response to mounting Palestinian suffering under Israel&rsquo;s occupation and blockade of Gaza.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">In northern Israel, a brief exchange of strikes with Lebanon&rsquo;s Hezbollah militant group fanned fears that the fighting could expand into a wider regional war. Hezbollah fired rockets and shells Sunday at Israeli positions in a disputed area along the border, and Israel fired back using armed drones. The Israeli military said the situation was calm after the exchange.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Israelis were still reeling from the breadth, ferocity and surprise of the Hamas assault. The group&rsquo;s fighters broke through Israel&rsquo;s security fence surrounding the Gaza Strip early Saturday. Using motorcycles and pickup trucks, even paragliders and speedboats on the coast, they moved into nearby Israeli communities &mdash; as many as 22 locations.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://themessenger.com/news/hamas-threatens-to-start-executing-hostages-if-gaza-strikes-continue"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://themessenger.com/news/hamas-threatens-to-start-executing-hostages-if-gaza-strikes-continue</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Hamas Threatens to Start Executing Hostages If Gaza Strikes Continue</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Hamas on Monday threatened to execute Israeli hostages being held in Gaza if Israel continues to conduct airstrikes without warning.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&ldquo;Any targeting of innocent civilians without warning will be met regretfully by executing one of the captives in our custody, and we will be forced to broadcast this execution,&rdquo; Abu Obeida, a spokesman for Hamas&rsquo; Qassam Brigades, said in a statement to Al Jazeera.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Hamas has claimed to be holding more than 100 Israelis prisoner in the Gaza Strip, according to the Qatar-based network.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The warning from Hamas came as Israeli Defense Forces intensified a bombardment of Gaza as dusk fell on Monday.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Images shown live on CNN showed heavy rocket fire lighting up the sky above Gaza, a Palestinian enclave about the size of Omaha, Nebraska, that's home to some two million people and considered one of the most densely populated places in the world.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">There are reports that American citizens are among those being held captive in Gaza. The State Dept. said it was working to confirm those reports.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://www.foxnews.com/politics/christian-baker-faces-new-lawsuit-over-gender-transition-cake-after-supreme-court"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.foxnews.com/politics/christian-baker-faces-new-lawsuit-over-gender-transition-cake-after-supreme-court</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Christian baker faces new lawsuit over gender-transition cake after Supreme Court</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The Colorado Supreme Court agreed to hear the case against Christian cake baker Jack Phillips, which he says is the "light at the end of the tunnel" after more than 11 years in court.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Phillips, owner of Masterpiece Cakeshop in Colorado, declined to create a custom cake for a same-sex wedding in a move that sparked a 2012 lawsuit that ultimately landed him at the U.S. Supreme Court. In 2018, the nine justices ruled that the state of Colorado was hostile to Phillip&rsquo;s religious beliefs and that the government can&rsquo;t force anyone to create custom works of art that communicate a message.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">But in 2018, Phillips faced a second lawsuit, this time from a transgender lawyer who requested a cake celebrating a gender transition. When Phillips declined, he was back in court on grounds that he discriminated against the lawyer. The Colorado Supreme Court just agreed to hear his case.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">"I hope it is the light at the end of the tunnel. I&rsquo;m pretty excited about it," Phillips told Fox News Digital in an interview. "The state court turned us down in our first case, but I think they realize now that I serve everybody."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">"This case is not who I serve, but it&rsquo;s always the what I&rsquo;m going to create not the who that&rsquo;s asking for it. And I hope they get that right this time," said Phillips.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Jake Warner, attorney for the Alliance Defending Freedom (ADF) defending Phillips, said that the lawsuit from the beginning was "clearly a set-up" with the intent of "targeting" Phillips and his beliefs.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">In 2018, Autumn Scardina, who identifies as transgender, asked Phillips to make a cake celebrating a gender transition &ndash; pink on the inside, blue on the outside. When Phillips declined, Scardina asked for a cake depicting Satan smoking a marijuana joint &ndash; which Phillips also declined.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">During the trial phase, "Scardina promised Phillips that, were this suit dismissed, Scardina would call Phillips the next day to request another cake and start another lawsuit," legal documents state.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Despite being in court for more than a decade, "numerous threatening emails" and death threats, Phillips says the case has helped to "strengthen" his faith.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">"We just celebrated our 30th anniversary of being in business Labor Day weekend. And so for 30 years we&rsquo;ve served everybody who&rsquo;s come into our shop," he said.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">"But this whole legal battle has helped strengthen my faith in Jesus Christ and strengthen our family, brought us all closer together. It&rsquo;s brought together a lot of people who have helped support us in so many ways."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Phillips mentioned that a gay man testified on his behalf in court "because he understood that I serve everybody, gladly served him, but he knows that I couldn&rsquo;t create every cake that people would ask me for."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">"It&rsquo;s been an encouraging time to see people stand beside us like that," he said.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">When it comes to this latest challenge, Phillips said Scardina is "not the enemy" and that he has "nothing to forgive."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">"This person isn&rsquo;t fighting against me, this case is against the state and my right to express my religious freedom and do so without fear of punishment in the marketplace," said Phillips.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Oral arguments for the case have yet to be set but likely will be scheduled for the springtime next year.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">ADF will argue that because of the Supreme Court&rsquo;s ruling in Phillip&rsquo;s previous case and the latest ruling in 303 Creative vs. Elenis involving a website designer, which determined that the government can&rsquo;t compel an artist to speak a message with which they disagree, that the law is on Phillips&rsquo; side.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">"What's critical now after 303 is the fact that this cake actually does communicate a message. The trial court found that this cake symbolizes the transition from male to female and went into great detail about the symbolism of the cake. The court found that blue represents male and pink represents female and that this cake communicates a message given the context of how cake artists are often asked to create custom cakes," Warner said.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">"In light of 303 Creative, the Colorado Supreme Court should reverse the decision below and affirm Jack's right to speak consistently with his beliefs. He shouldn't be punished for declining to create a custom cake promoting a message that goes against his beliefs," Warner added.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://www.theepochtimes.com/us/in-depth-us-gives-more-than-4-1-billion-in-grants-for-lgbt-and-transgender-initiatives-worldwide-5498747?utm_source=partner&amp;utm_campaign=BonginoReport"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.theepochtimes.com/us/in-depth-us-gives-more-than-4-1-billion-in-grants-for-lgbt-and-transgender-initiatives-worldwide-5498747?utm_source=partner&amp;utm_campaign=BonginoReport</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>US Gives More Than $4.1 Billion in Grants for LGBT and Transgender Initiatives Worldwide</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">During the past three fiscal years, $4.1 billion in federal money from taxpayers has been flowing to LGBT initiatives in the United States and around the world, an Epoch Times investigation has revealed.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">From Oct. 1, 2020, through Sept. 30, 2023, the U.S. government issued more than 1,100 grants to fund LGBT-promoting projects around the world, according to the Epoch Times review of a federal spending website.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The scope of projects varies widely.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Plans to create a "safe space for LGBTQ youth and adults to seek support and resources" earned a $1.8 million grant from the U.S. government in 2022 for the LGBT Life Center in Norfolk, Virginia.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">A proposal for encouraging "diversity, equity, and inclusion in Serbia's workplaces and business communities by promoting economic empowerment of and opportunity for LGBTQI+ people in Serbia" also was a winning plan. To fund it, the U.S. government awarded a Serbian activist group a grant of $500,000.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">An Armenian activist group, the Pink Human Rights Defender, received $1 million from the United States "to empower the LGBTI community" in Armenia, a tiny country next to Turkey.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The federal spending website can be filtered to show entries that include specific keywords. A list of payouts filtered by using the keyword "LGBT" included 1,181 grants, 31 loans, and nine direct payments during the past three fiscal years.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Overall, during the past fiscal year that ended Sept. 30, the government issued 454,821 grants.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Government grants provide free money for specific purposes. Federal loans can be repaid over long periods of time at low interest rates. Direct payments from the government give money to groups&mdash;they may be unrestricted, or for a specific use.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Of grants connected to the keyword "LGBT," individual payouts of at least $1 million totaled more than $3.7 billion combined. Many additional smaller grants also were awarded for LGBT initiatives but were not reviewed.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">When the list was filtered for grants including the word "transgender," 574 were listed. In that category, grants that paid out at least $1 million totaled nearly $478 million. Seven direct payments and nine loans with the keyword "transgender" also were issued by the U.S. government.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Yet money flows to these projects.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The U.S. Department of Education (DOE) gave $1.2 million to "LGBTQIA+ pride centers" in the San Diego Community College District.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Another DOE grant of almost $1.6 million was awarded for North Dakota's &ldquo;indigenous, LGBTQIA+, rural and underserved school-based mental health needs.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">A DOE grant gave $1.4 million to Boston College to study "mechanisms of health promotion in diverse youth through gay-straight alliances."&nbsp; In plain speak, the grant funded the promotion of gay-straight alliance clubs in Massachusetts middle and high schools.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">"The federal government thumbs their nose at the American people and continues to push this ideology into our schools,"&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">"They're doing it all over the world."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">And that - is your news for today&hellip; this has been your CrossPolitic Daily NewsBrief. Just so y&rsquo;all are aware - this will be the only newsbrief for the next week or so, as I will be out of town for our Fight Laugh Feast Conference at the Ark Encounter - as well as visiting my brother in North Carolina after that&hellip; if you liked the show &hellip;..</span></p>]]></description>
   <author><![CDATA[Garrison Hardie]]></author>
   <enclosure url="https://app.dropwave.io/episode/91befb2c-29af-424c-b413-285f79bee212/daily-news-brief-for-tuesday-october-10th-2023.mp3" length="828" type="audio/mp3"/>
   <guid isPermaLink="false"><![CDATA[91befb2c-29af-424c-b413-285f79bee212]]></guid>
   <pubDate>Tue, 10 Oct 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
   <source url=""><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></source>
   <itunes:author><![CDATA[Garrison Hardie]]></itunes:author>
   <itunes:image href="https://assets-cdn2.dropwave.io/2ab40ac0-e99d-4f25-a6d2-541d2c9b290a/cover-art/mUK8zsnHkCK3vep7E1W6UgYb9dTnLenASAMEFha3.jpg"/>
   <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
   <itunes:duration>828</itunes:duration>
   <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
  
  </item><item>
   <title><![CDATA[Daily News Brief for Friday, October 6th, 2023 [Daily News Brief]]]></title>
   <link/>
   <description><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">This is Garrison Hardie with your CrossPolitic Daily News Brief for Friday, October 6th, 2023.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Dropwave</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Do you have a podcast, or thinking about starting one? Does your church have a podcast feed for sermons? Then Dropwave.io is for you. Cancel culture is like walking on a thin glass bridge over the Grand Canyon. Every step you take could get you killed, I mean canceled. Since the beginning CrossPolitic has been working on being antifragile, so no matter what happens, our content can still be delivered to your tv and to your podcast. This past year, the Waterboy and his friend Jeremi, have been working on building a podcast hosting solution for rowdy platforms like CrossPolitic, so that you can be confident your podcast will never fall through that glass bridge. Dropwave offers seamless onboarding for shows that have been around for years to easy to use solutions for starting your own podcast. Dropwave will track all your show&rsquo;s downloads by city, state, and country, and it offers network and enterprise packages for solutions like the Fight Laugh Feast Network. Free to speak, Free to podcast, free to start your journey now at www.Dropwave.io.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://www.theblaze.com/news/child-allegedly-shoots-two-teens-at-football-practice-over-bag-of-chips"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.theblaze.com/news/child-allegedly-shoots-two-teens-at-football-practice-over-bag-of-chips</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Child allegedly shoots two teens at football practice over 'bag of chips'</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">An 11-year-old was arrested Monday after allegedly opening fire at a Pop Warner youth football practice in Apopka, Florida.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Police say that while only one shot was fired, two kids were ultimately struck &mdash; one in the back and the other in the arm.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The suspect is presently facing one count of attempted second-degree murder, though Apopka Police Chief Michael McKinley indicated prosecutors may pursue additional charges.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">WOFL-TV reported that the APD received a report of a shooting around 8:20 p.m. near a football field at the Northwest Recreation Center on Jason Dwelley Parkway where a kids' soccer game was also taking place.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">In the 911 call obtained by WESH-TV, one victim's mother can be heard saying, "My son got shot, miss! ... In his back!"</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The first officer arrived on the scene just four minutes later, finding one victim on the ground and another victim holding his grazed elbow.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The two victims, both 13 years old, were taken to Arnold Palmer Hospital and are expected to make a full recovery.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Surveillance footage shows juveniles crewing at the edge of the parking lot around 8:17 p.m., some still wearing their football jerseys.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The first victim, a heavy-set male with red shorts, can be seen chasing the alleged shooter toward his mother's vehicle around 8:18 p.m. Seconds later, the suspect opens the front passenger door and reaches into the vehicle, where his mother was reportedly in the driver's seat.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Inside and under the passenger seat was a purple handgun, according to the arrest report.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Brandishing the weapon, the suspect appears to turn the tables and chase the heavy-set victim, ultimately firing one shot into the victim's back. The same round proceeded to graze the second victim's elbow.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Following the shooting, WOFL indicated the alleged shooter was brought back to his mother's vehicle. He is now being held at a juvenile detention center.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">According to the arrest report, some witnesses claimed the victims had been "bullying" the alleged shooter. Others suggested the dispute was over "a bag of chips," reported the Orlando Sentinel.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Apopka Police Chief Michael McKinley told reporters, "It's unbelievable that young kids out here to play football and have a good time would get into an altercation."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">McKinley indicated the APD would be pursuing second-degree misdemeanor charges against the mother for allegedly having her firearm in an unlocked box, reported WKMG-TV.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Orange-Osceola State Attorney Andrew Bain, who took over for Monique Worrell after her suspension by Gov. Ron DeSantis, said his office will ensure there will be a reckoning.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">"The level of violence unacceptable right now, especially from our youth," said Bain. "We&rsquo;re going to stand strong to deal with those cases and try to end or put a big slow-down to what&rsquo;s going on in the streets right now."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Apopka Pop Warner canceled its Wednesday practice, noting in a statement, "One of our players was involved in a shooting incident that resulted in the injury of two players. We are deeply saddened by this event and our thoughts and prayers are with the families affected."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://www.breitbart.com/europe/2023/10/04/uk-announced-new-zealand-style-plan-to-ban-smoking-altogether/"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.breitbart.com/europe/2023/10/04/uk-announced-new-zealand-style-plan-to-ban-smoking-altogether/</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>UK Announces New Zealand Style Plan to Ban Smoking Altogether</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The United Kingdom is to phase out smoking altogether, the government says, by banning young people from buying cigarettes at all with a minimum age to buy rising from 18 every year until there isn&rsquo;t anyone left alive old enough to enjoy the habit.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Conservative Prime Minister Rishi Sunak announced his intention to steer the UK towards becoming tobacco-free by increasing the minimum age to buy products every year from here on, so the teenagers of today will never be old enough to legally take the habit up. Sunak acknowledged restricting personal freedoms was not always an easy choice for an instinctive Conservative but &mdash; underlining the way government decisions are driven by socialised healthcare &mdash; said it was important because smokers cost taxpayers through needing more hospital care.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">This is about &ldquo;preventative care&rdquo; to keep people out of hospitals, the Prime Minister said and told his governing party&rsquo;s annual conference that: &ldquo;I propose that in future, we raise the smoking age by one year every year. That means a 14-year-old today will never legally be sold a cigarette, and that they and their generation can grow up smoke-free&rdquo;.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">This would work, Sunak said, because the UK&rsquo;s previous experience with increasing the smoking age from 16 to 18 saw a drop in the number of people starting smoking. The Prime Minister said he would also look at cracking down on &lsquo;vapes&rsquo;, the electronic tobacco alternative.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">A report explaining the system as already implemented in New Zealand, which is becoming known for its draconian health interventions, stated in 2022:</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The law states that tobacco can&rsquo;t ever be sold to anybody born on or after January 1, 2009 &ndash; and from now on, the minimum age for buying cigarettes will keep going up and up.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">In theory, somebody trying to buy a pack of cigarettes 50 years from now would need ID to show they were at least 63 years old. But health authorities hope smoking will fade away well before then. They have a stated goal of making New Zealand smoke-free by 2025.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">New Zealand also took other measures in its law shakeup, including making getting hold of cigarettes more difficult for those who could legally use them. They are no longer sold in regular stores, but can only be bought at specialist tobacconists, cutting the number of locations where smokes are sold nationwide from thousands of locations to hundreds.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/policy/defense-national-security/biden-faa-nominee-promises-end-work-from-home"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/policy/defense-national-security/biden-faa-nominee-promises-end-work-from-home</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Biden pick to lead FAA promises hard push to end work-from-home policies</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">President Joe Biden's nominee to lead the Federal Aviation Administration would prioritize ending pandemic telework policies for federal employees and bring the out-of-date agency into the 21st century.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Former FAA Deputy Administrator Michael Whitaker told Senate Commerce, Science, and Transportation Committee members during his confirmation hearing on Wednesday that, if approved, he would focus heavily on matters with agency employees.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">"I do believe that it's important to be in person for collaboration and working together," said Whitaker, a pilot and former aviation industry executive. "This has been a challenging issue for all organizations, private or public. And I think what needs to happen is after understanding the situation that we're in and the limitations that might be there, issuing very clear guidance, what the expectations are to get people in the office."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">In July, the FAA announced that employees would have to return to the office no fewer than three days per week starting on Oct. 9. The union pushed back against a 100% return to office, complicating the agency's attempt to reinstate the policy.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Sen. Ted Cruz (R-TX) egged Whitaker on over the work-from-home policies and claimed the federal government was the only employer that had not returned to pre-pandemic policies.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">"When I talk to businesses in the private sector, virtually all of them, employees are going back to work, and they're physically present. And yet, throughout the Biden administration, we have a pattern in just about every agency where large portions of the workforce have apparently decided going into the office is optional," Cruz said. "That seriously limits the effectiveness of an agency and particularly an agency whose mission is protecting people's lives and the airspace."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">When asked by Cruz if he would commit to "working diligently" to bring employees back into the office, Whitaker agreed.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Whitaker was second in command at the FAA from 2012 through 2015. The agency has had a gap in leadership over the past 18 months. Returning to the FAA at this point, Whitaker said, would warrant three actions he would take in his five-year term as administrator.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">"First, I will work not just to maintain the safety record we have collectively achieved but build upon it. The two Boeing MAX crashes remind us that we must be ever-vigilant," Whitaker said.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The agency ought to ensure gaps in the FAA certification process are closed so that undisclosed changes manufacturers make to aircraft can still be caught before being put into use.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Second, the FAA should be more "agile and creative" and willing to "adapt quickly" and plan for the future rather than focus on the present.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The FAA has but one academy that takes years to complete, and it can only accommodate 1,800 air traffic controllers at a time.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Whitaker's final point was that the government should make the FAA a place where people interested in aviation careers, particularly air traffic controllers, want to work.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">He was tasked with hiring 6,000 air traffic controllers during his previous stint at the FAA but came up far short.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://dailycaller.com/2023/10/05/rnc-republican-presidential-primary-debates-donald-trump/"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://dailycaller.com/2023/10/05/rnc-republican-presidential-primary-debates-donald-trump/</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Even The RNC&rsquo;s Own Members Are Admitting Trump-less Debates May Be A Waste Of Time</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Members of the Republican National Committee (RNC) are frustrated with the current direction of their GOP primary debates, admitting that without President Donald Trump the events may not be worth it, according to Politico.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The frontrunner for the Republican nomination, Trump has skipped the first two presidential debates, a decision that has drawn criticism from rival candidates. After the first two debates were widely panned, some within the RNC think they need the President on the stage to make the forums worth it.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&ldquo;I think the only way you salvage it is if you get the frontrunner there,&rdquo; Tyler Bowyer, a national committeeman from Arizona, told Politico. &ldquo;Plan a debate where you get the frontrunner to agree to it.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The first GOP presidential debate, sponsored by the conservative youth organization Young America&rsquo;s Foundation (YAF), was aired exclusively on Fox News, Fox Business and Rumble. The debate was moderated by Fox News&rsquo; Bret Baier and Martha MacCallum in Milwaukee, Wisconsin.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The second debate was aired by the exact same networks, in addition to Spanish-language network Univision. The moderators included Univision anchor Ilia Calder&oacute;n, Fox Business host Stuart Varney and Fox News host Dana Perino.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">That debate fell flat, with many prominent conservative media figures criticizing the moderators for asking poor questions while candidates bickered and talked over one another. The RNC previously promised in 2022 to use debates to &ldquo;raise conservative media up&rdquo; and incorporate other outlets, but after the first two debates, conservative media companies outside of the mainstream media told the Daily Caller that they are feeling snubbed by the committee.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&ldquo;You can&rsquo;t put your head in the sand and pretend these debates are going to result in someone other than Donald Trump getting the nomination,&rdquo; Patti Lyman, the RNC&rsquo;s national committeewoman from Virginia, told Politico, adding that the debates were &ldquo;embarrassing&rdquo; and &ldquo;reflected very poorly on our party.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Despite some members pushing for Trump to take the debate stage, top officials are reportedly not attempting to get the front runner on the debate stage, a person with knowledge of the committee&rsquo;s operations told Politico. That reportedly includes RNC chairwoman Ronna McDaniel and chairman for the RNC&rsquo;s Temporary Committee on Presidential Debates David Bossie.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Trump himself doesn&rsquo;t think the debates should go on; the President told the Daily Caller that the RNC &ldquo;has to stop the debates&rdquo; because they are &ldquo;bad for the Republican party.&rdquo; Trump and his advisors have additionally urged the RNC to &ldquo;refocus its manpower and money&rdquo; on election integrity efforts rather than the debates, Politico reported.</span></p>]]></description>
   <author><![CDATA[Garrison Hardie]]></author>
   <enclosure url="https://app.dropwave.io/episode/209c7c1e-8ae8-4f94-8d42-c0a5726e5bd4/daily-news-brief-for-friday-october-6th-2023.mp3" length="745" type="audio/mp3"/>
   <guid isPermaLink="false"><![CDATA[209c7c1e-8ae8-4f94-8d42-c0a5726e5bd4]]></guid>
   <pubDate>Fri, 06 Oct 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
   <source url=""><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></source>
   <itunes:author><![CDATA[Garrison Hardie]]></itunes:author>
   <itunes:image href="https://assets-cdn2.dropwave.io/2ab40ac0-e99d-4f25-a6d2-541d2c9b290a/cover-art/mUK8zsnHkCK3vep7E1W6UgYb9dTnLenASAMEFha3.jpg"/>
   <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
   <itunes:duration>745</itunes:duration>
   <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
  </item>
 </channel>
</rss>
