<?xml version="1.0"?>
<?xml-stylesheet href="/storage/feed-stylesheet.xsl" type="text/xsl"?>

<rss xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
 <channel>
  <title>FLF - Daily News Brief</title>
  <link>https://dropwave.io</link>
  <description><![CDATA[FIGHT LAUGH FEAST PRESENTS SHOWS PROCLAIMING THE LORDSHIP OF CHRIST OVER ALL OF LIFE.
]]></description>
  <language>en</language>
  <managingEditor><![CDATA[fightlaughfeast@gmail.com (FLF, LLC)]]></managingEditor>
  <webMaster><![CDATA[support@dropwave.io (DropWave Support)]]></webMaster>
  <pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 07:25:46 +0000</pubDate>
  <lastBuildDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 07:25:46 +0000</lastBuildDate>
  <image>
   <url>https://is4-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Podcasts113/v4/58/56/52/5856525c-2973-cf29-3db9-21faa8595391/mza_1144696925612154085.png/1200x1200bb.jpg</url>
   <link>https://dropwave.io</link>
   <title><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></title>
  </image>
  <itunes:author><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></itunes:author>
  <itunes:image href="https://is4-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Podcasts113/v4/58/56/52/5856525c-2973-cf29-3db9-21faa8595391/mza_1144696925612154085.png/1200x1200bb.jpg"/>
  <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
  <itunes:owner>
   <itunes:name><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></itunes:name>
   <itunes:email>fightlaughfeast@gmail.com</itunes:email>
  </itunes:owner>
  <itunes:category text="News"/>
  <item>
   <title><![CDATA[Daily News Brief for Friday, December 1st, 2023 [Daily News Brief]]]></title>
   <link/>
   <description><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">This is Garrison Hardie with your CrossPolitic Daily News Brief for Friday, December 1st, 2023.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Pub Membership Plug:</strong></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Public Houses, or Pubs, are not just places to drink beer, wine, cider or even something a little stronger. It is also a unique social centre, very often the focus of community life in villages, towns and cities throughout the length and breadth of the world. We here at CrossPolitic hope to emulate that for you and yours. That&rsquo;s why you should grab yourself a pub membership at fightlaughfeast.com&hellip; we need you on this ride with us. So pull up a chair, grab a pint, and join us on this ride at fightlaughfeast.com - that&rsquo;s fightlaughfeast.com.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://www.theblaze.com/news/damning-study-suggests-pandemic-lockdowns-accelerated-significant-memory-and-cognitive-decline-in-seniors"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.theblaze.com/news/damning-study-suggests-pandemic-lockdowns-accelerated-significant-memory-and-cognitive-decline-in-seniors</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Damning study suggests pandemic lockdowns accelerated 'significant' memory and cognitive decline in seniors</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The lockdowns and societal restrictions championed by teachers' unions and other leftists during the pandemic were not just ruinous for the mental health of children and teens. A new study out of the U.K. indicates pandemic restrictions also had a deleterious impact on the minds of the elderly.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Dr. Anne Corbett of the University of Exeter Medical School and her team examined neuropsychology data from 3,142 individuals, all 50 years of age or over, who had been participating in a multi-decade dementia study in Britain. The researchers compared data on this cohort collected before the pandemic, early in the pandemic, then once more toward the tail end of the pandemic.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The researchers observed "[s]ignificant worsening of executive function and working memory" in the first year of the pandemic across the whole cohort, the average age of which was 67.5. Working memory continued to worsen across the whole cohort in the second year of the pandemic. By the time restrictions had ultimately been eased, the damage had been done.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">According to the study, cognitive decline was significantly associated with reduced exercise and increased drinking across the whole cohort. Depression, another driving factor of cognitive decline, was notable amongst those who contracted COVID-19. Loneliness proved especially detrimental to those with mild cognitive impairment.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">"People aged 50 years and older in the UK had accelerated decline in executive function and working memory during the first year of the COVID-19 pandemic, during which the UK was subjected to three societal lockdowns for a total period of 6 months," said the study, published in the Lancet journal Healthy Longevity.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The British government, which funded this study via the National Institute for Health and Care Research, not only limited the number of times citizens could exercise outside during the pandemic, but shuttered gyms, golf courses, sports courts, swimming pools, and indoor sports facilities.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">"The scale of change is also of note, with all groups&mdash;the whole cohort and the individual subgroups&mdash;showing more than a 50% greater decline in working memory and executive function and many effect sizes reaching a clinically significant threshold of greater than 0&middot;3," said the researchers.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The researchers further stressed that "[t]hese factors map closely to the population-wide changes in health and lifestyle seen during and after the lockdowns, raising the important question of the effect of the pandemic on cognitive health and risk across populations."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://www.foxnews.com/politics/appeals-court-reinstates-gag-order-trump-fraud-case"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.foxnews.com/politics/appeals-court-reinstates-gag-order-trump-fraud-case</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Appeals court reinstates gag order in Trump fraud case</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">A New York appeals court reinstated a gag order preventing former President Donald Trump from maligning court staffers on Thursday.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">New York Judge Arthur Engoron had initially issued the gag order in early October after Trump lashed out at one of his law clerks on social media. Trump is currently fighting accusations of business fraud leveled by New York Attorney General Letitia James.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Appeals court Judge David Friedman had issued a stay on Engoron's gag order on Nov. 16, saying it potentially infringed on Trump's First Amendment rights.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">By that time, Engoron had already fined Trump $5,000 for violating the order on social media on Oct. 20, and did so again on Oct. 25 for another $10,000 before threatening imprisonment if further violations were committed.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Trump took the stand to testify personally in early November. He repeatedly cast James&rsquo; yearslong investigation and lawsuit as a "disgrace" and an attack on his business and his family.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Trump has denied any wrongdoing and insists his assets were actually undervalued. Trump has repeatedly said his financial statements had disclaimers requesting that the numbers be evaluated by the banks.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Engoron ruled in September that both Trump and his company had committed fraud by deceiving banks, insurers and others by overvaluing his assets and exaggerating his net worth on paperwork used in making deals and securing financing.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Trump has attacked Engoron and James &mdash; both Democrats &mdash; as politically biased "operatives."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">"They are defending the Worst and Least Respected Attorney General in the United States, Letitia James, who is a Worldwide disgrace, as is her illegal Witch Hunt against me. The Radical and Unprecedented actions of Judge Engoron will keep BUSINESSES and JOBS forever out of New York State," Trump wrote in a recent social media post.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://www.justfactsdaily.com/1-in-every-39-americans-will-die-of-a-drug-overdose-at-current-rate"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.justfactsdaily.com/1-in-every-39-americans-will-die-of-a-drug-overdose-at-current-rate</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>1 in Every 39 Americans Will Die of a Drug Overdose at Current Rate</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Despite the passage of state and federal laws that were supposed to reduce fatal drug overdoses, the annual U.S. drug overdose death rate has quintupled over recent decades:</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Over the most current year of available data, more than 110,000 people in the U.S. died of drug overdoses, a rate of 33 per 100,000 population.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">In order to measure these deaths in clear, relevant terms, Just Facts enlisted the expertise of a licensed actuary and a Ph.D. mathematician to calculate, double-check, and triple-check the average lifetime odds of dying of a drug overdose.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The shocking result of these calculations is that 1 in 39 people will have their lives cut short by drug overdoses if the rate of such deaths stays at the current level. Those odds will become far worse if the rising trend continues.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The lifetime risks of tragic events are much more revealing than the raw numbers or annual rates commonly reported by government agencies and the media. This is partly because the U.S. is the third-most populous nation in the world, so tens, hundreds, or even thousands of events may amount to a very low risk.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The other reason, which is less obvious, is explained by a 1987 Department of Justice report on the likelihood of being a crime victim:</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Annual victimization rates alone do not convey the full impact of crime as it affects people. No one would express his or her concern by saying, &ldquo;I am terribly afraid of being mugged between January and December of this year.&rdquo; People are worried about the possibility that at some time in their lives they will be robbed or raped or assaulted, or their houses will be burglarized.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Each month, the CDC estimates drug overdose deaths based on data reported by the 50 states and the District of Columbia. The latest estimates, which include deaths up through June 2023, show that 111,877 people died of a drug overdose in the prior 12 months.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">To place such figures into the broader context of the U.S. population and people&rsquo;s lifespans, Just Facts asked a licensed actuary to develop a method for calculating the average lifetime risk of death from various causes. The actuary used two separate methods, both of which yielded the same results. To further ensure accuracy, Just Facts had a Ph.D. mathematician check the formulas.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Applying this methodology to the CDC&rsquo;s latest estimates of overdose deaths, roughly 1 in every 39 people will die of drug overdose if the rate of such deaths stays at its current level.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Beyond lifetime risk, another important measure of a mortal danger is the years of life that it robs from its victims. Because humans cannot prevent death but only delay it, there is a material difference between the tragic premature deaths of a 20-year-old in the prime of her life and a 90-year-old in poor health.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Although some leading medical scholars ignored that vital fact during the Covid-19 pandemic, a 1983 CDC report about fatal accidents explains that the &ldquo;the allocation of health resources must consider not only the number of deaths by cause but also by age.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The average age of people who die of drug overdoses is about 43 years, while the average U.S. lifespan is about 77 years. In contrast, the average age of people whose deaths involved Covid-19 is about 75 years. Yet, government officials locked down entire states for extended periods to prevent the spread of Covid, causing multitudes of collateral deaths. This likely included overdoses, which soared in the wake of these measures.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://www.foxnews.com/sports/jets-aaron-rodgers-takes-big-step-hopeful-return-achilles-injury"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.foxnews.com/sports/jets-aaron-rodgers-takes-big-step-hopeful-return-achilles-injury</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Jets' Aaron Rodgers takes big step in hopeful return from Achilles injury</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The New York Jets opened the 21-day practice window for Aaron Rodgers on Wednesday, sparking hope the quarterback could return this season just mere months after tearing his Achilles.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Jets head coach Robert Saleh told reporters that it doesn&rsquo;t necessarily mean Rodgers is going to come back and play, but is rather a "progression in his rehab."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">"For Aaron, what he would be doing in practice is no different than what he&rsquo;d be doing on the field with regard to certain drills in the individual &ndash; instead of throwing with staff members, he&rsquo;s throwing with teammates," Saleh told reporters. "There&rsquo;s no added risk to it. There&rsquo;s certain things he&rsquo;s been cleared for that we&rsquo;re going to allow him to do."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Saleh lauded Rodgers&rsquo; drive and motivation for pushing himself to get back to where he is and the want and need for him to be with his teammates.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">"He&rsquo;s sacrificed so much already for the organization and himself and his teammates and he&rsquo;s doing it again. I think it&rsquo;s a testament to who he is as a human," Saleh added.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Rodgers&rsquo; timeline is still really unclear.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">He tried to lay it out the best he could in his appearance on "The Pat McAfee Show" this week.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">"Once I'm healthy, then it's where we're at, are we alive, are we in it&hellip; It's health first, and are we alive for the playoffs second.".</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">New York is 4-7 entering Week 13 and their playoff hopes are dwindling.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>]]></description>
   <author><![CDATA[Garrison Hardie]]></author>
   <enclosure url="https://app.dropwave.io/episode/eb95130b-9887-45f4-8c51-6a03065d5bcd/daily-news-brief-for-friday-december-1st-2023.mp3" length="652" type="audio/mp3"/>
   <guid isPermaLink="false"><![CDATA[eb95130b-9887-45f4-8c51-6a03065d5bcd]]></guid>
   <pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
   <source url=""><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></source>
   <itunes:author><![CDATA[Garrison Hardie]]></itunes:author>
   <itunes:image href="https://assets-cdn2.dropwave.io/2ab40ac0-e99d-4f25-a6d2-541d2c9b290a/cover-art/mUK8zsnHkCK3vep7E1W6UgYb9dTnLenASAMEFha3.jpg"/>
   <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
   <itunes:duration>652</itunes:duration>
   <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
  
  </item><item>
   <title><![CDATA[Daily News Brief for Thursday, November 30th, 2023 [Daily News Brief]]]></title>
   <link/>
   <description><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">This is Garrison Hardie with your CrossPolitic Daily News Brief for Thursday, November 30th, 2023.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Download our new app!:</strong></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">You guys are aware that we have a new app right? If not you should download it right now! Head on over to your app store, and type in &ldquo;CrossPolitic&rdquo;, &ldquo;Fight Laugh Feast&rdquo;, or &ldquo;PubTV&rdquo;. Once you find the app, you may need to update your app, or if you have a droid phone, you may need to delete your current FLF app, and re-download it! Once downloaded you&rsquo;ll be able to view or listen to our content right on your mobile device! As always, if you&rsquo;d like to sign up for a pub membership, you can head on over to fightlaughfeast.com&hellip; that&rsquo;s fightlaughfeast.com.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://www.dailysignal.com/2023/11/29/hidden-tax-how-much-does-regulation-cost-average-american-family/"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.dailysignal.com/2023/11/29/hidden-tax-how-much-does-regulation-cost-average-american-family/</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Here&rsquo;s How Much Regulations Cost Average American Family&mdash;and How Biden Is Making It Worse</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">FIRST ON THE DAILY SIGNAL&mdash;Americans expect to pay federal taxes, but the federal government also picks their pockets in more hidden ways, and President Joe Biden is making the problem worse in pursuing his political agenda, according to the Competitive Enterprise Institute.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">American households pay at least $14,000 in hidden regulatory costs every year,&rdquo; Wayne Crews, the Fred L. Smith fellow in regulatory studies at the institute, says in a new video provided exclusively to The Daily Signal.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://youtu.be/ANxJVzePPG0"><span style="font-weight: 400;" data-rich-links="{&quot;fple-t&quot;:&quot;10,000 Reasons to Reform the Regulatory State&quot;,&quot;fple-u&quot;:&quot;https://youtu.be/ANxJVzePPG0&quot;,&quot;fple-mt&quot;:null,&quot;type&quot;:&quot;first-party-link&quot;}">10,000 Reasons to Reform the Regulatory State</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;">- Play 0:00-1:18</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">His analysis&mdash;the latest in a series of annual reports&mdash;finds that the average American household pays $14,514 annually in a hidden regulatory cost.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Crews calculated the costs of regulation on the entire economy as $1.939 trillion, and found the average cost per household by dividing that gargantuan number by 133.6 million households.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">While federal law requires an annual estimate of the cost of regulation, the federal government has not met that requirement since 2002, according to the report. While the Office of Management and Budget has estimated some costs and benefits of major rules, the report finds those analyses incomplete because they do not encompass all rulemaking in each year.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Crews&rsquo; report uses a baseline of roughly $1.9 trillion for the costs of federal regulation, encompassing compliance costs, economic losses and losses in gross domestic product, social costs, and other costs. The analyst took recent government reports into account to reach the $1.939 trillion figure, although he acknowledged that it represents an estimate &ldquo;based on a nonscientific, disclaimer-laden, of GDP losses and compliance costs derived from available official data and other accessible sources.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The $1.9 trillion represents more than three-fifths the level of corporate pretax profits in 2022 ($3.138 trillion) and a far larger number than estimated corporate tax revenues ($382 billion).</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The report notes that while President Donald Trump&rsquo;s four years &ldquo;brought unique reversals, such as a reduced flow of new rules and some rollbacks of existing ones&rdquo;, President Joe Biden reversed those trends. &ldquo;Unprecedented open-ended deficits now standing at $1.4 trillion annually are expected to top $2 trillion annually by 2030,&rdquo; Crews writes. The national debt is nearing $34 trillion (at $33.8 trillion now, according to the U.S. Treasury), which Crews notes is &ldquo;up from almost $20 trillion when Donald Trump assumed office in 2017.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The report notes that Biden has launched many &ldquo;whole-of-government interventions,&rdquo; most notably on climate change and rooting out &ldquo;inequity from our economy.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&ldquo;These efforts have accelerated a long-standing process that is replacing self-determination and limited government with top-down behavioral, social, and civil rights codes,&rdquo; Crews writes.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Regulations issued by the executive branch far outstrip the number of laws Congress passes each year. During the 2022 calendar year, agencies issued 3,168 rules, while Congress enacted only 247 laws.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">While taxes clearly impact Americans&rsquo; pocketbooks and appear itemized on pay stubs, &ldquo;regulatory costs are baked into prices, without separate charges on receipts,&rdquo; the report notes. &ldquo;Many regulations have opportunity costs, which are invisible and impossible to calculate. They can affect households directly or indirectly, such as when businesses will pass some regulatory costs on to consumers, just as they do the corporate tax.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The report suggests a wide range of reforms to check the growth of regulation. It urges Congress to require congressional approval of significant or controversial agency rules before they become binding. It urges Congress to require annual regulatory transparency report cards and legislation requiring the automatic sunsetting of regulations. It urges Congress to pass a law preventing presidents from using &ldquo;emergency declarations&rdquo; to impose permanent government controls. It also urges Congress to identify which federal agencies do more harm than good and to eliminate them or shrink their budgets. It also urges Congress to set up a regulation-reduction commission to identify unneeded regulations to eliminate.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://mynorthwest.com/3940877/rantz-inside-look-seattle-antifa-antisemites-starbucks/"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://mynorthwest.com/3940877/rantz-inside-look-seattle-antifa-antisemites-starbucks/</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>An inside look as Seattle Antifa, antisemites vandalized Starbucks</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Antisemitic Antifa activists, anarchists and other radicals targeted the Seattle Starbucks Reserve Roastery as part of a call to &ldquo;Block Black Friday.&rdquo; They caused felony-level damage that led to one arrest.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Activists promoted direct action by sharing social media flyers. The flyer claims the protest and mass vandalism were &ldquo;autonomously organized by Seattle area radicals, anarchists, and community members.&rdquo; The hope was to &ldquo;shut [Black Friday] down for Palestine.&rdquo; They were mostly successful.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Exclusive videos from inside the caf&eacute; as Antifa and anarchists vandalized the storefront and taunted customers with vulgar hand gestures and taunts. It got so rowdy and dangerous that activists said they forced Starbucks to close.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Several dozen activists surrounded the Starbucks Roastery. Many of them were dressed in black bloc, a style of clothing intended to hide personally identifiable characteristics so that police have trouble making arrests. It&rsquo;s a hallmark of Antifa action.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The video shows one masked activist tagging the building with the phrase &ldquo;Free Palestine&rdquo; in spray paint. They also spray-painted the Palestinian flag, anarchist symbols and messages like &ldquo;Never Again,&rdquo; &ldquo;Free Gaza,&rdquo; , &ldquo;You are genocide supporters&rdquo; and &ldquo;Land Back.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The video also captures a masked activist flipping off customers. They even carved &ldquo;Free Gaza&rdquo; into the store&rsquo;s wooden door. Another activist pounds his hand on the storefront window, taunting customers. One of the windows was nearly shattered and must be replaced and security cameras on the roof were sprayed with paint.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&ldquo;During all of this, the atmosphere was upbeat but chill, with people eating tamales and drinking coffee that were being distributed from a truck parked next to the demo,&rdquo; an anonymous author published on Puget Sound Anarchists.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The anarchist went on to brag about how effective the Starbucks protest was for their movement.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The damage was significant, yet Seattle Police (SPD) did not intervene.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&ldquo;It was a temporary disruption that was handled and thankfully did not turn into a major issue,&rdquo; a Seattle Police Department spokesperson told The Jason Rantz Show on KTTH. &ldquo;As with any crime, incidents of vandalism are handled on a case-by-case basis. There are a multitude of factors that can determine when officers intervene. We are not at liberty to discuss our tactics as far as when officers will intervene.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The group marched into downtown Seattle after their assault on Starbucks. Once there, they disrupted the annual Seattle Christmas tree lighting ceremony.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The author admits that activists &ldquo;took over the stage soon after arriving and started throwing Christmas decorations to the ground and trashing the scenery.&rdquo; There were a handful of activists who stayed on the stage, holding a banner reading &ldquo;From Turtle Island to Gaza: Land Back.&rdquo; Land Back refers to a movement of literal land reclamation to its so-called original stewards.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">As activists chanted and gave speeches in front of a crowd angry that the ceremony was interrupted, an officer spotted suspect Tarik Aly Youssef, who is based in Vancouver, Washington.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">On a TikTik account (@_thesphinx_) that appears to belong to the 25-year-old suspect, Youssef described himself as a transgender, polyamorous, pansexual, anti-capitalist, autistic Egyptian who is an &ldquo;honorary member of Trantifa&rdquo; (a name for transgender Antifa members). After The Jason Rantz Show on KTTH contacted Youssef via TikTok, the account&rsquo;s videos were removed, and the account appears to be deleted.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://www.foxnews.com/politics/united-nations-set-call-americans-reduce-meat-consumption"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.foxnews.com/politics/united-nations-set-call-americans-reduce-meat-consumption</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>United Nations set to call on Americans to reduce meat consumption</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">A lead United Nations agency overseeing food and agriculture policy is expected to issue a road map in the coming weeks which will call on the West, including America, to dramatically reduce its meat consumption.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The UN's Food &amp; Agriculture Organization (FAO) will publish its so-called global food systems&rsquo; road map during the upcoming COP28 climate summit in Dubai which will kick off on Thursday and extend nearly two weeks until mid-December. FAO's first-of-its-kind document will recommend nations that "over-consume meat" to limit their consumption as part of a broader effort to reduce greenhouse gas emissions, Bloomberg reported.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">"The failure of leading meat and dairy companies to reduce emissions underlines the urgent need for more policy focus on the food and agriculture sector," Jeremy Coller, the chair and founder of the FAIRR Initiative, an investor network that works with financial institutions to promote climate-friendly agriculture worldwide, said in a recent statement.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">In addition to issuing guidelines for reducing meat consumption in the West, the FAO is expected to highlight how farmers should adapt to "erratic weather" and tackle their emissions produced from food waste and use of fertilizer, according to Bloomberg. The recommendations, which the U.S. COP28 delegation may sign onto, will not be binding.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Overall, the road map will seek to guide policy on lowering the climate impact of the global agriculture industry, which has rarely received such attention at past UN climate conferences. Past COP summits have been far more keen to address emissions generated from the global power, transportation and manufacturing sectors.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The global food system &mdash; which includes land-use change, actual agricultural production, packaging and waste management &mdash; generates about 18 billion tons of carbon dioxide per year, the equivalent of 34% of total worldwide emissions, according to a March 2021 study published in the Nature Food journal. FAO data indicates livestock alone is responsible for around 14.5% of global greenhouse gas emissions.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The UN has, for years, called for individuals to ditch animal-based diets, which it says "have a high impact on our planet." Instead, individuals should choose plant-based foods, according to the UN, which can reduce a person's annual carbon footprint by up to 2.1 tons.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">In the U.S., though, agriculture alone generates about 10% of total greenhouse gas emissions, federal data shows. The American agriculture sector accounts for just 1.4% of global emissions and has implemented a wide range of solutions, making it the nation's lowest-emitting economic sector.</span></p>]]></description>
   <author><![CDATA[Garrison Hardie]]></author>
   <enclosure url="https://app.dropwave.io/episode/e7b7fcfd-dbcb-4478-a3a9-86bc9a32656c/daily-news-brief-for-thursday-november-30th-2023.mp3" length="814" type="audio/mp3"/>
   <guid isPermaLink="false"><![CDATA[e7b7fcfd-dbcb-4478-a3a9-86bc9a32656c]]></guid>
   <pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
   <source url=""><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></source>
   <itunes:author><![CDATA[Garrison Hardie]]></itunes:author>
   <itunes:image href="https://assets-cdn2.dropwave.io/2ab40ac0-e99d-4f25-a6d2-541d2c9b290a/cover-art/mUK8zsnHkCK3vep7E1W6UgYb9dTnLenASAMEFha3.jpg"/>
   <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
   <itunes:duration>814</itunes:duration>
   <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
  
  </item><item>
   <title><![CDATA[Daily News Brief for Tuesday, November 28th, 2023 [Daily News Brief]]]></title>
   <link/>
   <description><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">This is Garrison Hardie with your CrossPolitic Daily News Brief for Tuesday, November 28th, 2023.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Kepler Education:</strong></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Kepler is an online marketplace for Classical Christian education that assures parents maintain their agency without forfeiting the assistance and expertise of qualified conservative Christian teachers. Kepler offers university model courses in the classical tradition that fit your schedule and budget. Visit </span><a href="http://www.kepler.education/"><span style="font-weight: 400;">www.kepler.education</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> and use our simple search tool to find the course and teacher that meets your child&rsquo;s needs. Or simply ask for help to get assistance from a real human being.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://www.theguardian.com/world/2023/nov/27/talks-under-way-to-extend-israel-hamas-ceasefire-as-return-to-fighting-looms"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.theguardian.com/world/2023/nov/27/talks-under-way-to-extend-israel-hamas-ceasefire-as-return-to-fighting-looms</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Talks under way to extend Israel-Hamas ceasefire as return to fighting looms</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Talks are under way to extend the temporary ceasefire in Gaza, with Hamas and Israel both saying they would like to see further releases of hostages in return for freedom for more Palestinians held in Israeli jails.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">But the ceasefire is due to expire, threatening a return to the bloody fighting and bombardment that has devastated swaths of Gaza, killed many thousands of civilians and caused an acute humanitarian crisis.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The third release of prisoners and of mostly Israeli hostages held in Gaza by Hamas took place without major problems on Sunday night.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Israel and Hamas have each raised concerns over the lists of hostages and Palestinian prisoners due to be released on Monday, which Qatari mediators are now working to resolve.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&ldquo;There is a slight issue with today&rsquo;s lists. The Qataris are working with both sides to &hellip; avoid delays,&rdquo; an official briefed on the matter said.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Seventeen hostages were released by Hamas on Sunday, including a Russian national and three Thai nationals. The Israelis were all women or children. Thirty-nine Palestinian prisoners, mostly children, were freed from Israeli jails, authorities said.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Benjamin Netanyahu, the Israeli prime minister, has said he did not want to end the ceasefire but pledged that Israel would resume its military offensive in Gaza at the end of the truce.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Netanyahu, who has promised Israelis he will &ldquo;crush&rdquo; Hamas, said he would welcome an extension to allow the release of 10 additional hostages every day in return for freedom for 30 Palestinian prisoners, as agreed under the original deal.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Israeli officials insist they will not call off their offensive until they are certain that Hamas no longer poses a threat to Israel.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Joe Biden said on Sunday that his administration would &ldquo;continue to remain personally engaged to see that this deal is fully implemented and work to extend the deal as well&rdquo;.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Local media in Israel reported optimism among senior officials that the truce, which was the result of several weeks of complex indirect negotiations mediated by the US, Qatar and Egypt, would be extended.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Sixty-two of the more than 240 hostages held by Hamas since last month have been released, one hostage was freed by Israeli forces, and two were found dead inside Gaza. A total of 117 Palestinians have been freed since the truce began.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Between 13,000 and 15,000 Palestinians have been killed by the Israeli offensive launched after the Hamas attack, roughly two-thirds of them women and children, according to the health ministry in Hamas-ruled Gaza. More than 1 million people have been forced from their homes.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The UN says the truce has made it possible to scale up the delivery of food, water and medicine to the largest volume since the start of the war. But the 160 to 200 trucks a day is still less than half what Gaza was importing before the fighting, while humanitarian needs have soared.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Details have emerged of the conditions of the detention of some hostages. Local media has reported shortages of food and medicine, and cramped accommodation possibly underground, but no physical mistreatment. According to one report, a former hostage has told his friends that his captors had brought other children to play with him while he was in captivity. Some learned of the fate of relatives from Hebrew-language radio networks they could listen to. Two teenagers learned that their mother had been killed and their father remained missing only when released.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Calls from the hostages&rsquo; families to prioritise their release have sharpened the dilemma facing Israel&rsquo;s leaders as they seek to reconcile the military offensive with the goal of freeing all of the captives.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://www.dailysignal.com/2023/11/23/new-biden-rule-reveals-transgender-movements-endgame-no-dissenting-parents-allowed/"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.dailysignal.com/2023/11/23/new-biden-rule-reveals-transgender-movements-endgame-no-dissenting-parents-allowed/</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Lack of &lsquo;Affirmation&rsquo; Is Child Abuse: New Biden Rule Applies Transgender Standard to Foster Care</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The transgender standard is set to become a litmus test for parenthood, according to the logic of a new policy working its way through the Department of Health and Human Services under President Joe Biden.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">A new rule in HHS&rsquo; Administration for Children and Families would apply the idea that any lack of &ldquo;affirmation&rdquo; constitutes a form of child abuse to foster care placements. Once that idea takes root in foster care, child protective services agencies might start applying it more broadly.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The rule would reinterpret the Social Security Act, which requires agencies to ensure that each child in foster care receives &ldquo;safe and proper&rdquo; care. The rule would lay out steps agencies must take to meet that requirement for &ldquo;LGBTQI+ children,&rdquo; defined as kids who &ldquo;identify as lesbian, gay, bisexual, transgender, queer or questioning, intersex, as well as children who are non-binary, or have non-conforming gender identity or expression.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Before agencies place a child with a foster parent, known as a &ldquo;provider,&rdquo; that person must &ldquo;establish an environment free of hostility, mistreatment, or abuse based on the child&rsquo;s LGBTQI+ status;&rdquo; receive training &ldquo;to be prepared with the appropriate knowledge and skills to provide for the needs of the child related to the child&rsquo;s self-identified sexual orientation, gender identity, and gender expression;&rdquo; and must be able to &ldquo;facilitate the child&rsquo;s access to age-appropriate resources, services, and activities that support their health and well-being.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">As the Ethics and Public Policy Center&rsquo;s Rachel Morrison pointed out for The Federalist Society, the rule does not define &ldquo;hostility,&rdquo; &ldquo;mistreatment,&rdquo; or &ldquo;abuse.&rdquo; However, it does clarify that &ldquo;a provider who attempted to undermine, suppress, or change the sexual orientation, gender identity, or gender expression of a child, including through the use of so-called &lsquo;conversion therapy,&rsquo; would not be a safe and appropriate placement.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The proposed rule cites medical associations such as the American Psychological Association to claim that efforts to &ldquo;undermine, suppress, or change&rdquo; sexual orientation, gender identity, or gender expression &ldquo;are not supported by evidence and have been rejected as harmful.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The rule does not acknowledge that gender ideology has infiltrated these medical associations and that many doctors&mdash;including those who once embraced gender ideology&mdash;have warned against confusing children on their gender and putting them on a path to mutilating their own bodies.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Dr. Stephen B. Levine, a psychiatrist and early proponent of transgender medical interventions, joined and briefly helped lead the Harry Benjamin International Gender Dysphoria Association, which later became the World Professional Association for Transgender Health, the central medical group that organizations such as the American Psychiatric Association rely upon.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">European countries, long considered more &ldquo;progressive&rdquo; than the U.S., have found a lack of evidence for medical interventions on children and are recommending a &ldquo;watchful waiting&rdquo; approach for minors.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Yet Levine argues that &ldquo;affirming&rdquo; a transgender identity is a &ldquo;powerful psychotherapeutic intervention&rdquo; that will set kids on the path to mutilation and sterilization&mdash;long before they have any concept about what their own fertility means.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Under Biden&rsquo;s proposed new rule, any potential foster parent who aims to protect a child from this confusion and damage may soon face expulsion from the program. That means the process will be designed to weed out guardians who actually would take good care of the kids and enable guardians who would assist in harming them.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">California&rsquo;s Democratic governor, Gavin Newsom, signed a bill turning California into a &ldquo;sanctuary state&rdquo; for &ldquo;gender-affirming care,&rdquo; which the law defines as an absolute right. The law gives California courts the ability to award custody over a child if someone removes the child from his or her parents in another state in order to obtain such &ldquo;care&rdquo; for that child despite the parents&rsquo; disagreement.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://dailycaller.com/2023/11/27/businesses-diversity-equity-inclusion-economic-uncertainty/"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://dailycaller.com/2023/11/27/businesses-diversity-equity-inclusion-economic-uncertainty/</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Businesses Ditch &lsquo;Diversity&rsquo; Initiatives In Droves Amid Economic Uncertainty</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Diversity, equity and inclusion (DEI) initiatives lost steam in 2023 compared to previous years as companies increasingly shift resources due to tightening economic condition</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The total percentage of American organizations with a DEI budget dropped 4 percentage points, from 58% in 2022 to 54% in 2023, while the number of organizations with a DEI strategy fell 9 points in that same time frame, according to a report from a consulting firm. DEI initiatives in the workplace gained huge traction following the death of George Floyd, which encouraged companies to divert resources to the practice, but now &ldquo;external forces,&rdquo; including tightening economic conditions as well as public and judicial pressure, are pushing back on those efforts.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&ldquo;After two years of unprecedented investment sparked by 2020&rsquo;s racial justice movement, this year, global momentum around DEI slowed,&rdquo; according to the report from Paradigm. &ldquo;There are a number of headwinds contributing to this shift: the first is economic uncertainty that not only led to reduced spending across the board, it also firmly shifted the power balance back to employers.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Despite the decline in funding, there was a 6-point increase in the number of companies that had a senior DEI leader and an 8-point increase in organizations that had goals related to representation for women in leadership from 2022 to 2023, according to Paradigm. A total of 20% of companies in 2023 had goals related to increasing employment related to race or ethnicity, which is a 4-point increase year-over-year.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The shift follows concerns from companies that the Supreme Court could target DEI and race-based hiring in the workplace the same way it struck down race-based admissions at colleges and universities earlier this year. A pair of decisions by the Supreme Court in June involving Harvard and the University of North Carolina cumulatively ruled that using race as a factor in college admissions is not permissible under the Fourteenth Amendment of the U.S. Constitution.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&ldquo;Over the past several months, we&rsquo;ve heard from a number of HR leaders who are de-emphasizing data and analytics as a part of their DEI efforts, in response to the changing legal landscape and increased scrutiny on DEI efforts,&rdquo; according to the report from Paradigm.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Only 26% of companies examine the final results of hiring by race or ethnicity, while 33% analyze promotions in the same manner, according to Paradigm. Around 36% of organizations measured the attrition rate of their employees by race or ethnicity.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Businesses pulled back from hiring in October, adding only 150,000 jobs for the month compared to 297,000 in September, while unemployment ticked up to 3.9% from 3.8%. The Leading Economic Index predicted that 2024 will only see 0.8% in the U.S. economy due to a possible recession.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://nypost.com/2023/11/26/business/ny-retailers-blast-hochul-over-theft-which-has-cost-stores-4-4-billion/"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://nypost.com/2023/11/26/business/ny-retailers-blast-hochul-over-theft-which-has-cost-stores-4-4-billion/</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>NY retailers lost $4.4 billion due to organized shoplifting rings in 2022: group</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Retailers across New York state say there&rsquo;s no end in sight to the rising epidemic of organized shoplifting rings &mdash; and warn it could lead to more store closures, increased costs for consumers and threats of violence against store employees.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Store owners said they lost $4.4 billion last year as a result of retail theft &mdash; which they say adds to the urgency for Gov. Kathy Hochul to crack down.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">However, Hochul vetoed a bipartisan bill last week &mdash; to the chagrin of store owners &mdash; that would have created a task force to combat organized theft.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Hochul rejected a proposal that would have created a 15-member panel made up of experts appointed by the governor, Legislature and the state attorney general that would have put together a list of recommendations to respond to retail theft.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The Retail Council of New York State, the Albany-based lobbying group which represents retailers statewide, said it was &ldquo;extremely disappointed&rdquo; by Hochul&rsquo;s veto.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Melissa O&rsquo;Connor, the president and CEO of the group, released a statement saying that she urged the governor to take &ldquo;immediate action&rdquo; so as to formulate &ldquo;an effective, collaborative response to this problem.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&ldquo;She made it abundantly clear that retail theft prevention will be a priority for her administration, and we look forward to working with her to achieve results,&rdquo; O&rsquo;Connor said.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">A spokesperson for Hochul said that adopting the proposal would have cost the state $35 million &mdash; an expenditure that wasn&rsquo;t allotted in the most recent budget.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Law enforcement officials from New York City to Albany to Syracuse have reported increases in incidents of retail theft &mdash; blaming the spike on progressive prosecutors who encourages criminal behavior with lenient punishment for shoplifters.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Last month, the chief of police in Syracuse said that the city has seen a 55% spike in shoplifting since 2021 &mdash; and that&rsquo;s a conservative estimate.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&ldquo;That number is likely higher because businesses often don&rsquo;t report it &mdash; but they do continue to express concerns,&rdquo; Syracuse Police Chief Joe Cecile said.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">So far this year, the Albany Police Department has fielded 23 calls for larcenies at a single Stewart&rsquo;s convenience store on Central Avenue &mdash; up from 14 at the same time in 2022.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The rash of retail thefts at the location forced the owner to shut down.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">A New York Police Department spokesperson pointed to crime statistics showing that there were more than 93,000 incidents of petty larceny through the end of October &mdash; which is 29% higher compared to the same period two years ago but 5% lower compared to the same period last year.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Around one-third of all shoplifting arrests in the five boroughs last year involved just 327 people who were collectively arrested and re-arrested a total of more than 6,000 times, according to the NYPD.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">These 327 alleged shoplifters targeted 18 department stores and seven chain pharmacy locations, which accounted for 20% of all complaints, the NYPD said.</span></p>]]></description>
   <author><![CDATA[Garrison Hardie]]></author>
   <enclosure url="https://app.dropwave.io/episode/83f73ff3-9ea0-429b-85a4-4be78e6bc1c4/daily-news-brief-for-tuesday-november-28th-2023.mp3" length="864" type="audio/mp3"/>
   <guid isPermaLink="false"><![CDATA[83f73ff3-9ea0-429b-85a4-4be78e6bc1c4]]></guid>
   <pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2023 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
   <source url=""><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></source>
   <itunes:author><![CDATA[Garrison Hardie]]></itunes:author>
   <itunes:image href="https://assets-cdn2.dropwave.io/2ab40ac0-e99d-4f25-a6d2-541d2c9b290a/cover-art/mUK8zsnHkCK3vep7E1W6UgYb9dTnLenASAMEFha3.jpg"/>
   <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
   <itunes:duration>864</itunes:duration>
   <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
  
  </item><item>
   <title><![CDATA[Daily News Brief for Wednesday, November 22nd, 2023 [Daily News Brief]]]></title>
   <link/>
   <description><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">This is Garrison Hardie with your CrossPolitic Daily News Brief for Wednesday, November 22nd, 2023.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Pub Membership Plug:</strong></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Public Houses, or Pubs, are not just places to drink beer, wine, cider, or even something a little stronger. It is also a unique social center, very often the focus of community life in villages, towns, and cities throughout the length and breadth of the world. We here at CrossPolitic hope to emulate that for you and yours. That&rsquo;s why you should grab yourself a pub membership at fightlaughfeast.com&hellip; we need you on this ride with us. So pull up a chair, grab a pint, and join us on this ride at fightlaughfeast.com - that&rsquo;s fightlaughfeast.com.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Ladies and gentlemen, we start today&rsquo;s news brief with a broken record to announce!&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://www.foxnews.com/sports/trans-swimmer-breaks-nj-college-record-switching-mens-team-womens"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.foxnews.com/sports/trans-swimmer-breaks-nj-college-record-switching-mens-team-womens</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Trans swimmer breaks New Jersey college record after switching from men's team to women's</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Yes, yes&hellip; Lia Thomas 2.0. Mediocre men striking again!</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">A transgender swimmer at Ramapo College of New Jersey broke a women's school record over the weekend after competing for the men's team for three years.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Meghan Cortez-Fields won first place and broke a school record in the 100-yard butterfly with a time of 57.22 at the Cougar Splash Invitational, a two-day meet between six schools in Dallas, Pennsylvania. She also came in first place in the 200-yard individual medley and earned second place in the 200-yard butterfly.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The Ramapo swim team congratulated Cortez-Fields on Instagram for breaking the school record but deleted the post after former NCAA swimmer Riley Gaines drew attention to meet results on X.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">"Those who choose to remain blind to the injustice of allowing mediocre male athletes to become record-breaking female athletes are either incompetent or misogynists. There is no in-between anymore," Gaines, an ambassador for the Independent Women's Forum, told Fox News. "Women are being asked to smile and step aside and allow these men onto our teams all the while stripping us of opportunities, privacy, and safety."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">A Ramapo spokesperson told Fox News the school "supports all of our student-athletes."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">"The original post of Meghan&rsquo;s achievement was deleted by a peer who wanted to protect their teammate from insulting comments on the post," the spokesperson continued. "The College continues to post team and individual student-athlete achievements for all programs on our Athletics website."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Cortez-Fields swam on Ramapo&rsquo;s men's team for three years before moving to the women&rsquo;s team this season as a senior. Last year, she told The Ramapo News she admired Lia Thomas, the trans-University of Pennsylvania swimmer who won an NCAA Championship in 2022.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Some hailed Thomas for her bravery, while others, like Gaines, accused her of robbing biological females of opportunities to compete and win.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Cortez-Fields has won at least one heat in three of the four women's meets so far this year.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://www.breitbart.com/sports/2023/11/20/trans-athlete-who-seriously-injured-female-player-quits-team-after-opponents-refuse-play-against-him/"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.breitbart.com/sports/2023/11/20/trans-athlete-who-seriously-injured-female-player-quits-team-after-opponents-refuse-play-against-him/</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Trans Athlete Who Seriously Injured Female Player Quits Team After Opponents Refuse to Play Against Him</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">A male-born transgender athlete has quit a British soccer team when faced with opposing teams refusing to play against his team after he broke an opponent&rsquo;s knee during a match. But even after quitting, the trans player is threatening to sue.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Opponents had refused to play against Francesca Needham, 30, after he broke a female player&rsquo;s knee as she tried to block his shot. Many claimed they were &ldquo;terrified&rdquo; to face Needham on the field, according to the Daily Mail.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Needham ultimately resigned from the Rossington Main Ladies team in Doncaster, South Yorkshire, saying he did so for the good of the team after many opponents refused to play them. But he was not happy to fade off into the sunset.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">In a statement to the team&rsquo;s Facebook page, Needham decried the fact that he &ldquo;faced challenges from teams unwilling to play against us while I am on the field.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">He went on to warn about legal action.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&ldquo;This unfortunate circumstance has prompted me to investigate pursuing a case of discrimination, as I believe it represents a breach of a code of conduct regarding diversity and inclusion, as well as safeguarding of adults in football established by both the Football Association and the Sheffield and Hallamshire Women and Girls League,&rdquo; he wrote.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&ldquo;It was obvious,&rdquo; the manager told the Mail. &ldquo;Unfortunately, the FA allowed it to happen but didn&rsquo;t let anyone know. She&rsquo;s quite a big, strong player. People have refused to play because they are worried about the safety of the players.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&ldquo;My players were backing out of challenges as psychologically it&rsquo;s quite a big thing when you are playing against a biological man, it&rsquo;s quite scary. They were terrified,&rdquo; he added.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Another league manager said that he has teenagers on his team, and parents were not happy over Needham&rsquo;s inclusion.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://redstate.com/jeffc/2023/11/21/bombshell-report-j6-footage-shows-capitol-police-officers-firing-rubber-bullets-at-peaceful-protesters-n2166603"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://redstate.com/jeffc/2023/11/21/bombshell-report-j6-footage-shows-capitol-police-officers-firing-rubber-bullets-at-peaceful-protesters-n2166603</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Bombshell Report: J6 Footage Shows Capitol Police Officers Firing Rubber Bullets at Peaceful Protesters</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">In what could possibly be a major revelation related to the J6 riot at the U.S. Capitol building, a recent report suggests that Capitol Police fired rubber bullets into a peaceful crowd of Trump supporters during the incident. If true, this development raises serious questions about the potential role of law enforcement in the escalation of violence on that day.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Human Events published a report detailing an interview between conservative commentator Jack Posobiec and conservative activist Raheem Kassam, who were both present near the Capitol building on Jan. 6, 2021. The report claimed that new footage released by House Speaker Mike Johnson shows that Capitol Police, at least in one instance, opened fire on a crowd of peaceful protesters.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">New footage from January 6, 2021, released by Speaker Mike Johnson, reveals that Capitol Police fired rubber bullets and other projectiles into the non-violent crowd that was protesting outside of the building, inciting chaos and confusion.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Jack Posobiec and Raheem Kassam were reporting on the grounds in Washington DC that day, walking towards the Capitol when they heard flash bangs go off at around 1:10 pm EST, right around the time President Donald Trump&rsquo;s speech was ending.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Posobiec hosted Kassam on his show, Human Events, Monday to recount the events and timeline of the day from their perspective now that these new revelations have finally come to light.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Raheem recalled hearing a bang for the first time and initially thought it sounded like &ldquo;pallets falling off of the back of a truck&rdquo; before quickly getting a better view from a rooftop of the scuffle unfolding.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://twitter.com/i/status/1726698078399308152"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://twitter.com/i/status/1726698078399308152</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> - Play Video&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The footage showed law enforcement firing non-lethal rounds into a crowd that was protesting outside the Capitol building, which incited chaos and confusion among the participants.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Last week, Speaker Johnson announced the release of all the J6 footage, explaining that it would allow people &ldquo;to see for themselves what happened that day, rather than having to rely upon the interpretations of a small group of government officials,&rdquo; a thinly veiled dig at the Democratic House Select Committee that was formed shortly after the incident.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">If Kassam&rsquo;s claims are true and it is verified by further investigation, it would further wreck the narrative spun by Democrats and others on the left about the matter. It would mean that law enforcement is, at least in part, responsible for the violence that occurred at the Capitol building.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://www.dailyfetched.com/truth-social-files-defamation-lawsuit-against-20-leftist-media-outlets/"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.dailyfetched.com/truth-social-files-defamation-lawsuit-against-20-leftist-media-outlets/</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Truth Social Files Massive Defamation Lawsuit against 20 Leftist Media Outlets</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Trump-owned social media company Truth Social filed a defamation lawsuit on Monday against 20 leftist media outlets and two social media companies for defamation.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Plaintiff Trump Media &amp; Technology Group Corp sued the following outlets:</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The Guardian</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Hollywood Reporter</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The Miami Herald</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Reuters</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Rolling Stone</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The Hill</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The suit alleges:</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&ldquo;An unprecedented and seemingly coordinated media campaign by no less than 20 major media outlets, to attack Trump Media &amp; Technology Group (&ldquo;TMTG&rdquo;) and its social media platform, Truth Social, by falsely reporting that TMTG had lost $73 million.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The suit claimed the number was &ldquo;an utter fabrication&rdquo; and that each defendant, &ldquo;in apparent coordination,&rdquo; published the number almost in unison.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The suit claims the outlets sourced an SEC filing, but that $73 million loss amount is not contained in the cited filing.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Truth Social alleges that this was &ldquo;a coordinated effort&rdquo; to damage its reputation and hinder an anticipated merger.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The suit contends:</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&ldquo;All defendants ran nearly identical headlines that reported some variation of &lsquo;Trump&rsquo;s Truth Social&rsquo; having lost &lsquo;$73 million.'&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The suit states the false reports &ldquo;deeply harmed&rdquo; Truth Social as it had the effect of &ldquo;eroding faith in the company&rsquo;s operations and management.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">It also adds that it made it &ldquo;more difficult&rdquo; for the company to raise additional funds ahead of its anticipated merger, which is currently pending with the SEC.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Rumble CEO Chris Pavlovski said:</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&ldquo;Truth Social just filed an unprecedented defamation lawsuit incorporating twenty media companies. The tide is finally turning, corporate media and activists are going to feel the heat.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Meanwhile, Elon Musk has initiated a &ldquo;thermonuclear lawsuit&rdquo; against the George Soros-backed Media Matters for America.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">In a statement attached to a post on X, Musk said:</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&ldquo;This week, Media Matters for America posted a story that completely misrepresented the real user experience on X in another attempt to undermine freedom of speech and mislead advertisers.&rdquo;</span></p>]]></description>
   <author><![CDATA[Garrison Hardie]]></author>
   <enclosure url="https://app.dropwave.io/episode/dea6204a-5c64-48cf-b192-1f905c706e85/daily-news-brief-for-wednesday-november-22nd-2023.mp3" length="652" type="audio/mp3"/>
   <guid isPermaLink="false"><![CDATA[dea6204a-5c64-48cf-b192-1f905c706e85]]></guid>
   <pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
   <source url=""><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></source>
   <itunes:author><![CDATA[Garrison Hardie]]></itunes:author>
   <itunes:image href="https://assets-cdn2.dropwave.io/2ab40ac0-e99d-4f25-a6d2-541d2c9b290a/cover-art/mUK8zsnHkCK3vep7E1W6UgYb9dTnLenASAMEFha3.jpg"/>
   <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
   <itunes:duration>652</itunes:duration>
   <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
  
  </item><item>
   <title><![CDATA[Daily News Brief for Tuesday, November 21st, 2023 [Daily News Brief]]]></title>
   <link/>
   <description><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">This is Garrison Hardie with your CrossPolitic Daily News Brief for Tuesday, November 21st, 2023.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Download our new app!:</strong></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">You guys are aware that we have a new app right? If not you should download it right now! Head on over to your app store, and type in &ldquo;CrossPolitic&rdquo;, &ldquo;Fight Laugh Feast&rdquo;, or &ldquo;PubTV&rdquo;. Once you find the app, you may need to update your app, or if you have a droid phone, you may need to delete your current FLF app, and re-download it! Once downloaded you&rsquo;ll be able to view or listen to our content right on your mobile device! As always, if you&rsquo;d like to sign up for a pub membership, you can head on over to fightlaughfeast.com&hellip; that&rsquo;s fightlaughfeast.com.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://nypost.com/2023/11/20/news/supreme-court-spurns-chauvin-appeal-of-george-floyd-verdict/"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://nypost.com/2023/11/20/news/supreme-court-spurns-chauvin-appeal-of-george-floyd-verdict/</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Supreme Court won&rsquo;t hear Derek Chauvin&rsquo;s appeal of George Floyd murder conviction</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The Supreme Court said Monday that it would not hear former Minneapolis police officer Derek Chauvin&rsquo;s appeal of his second-degree murder conviction in the May 2020 death of George Floyd.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Chauvin was found guilty by a state court in April 2021 and sentenced to 22 1/2 years in prison in connection with Floyd&rsquo;s May 25, 2020, death, which triggered riots across the country and a prolonged debate on race relations in America.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The high court did not specify why it declined to take up the appeal and did not indicate whether any justices would have heard the case.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Chauvin, 47, is also appealing his conviction and 21-year sentence on separate federal charges in connection with Floyd&rsquo;s death. Those punishments were not considered by the high court.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The ex-cop&rsquo;s lawyers had argued their client was denied a fair trial due to the publicity surrounding the case and concerns about potential violence if he was acquitted.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&ldquo;Mr. Chauvin&rsquo;s case shows the profound difficulties trial courts have to ensure a criminal defendant&rsquo;s right to an impartial jury consistently when extreme cases arise,&rdquo; Chauvin&rsquo;s legal team told the Supreme Court.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&ldquo;This was particularly true here when the jurors themselves had a vested interest in finding Mr. Chauvin guilty in order to avoid further rioting in the community in which they lived and the possible threat of physical harm to them or their families.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Approximately nine minutes of harrowing cellphone footage showed Chauvin placing his knee on Floyd&rsquo;s neck despite pleas from the 46-year-old black man that he couldn&rsquo;t breathe.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Floyd was being arrested for allegedly using a counterfeit $20 bill when Chauvin confronted him. A medical examiner concluded that recent methamphetamine and fentanyl use may have contributed to his death as well.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Chauvin&rsquo;s legal team had argued his case to the Minnesota Court of Appeals, but that court upheld his conviction back in April and declined to give him a new trial.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Then in July, the highest court in Minnesota upheld the lower court rulings, which led to the request to the US Supreme Court.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The nine-member Supreme Court receives somewhere around 7,000 case requests on average every year and typically only accepts between 90 and 150 of them.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/policy/infrastructure/buttigieg-promises-less-chaos-travelers-2022-season-lurks-memories"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/policy/infrastructure/buttigieg-promises-less-chaos-travelers-2022-season-lurks-memories</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Buttigieg promises less chaos for travelers as 2022 nightmare season lurks in memories</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Transportation Secretary Pete Buttigieg said this Thanksgiving travel season is expected to be one of the busiest in U.S. history, but travelers can anticipate fewer flight cancellations than they've seen in recent years.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Speaking alongside Federal Aviation Administration Administrator Mike Whitaker at a Monday news conference, Buttigieg said, &ldquo;We are seeing more people flying than ever with fewer cancellations.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The National Airspace System is reporting the lowest cancellation rates in five years. Flight cancellations are down to 1.3% so far in 2023, compared to 2.3% in 2022, according to preliminary data from the Aviation System Performance Metrics.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Airlines have made some improvements from post-pandemic complications that were seen in Southwest&rsquo;s 2022 holiday travel disaster. Canceled and delayed flights affected an estimated 2 million passengers, and the company lost around $220 million in the final three months of last year.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The FAA is investigating multiple domestic airlines for unrealistic scheduling of flights, including Southwest&rsquo;s December meltdown.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&ldquo;In the Southwest case, there was a huge volume of passengers impacted, which means there's been a huge volume of work for the team to go through,&rdquo; Buttigieg said. &ldquo;But I can tell you that it's underway and that we intend to send a continued signal that airlines need to only schedule the flights that they can serve.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&ldquo;I want to remind the industry that unrealistic scheduling is prohibited under the law,&rdquo; Buttigieg added.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Whitaker said skies will remain extremely busy like last year, adding, "We will be working around the clock to make sure passengers get to their destination safely."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">In an earlier projection, the Transportation Security Administration said the Tuesday and Wednesday before Thanksgiving and the Sunday after are the busiest travel days. TSA is expecting to screen 2.6 million passengers on Tuesday, 2.7 million passengers on Wednesday, and 2.9 million passengers on Sunday, the busiest travel day.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&ldquo;We expect this holiday season to be our busiest ever. In 2023, we have already seen seven of the top 10 busiest travel days in TSA&rsquo;s history,&rdquo; TSA Administrator David Pekoske said in a press release last week. &ldquo;We are ready for the anticipated volumes and are working closely with our airline and airport partners to make sure we are prepared for this busy holiday travel season."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://redstate.com/mike_miller/2023/11/19/michigan-township-declares-itself-a-second-amendment-sanctuary-promptly-forms-militia-n2166546"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://redstate.com/mike_miller/2023/11/19/michigan-township-declares-itself-a-second-amendment-sanctuary-promptly-forms-militia-n2166546</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Michigan Township Declares Itself a 'Second Amendment Sanctuary,' Promptly Forms Militia</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">As the Biden Border Crisis continues unchecked, Chicago and New York City recently made news with their efforts to push back against the shipping of illegal aliens to their respective "sanctuary cities."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The Holton Township Board of Trustees in Michigan's Muskegon County last Tuesday adopted a resolution declaring the township a "Second Amendment Sanctuary" and also adopted an addendum establishing a township militia.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Self-explanatory, on the surface:</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Whereas, the Holton Township Board declares and confirms to express its intent to stand as a Sanctuary Township for Second Amendment rights, and to oppose, within the limits of the Constitution of the United States and the Commonwealth of Michigan, any efforts to unconstitutionally restrict such rights.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Holton Township officials made clear to the media that the resolution means the township will not enforce red flag laws restricting firearms or ammunition possession.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">[Have long been promoted by the left] as a way to prevent gun violence by allowing law enforcement to temporarily seize firearms from individuals deemed to be a danger to themselves or others. While this may sound like a good idea on the surface, there are several compelling reasons not to rely on this approach.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">First and foremost, red flag laws violate due process and the constitutional rights of gun owners. Under these laws, individuals can have their firearms confiscated based solely on the suspicion of a third party, without being given the opportunity to defend themselves or even be heard in court. This is a clear violation of the Fourth and Fifth Amendments, which protect against unreasonable searches and seizures, and guarantee due process of law.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Moreover, red flag laws are inherently subjective and can be easily abused. The criteria for determining who is a &ldquo;dangerous&rdquo; individual are often vague and open to interpretation, leaving room for personal bias and political agendas to influence the decision-making process.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">In other words, in the case of the Holton County Township Board: "Not in our township. Not on our watch."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The Militia Public Security Act addendum states the township is adopting &ldquo;policies necessary for the security and rights of Holton Township residents,&rdquo; including a militia compromised of everyday citizens.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Legal residents of the township are eligible to join the militia and may make their intentions known by acknowledging their intent on social media or stating their intent by letter to the Township Militia. Restrictions include:</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://www.newsmax.com/world/globaltalk/china-taiwan-airspace/2023/11/19/id/1142840/"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.newsmax.com/world/globaltalk/china-taiwan-airspace/2023/11/19/id/1142840/</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Taiwan Reports Chinese Aircraft Threatening Airspace</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Taiwan reported renewed Chinese military activity around the island on Sunday, with nine aircraft crossing the sensitive median line of the Taiwan Strait and warships carrying out "combat readiness patrols."</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Democratically-governed Taiwan, which China claims as its own territory, has complained for the past four years of regular Chinese military patrols and drills near the island, as Beijing seeks to pressure Taipei over its sovereignty claims.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">With Chinese President Xi Jinping in San Francisco last week for the Asia Pacific Economic Cooperation (APEC) summit, where he met U.S. President Joe Biden, the scale of that military activity around Taiwan had scaled off.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">But Taiwan's defense ministry reported that starting onSunday morning it had detected nine Chinese aircraft crossing the Taiwan Strait's median line, which had previously served as an unofficial barrier between the two and which Chinese planes now regularly fly over.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The aircraft involved included Su-30 and J-10 fighters, as well as early warning and electronic warfare aircraft, the ministry said.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The aircraft were accompanying Chinese warships carrying out "joint combat readiness patrols" it added.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Taiwan sent its own forces to monitor, the ministry said.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">China's defense ministry did not answer calls seeking comment. China says its activities near Taiwan are aimed at "collusion" between Taiwan separatists and the United States and to protect China's territorial integrity.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Taiwan's government, which has repeatedly offered talks with China, rejects Beijing's sovereignty claims and says only the island's people can decide their future.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Taiwan was a major focus of the Biden-Xi talks in San Francisco.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Xi told Biden during their four-hour meeting on Wednesday that</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Taiwan was the biggest, most dangerous issue in U.S.-China ties, according to a senior U.S. official.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Taiwan holds presidential and parliamentary elections on Jan. 13, with the island's fraught relations with China an important topic on the campaign trail.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Over the past year and a half China has staged two large-scale war games around Taiwan, though China's air force has not flown over the island or into its territorial air space.</span></p>]]></description>
   <author><![CDATA[Garrison Hardie]]></author>
   <enclosure url="https://app.dropwave.io/episode/19561086-e454-434e-9495-aab58dd64890/daily-news-brief-for-tuesday-november-21st-2023.mp3" length="623" type="audio/mp3"/>
   <guid isPermaLink="false"><![CDATA[19561086-e454-434e-9495-aab58dd64890]]></guid>
   <pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
   <source url=""><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></source>
   <itunes:author><![CDATA[Garrison Hardie]]></itunes:author>
   <itunes:image href="https://assets-cdn2.dropwave.io/2ab40ac0-e99d-4f25-a6d2-541d2c9b290a/cover-art/mUK8zsnHkCK3vep7E1W6UgYb9dTnLenASAMEFha3.jpg"/>
   <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
   <itunes:duration>623</itunes:duration>
   <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
  
  </item><item>
   <title><![CDATA[Daily News Brief for Friday, November 17th, 2023 [Daily News Brief]]]></title>
   <link/>
   <description><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">This is Garrison Hardie with your CrossPolitic Daily News Brief for Friday, November 17th, 2023.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>Download our new app!:</strong></span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">You guys are aware that we have a new app right? If not you should download it right now! Head on over to your app store, and type in &ldquo;CrossPolitic&rdquo;, &ldquo;Fight Laugh Feast&rdquo;, or &ldquo;PubTV&rdquo;. Once you find the app, you may need to update your app, or if you have a droid phone, you may need to delete your current FLF app, and re-download it! Once downloaded you&rsquo;ll be able to view or listen to our content right on your mobile device! As always, if you&rsquo;d like to sign up for a pub membership, you can head on over to fightlaughfeast.com&hellip; that&rsquo;s fightlaughfeast.com.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://www.foxnews.com/politics/house-ethics-committee-head-moves-to-expel-george-santos-after-release-of-damning-report"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.foxnews.com/politics/house-ethics-committee-head-moves-to-expel-george-santos-after-release-of-damning-report</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>House Ethics Committee head to move to expel George Santos after release of damning report</strong></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The chairman of the House Ethics Committee will move to expel Rep. George Santos, R-N.Y., from Congress after the release of a damning report into the embattled Long Island Republican.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">"Chairman Guest feels that the evidence uncovered in the Committee&rsquo;s investigation is more than sufficient to warrant punishment, and that the most appropriate punishment is expulsion," Republican Mississippi Rep. Michael Guest's personal office told Fox News Digital on Thursday.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">"So, separate from the Committee process and his role as Chairman, he plans to file an expulsion resolution during tomorrow&rsquo;s 9:00 am pro forma session."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The ethics committee released a damning report that accused Santos of having "used campaign funds for personal purposes" and "engaged in fraudulent conduct," among other allegations.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Guest filing the resolution on Friday tees up an expected vote on whether to boot Santos from the House sometime after lawmakers return from the Thanksgiving break on Nov. 28.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">A 56-page deep dive into the allegations against Santos by the panel's Investigative subcommittee detailed campaign funds being spent at spas and luxury stores, among other questionable places.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The bipartisan subcommittee unanimously agreed that Santos "knowingly caused his campaign committee to file false or incomplete reports with the Federal Election Commission; used campaign funds for personal purposes; engaged in fraudulent conduct in connection with RedStone Strategies LLC; and engaged in knowing and willful violations of the Ethics in Government Act as it relates to his Financial Disclosure (FD) Statements filed with the House."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">That includes $50,000 in campaign donations that were wired to Santos' personal account on Oct. 21, 2022, and allegedly used to, among other things, "pay down personal credit card bills and other debt; make a $4,127.80 purchase at Hermes; and for smaller purchases at OnlyFans; Sephora; and for meals and for parking."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Santos also spent more than $2,200 at resorts in Atlantic City, New Jersey, from July 23, 2022, to July 24, 2022, according to the report, despite a staffer telling the subcommittee that "he was not aware of any events in Atlantic City and did not attend any campaign events in Atlantic City."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Santos posted a lengthy response to the report on X, in which he announced he would not seek re-election in 2024 and accused the House Ethics Committee of bias.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">"If there was a single ounce of ETHICS in the &lsquo;Ethics committee&rsquo;, they would have not released this biased report. The Committee went to extraordinary lengths to smear myself and my legal team about me not being forthcoming (My legal bills suggest otherwise)," Santos wrote. "It is a disgusting politicized smear that shows the depths of how low our federal government has sunk. Everyone who participated in this grave miscarriage of Justice should all be ashamed of themselves."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">GOP lawmakers from New York previously moved to expel Santos earlier this month, but the effort failed along bipartisan lines. Most Democrats who said they voted to punt the measure explained they were waiting for the findings of the ethics committee report.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://dailycaller.com/2023/11/16/chinas-xi-receives-standing-ovation-american-business-leaders/"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://dailycaller.com/2023/11/16/chinas-xi-receives-standing-ovation-american-business-leaders/</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>China&rsquo;s Xi Receives Standing Ovation From American Business Leaders</strong></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Chinese President Xi Jinping received a standing ovation from American business leaders during an exclusive dinner in San Francisco on Wednesday.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Xi met with President Joe Biden on the sidelines of the Asia-Pacific Economic Cooperation (APEC) conference in San Francisco Wednesday and had talks on a broad range of issues, including military communications, fentanyl trafficking and Taiwan. During a private dinner in the city&rsquo;s downtown Hyatt Regency hours later, Xi gave a speech about the need for China-U.S. cooperation and received praise from hundreds of high-level American business executives.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">&ldquo;China is pursuing high-quality development, and the United States is revitalizing its economy,&rdquo; Xi said during his speech. &ldquo;There is plenty of room for our cooperation.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Among the leaders at the reception and dinner were Apple CEO Tim Cook, Blackrock CEO Larry Fink, Tesla and X CEO Elon Musk and a number of executives from FedEx, Qualcomm, KKR, Blackstone and Boeing, according to The Wall Street Journal. Tickets to attend the dinner started at $2,000 per person, up to $40,000 for a chance to dine with Xi at his table.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">&ldquo;I think it&rsquo;s important Americans and Chinese are meeting again face to face,&rdquo; said managing director for China of McLarty Associates John L. Holden, who attended the dinner, according to The New York Times. &ldquo;This is not a magic bullet, but it is something that can provide possibilities that wouldn&rsquo;t exist otherwise.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">&ldquo;All of you here this evening remain keenly interested to do business in China, and to find ways to advance our bilateral economic relationship,&rdquo; Commerce Secretary Gina Raimondo told the audience at the dinner, CNBC reported. &ldquo;I know that, because half of you have come to see me to tell me that.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">During his speech, Xi claimed that China is &ldquo;ready to be partners and friends&rdquo; rather than adversaries with the U.S, according to the Times. He also evoked China&rsquo;s history with the U.S., recalling American and Chinese cooperation to defeat the Japanese during World War II.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Democratic California Gov. Gavin Newsom gifted Xi a Golden State Warriors Basketball jersey during the dinner, according to a Chinese Foreign Affairs spokesperson in attendance.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">In his meeting with Biden hours prior, Xi agreed to reestablish military-to-military communication lines with the U.S., which had been cut off in February. Xi also agreed to take steps to &ldquo;dramatically curtail&rdquo; the creation of fentanyl precursors created in China, which often end up in Mexico to be made into completed products and are subsequently trafficked into the U.S.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Biden praised his Wednesday meeting with Xi and then called him a &ldquo;dictator&rdquo; minutes later.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">&ldquo;Well, look, he is,&rdquo; Biden said during a press conference Wednesday.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=NoeFN1wgTdo"><span style="font-weight: 400;" data-rich-links="{&quot;fple-t&quot;:&quot;Biden again calls Xi &lsquo;dictator&rsquo; after Chinese prez warns against &lsquo;turning back&rsquo; on Beijing&quot;,&quot;fple-u&quot;:&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=NoeFN1wgTdo&quot;,&quot;fple-mt&quot;:null,&quot;type&quot;:&quot;first-party-link&quot;}">Biden again calls Xi &lsquo;dictator&rsquo; after Chinese prez warns against &lsquo;turning back&rsquo; on Beijing</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;">-Play Clip</span></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The White House and China&rsquo;s foreign ministry did not immediately respond to a request for comment.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://www.foxnews.com/us/pro-palestinian-protesters-block-bridges-boston-san-francisco-rush-hour"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.foxnews.com/us/pro-palestinian-protesters-block-bridges-boston-san-francisco-rush-hour</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>Pro-Palestinian protesters block bridges in Boston, San Francisco during rush hour</strong></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Pro-Palestinian protesters blocked traffic on bridges in Boston and San Francisco during rush hour Thursday morning to call for a cease-fire in Gaza as Israel continues to target Hamas leadership more than a month after the militant group&rsquo;s deadly incursion into Israel.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">On the Boston University bridge, the group IfNotNow, which says it represents members of Boston&rsquo;s Jewish community, chanted "Cease-fire now!" and demanded that Sen. Elizabeth Warren, D-Mass., support an immediate cease-fire and use her influence to stop the Israeli government&rsquo;s military action in Gaza.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The protest slowed traffic to a trickle on the bridge, which connects Boston and Cambridge, as the group held signs that said, "Let Gaza Live," and unfurled a banner across the roadway that read, "Jews say: Ceasefire now."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">"We care about Palestinian lives, we only want to hurt Hamas," one protester on the bridge told NBC Boston, while another said, "There can&rsquo;t be peace for Jews unless there is peace for Palestinians."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Meanwhile, Pro-Palestinian protesters also shut down the Bay Bridge in San Francisco, where President Biden was courting world leaders at the Asia-Pacific Economic Cooperation summit.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The Arab Resource and Organizing Center planned the demonstration, in which protesters were heard shouting, "Free Palestine" and "We want justice." Others chained themselves to the bridge or lay in the road covered with sheets smeared with fake blood, FOX2 KTVU reported.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Authorities had closed one lane on the bridge as a preventative measure during the summit, the station reported, citing the California Highway Patrol.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Israel vowed to wipe out Hamas after the militant group launched its Oct. 7 surprise attack, in which at least 1,200 people died in Israel and around 240 were taken captive by militants back to Gaza.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">More than 11,200 Palestinians have been killed since the war began, according to the Health Ministry in Hamas-run Gaza.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The protest came as Israeli forces dropped leaflets warning Palestinians to flee parts of southern Gaza, residents said Thursday, signaling a possible expansion of their offensive.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://www.breitbart.com/politics/2023/11/15/nolte-miserable-chicagoans-drop-mayor-brandon-johnsons-approval-rating-to-28/"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.breitbart.com/politics/2023/11/15/nolte-miserable-chicagoans-drop-mayor-brandon-johnsons-approval-rating-to-28/</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>Miserable Chicagoans Drop Mayor Brandon Johnson&rsquo;s Approval Rating to 28%</strong></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">In Wednesday&rsquo;s glorious edition of Democrats Getting What They Voted For, newly elected Democrat Chicago Mayor Brandon Johnson has an approval rating of just 28 percent.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Echelon Insights polled 800 registered voters in Chicago between October 18 and 22.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">So how is it possible that Johnson, who won a majority just seven short months ago, is now sitting with a dismal 28 percent approval rating, which is only one point higher than Lori Lightfoot (the sitting mayor he defeated) had in February 2023, which was only one month before she lost her reelection campaign?</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">I think the answer to this disconnect is obvious.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">In Chicago, dead people can vote, but dead people cannot be polled over the telephone.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">When asked about Chicago&rsquo;s worst issues, 69 percent of those polled said crime. That&rsquo;s only a two-point decrease since February. Then came high taxes (31 percent) and homelessness (20 percent). Everything else was under 15 percent.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">When asked how Mayor Johnson is doing on those top three issues, only 21 percent approved of the job he&rsquo;s doing on crime, while 66 percent disapproved. On economic development, only 32 percent approved, while 43 percent disapproved. On housing and homelessness, only 18 percent approved, while 63 percent disapproved.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">On the specific issue of &ldquo;management of immigrants transported to the city,&rdquo; only 23 percent approved, while 64 percent disapproved. This question relates directly to His Fraudulency, Joe Biden, throwing the southern border wide open to millions of unvetted, third-world illegal aliens.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">On that same question, living Chicago voters were asked, &ldquo;How do you feel about Mayor Brandon Johnson&rsquo;s proposed plan to house migrants in &lsquo;base camps&rsquo; made up of large, heated tents in various parts of Chicago?&rdquo; Only 28 percent approved, while 63 percent disapproved. Those who said they &ldquo;strongly oppose&rdquo; on this question made up nearly half, 46 percent.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">When asked if they supported or opposed Chicago&rsquo;s status as a sanctuary city, a majority of 52 percent opposed, while 42 percent supported.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">In February 2023, the month before Chicago voted Lightfoot out, 28 percent said the city was headed in the right direction. That number has now dropped to just 20 percent, while 65 percent say things are headed in the wrong direction.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Now that cash bail has been eliminated statewide, it hurts Chicago more than any other city. Only 35 percent of Chicagoans support that policy, but the Democrat governor who instituted that suicide pact won around 80 percent of the vote in Cook County, which is where Chicago sits.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">This poll tells us that Chicagoans are getting exactly what they voted for and are quite upset over it, which tells you just how damaged Democrats are.</span></p>]]></description>
   <author><![CDATA[Garrison Hardie]]></author>
   <enclosure url="https://app.dropwave.io/episode/84b9aa7f-c0cb-475d-8e10-f189870db059/daily-news-brief-for-friday-november-17th-2023.mp3" length="750" type="audio/mp3"/>
   <guid isPermaLink="false"><![CDATA[84b9aa7f-c0cb-475d-8e10-f189870db059]]></guid>
   <pubDate>Sat, 18 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
   <source url=""><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></source>
   <itunes:author><![CDATA[Garrison Hardie]]></itunes:author>
   <itunes:image href="https://assets-cdn2.dropwave.io/2ab40ac0-e99d-4f25-a6d2-541d2c9b290a/cover-art/mUK8zsnHkCK3vep7E1W6UgYb9dTnLenASAMEFha3.jpg"/>
   <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
   <itunes:duration>750</itunes:duration>
   <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
  
  </item>
 </channel>
</rss>
