<?xml version="1.0"?>
<?xml-stylesheet href="/storage/feed-stylesheet.xsl" type="text/xsl"?>

<rss xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
 <channel>
  <title>FLF - Daily News Brief</title>
  <link>https://dropwave.io</link>
  <description><![CDATA[FIGHT LAUGH FEAST PRESENTS SHOWS PROCLAIMING THE LORDSHIP OF CHRIST OVER ALL OF LIFE.
]]></description>
  <language>en</language>
  <managingEditor><![CDATA[fightlaughfeast@gmail.com (FLF, LLC)]]></managingEditor>
  <webMaster><![CDATA[support@dropwave.io (DropWave Support)]]></webMaster>
  <pubDate>Mon, 15 May 2023 07:25:45 +0000</pubDate>
  <lastBuildDate>Mon, 15 May 2023 07:25:45 +0000</lastBuildDate>
  <image>
   <url>https://is4-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Podcasts113/v4/58/56/52/5856525c-2973-cf29-3db9-21faa8595391/mza_1144696925612154085.png/1200x1200bb.jpg</url>
   <link>https://dropwave.io</link>
   <title><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></title>
  </image>
  <itunes:author><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></itunes:author>
  <itunes:image href="https://is4-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Podcasts113/v4/58/56/52/5856525c-2973-cf29-3db9-21faa8595391/mza_1144696925612154085.png/1200x1200bb.jpg"/>
  <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
  <itunes:owner>
   <itunes:name><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></itunes:name>
   <itunes:email>fightlaughfeast@gmail.com</itunes:email>
  </itunes:owner>
  <itunes:category text="News"/>
  <item>
   <title><![CDATA[CrossPolitic Daily News Brief for Friday, May 12th, 2023 [Daily News Brief]]]></title>
   <link>https://app.dropwave.io/episode/dd8d4133-255d-4445-a0b4-aade324fe060/crosspolitic-daily-news-brief-for-friday-may-12th-2023-1.mp3</link>
   <description><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">This is Garrison Hardie with your CrossPolitic Daily News Brief for Friday, May 12th, 2023.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>Concordis Education Partners:</strong></span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Classical Christian education has reminded us to aim education at truth, but the trivium has been used as a formula rather than a way of training students in discernment.&nbsp;&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">To teach well, you must coach.&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">&nbsp;</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Concordis Foundation is offering their third annual BOOT CAMP &ndash; a faculty summit &ndash; July 11-13th in Moscow, Idaho.&nbsp; This is a three-day intensive teaching training where you learn to coach students, using the trivium, so that you can meet students at all learning levels.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">&nbsp;</span></p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Learn more at</span><a href="https://concordispartners.com/"><span style="font-weight: 400;"> </span><span style="font-weight: 400;">concordispartners.com</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;">&nbsp;&nbsp;</span></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://www.foxnews.com/politics/border-patrol-chief-authorizes-release-migrants-us-without-court-dates-title-42-ends"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.foxnews.com/politics/border-patrol-chief-authorizes-release-migrants-us-without-court-dates-title-42-ends</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>Border Patrol chief authorizes release of migrants into US without court dates as Title 42 ends</strong></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The head of U.S. Border Patrol has sent out a memo authorizing the release of illegal migrants into the U.S. without court dates if agents face overcrowding as the Biden administration scrambles to deal with a historic surge in migration at the border ahead of the end of Title 42.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The memo says that migrants can be allowed into the country on parole &mdash; a process typically reserved for "urgent humanitarian reasons or significant public benefit" &mdash; if Customs and Border Protection (CBP) faces overcrowding. The memo calls the practice "parole with conditions" as migrants are required to make an appointment with Immigration and Customs Enforcement (ICE) or request a Notice to Appear by mail.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Under a parole release, migrants are rapidly released into the country, do not get an alien registration number and do not receive a court date.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The use of parole is being authorized if a sector capacity goes above 125%, if agents apprehend 7,000 a day over 72 hours or if average time in custody goes above 60 hours.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Agents have been encountering over 10,000 migrants a day since Monday, and there are no signs of that slowing down with the looming end of Title 42, which is expected to bring an even bigger wave with it.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The memo noted the enormous numbers agents are encountering.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">"For the past 7 days, USBP has averaged over 8,750 encounters per day. This is over double the average daily encounters of 4,284 in May of 2019, the highest month of the 2019 surge. Even with significant personnel along the SWB, a significant detention capacity, and interagency resources supporting the effort, this situation requires urgent action," the memo states.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The public health order has been used since March 2020 to expel over two million migrants due to the COVID-19 pandemic. The Biden administration has told migrants that it will not be easier to enter the U.S. once the order drops as there will be stiffer penalties until Title 8. Parole is not a Title 8 authority.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The use of parole is legally questionable, with critics arguing it is not supposed to be used to wave in thousands of migrants. The state of Florida successfully sued the Biden administration in March to block a similar policy, "Parole + ATD."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">On Thursday, Fox Digital reported that Florida sued this week over the latest plan to release migrants into the U.S. interior, saying it is "materially identical" to the policy that the federal court enjoined.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">"Florida seeks a temporary restraining order to preserve the status quo until the parties can brief motions for a preliminary injunction or to postpone the effective date of the new policy," the lawsuit states. "The Biden Administration&rsquo;s behavior, if left unchecked, makes a mockery of our system of justice and our Constitution."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The judge has given the Biden administration a 4 p.m. deadline Thursday to respond to the request for a temporary restraining order, adding that it appears the administration is "preparing to flout" the court&rsquo;s order.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">A Department of Homeland Security (DHS) spokesperson this week claimed that the releases are similar to those conducted by prior administrations.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://thepostmillennial.com/breaking-house-votes-yes-on-measure-to-secure-us-mexico-border?utm_campaign=64487"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://thepostmillennial.com/breaking-house-votes-yes-on-measure-to-secure-us-mexico-border?utm_campaign=64487</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>House votes YES on Secure Border Act in 219-213 vote, includes e-Verify requirement, with 2 Republicans joining Democrats to vote against border security</strong></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">On Thursday, House Representatives debated the Secure the Border Act of 2023 as Title 42 expired at the southern border, which lays out sweeping new requirements and restrictions for securing the southern border.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The bill passed 219-213. Two Republicans, Reps. Thomas Massie and John Duarte voted along side all Democrat members against the bill.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The bill was introduced to the House of Representatives on May 2 in anticipation of the flood of illegal immigrants expected in the wake of Title 42, which allowed expulsions due to the pandemic emergency.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The bill calls for the "immediate resumption of border wall construction" no later than seven days after the bill is enacted, using previously set aside funds and materials for its construction.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">No later than 180 days after the bill is enacted, a report shall be submitted to congressional committees that outlines a strategic 5-year technology investment plan for border security, including potential upgrades in security technology, communications equipment, screening equipment, incorporating in input from the private sector.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">In an effort to retain Border Patrol personnel, the bill will authorize up to $100,000,000 in appropriated funds for the Commissioner of the US Customs and Border Protection to give to front-line agents who hold a position equal to or below level GS-12, has been with Border Patrol for five years or longer, and commits two additional years of service with Border Patrol upon acceptance of the bonus.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The bill also requires that the Commissioner hire and train enough Border Patrol agents to maintain an active duty presence of no less than 22,000 full-time agents.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The bill also includes a provision prohibiting the requirement to take a Covid-19 vaccine or adverse actions taken against a Department of Homeland Security employee.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The Secretary of Homeland Security would be required to send a report no later than 60 days after the bill is enacted on whether Mexican drug cartels meet the criteria for being designated as a foreign terrorist organization.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The bill amends the Immigration and Nationality Act, stating that those found not to be eligible for parole shall be deported from the country.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The bill also increases penalties for illegal entry or presence in the country from $50-$250 up to $500-$1000.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Illegal immigrants who overstay a visa are subject to imprisonment of no more than six months and/or a fine for the first offense, and a fine and/or no more than two years of imprisonment for subsequent offenses.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The bill also mandates the use of e-Verify, a system used to check if a person is authorized to work in the United States.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/policy/education/connecticut-wesleyan-pay-for-students-abortions"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/policy/education/connecticut-wesleyan-pay-for-students-abortions</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>Connecticut liberal arts college says it will pay for students to get abortions</strong></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">A liberal arts university in Connecticut says it will now cover the costs of any student who wishes to get an abortion or a Plan B contraceptive, regardless of their insurance status.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Wesleyan University announced last week that, following a pressure campaign from the university's Young Democratic Socialists of America chapter, the school would now pay for any student to get an abortion or emergency contraceptives. The school has also committed to footing the bill for any transportation costs incurred by students seeking abortions.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">&ldquo;Consistent with the health center&rsquo;s mission to provide education and support in the decision-making process, students will be able to access emergency contraceptives by consulting with a nurse at Davison Health Center," the university told NBC Connecticut in a statement.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The decision comes after the Young Democratic Socialists of America chapter at Wesleyan collected over 700 signatures on a petition that urged the school to "ensure all students are able to overcome financial burdens to and lack of transportation for abortion procedures."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">"This victory comes in the wake of landmark efforts by Barnard College students to secure abortion pills on campus as well as a broader movement for reproductive justice nationwide," the student organization said in a press release. "Wesleyan now plays a pioneering role in reproductive healthcare among private liberal arts colleges by committing to cover the entire cost of abortion after insurance for all students."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">After the Supreme Court issued a ruling that overturned Roe v. Wade last year, the availability of abortion for college students has gained increased attention, as numerous states with widely recognized state universities have banned abortion altogether. Students have increasingly reported that access to abortion has become a factor in their college decision-making process.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Democratic-controlled states, meanwhile, have taken steps to make abortion as available to college students as a flu shot.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The entire University of California and California State University systems are required by law to provide abortion pills to students at their respective university health centers, and last year, the University of Massachusetts Amherst announced it would be providing abortion pills on campus as well.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://www.foxnews.com/us/marine-veteran-charged-manhattan-da-jordan-neely-subway-chokehold-death"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.foxnews.com/us/marine-veteran-charged-manhattan-da-jordan-neely-subway-chokehold-death</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>Marine veteran to be charged by Manhattan DA in Jordan Neely subway chokehold death</strong></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">A New York City subway rider accused of choking a homeless man to death is expected to turn himself in to police on Friday morning to face a manslaughter charge.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">"We can confirm that Daniel Penny will be arrested on a charge of Manslaughter in the Second Degree," a spokesperson for the Manhattan District Attorney's Office said. "We cannot provide any additional information until he has been arraigned in Manhattan Criminal Court, which we expect to take place tomorrow."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">On May 1, Penny, a 24-year-old Marine veteran and college student, put 30-year-old Jordan Neely in a fatal chokehold after what police described as an altercation on a northbound F train.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Neely was allegedly threatening passengers on the subway and having a mental episode. He was yelling and pacing back and forth, when Penny interjected, tackled him to the ground and put him in a chokehold, witnesses and police said.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The incident sparked protests and violent clashes last week after the Marine veteran was taken into custody and released.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">And now for my favorite topic&hellip; sports!</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://www.boundingintosports.com/2023/05/prosecutors-confirm-former-buffalo-bills-punter-matt-araiza-was-not-present-when-alleged-gang-rape-occurred/"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.boundingintosports.com/2023/05/prosecutors-confirm-former-buffalo-bills-punter-matt-araiza-was-not-present-when-alleged-gang-rape-occurred/</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>Prosecutors Confirm Former Buffalo Bills Punter Matt Araiza Was Not Present When Alleged Gang Rape Occurred</strong></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">After having the criminal charges against him dropped, former Buffalo Bills punter Matt Araiza now has to undergo a stressful process of fighting the civil lawsuit against him for an alleged gang rape at a college party that occurred when Arazia and the plaintiff were attending San Diego State University at the same time.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">However, based on new information, that might be over soon, and potentially in Araiza&rsquo;s favor.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">During a nearly year long investigation by San Diego police and detailed review by prosecutors, they have come to the conclusion that the alleged gang rape that the female plaintiff accused Araiza of being part of stands in question since evidence shows that Arazia, then a college student at the time when the plaintiff was 17-years-old, was not even present during the alleged crime.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Yahoo Sports has obtained a 200-plus page transcript, covering a meeting in which a San Diego deputy district attorney broke the back of the case.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">According Yahoo Sports&rsquo; summary, &ldquo;Araiza couldn&rsquo;t have led the girl into the alleged gang rape because he had &lsquo;left&rsquo; the home at about 12:30 a.m., an hour prior to when evidence suggested the alleged gang rape would have occurred.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Deputy district attorney Trisha Amador stated that &ldquo;He wasn&rsquo;t even at the party anymore. All I know is that at that point, suspect Araiza is gone from the party.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Prosecutors additionally told the plaintiff that the recordings that were made of the situation &ldquo;made it impossible&rdquo; to identify Araiza or any other potential suspects since their faces and voices aren&rsquo;t clear enough to make a prosecution.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Further, there are questions as to whether a rape occurred at all as the plaintiff claimed, and not a consensual sexual situation.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">&ldquo;In looking at the videos on the sex tape, I absolutely cannot prove any forceable sexual assault based upon what happened,&rdquo; said Deputy DA Amador.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Because of this lawsuit, then-rookie Araiza was cut from the Bills team, crippling his rookie season so he could &ldquo;take care of this situation,&rdquo; according to Buffalo general manager Brandon Beane.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">But Araiza isn&rsquo;t out of the woods yet, despite the prosecutors themselves admitting he wasn&rsquo;t present at the event &ndash; civil suits have a much lower standard of proof than criminal cases do.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">As news broke of the developments in the civil suit, online figures in sports and media began to defend Arazia, including Daily Wire columnist Matt Walsh and Outkick.com founder Clay Travis.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">&ldquo;False rape accusers should receive the same penalty that we give to rapists,&rdquo; Walsh posted to Twitter. &ldquo;Instead, in a vast majority of cases, they receive no penalty at all and are free to move on like nothing happened.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">&ldquo;The Bills released punter Matt Araiza for an allegation of sexual assault that police proved was 100% a lie,&rdquo; tweeted Travis. &ldquo;Why shouldn&rsquo;t his accuser face criminal charges for lying? He&rsquo;s lost a year of his career &amp; his good name. She has zero consequences. Not right.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Thanks to all the legal trouble, Araiza is still a free agent. We&rsquo;ve seen plenty of comebacks from legal trouble in the National Felon League. Araiza could be the next to move on to a respectable career.</span></p>]]></description>
   <author><![CDATA[Garrison Hardie]]></author>
   <enclosure url="https://app.dropwave.io/episode/dd8d4133-255d-4445-a0b4-aade324fe060/crosspolitic-daily-news-brief-for-friday-may-12th-2023-1.mp3" length="813" type="audio/mp3"/>
   <guid isPermaLink="false"><![CDATA[dd8d4133-255d-4445-a0b4-aade324fe060]]></guid>
   <pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
   <source url=""><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></source>
   <itunes:author><![CDATA[Garrison Hardie]]></itunes:author>
   <itunes:image href="https://assets-cdn2.dropwave.io/2ab40ac0-e99d-4f25-a6d2-541d2c9b290a/cover-art/hUZu1H9lrRY0wXg66WHC8eLwYBA3hbRNTAHQmHt2.png"/>
   <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
   <itunes:duration>813</itunes:duration>
   <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
  
  </item><item>
   <title><![CDATA[Daily News Brief for Thursday, May 11th, 2023 [Daily News Brief]]]></title>
   <link>https://app.dropwave.io/episode/5e49b965-0f39-436b-b8ad-84cb68c15981/daily-news-brief-for-thursday-may-11th-2023.mp3</link>
   <description><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">This is Garrison Hardie with your CrossPolitic Daily News Brief for Thursday, May 11th, 2023.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://www.breitbart.com/middle-east/2023/05/09/israel-kills-three-islamic-jihad-terrorist-commanders-in-strikes-on-gaza/"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.breitbart.com/middle-east/2023/05/09/israel-kills-three-islamic-jihad-terrorist-commanders-in-strikes-on-gaza/</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>Israel Kills Three Islamic Jihad Terrorist Commanders in Strikes on Gaza</strong></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Israel killed three senior commanders of the Iran-backed Islamic Jihad terrorist group in targeted airstrikes early Tuesday.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">AP reports the targeted air strikes hit the top floor of an apartment building in Gaza City and a house in the southern town of Rafah.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The Palestinian Health Ministry said 20 people were wounded and ambulances were continuing to evacuate people from the targeted areas.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Israel&rsquo;s Home Front command ordered the closure of schools, beaches and highways in cities and towns in southern Israel, and limited public gatherings ahead of anticipated retaliatory strikes.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The military said the three men targeted in the counter-terror operation had been responsible for recent rocket fire toward Israel.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">It identified them as Khalil Bahtini, the Islamic Jihad commander for northern Gaza Strip; Tareq Izzeldeen, the group&rsquo;s intermediary between its Gaza and West Bank members; and Jehad Ghanam, the secretary of the Islamic Jihad&rsquo;s military council.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Their funerals were planned for later in the day.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The bombings came days after Gazan terrorists led by Islamic Jihad fired 104 rockets toward Israel in response to the death of an alleged senior member of the group who had been on hunger strike in Israeli prison, the Times of Israel reports.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Several rockets struck during the May 2 clash, injuring three workers and damaging homes and cars.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Islamic Jihad, which is smaller than Gaza&rsquo;s ruling Hamas group, confirmed the three were among the dead. The Palestinian Health Ministry said that along with the three commanders, their wives, several of their children and others nearby were also killed &mdash; 13 in all.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Hamas leader Ismail Haniyeh warned that Israel will &ldquo;pay the price&rdquo; for the killings. &ldquo;Assassinating the leaders with a treacherous operation will not bring security to the occupier, but rather more resistance,&rdquo; Haniyeh said in a statement.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/news/crime/portland-revives-police-unit-traffic-deaths-surge"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/news/crime/portland-revives-police-unit-traffic-deaths-surge</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>Portland revives police unit as traffic deaths surge</strong></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Portland, Oregon, police will announce the reinstatement of their traffic division on Tuesday after facing one of its deadliest years for pedestrians in 2022.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">After dissolving its traffic division in 2020, traffic deaths broke a 70-year record. In 2022, 63 people were killed in traffic crashes, equal to a 30-year-high record in 2021. Those deaths included 31 pedestrians who were killed, reaching historic high levels.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Police Chief Chuck Lovell blamed historically low staffing numbers and said the bureau needed to focus on 911 calls as reasons to disband the division in 2020.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Lovell and Mayor Ted Wheeler were united on the narrative that cutting out the traffic division was due to staffing decreases and funding concerns.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">However, Jo Ann Hardesty, the former commissioner of the Portland Bureau of Transportation, saw this measure as a political measure to gather public sympathy.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Hardesty described the narrative around the police as pushing that their only problem is a lack of officers and money, when the issue lies much deeper than that, pointing to a rise in violence and pushing to keep the Portland community safe.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">In the past, Portland has taken measures to increase pedestrian safety, including implementing a "left-turn calming" tool aimed at making intersections safer for walkers by slowing turning speeds. Starting in 2020, the initiative takes after New York City&rsquo;s "turning calm" project.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Lovell is expected to make an announcement Tuesday afternoon after the two-year hiatus made Portland one of the largest cities in the nation to lack a traffic division.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://thepostmillennial.com/oregonians-blast-lawmakers-over-proposed-bill-to-legalize-homeless-camps?utm_campaign=64487"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://thepostmillennial.com/oregonians-blast-lawmakers-over-proposed-bill-to-legalize-homeless-camps?utm_campaign=64487</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>Oregonians blast lawmakers over proposed bill to legalize homeless camps</strong></span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Oregon Democratic lawmakers have canceled a public hearing on a bill that would have allowed homeless people to camp in public places and sue if told to leave, following massive pushback.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Democratic lawmakers proposed the bill that would have decriminalized camping on public property and would allow homeless individuals to sue for up to $1,000 if they are "harassed" or told to relocate.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">House Bill 3501, also known as the &ldquo;Right to Rest Act,&rdquo; was sponsored by Democratic state Reps. Farrah Chaichi and Khanh Pham. It stated that &ldquo;persons experiencing homelessness&rdquo; will have "a privacy interest and a reasonable expectation of privacy in any property belonging to the person, regardless of whether the property is located in a public space."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The bill added that the homeless will "be permitted to use public spaces in the same manner as any other person without discrimination based on their housing status" and stated that they have a right to "move freely in public spaces without discrimination and time limitations that are based on housing status."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Over 2,000 written statements in opposition were received through the legislature's website. Fahey added that the bill had become a "significant distraction" from representatives' work.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Oregon's homeless population spiked approximately 22.5 percent from 2020 to 2022, Fox News reported. Portland Democratic Mayor Ted Wheeler&rsquo;s office reported a 50 percent increase in homelessness from 2019 to 2022.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">According to census data, Portland lost 0.04 percent of its population after 30 years straight of growth; the general population has declined for three years in a row.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Portland resident Jacob Adams told Fox &amp; Friends in February "I love Portland, and I love where I live," discussing a homeless encampment next to his house, where there are regular fires and drug activity, even gunshots. "I'm asking you to please do something, so the people of the city feel safe."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/policy/immigration/abbott-reveals-brownsville-border-wired-shut-texas"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/policy/immigration/abbott-reveals-brownsville-border-wired-shut-texas</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>Abbott reveals Brownsville border 'wired shut' to ward off thousands of migrants</strong></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Gov. Greg Abbott (R-TX) showed how the state is seeking to temper a rush of migrants at the southern border late Monday evening, posting a video revealing barbed wiring strung across gaps along the border.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The video shows a nighttime shot of the border just two days before the expected end of the Trump-era Title 42 policy that allowed the swift expulsion of migrants on the grounds of public health. Hundreds of feet of spiraled wire can be seen along the ground, and some areas show the wire stacked to form a partition several feet tall.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">&ldquo;This is one thing Texas is doing to secure the border,&rdquo; Abbott wrote in his post sharing the video of the sprawling wire fence. &ldquo;This is the area near Brownsville where migrants were crossing in large numbers a few days ago. We now have it wired shut. Other areas will surface for crossing. We will wire them shut also.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Abbott's tweet came just hours after he made his first public address over the border crisis since 34-year-old George Alvarez was arrested and charged with eight counts of manslaughter after his SUV plowed through a group of people outside Bishop Enrique San Pedro Ozanam Center, a migrant facility, on Sunday.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The collision involving Alvarez is still under investigation, and a toxicology report is pending. Police revealed Monday that Alvarez has an extensive criminal history, including multiple assault charges. A witness to the collision said the driver made anti-immigrant remarks before he was detained by members of the public, according to the Independent.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Additional security risks have reportedly continued at the Ozanam Center since the fatal crash. On Monday, a driver reportedly approached the migrant facility's gate with a gun and attempted to enter, according to a News Nation reporter. That facility has been operating over its intended capacity for almost a month and is planning to expand the number of sleeping spaces from 250 to 380 per night.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Abbott's update comes as multiple Customs and Border Protection officials are reportedly considering "safe" street releases of immigrants to communities on the U.S. side of the border if no nongovernmental organization shelters or CBP facilities have the capacity to hold them.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The Republican governor on Monday accused cartels of "working in collaboration with President Biden and the federal government to facilitate that illegal" border crossing.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Thousands of migrants are lining up near various sections of the border, stretching all the way from as far south as Brownsville to the northwestern city of El Paso. There, immigration enforcement agents announced plans to target migrants crowding the city streets, according to a CBP statement.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">In addition to the number of migrants at the border, Republicans in border states have rallied against the persistent smuggling of deadly fentanyl into the country. Neatly 385 million fatal doses have been seized by border</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://www.dailywire.com/news/sam-bankman-fried-tries-to-get-most-of-the-charges-against-him-dismissed"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.dailywire.com/news/sam-bankman-fried-tries-to-get-most-of-the-charges-against-him-dismissed</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>Sam Bankman-Fried Tries To Get Most Of The Charges Against Him Dismissed</strong></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Attorneys who represent former FTX CEO Sam Bankman-Fried are attempting to dismiss 10 of the 13 charges filed against the disgraced cryptocurrency entrepreneur.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Several firms controlled by Bankman-Fried imploded at the end of last year after customers and investors learned that FTX had improperly commingled funds with sister trading company Alameda Research. Lawyers for Bankman-Fried asserted in a Monday court filing that the original indictment levied against the entrepreneur came from a &ldquo;classic rush to judgment&rdquo; and that the case involved &ldquo;civil and regulatory issues&rdquo; rather than federal crimes.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">&ldquo;Rather than wait for traditional civil and regulatory processes following their ordinary course to address the situation, the government jumped in with both feet,&rdquo; the filing asserted. &ldquo;Each of the charges contained boilerplate recitals of statutory language, followed by literally one sentence purportedly describing the basis for the charge.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Bankman-Fried was detained in the Bahamas and extradited to the United States in December, nearly one month after FTX collapsed and bankruptcy procedures were initiated. Attorneys contended that officials violated the extradition treaty between the two nations since the Bahamian government issued a warrant of surrender &ldquo;specifying that he be tried on seven of the eight counts&rdquo; in the original indictment, even as American officials later brought additional charges without the consent of authorities in the island nation.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Bankman-Fried was initially charged in December with crimes such as conspiracy to commit wire fraud, conspiracy to commit securities fraud, and conspiracy to defraud the Federal Election Commission through campaign finance violations. Another superseding indictment unveiled in February added four new charges, including conspiracy to commit bank fraud and conspiracy to operate an unlicensed money transfer business. Bankman-Fried was also charged in March with paying bribes to one or more members of the Chinese Communist Party.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Bankman-Fried faces the charges in the Southern District of New York, which often oversees high-profile financial fraud cases. The entrepreneur, who has pleaded not guilty to all charges and currently resides with his parents in northern California, is expected to appear for trial in early October.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Lawyers for the entrepreneur meanwhile claimed that the collapse of FTX occurred in the context of broader difficulties in the cryptocurrency sector. &ldquo;As with a traditional bank run, numerous customers simultaneously sought to withdraw their assets, thus feeding fears that a collapse was inevitable,&rdquo; the court filing said. &ldquo;The market crash took down many of the major players in this sector, not just FTX.&rdquo;</span></p>]]></description>
   <author><![CDATA[Garrison Hardie]]></author>
   <enclosure url="https://app.dropwave.io/episode/5e49b965-0f39-436b-b8ad-84cb68c15981/daily-news-brief-for-thursday-may-11th-2023.mp3" length="705" type="audio/mp3"/>
   <guid isPermaLink="false"><![CDATA[5e49b965-0f39-436b-b8ad-84cb68c15981]]></guid>
   <pubDate>Thu, 11 May 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
   <source url=""><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></source>
   <itunes:author><![CDATA[Garrison Hardie]]></itunes:author>
   <itunes:image href="https://assets-cdn2.dropwave.io/2ab40ac0-e99d-4f25-a6d2-541d2c9b290a/cover-art/hUZu1H9lrRY0wXg66WHC8eLwYBA3hbRNTAHQmHt2.png"/>
   <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
   <itunes:duration>705</itunes:duration>
   <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
  
  </item><item>
   <title><![CDATA[CrossPolitic Daily News Brief for Wednesday, May 10th, 2023. [Daily News Brief]]]></title>
   <link>https://app.dropwave.io/episode/e72f2f35-fc56-47f0-bf22-5e75cb3db49e/crosspolitic-daily-news-brief-for-wednesday-may-10th-2023.mp3</link>
   <description><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">This is Garrison Hardie from your CrossPolitic Daily News Brief for Wednesday, May 10th, 2023.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>Concordis Education Partners:</strong></span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Classical Christian education has reminded us to aim education at truth, but the trivium has been used as a formula rather than a way of training students in discernment.&nbsp;&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">To teach well, you must coach.&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">&nbsp;</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Concordis Foundation is offering their third annual BOOT CAMP &ndash; a faculty summit &ndash; July 11-13th in Moscow, Idaho.&nbsp; This is a three-day intensive teaching training where you learn to coach students, using the trivium, so that you can meet students at all learning levels.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">For more information, visit them at </span><a href="http://concordispartners.com/"><span style="font-weight: 400;">concordispartners.com</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://www.breitbart.com/border/2023/05/08/texas-military-deploys-additional-troops-to-border-ahead-of-title-42-end/"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.breitbart.com/border/2023/05/08/texas-military-deploys-additional-troops-to-border-ahead-of-title-42-end/</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>Texas Military Deploys Additional Troops to Border Ahead of Title 42 End</strong></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Texas Governor Greg Abbott ordered the deployment of an additional 545 National Guardsmen to assist in the newest surge of migrants crossing the border from Mexico. The deployment under the state&rsquo;s Operation Lone Star comes days ahead of the expected May 11 end of the Title 42 migrant expulsion program.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">&ldquo;These additional forces will bolster the thousands of Texas National Guard service members already assisting local and state law enforcement agencies to secure the border; stop the smuggling of drugs, weapons, and people into Texas; and prevent, detect, and interdict transnational criminal behavior between the ports of entry,&rdquo; Texas Military Department officials said in a written statement. &ldquo;We have expanded our capabilities to include boat teams that patrol hundreds of river miles, drones and helicopters that detect illicit activity from the air, and brush teams, security points, and roving patrols that block and interdict illegal smuggling (drugs, weapons, and people) into Texas.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">On Sunday, Border Patrol agents in the five Texas-based sectors apprehend more than 5,100 migrants who crossed the border from Mexico, according to a law enforcement source. This represents nearly 60 percent of the nearly 8,700 who crossed along the entire southwest border with Mexico.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The number of migrants crossing the border from Mexico surged last week ahead of this week&rsquo;s expected end to the CDC&rsquo;s Title 42 migrant expulsion protocol. On Friday and Saturday, the number of apprehensions exceeded 9,000 per day, Breitbart Texas reported</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">U.S. Border Patrol Chief Raul Ortiz reported the apprehension of 54,951 migrants during the preceding seven-day period. In addition, another 18,698 migrants were classified as &ldquo;got-aways.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">So far this fiscal year, agents apprehended nearly 1.4 million migrants along the southwest border, according to a law enforcement official. Migrant got-aways jumped to nearly 453,000 bringing the total number of known border crossers this fiscal year to more than 1.8 million migrants in less than seven months.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://thepostmillennial.com/white-house-to-limit-press-credentials-to-those-who-act-professional?utm_campaign=64487"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://thepostmillennial.com/white-house-to-limit-press-credentials-to-those-who-act-professional?utm_campaign=64487</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>White House to limit press credentials to those who act 'professional'</strong></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">On Friday, the White House released a new set of rules for press badges, also known as hard passes, that stated the recipient must act in a "professional manner" in order to keep their badge and told all who currently possess a pass must reply by July 31.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The New York Post reports that the announcement said, "The White House expects that all hard pass holders will act in a professional manner while on White House grounds by respecting their colleagues, White House employees, and guests; observing stated restrictions on access to areas of the White House or credentialed events; and not impeding events or briefings on campus."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">"Absent security concerns involving the United States Secret Service or other exigent circumstances, the White House will provide a written warning to you if your conduct violates these expectations. Subsequent violations may lead to the suspension or revocation of your hard pass, following notice and an opportunity to respond," the notice continued.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The move comes after Today News Africa reporter Simon Ateba grilled Press Secretary Karine Jean-Pierre in January and told her, "You don't seem a good fit for this job."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Reporters who have had badges auto-renew since 2017 need to have their employer submit a letter to the White House confirming "full-time employment with an organization whose principal business is news dissemination."&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The notice said that freelancers, "will need letters from two news organizations describing your affiliation, or, if you freelance primarily for one organization, a letter from that organization describing the extent and duration of your relationship with the organization."&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The journalists need to provide proof of a personal or professional address in the DC area, submit to a background check, have an "accreditation by a press gallery in either the Supreme Court, US Senate or US. House of Representatives," and "have accessed the White House campus at least once during the prior six months for work, or have proof of employment within the last three months to cover the White House."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">A White House press official told the Post, "This has been thoughtfully considered for more than a year. We worked hard to be responsive to needs and feedback of journalists covering the White House. As we return to these prior criteria, which help ensure hard passes are in the hands of reporters who need regular access to campus as part of their duties, we are providing a nearly 3-month window for reporters to turn in their applications and reach out with any questions. The criteria will apply evenly to everyone,"</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://thepostmillennial.com/breaking-tucker-carlson-to-launch-new-show-exclusively-on-twitter?utm_campaign=64487"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://thepostmillennial.com/breaking-tucker-carlson-to-launch-new-show-exclusively-on-twitter?utm_campaign=64487</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>Tucker is back EXCLUSIVELY on Twitter</strong></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Tucker Carlson announced that he will soon be relaunching his own show and streaming it exclusively on Twitter.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Carlson made the announcement in a post to Twitter on Tuesday, simply captioned "We're back."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://twitter.com/i/status/1656037032538390530"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://twitter.com/i/status/1656037032538390530</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> - Play Video&nbsp;</span></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Carlson reportedly spoke with Twitter CEO Elon Musk about working together this past week, according to one report.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Axios reported on Sunday that "Carlson and Elon Musk had a conversation about working together, but didn't discuss specifics."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Carlson is not the first to bring his show to Twitter since the social media giant was acquired by Musk. Earlier this week, Daily Wire's Matt Walsh announced that he would be uploading his full shows to Twitter. This announcement came after a hack on his account.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://twitter.com/i/status/1648844750613512195"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://twitter.com/i/status/1648844750613512195</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> - Play Video&nbsp;</span></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Tucker Carlson and Fox News parted ways on April 24.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://thepostmillennial.com/oklahoma-revokes-funding-for-pbs-over-lgbtq-content-for-kids?utm_campaign=64487"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://thepostmillennial.com/oklahoma-revokes-funding-for-pbs-over-lgbtq-content-for-kids?utm_campaign=64487</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>Oklahoma revokes funding for PBS over LGBTQ content for kids</strong></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Oklahoma Gov. Kevin Stitt (R) has defended his decision to veto a bill seeking to fund the state&rsquo;s PBS station through 2026, arguing that the state-funded broadcaster is indoctrinating and sexualizing children.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Last week Stitt vetoed HB 2820, which would have funded the statewide PBS station Oklahoma Educational Television Authority (OETA) until 2026. In a recent interview with Fox News, Stitt explained his reason for doing so, highlighting objectionable content such as a segment of &ldquo;Let&rsquo;s Learn&rdquo; featuring the children&rsquo;s book &ldquo;The Hips on the Drag Queen Go Swish, Swish, Swish,&rdquo; being read by a drag queen called Lil Miss Hot Mess.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">&ldquo;OETA, to us, is an outdated system. You know, the big, big question is why are we spending taxpayer dollars to prop up or compete with the private sector and run television stations? And then when you go through all of the programming that's happening and the indoctrination and over-sexualization of our children, it's just really problematic, and it doesn't line up with Oklahoma values,&rdquo; Stitt told Fox News.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">In addition to Lil Miss Hot Mess, one of the founders of Drag Queen Story Time, reading The Hips on the Drag Queen Go Swish, Swish, Swish,&rdquo; the governor&rsquo;s office mentioned a PBS Newshour segment that featured parents who supported children having access to experimental medical sex changes, as well as abundant &ldquo;Pride Month&rdquo; programming, and a special about a town of Christians and drag queens who &ldquo;step into the spotlight to dismantle stereotypes.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Stitt objects to the use of tax dollars funding someone&rsquo;s agenda.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">He went on to call the concept of the public television station &ldquo;outdated.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Stitt&rsquo;s decision has been criticized by some on the left, including by State Rep. Monroe Nichols (D) who accused Stitt of &ldquo;continued attacks on public education and underrepresented Oklahoma communities.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Stitt responded by calling this accusation &ldquo;nonsense,&rdquo; and just another attempt by Democrats to push a radical left agenda on children.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>Now it&rsquo;s time for my favorite topic&hellip; sports!!!</strong></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://www.foxnews.com/sports/super-bowl-champ-offers-georgia-tech-grads-key-fulfilling-life-get-married-start-family"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.foxnews.com/sports/super-bowl-champ-offers-georgia-tech-grads-key-fulfilling-life-get-married-start-family</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;">&nbsp;</span></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>Super Bowl champ offers Georgia Tech grads the key to fulfilling life: 'Get married and start a family'</strong></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Kansas City Chiefs kicker Harrison Butker, a two-time Super Bowl winner, appeared at Georgia Institute of Technology on Saturday and gave the commencement speech.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The former Yellow Jackets standout gave the graduates some words of wisdom.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Butker said he planned to "pop off some hard truths" in his speech. He said that it does not matter how much money you attain or the amount of success that comes to you career-wise, "none of it will matter if you are alone and devoid of purpose."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://twitter.com/i/status/1654913549716582406"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://twitter.com/i/status/1654913549716582406</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> - Play Video 0:00-4:20</span></span></p>]]></description>
   <author><![CDATA[Garrison Hardie]]></author>
   <enclosure url="https://app.dropwave.io/episode/e72f2f35-fc56-47f0-bf22-5e75cb3db49e/crosspolitic-daily-news-brief-for-wednesday-may-10th-2023.mp3" length="1086" type="audio/mp3"/>
   <guid isPermaLink="false"><![CDATA[e72f2f35-fc56-47f0-bf22-5e75cb3db49e]]></guid>
   <pubDate>Wed, 10 May 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
   <source url=""><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></source>
   <itunes:author><![CDATA[Garrison Hardie]]></itunes:author>
   <itunes:image href="https://assets-cdn2.dropwave.io/2ab40ac0-e99d-4f25-a6d2-541d2c9b290a/cover-art/hUZu1H9lrRY0wXg66WHC8eLwYBA3hbRNTAHQmHt2.png"/>
   <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
   <itunes:duration>1086</itunes:duration>
   <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
  
  </item><item>
   <title><![CDATA[CrossPolitic Daily News Brief for Tuesday, May 9th, 2023. [Daily News Brief]]]></title>
   <link>https://app.dropwave.io/episode/eade695e-9ed3-47f9-a2e6-93f67f318e99/crosspolitic-daily-news-brief-for-tuesday-may-9th-2023.mp3</link>
   <description><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">This is Garrison Hardie with your CrossPolitic Daily News Brief for Tuesday, May 9th, 2023.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Samaritan Ministries:</strong></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Don&rsquo;t be limited by restrictive networks. There&rsquo;s another way. A Biblical way. Samaritan Ministries. Say you have a medical need. You don&rsquo;t have to check and see what hospital is in your network, or be concerned about the doctor being in-network, too. No. You go to the hospital you choose, and don&rsquo;t give a second thought as to what&rsquo;s in-network and what&rsquo;s not, because with Samaritan Ministries, you&rsquo;re in control of your health care. Afterwards, fellow members pray for you, and send money directly to you to help you pay your medical bills. And when they have a medical need, you&rsquo;ll do the same for them. That&rsquo;s what Biblical health care sharing looks like. Check it out today at samaritan ministries dot org slash cross politic</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">First, we start with the news of a coronation for our friends across the pond.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://www.cnn.com/2023/05/06/europe/coronation-king-charles-ckc-gbr-intl/index.html"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.cnn.com/2023/05/06/europe/coronation-king-charles-ckc-gbr-intl/index.html</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>King Charles III is crowned in once-in-a-generation ceremony</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Britain&rsquo;s King Charles III has been crowned in a once-in-a-generation royal event witnessed by hundreds of high-profile guests inside Westminster Abbey, as well as tens of thousands of well-wishers who gathered in central London despite the rain.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">While Charles became King on the death of his mother, Queen Elizabeth II last September, the coronation on Saturday was the formal crowning of the monarch.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The service was a profoundly religious affair, reflecting the fact that aside from being head of state of the United Kingdom and 14 other countries, Charles is also the Supreme Governor of the Church of England.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">In the most significant moment of the day, Archbishop of Canterbury Justin Welby placed the 360-year-old St. Edward&rsquo;s Crown on Charles&rsquo; head. The spiritual leader of the Anglican Church then declared: &ldquo;God Save the King.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The intricate service lasted just over two hours &ndash; about an hour shorter than Elizabeth II&rsquo;s coronation in 1953 &ndash; and followed a traditional template that has stayed much the same for more than 1,000 years.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">However, it has been modernized in certain key ways. The archbishop acknowledged the multiple faiths observed in the UK during the ceremony, saying the Church of England &ldquo;will seek to foster an environment in which people of all faiths may live freely.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The King took the Coronation Oath and became the first monarch to pray aloud at his coronation. In his prayer he asked to &ldquo;be a blessing&rdquo; to people &ldquo;of every faith and conviction.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">In what is considered the most sacred part of the ceremony, the King was anointed with holy oil by the Archbishop of Canterbury. He was also presented with the coronation regalia, including the royal Robe and Stole, in what is known as the investiture part of the service.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Then, for the first time in coronation history, the archbishop invited the British public, as well as those from &ldquo;other Realms,&rdquo; to recite a pledge of allegiance to the newly crowned monarch and his &ldquo;heirs and successors.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Ahead of the event, some parts of the British media and public interpreted the invitation as a command, reporting that people had been &ldquo;asked&rdquo; and &ldquo;called&rdquo; to swear allegiance to the King. In the face of such criticism, the Church of England revised the text of the liturgy so that members of the public would be given a choice between saying simply &ldquo;God save King Charles&rdquo; or reciting the full pledge of allegiance.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The ceremony also included a reading from the Bible by UK Prime Minister Rishi Sunak and, in another coronation first, gospel music.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Once the King was crowned, his wife, Queen Camilla, was crowned in her own, shorter ceremony with Queen Mary&rsquo;s Crown &ndash; marking the first time in recent history that a new crown wasn&rsquo;t made specifically for this occasion.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">After the ceremony, the newly crowned King and Queen rode back to Buckingham Palace in a much larger parade, featuring 4,000 members of the armed forces, 250 horses and 19 military bands.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The pomp and pageantry concluded with a royal salute and the customary balcony appearance by the King and family members. They and the crowds below watched a flypast of military aircraft, slimmed down because of the poor weather.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Despite the splendor of the occasion, it has not been without controversy. Some have objected to millions of pounds of taxpayers&rsquo; money being spent on a lavish ceremony at a time when millions of Britons are suffering a severe cost-of-living crisis.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Security is by far the most costly element of large events and the Met said ahead of time that Saturday would be the largest one-day policing operation in decades, with more than 11,500 officers on duty in London.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The coronation has also attracted anti-monarchy demonstrations, with a small number of protesters arrested in central London on Saturday morning before the event began.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Republic, a campaign group that calls for the abolition of the monarchy, said the idea of the &ldquo;homage of the people&rdquo; was &ldquo;offensive, tone deaf and a gesture that holds the people in contempt.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Some eyebrows were also raised earlier this week when a controversial and widely criticized UK public order bill came into force.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Since the death of Queen Elizabeth II last year, there have been a number of instances of anti-monarchists turning up at royal engagements to voice their grievances against the institution.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The new rules, signed into law by the King on Tuesday, just days before the coronation, empower the police to take stronger action against peaceful protesters.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://thepostmillennial.com/biden-to-veto-house-remain-in-mexico-bill?utm_campaign=64487"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://thepostmillennial.com/biden-to-veto-house-remain-in-mexico-bill?utm_campaign=64487</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Biden to veto House 'remain in Mexico' bill</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">On Monday, the White House announced that Joe Biden would veto an immigration bill coming out of the House of Representatives that would reinstitute several Trump-era policies including construction of the border wall and the remain in Mexico policy, which stated that anyone seeking asylum had to wait in Mexico as their claim was processed.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">According to the Associated Press, the White House Office of Management and Budget said in a statement, "While we welcome Congress' engagement on meaningful steps to address immigration and the challenges at the border, this bill would make things worse, not better. Because this bill does very little to actually increase border security while doing a great deal to trample on the nation&rsquo;s core values and international obligations, it should be rejected."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">On Thursday, the House is set to vote on the 213-page Secure the Border Act. Thursday also marks the expiration of Title 42, the Trump-era policy instituted under Covid that granted Border Patrol and Department of Homeland Security officials the ability to expel illegal immigrants over health concerns.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The Secure the Border Act would also require employers to verify a worker's immigration status for employment and institute the E-Verify system</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">House Majority Leader Steve Scalise said, "Joe Biden sent a message that America&rsquo;s border is open, and millions of people answered that call and started coming across our border illegally. We&rsquo;re going to show the president how to solve the problem."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The Daily Mail reports, the Secure the Border Act would limit federal funds for NGOs (non-governmental organizations) that aid illegal immigrants crossing the border, would end Biden's expedited entry policy for Nicaraguans, Venezuelans, Haitians, and Cubans, and grant more money for hiring additional border agents.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Joe Biden loosened restrictions along the southern border after he took office and HHS Secretary Alejandro Mayorkas made the announcement that migrants seeking asylum would be permitted entry into the US as would unaccompanied minors.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">US Border Patrol Chief Raul Ortiz said that over the weekend 26,382 apprehensions were made by border patrol and that 11 pounds of fentanyl and 83 pounds of meth were seized.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Mexican cartels have exploited Biden's border crisis, with 2,378,944 illegal immigrant encounters reported in the 2022 fiscal year and 1,659,206 reported in FY 2021, by trafficking humans and drugs, especially fentanyl across the border in record numbers.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://www.dailywire.com/news/airlines-may-soon-be-on-the-hook-for-delayed-and-canceled-flights-transportation-dept-says"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.dailywire.com/news/airlines-may-soon-be-on-the-hook-for-delayed-and-canceled-flights-transportation-dept-says</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Airlines May Soon Be On The Hook For Delayed And Canceled Flights, Transportation Dept Says</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Transportation Secretary Pete Boo-tuh-jeg announced on Monday that the agency introduced rules requiring airlines to reimburse customers who incur expenses due to certain delayed and canceled flights, a move which comes as the industry faces elevated demand and a constrained labor force.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The proposed rules, which would apply when an airline delays a flight for more than three hours or cancels a flight for a &ldquo;controllable&rdquo; reason, would mandate that the firms offer compensation for stranded passengers, as well as a meal or meal voucher, overnight accommodations, and ground transportation between the airport and hotel.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&ldquo;When an airline causes a flight cancellation or delay, passengers should not foot the bill,&rdquo; Buttigieg said in a statement, noting that the proposed reimbursement rules would be the first in American history.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The move comes after Southwest Airlines experienced holiday travel disruptions last year due to extreme winter weather conditions, staff shortages, and an outdated computer system. The carrier canceled thousands of flights days after other carriers had resumed normal operations. Buttigieg told the company, which has since promised to compensate passengers for all expenses incurred during that time, that the disruptions were &ldquo;unacceptable&rdquo; and promised that his agency would exercise &ldquo;the fullest extent of its investigative and enforcement powers&rdquo; to ensure customers are reimbursed.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The new proposals also occur as the sector faces a severely limited pool of available pilots and frontline staff. Carriers previously encouraged commercial pilots to retire as worldwide lockdowns caused demand for air travel to plummet in the spring of 2020, worsening a previous trend toward a lack of available pilots. Elevated prices for airline tickets and a rapid return in travel demand, however, are now prompting lawmakers to consider the problem.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Regional Airline Association CEO Faye Malarkey Black told members of the House Transportation and Infrastructure Committee last month that more than 50% of current pilots would be forced to retire within the next 15 years because of federal rules mandating that pilots exit their positions once they reach 65 years of age, even as only 8% of pilots are below 30 years of age due to the high cost of flight education. Buttigieg has opposed legislation that would increase the retirement threshold to 67 years of age, contending that &ldquo;the answer is to make sure we have as many and as good pilots ready to take their place, to have a stronger pipeline.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://www.nbcnews.com/health/health-news/fecal-transplant-pill-fda-approval-rcna81779"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.nbcnews.com/health/health-news/fecal-transplant-pill-fda-approval-rcna81779</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>FDA approves first pill for fecal transplants, made from healthy bacteria in human waste</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">U.S. health officials on Wednesday approved the first pill made from healthy bacteria found in human waste to fight dangerous gut infections &mdash; an easier way of performing so-called fecal transplants.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The new treatment from Seres Therapeutics provides a simpler, rigorously tested version of stool-based procedures that some medical specialists have used for more than a decade to help patients.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The Food and Drug Administration cleared the capsules for adults 18 and older who face risks from repeat infections with Clostridium difficile, a bacteria that can cause severe nausea, cramping and diarrhea.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<ol>
<li><span style="font-weight: 400;"> diff is particularly dangerous when it reoccurs, leading to between 15,000 and 30,000 deaths per year. It can be killed with antibiotics but they also destroy good bacteria that live in the gut, leaving it more susceptible to future infections. The new capsules are approved for patients who have already received antibiotic treatment.</span></li>
</ol>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">More than 10 years ago, some doctors began reporting success with fecal transplants &mdash; using stool from a healthy donor &mdash; to restore the gut&rsquo;s healthy balance and prevent reinfections.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The FDA approved the first pharmaceutical-grade version of the treatment last year from a rival drugmaker, Ferring Pharmaceuticals. But that company&rsquo;s product &mdash; like most of the original procedures &mdash; must be delivered via the rectum.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Cambridge, Mass.-based Seres will market its drug as a less invasive option. The treatment will be sold under the brand name Vowst and comes as a regimen of four daily capsules taken for three consecutive days.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Both of the recent FDA approvals are the product of years of pharmaceutical industry research into the microbiome, the community of bacteria, viruses and fungi that live in the gut.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Currently most fecal transplants are provided by a network of stool banks that have popped up at medical institutions and hospitals across the country.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">While the availability of new FDA-approved options is expected to decrease demand for donations from stool banks, some plan to stay open.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The FDA warned in its approval announcement that the drug &ldquo;may carry a risk of transmitting infectious agents. It is also possible for Vowst to contain food allergens,&rdquo; the agency noted.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The FDA approved the treatment based on a 180-patient study in which nearly 88% of patients taking the capsules did not experience reinfection after 8 weeks, compared with 60% of those who received dummy pills.</span></p>]]></description>
   <author><![CDATA[Garrison Hardie]]></author>
   <enclosure url="https://app.dropwave.io/episode/eade695e-9ed3-47f9-a2e6-93f67f318e99/crosspolitic-daily-news-brief-for-tuesday-may-9th-2023.mp3" length="778" type="audio/mp3"/>
   <guid isPermaLink="false"><![CDATA[eade695e-9ed3-47f9-a2e6-93f67f318e99]]></guid>
   <pubDate>Tue, 09 May 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
   <source url=""><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></source>
   <itunes:author><![CDATA[Garrison Hardie]]></itunes:author>
   <itunes:image href="https://assets-cdn2.dropwave.io/2ab40ac0-e99d-4f25-a6d2-541d2c9b290a/cover-art/hUZu1H9lrRY0wXg66WHC8eLwYBA3hbRNTAHQmHt2.png"/>
   <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
   <itunes:duration>778</itunes:duration>
   <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
  
  </item><item>
   <title><![CDATA[CrossPolitic Daily News Brief for Friday, May 5th, 2023 [Daily News Brief]]]></title>
   <link>https://app.dropwave.io/episode/11f6aeb4-42f0-4413-bf0f-675fb220e80a/crosspolitic-daily-news-brief-for-friday-may-5th-2023.mp3</link>
   <description><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">This is Garrison Hardie with your CrossPolitic Daily News Brief for Friday, May 5th, 2023. Watch out for the revenge of the 5th if you&rsquo;re into that&hellip; or cinco de mayo, take your pick.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://tvpworld.com/69620835/us-navy-deployed-drag-queen-influencer-to-boost-youth-recruitment"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://tvpworld.com/69620835/us-navy-deployed-drag-queen-influencer-to-boost-youth-recruitment</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>As part of a recruitment drive aimed at the country&rsquo;s youth, the U.S. Navy deployed a "drag queen influencer" to assist in boosting lagging numbers in the military.</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">In November of last year Joshua Kelley aka &ldquo;Harpy Daniels&rdquo;, who has over 1,300,000 likes on TikTok, revealed that he was to be the Navy&rsquo;s &lsquo;Digital Ambassador&rsquo;.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Whilst the U.S. Navy only recently revealed about approaching Kelley, the drag queen claims to have danced in drag in front of an audience of service officers on a number of occasions, even sharing one video from 2018 on his Instagram.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Kelley was part of a Digital Ambassador initiative that lasted from October 2022 to March 2023, &ldquo;designed to explore the digital environment to reach a wide range of potential candidates,&rdquo; a Navy spokesperson told Fox News. The spokesperson also said that the Navy is navigating &ldquo;the most challenging recruiting environment it has faced since the start of the all-volunteer force.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&ldquo;The Navy did not compensate YN2 Kelley or any others for being Navy Digital Ambassadors. The pilot has concluded and we are now evaluating the program and how it will exist in the future," the spokesperson added.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Regarding his role as Digital Ambassador, Kelley wrote on his Instagram page: &ldquo;Thank you to the Navy for giving me this opportunity! I don't speak for the Navy but simply sharing my experience in the Navy! Hoorah, and let's go Slay!&rdquo;.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Not only the Navy but more broadly the U.S. military face big problems in convincing young people to join. Only 13 pct of 18-29-year-olds are &ldquo;highly willing&rdquo; to join the military, whilst 25 pct declared themselves &ldquo;somewhat willing&rdquo; and 26 pct are &ldquo;not willing at all.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Gender ideology has become a hot topic in the Navy and all branches of the U.S. Armed Forces.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">In March, a group of House Democrats proposed legislation to prevent the Department of Defense from standing in the way of transgender people who want to serve in the military.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Some critics have argued that the purpose of the U.S. military is to provide security for the country, not to be a tool for gender ideology politics. Whilst others have suggested that in an unstable world, where a lot of military strategy is played out through bravado, such as with military drills, it is perhaps surprising that the U.S. would do the opposite of striking fear into their enemies.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">It&rsquo;s a good thing we have Joshua to scare off said enemies, which ties in nicely for this next story!</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://www.usnews.com/news/world/articles/2023-05-03/second-oil-tanker-in-a-week-seized-by-iran-in-gulf-u-s-navy"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.usnews.com/news/world/articles/2023-05-03/second-oil-tanker-in-a-week-seized-by-iran-in-gulf-u-s-navy</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Iran Seizes Second Oil Tanker in a Week in Gulf -U.S. Navy</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Iran seized a second oil tanker in a week on Wednesday in Gulf waters, and the U.S. State Department called for its release, in the latest escalation in a series of seizures or attacks on commercial vessels in Gulf waters since 2019.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The Baa-rain-based Fifth Fleet of the U.S. Navy said the Panama-flagged oil tanker Niovi was seized by Iran's Islamic Revolutionary Guard Corps Navy (IRGCN) at 6:20 a.m. (0220 GMT) while passing through the Strait of Hor-mooz.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">In Iran's first response, Tehran's prosecutor announced the oil tanker was seized on a judicial order following a complaint by a plaintiff, the judiciary's Mizan news agency said. No further details were provided.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The incident comes after Iran on Thursday seized a Marshall Islands-flagged oil tanker in the Gulf of Oman called the Advantage Sweet. That tanker is being held by Iranian authorities in Bandar Abbas, the Marshall Islands flag registry said on Tuesday.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Maritime security firm Ambrey has said it believed the Advantage Sweet's seizure was in response to a recent seizure via a court order by the United States of an oil cargo aboard the Marshall Islands tanker Suez Rajan.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The Niovi oil tanker seized on Wednesday had been travelling from Dubai toward the UAE's Fujairah port when it was forced by IRGCN boats to change course towards Iranian territorial waters, the Navy said.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The Niovi last reported its position at 0231 GMT on Wednesday off the coast of Oman in the Strait of Hormuz with the UAE as its destination, Refinitiv ship tracking data showed.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">According to the International Maritime Organization shipping database,, the Niovi's owner is Grand Financing Co, and the ship is managed by Greece-based Smart Tankers, which did not immediately respond to a request for comment.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Vedant Patel, a deputy spokesperson at the U.S. State Department, told reporters the Biden administration and the "international community" call on Iran and its Navy to release the ships and their crews. "Iran's harassment of vessels and interference with navigational rights in regional and international waters are contrary to international law and disruptive to regional stability and security," Patel said.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">About a fifth of the world's crude oil and oil products passes through the Strait of Hormuz, a choke point between Iran and Oman, according to data from analytics firm Vortexa.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Since 2019, there have been a series of attacks on shipping in the strategic Gulf waters at times of tension between the United States and Iran.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Indirect talks between Tehran and Washington to revive Iran's 2015 nuclear pact with world powers have stalled since September over a range of issues, including the Islamic Republic's violent crackdown on popular protests, Tehran's sale of drones to Russia and acceleration of its nuclear program.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://justthenews.com/nation/crime/alleged-texas-killer-captured-following-manhunt"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://justthenews.com/nation/crime/alleged-texas-killer-captured-following-manhunt</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Fugitive illegal alien accused of mass killing in Texas captured</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Authorities on Tuesday apprehended an individual suspected of killing five people in Cleveland, Texas, following a Friday evening altercation.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Authorities arrested Francisco Oropesa without incident on Tuesday evening, NBC News reported, citing the Montgomery County Sheriff's Office.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">His arrest marks an end to the manhunt that had baffled law enforcement for days. Authorities indicated earlier this week that they had "zero leads" as to his whereabouts.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">As of Monday, it was believed that Oropesa had slipped past a network of roadblocks in the Cleveland area, despite extensive efforts by law enforcement to contain him within a set perimeter.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">During the manhunt, reports emerged that the fugitive had been deported four times, twice in 2009, and again in 2012 and 2016.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The manhunt ensued following Oropesa's alleged killing of five of his neighbors after reportedly being asked to stop shooting his firearm. Authorities indicated that four adults were found dead at the scene while one child died at the hospital later.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://www.latimes.com/california/story/2023-05-03/gun-rights-advocates-renew-legal-fight-over-californias-10-day-wait-on-firearm-purchases"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.latimes.com/california/story/2023-05-03/gun-rights-advocates-renew-legal-fight-over-californias-10-day-wait-on-firearm-purchases</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Gun rights advocates renew legal fight over California&rsquo;s 10-day wait for firearm buyers</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Renewing a legal battle that some had considered settled, gun rights advocates filed a federal lawsuit this week challenging a California law that places a 10-day waiting period on most firearm purchases.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The law, which requires people to wait the prescribed &ldquo;cooling off&rdquo; period even if they&rsquo;ve passed a more immediate background check, is aimed in part at deterring people from rushing to harm themselves or others with newly purchased weapons during periods of sudden distress or anger.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Gun control advocates and state officials say the law reduces gun violence, including suicides, and the law has been upheld in the face of legal challenges before &mdash; including by the U.S. Supreme Court, which in 2018 declined to hear an appeal to a lower court decision upholding it.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">However, things have changed since the high court ruled last year &mdash; in New York State Rifle &amp; Pistol Assn. vs. Bruen &mdash; that restrictions on firearms violate the 2nd Amendment if they aren&rsquo;t deeply rooted in the nation&rsquo;s history or analogous to some historical rule.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">According to the San Diego gun owners and advocacy groups suing the state, the high court&rsquo;s 2018 decision allowing the waiting period law to stand was &ldquo;abrogated,&rdquo; or undone, by its more recent Bruen decision, and, therefore, the law is unconstitutional under the court&rsquo;s newer historical standard.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The plaintiffs argue enforcement of the law &ldquo;prevents law-abiding people from taking possession of lawfully acquired firearms for immediate self-defense and other lawful purposes &mdash; even after [state officials] know the individual is eligible to exercise their fundamental, constitutionally protected right to keep and bear arms.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The office of California Atty. Gen. Rob Bonta said it was reviewing the lawsuit Tuesday but could not otherwise comment. Bonta is the lead defendant in the lawsuit.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">According to legal experts, the revived challenge reflects how massively the legal landscape around gun laws has changed since President Trump shifted the Supreme Court to the right and the court issued its Bruen decision.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">It also reflects the increased confidence among gun rights advocates that the high court is ready and willing to overturn more gun laws, the experts said &mdash; even those it may have allowed to stand in the past.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Jake Charles, an associate professor at Pepperdine Caruso School of Law and an expert in firearms law, said he was &ldquo;surprised it took until May of this year&rdquo; for the waiting period law to be challenged again under Bruen &mdash; in part because it is obviously vulnerable.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Prior to Bruen, federal courts across the country judged gun laws not only through a historical lens, but by assessing whether they served a well-reasoned purpose of modern government.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">When the California-based U.S. 9th Circuit Court of Appeals upheld California&rsquo;s 10-day waiting period law in 2016, it did so based on such a review. Writing for the court, Circuit Judge Mary Schroeder found that the 10-day waiting period was &ldquo;a reasonable safety precaution,&rdquo; and therefore constitutional.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Now, however, Bruen has changed the relevant legal analysis and Schroeder&rsquo;s reasoning is now irrelevant, the plaintiffs argue.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The law&nbsp; rvive, they argue, because waiting period laws were not enacted in the country until 1923 &mdash; making them too recent to be considered part of the nation&rsquo;s tradition under Bruen.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Gun law experts said it&rsquo;s a strong argument.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Attorneys for California may still argue the law is similar enough to some historical law that didn&rsquo;t institute a waiting period for purchased weapons but restricted the purchase of them in some other way. The state has already argued that other modern gun laws being challenged &mdash; including its bans on assault-style weapons and high-capacity magazines &mdash; are similar enough to other historical laws to survive Bruen&rsquo;s test, even if they aren&rsquo;t exactly the same.</span></p>]]></description>
   <author><![CDATA[Garrison Hardie]]></author>
   <enclosure url="https://app.dropwave.io/episode/11f6aeb4-42f0-4413-bf0f-675fb220e80a/crosspolitic-daily-news-brief-for-friday-may-5th-2023.mp3" length="673" type="audio/mp3"/>
   <guid isPermaLink="false"><![CDATA[11f6aeb4-42f0-4413-bf0f-675fb220e80a]]></guid>
   <pubDate>Fri, 05 May 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
   <source url=""><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></source>
   <itunes:author><![CDATA[Garrison Hardie]]></itunes:author>
   <itunes:image href="https://assets-cdn2.dropwave.io/2ab40ac0-e99d-4f25-a6d2-541d2c9b290a/cover-art/hUZu1H9lrRY0wXg66WHC8eLwYBA3hbRNTAHQmHt2.png"/>
   <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
   <itunes:duration>673</itunes:duration>
   <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
  
  </item><item>
   <title><![CDATA[Daily News Brief for Thursday, May the 4th be with you, 2023. [Daily News Brief]]]></title>
   <link>https://app.dropwave.io/episode/6b4e5a42-92bd-4e73-8198-9fc7232a40c6/daily-news-brief-for-thursday-may-the-4th-be-with-you-2023.mp3</link>
   <description><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">This is Garrison Hardie with your CrossPolitic Daily News Brief for Thursday, May the 4th be with you, 2023.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://youtu.be/-bzWSJG93P8"><span style="font-weight: 400;" data-rich-links="{&quot;fple-t&quot;:&quot;Star Wars- The Imperial March (Darth Vader's Theme)&quot;,&quot;fple-u&quot;:&quot;https://youtu.be/-bzWSJG93P8&quot;,&quot;fple-mt&quot;:null,&quot;type&quot;:&quot;first-party-link&quot;}">Star Wars- The Imperial March (Darth Vader's Theme)</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;">-Play 0:00-0:36</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Star Wars Day is an informal commemorative day observed annually on May 4 to celebrate the Star Wars media franchise created by founder, former chairman and CEO of Lucasfilm, George Lucas. Observance of the day spread quickly through media and grassroots celebrations since the franchise began in 1977.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The date originated from the pun "May the Fourth be with you", a variant of the popular Star Wars catchphrase "May the Force be with you". Even though the holiday was not created or declared by Lucasfilm, many Star Wars fans around the world have chosen to celebrate the holiday. It has since been embraced by Lucasfilm and parent company Disney as an annual celebration of Star Wars.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Additionally, the release date of the original Star Wars movie on May 25, 1977 is also celebrated as Geek Pride Day.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Olive Tree Biblical Software:</strong></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Discover why more than a million people use the free Olive Tree Bible App as their go-to for reading, studying, and listening to the God&rsquo;s Word.&nbsp;&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Download one of many free Bibles and start taking notes, highlighting verses, and bookmarking your favorite passages.&nbsp;&nbsp;</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Read at your own pace, or choose from a large selection of Reading Plans, including the Bible Reading Challenge.&nbsp;</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">When you are ready to go deeper into your studies, Olive Tree is right there with a large selection of study Bibles, commentaries, and other helpful study resources available for purchase.&nbsp;&nbsp;</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">An extensive bookstore allows you to build your digital library one book at a time.&nbsp;</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Olive Tree&rsquo;s sync technology lets you pick up where you left off on your tablet, pc or phone and get right to studying on another supported device.&nbsp;</span></li>
</ul>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://www.cnn.com/2023/05/03/europe/ukraine-drone-attack-putin-kremlin-intl/index.html"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.cnn.com/2023/05/03/europe/ukraine-drone-attack-putin-kremlin-intl/index.html</span></a></p>
<p><strong>Kyiv denies involvement in alleged Kremlin drone attack</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Russia claimed Ukraine launched an attempt to kill Russian President Vladimir Putin with a drone strike on the Kremlin overnight on Wednesday, an extraordinary allegation that was met with forceful denials in Kyiv.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The Kremlin said the attack was foiled and the alleged drones destroyed. Video that appeared on social media shows a bright flash and a puff of smoke over a part of the Kremlin, the official residence of the Russian president and the most potent symbol of power in Moscow.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">In a statement, the Kremlin said it regarded the alleged attack as terrorism and a deliberate attempt on Putin&rsquo;s life. &ldquo;Russia reserves the right to take retaliatory measures where and when it sees fit,&rdquo; it added.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Ukraine denied involvement in the alleged strike.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">US officials said they were still assessing the incident, and had no information about who might have been responsible. Whatever the truth, any admission of a security breach at the heart of the Kremlin is remarkable.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Moscow said the alleged attack took place in the early hours of Wednesday. The Russian president was not in the building at the time, Kremlin spokesperson Dmitry Peskov said.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">analysis of video showing the incident support the Kremlin&rsquo;s claim that two drones were flown above the Kremlin early Wednesday, but did not show evidence of Ukrainian involvement:</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">A video that appeared to show smoke rising from the Kremlin surfaced on a local neighborhood channel on social media platform Telegram at 2:37 a.m. local time Wednesday. The first reports of the incident citing the Kremlin came via Russian state media TASS and RIA around 2:33 p.m. local time &ndash; around 12 hours later.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Shortly after the first media reports, another video appearing to show the moment a drone exploded above the Kremlin began circulating widely on social media. In the video, the drone appears to fly towards the building&rsquo;s domed roof, followed by what looks like a small explosion.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">In this video, two people appear to be climbing on the dome holding flashlights, and can be seen ducking down just before the moment of the explosion. The people climbing the dome are not present in the first of these videos, but appear in the second, suggesting they were responding to the fire caused by the first drone at the time the subsequent drone appeared.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The Kremlin Press Service has called the purported drone attack an &ldquo;attempt on the President&rsquo;s life,&rdquo; said it was an &ldquo;act of terrorism&rdquo; and blamed Ukraine.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://www.outkick.com/audrey-hale-nashville-police-release-update-litigation/"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.outkick.com/audrey-hale-nashville-police-release-update-litigation/</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>POLICE ANNOUNCE MANIFESTO OF NASHVILLE TRANSGENDER MASS KILLER WON&rsquo;T BE RELEASED SOON</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The release of transgender mass killer Audrey Hale&rsquo;s manifesto has been put on hold.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The Nashville Police Department had previously told Fox News Digital last week the manifesto was being revealed and would be released. People are interested to see what drove Hale to murder six innocent people, including three children, at the Covenant School in late March.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Now, it appears that the process has hit a roadblock.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Metro Nashville PD announced Wednesday afternoon that &ldquo;Due to pending litigation filed this week, the Metropolitan Nashville Police Department has been advised by counsel to hold in abeyance the release of records related to the shooting at The Covenant School pending orders or direction of the court.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The update is in response to a lawsuit filed by former Hamilton County Sheriff Jim Hammond and the Tennessee Firearms Association against the Nashville city government and the police to release the manifesto, according to TimeFreePress.com.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">As of early May, the public still doesn&rsquo;t have any idea what is in the manifesto.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">It&rsquo;s been more than a month since Audrey Hale walked into the Covenant School to unleash her rampage of terror against children and staffers.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Despite the significant time that has passed, government officials have seemingly dragged their feet to make sure the manifesto doesn&rsquo;t come out. For most of the time, it appeared that Hale&rsquo;s writings would never be released.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Metro Nashville Council Member Courtney Johnston previously told the New York Post, &ldquo;What I was told is, her manifesto was a blueprint on total destruction, and it was so, so detailed at the level of what she had planned &hellip; That document in the wrong person&rsquo;s hands would be astronomically dangerous.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2023/05/03/fed-rate-decision-may-2023-.html"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.cnbc.com/2023/05/03/fed-rate-decision-may-2023-.html</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Fed increases rates a quarter point and signals a potential end to hikes</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The Federal Reserve on Wednesday approved its 10th interest rate increase in just a little over a year and dropped a tentative hint that the current tightening cycle is at an end.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">In a unanimous decision widely expected by markets, the central bank&rsquo;s Federal Open Market Committee raised its benchmark borrowing rate by 0.25 percentage point. The rate sets what banks charge each other for overnight lending but feeds through to many consumer debt products such as mortgages, auto loans and credit cards.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The increase takes the fed funds rate to a target range of 5%-5.25%, the highest since August 2007.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Markets, though, are more focused on whether the Fed will pause here, particularly with lingering concerns over economic growth and a banking crisis that has rattled nerves on Wall Street. Stocks rose slightly and Treasury yields were mostly lower immediately following the Fed news, but stocks struggled to hold on to the gains.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">During Wednesday&rsquo;s news conference, Chairman Jerome Powell said &ldquo;a decision on a pause was not made today&rdquo; but noted the change in the statement language around future policy firming was &ldquo;meaningful.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The post-meeting statement had only offered some clarity on the future pace of rate hikes &mdash; and not by what it said but what it didn&rsquo;t say. The document omitted a sentence present in the previous statement saying that &ldquo;the Committee anticipates that some additional policy firming may be appropriate&rdquo; for the Fed to achieve its 2% inflation goal.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The statement also tweaked language to outline the conditions under which &ldquo;additional policy firming may be appropriate.&rdquo; Previously, the FOMC had framed the forward guidance around how it would determine &ldquo;the extent of future increases in the target range.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The statement reiterated that the Fed &ldquo;will take into account the cumulative tightening of monetary policy, the lags with which monetary policy affects economic activity and inflation, and economic and financial developments.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Taken together, the moves are at least a tenuous nod that while tight policy could remain in effect, the path ahead is less clear for actual interest rate hikes as policymakers assess incoming data and financial conditions.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Wednesday&rsquo;s decision comes amid U.S. economic fragility and over the objections of prominent Democratic lawmakers, who urged the Fed this week to stop rate hikes that they insisted could cause a recession and excessive loss of jobs.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">However, the labor market has remained strong since the increases started in March 2022. At the same time, inflation is still well above the 2% target that policymakers consider optimum. Multiple officials have said rates probably will need to stay elevated even if the hikes are put on hold.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://www.theepochtimes.com/irs-spent-10-million-on-weapons-since-covid-19-pandemic-began-watchdog_5238319.html?utm_source=partner&amp;utm_campaign=BonginoReport"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.theepochtimes.com/irs-spent-10-million-on-weapons-since-covid-19-pandemic-began-watchdog_5238319.html?utm_source=partner&amp;utm_campaign=BonginoReport</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>IRS Spent $10 Million on Weapons Since COVID-19 Pandemic Began: Watchdog</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The Internal Revenue Service (IRS) has been splashing out millions stocking up on guns, ammunition, and combat gear since 2020, according to the findings of Open The Books, a watchdog group that tracks government spending.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">A report by the watchdog, published on April 27, found that the agency has spent a total of $10 million on weaponry and gear since the COVID-19 pandemic began, including $2.3 million on duty ammunition, $1.2 million on ballistic shields, and another $1.3 million on &ldquo;various other gear for criminal investigation agents.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Additionally, the agency has spent $474,000 on Smith &amp; Wesson rifles, $463,000 on Beretta 1301 tactical shotguns, and $243,000 on body armor vests since 2020.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Another $467,000 was reportedly spent on duty tactical lighting, $354,000 on tactical gear bags, and $267,000 on ballistic helmets in the same time.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The report, called &ldquo;The Militarization of Federal Bureaucracy,&rdquo; contains updated data through the end of March 2023.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Since 2006, the IRS has splashed out $35.2 million (adjusted for inflation) on guns, ammunition, and military-style equipment. The report found that 2020 and 2021 saw them spend increased amounts.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">In a statement to Open The Books in 2021, an IRS spokesperson said IRS Criminal Investigation special agents &ldquo;have been using weapons throughout their history as they have consistently found themselves investigating the most dangerous criminals involved in organized crime, drugs, and gangs.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The IRS Careers website for criminal investigation special agents states that applicants must be willing to &ldquo;carry a firearm, must be prepared to protect him/herself or others from physical attacks at any time and without warning and use firearms in life-threatening situations; must be willing to use force up to and including the use of deadly force.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://www.dailyfetched.com/san-francisco-loses-another-retail-giant-as-shops-continue-to-close-due-to-crime/"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.dailyfetched.com/san-francisco-loses-another-retail-giant-as-shops-continue-to-close-due-to-crime/</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>San Francisco Loses Another Retail Giant as Shops Continue To Close Due to Crime</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">According to a memo from Chief Stores Officer Jamie Nordstrom to employees, the company has decided not to renew its leases for its San Francisco Centre Nordstrom store and the Market Street Rack store.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&ldquo;We&rsquo;ve spent more than 35 years serving customers in downtown San Francisco, building relationships with them and investing in the local community,&rdquo; Nordstrom wrote.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&ldquo;But as many of you know, the dynamics of the downtown San Francisco market have changed dramatically over the past several years, impacting customer foot traffic to our stores and our ability to operate successfully.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The San Francisco Centre location will close at the end of August, and the Market Street Rack will close on July 1.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">the owner of the Westfield mall, told the San Francisco Standard that such closures &ldquo;underscores the deteriorating situation in Downtown San Francisco.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">A spokesperson for the mall added:</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&ldquo;A growing number of retailers and businesses are leaving the area due to the unsafe conditions for customers, retailers, and employees, coupled with the fact that these significant issues are preventing an economic recovery of the area.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The statement continued:</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">[Unibail-Rodamco-Westfield] has actively engaged with city leaders for many years to express our serious concerns, which are shared by our customers and retailers. We have urged the city to find solutions to the key issues and lack of enforcement again.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The news comes not long after San Francisco flagship Whole Foods retail store closed after just a year due to 568 emergency calls over 13 months amid soaring crime in the city.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Incidents included vagrants starting fights, throwing food, and defecating on the floor.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Twenty retailers have closed stores in the Union Square area since 2020, The Standard reports.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Last month, CashApp founder Bob Lee was fatally stabbed in the streets of San Fransisco, while former fire commissioner Don Carmignani was recently beaten over the head with a pipe by a vagrant.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Last October, The Daily Fetched reported that commuters were resorting to arming themselves with baseball bats and stun guns due to droves of violent drug addicts.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Residents of the SoMa, in northeast San Francisco, said the recent opening of the SoMa RISE drug sobering center, which opened in June, has plagued the neighborhood, making it unsafe.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Residents say the center, which aims to temper drug usage, has done nothing but draw heavy users to the neighborhood.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Residents said the influx of drug users had brought soaring crime, making the neighborhood more dangerous, Fox News reported.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">San Francisco Mayor London Breed touted the center as a safe haven for addicts looking to rebuild their lives.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">But according to SoMa resident and business owner Mark Sackett, the reality of the center in the neighborhood is much different.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://www.dailyfetched.com/joe-biden-offers-500k-grant-for-teachers-in-pakistan-to-help-transgender-youth/"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.dailyfetched.com/joe-biden-offers-500k-grant-for-teachers-in-pakistan-to-help-transgender-youth/</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Joe Biden Offers $500K Grant for Teachers in Pakistan to Help Transgender Youth</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">According to the State Department grant, it will teach English language skills to Pakistani transgender youth so they &ldquo;better participate in the global community and prepare them for success in the workplace.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The grant report aims to focus on three components:</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">(1) Professional Development for English Language Teachers from Non-Mainstream Institutions</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">(2) Professional Development for novice Pakistani English language teachers</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">(3) Professional Development for Transgender Youth and for Afghan Teachers, Students, and Young Professionals Residing in Pakistan.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The program component that includes a focus on transgender youth accepts proposals from applicants &ldquo;for a minimum of $25,000 and a maximum of $75,000 to implement: (1) intensive professional development courses for Pakistani transgender youth from the ages of 13-25, and (2) and intensive professional development courses for Afghan teachers, students, and young professionals residing in Pakistan.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The components aim to improve English language communication skills and connect trainees to a professional alumni network.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Applicants to the Biden grant program are encouraged to address, &ldquo;What is the most effective way to reach the greatest number of Pakistani transgender youth and Afghan teachers, students, and young professionals from diverse locations across Pakistan?&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">A spokesperson for the State Department said the education project from the agency focuses on transgender youth like it does with other &ldquo;marginalized communities.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">However, the spokesperson added that the grant funds won&rsquo;t be used for gender transitions.</span></p>]]></description>
   <author><![CDATA[Garrison Hardie]]></author>
   <enclosure url="https://app.dropwave.io/episode/6b4e5a42-92bd-4e73-8198-9fc7232a40c6/daily-news-brief-for-thursday-may-the-4th-be-with-you-2023.mp3" length="951" type="audio/mp3"/>
   <guid isPermaLink="false"><![CDATA[6b4e5a42-92bd-4e73-8198-9fc7232a40c6]]></guid>
   <pubDate>Thu, 04 May 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
   <source url=""><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></source>
   <itunes:author><![CDATA[Garrison Hardie]]></itunes:author>
   <itunes:image href="https://assets-cdn2.dropwave.io/2ab40ac0-e99d-4f25-a6d2-541d2c9b290a/cover-art/hUZu1H9lrRY0wXg66WHC8eLwYBA3hbRNTAHQmHt2.png"/>
   <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
   <itunes:duration>951</itunes:duration>
   <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
  
  </item><item>
   <title><![CDATA[Daily News Brief for Thursday, May the 4th be with you, 2023. [Daily News Brief]]]></title>
   <link>https://app.dropwave.io/episode/1251c2aa-1900-4260-a78b-0bfeda16c36d/daily-news-brief-for-thursday-may-the-4th-be-with-you-2023-1.mp3</link>
   <description><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">This is Garrison Hardie with your CrossPolitic Daily News Brief for Thursday, May the 4th be with you, 2023.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://youtu.be/-bzWSJG93P8"><span style="font-weight: 400;" data-rich-links="{&quot;fple-t&quot;:&quot;Star Wars- The Imperial March (Darth Vader's Theme)&quot;,&quot;fple-u&quot;:&quot;https://youtu.be/-bzWSJG93P8&quot;,&quot;fple-mt&quot;:null,&quot;type&quot;:&quot;first-party-link&quot;}">Star Wars- The Imperial March (Darth Vader's Theme)</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;">-Play 0:00-0:36</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Star Wars Day is an informal commemorative day observed annually on May 4 to celebrate the Star Wars media franchise created by founder, former chairman and CEO of Lucasfilm, George Lucas. Observance of the day spread quickly through media and grassroots celebrations since the franchise began in 1977.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The date originated from the pun "May the Fourth be with you", a variant of the popular Star Wars catchphrase "May the Force be with you". Even though the holiday was not created or declared by Lucasfilm, many Star Wars fans around the world have chosen to celebrate the holiday. It has since been embraced by Lucasfilm and parent company Disney as an annual celebration of Star Wars.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Additionally, the release date of the original Star Wars movie on May 25, 1977 is also celebrated as Geek Pride Day.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Olive Tree Biblical Software:</strong></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Discover why more than a million people use the free Olive Tree Bible App as their go-to for reading, studying, and listening to the God&rsquo;s Word.&nbsp;&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Download one of many free Bibles and start taking notes, highlighting verses, and bookmarking your favorite passages.&nbsp;&nbsp;</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Read at your own pace, or choose from a large selection of Reading Plans, including the Bible Reading Challenge.&nbsp;</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">When you are ready to go deeper into your studies, Olive Tree is right there with a large selection of study Bibles, commentaries, and other helpful study resources available for purchase.&nbsp;&nbsp;</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">An extensive bookstore allows you to build your digital library one book at a time.&nbsp;</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Olive Tree&rsquo;s sync technology lets you pick up where you left off on your tablet, pc or phone and get right to studying on another supported device.&nbsp;</span></li>
</ul>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://www.cnn.com/2023/05/03/europe/ukraine-drone-attack-putin-kremlin-intl/index.html"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.cnn.com/2023/05/03/europe/ukraine-drone-attack-putin-kremlin-intl/index.html</span></a></p>
<p><strong>Kyiv denies involvement in alleged Kremlin drone attack</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Russia claimed Ukraine launched an attempt to kill Russian President Vladimir Putin with a drone strike on the Kremlin overnight on Wednesday, an extraordinary allegation that was met with forceful denials in Kyiv.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The Kremlin said the attack was foiled and the alleged drones destroyed. Video that appeared on social media shows a bright flash and a puff of smoke over a part of the Kremlin, the official residence of the Russian president and the most potent symbol of power in Moscow.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">In a statement, the Kremlin said it regarded the alleged attack as terrorism and a deliberate attempt on Putin&rsquo;s life. &ldquo;Russia reserves the right to take retaliatory measures where and when it sees fit,&rdquo; it added.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Ukraine denied involvement in the alleged strike.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">US officials said they were still assessing the incident, and had no information about who might have been responsible. Whatever the truth, any admission of a security breach at the heart of the Kremlin is remarkable.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Moscow said the alleged attack took place in the early hours of Wednesday. The Russian president was not in the building at the time, Kremlin spokesperson Dmitry Peskov said.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">analysis of video showing the incident support the Kremlin&rsquo;s claim that two drones were flown above the Kremlin early Wednesday, but did not show evidence of Ukrainian involvement:</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">A video that appeared to show smoke rising from the Kremlin surfaced on a local neighborhood channel on social media platform Telegram at 2:37 a.m. local time Wednesday. The first reports of the incident citing the Kremlin came via Russian state media TASS and RIA around 2:33 p.m. local time &ndash; around 12 hours later.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Shortly after the first media reports, another video appearing to show the moment a drone exploded above the Kremlin began circulating widely on social media. In the video, the drone appears to fly towards the building&rsquo;s domed roof, followed by what looks like a small explosion.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">In this video, two people appear to be climbing on the dome holding flashlights, and can be seen ducking down just before the moment of the explosion. The people climbing the dome are not present in the first of these videos, but appear in the second, suggesting they were responding to the fire caused by the first drone at the time the subsequent drone appeared.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The Kremlin Press Service has called the purported drone attack an &ldquo;attempt on the President&rsquo;s life,&rdquo; said it was an &ldquo;act of terrorism&rdquo; and blamed Ukraine.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://www.outkick.com/audrey-hale-nashville-police-release-update-litigation/"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.outkick.com/audrey-hale-nashville-police-release-update-litigation/</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>POLICE ANNOUNCE MANIFESTO OF NASHVILLE TRANSGENDER MASS KILLER WON&rsquo;T BE RELEASED SOON</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The release of transgender mass killer Audrey Hale&rsquo;s manifesto has been put on hold.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The Nashville Police Department had previously told Fox News Digital last week the manifesto was being revealed and would be released. People are interested to see what drove Hale to murder six innocent people, including three children, at the Covenant School in late March.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Now, it appears that the process has hit a roadblock.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Metro Nashville PD announced Wednesday afternoon that &ldquo;Due to pending litigation filed this week, the Metropolitan Nashville Police Department has been advised by counsel to hold in abeyance the release of records related to the shooting at The Covenant School pending orders or direction of the court.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The update is in response to a lawsuit filed by former Hamilton County Sheriff Jim Hammond and the Tennessee Firearms Association against the Nashville city government and the police to release the manifesto, according to TimeFreePress.com.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">As of early May, the public still doesn&rsquo;t have any idea what is in the manifesto.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">It&rsquo;s been more than a month since Audrey Hale walked into the Covenant School to unleash her rampage of terror against children and staffers.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Despite the significant time that has passed, government officials have seemingly dragged their feet to make sure the manifesto doesn&rsquo;t come out. For most of the time, it appeared that Hale&rsquo;s writings would never be released.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Metro Nashville Council Member Courtney Johnston previously told the New York Post, &ldquo;What I was told is, her manifesto was a blueprint on total destruction, and it was so, so detailed at the level of what she had planned &hellip; That document in the wrong person&rsquo;s hands would be astronomically dangerous.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2023/05/03/fed-rate-decision-may-2023-.html"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.cnbc.com/2023/05/03/fed-rate-decision-may-2023-.html</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Fed increases rates a quarter point and signals a potential end to hikes</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The Federal Reserve on Wednesday approved its 10th interest rate increase in just a little over a year and dropped a tentative hint that the current tightening cycle is at an end.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">In a unanimous decision widely expected by markets, the central bank&rsquo;s Federal Open Market Committee raised its benchmark borrowing rate by 0.25 percentage point. The rate sets what banks charge each other for overnight lending but feeds through to many consumer debt products such as mortgages, auto loans and credit cards.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The increase takes the fed funds rate to a target range of 5%-5.25%, the highest since August 2007.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Markets, though, are more focused on whether the Fed will pause here, particularly with lingering concerns over economic growth and a banking crisis that has rattled nerves on Wall Street. Stocks rose slightly and Treasury yields were mostly lower immediately following the Fed news, but stocks struggled to hold on to the gains.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">During Wednesday&rsquo;s news conference, Chairman Jerome Powell said &ldquo;a decision on a pause was not made today&rdquo; but noted the change in the statement language around future policy firming was &ldquo;meaningful.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The post-meeting statement had only offered some clarity on the future pace of rate hikes &mdash; and not by what it said but what it didn&rsquo;t say. The document omitted a sentence present in the previous statement saying that &ldquo;the Committee anticipates that some additional policy firming may be appropriate&rdquo; for the Fed to achieve its 2% inflation goal.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The statement also tweaked language to outline the conditions under which &ldquo;additional policy firming may be appropriate.&rdquo; Previously, the FOMC had framed the forward guidance around how it would determine &ldquo;the extent of future increases in the target range.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The statement reiterated that the Fed &ldquo;will take into account the cumulative tightening of monetary policy, the lags with which monetary policy affects economic activity and inflation, and economic and financial developments.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Taken together, the moves are at least a tenuous nod that while tight policy could remain in effect, the path ahead is less clear for actual interest rate hikes as policymakers assess incoming data and financial conditions.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Wednesday&rsquo;s decision comes amid U.S. economic fragility and over the objections of prominent Democratic lawmakers, who urged the Fed this week to stop rate hikes that they insisted could cause a recession and excessive loss of jobs.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">However, the labor market has remained strong since the increases started in March 2022. At the same time, inflation is still well above the 2% target that policymakers consider optimum. Multiple officials have said rates probably will need to stay elevated even if the hikes are put on hold.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://www.theepochtimes.com/irs-spent-10-million-on-weapons-since-covid-19-pandemic-began-watchdog_5238319.html?utm_source=partner&amp;utm_campaign=BonginoReport"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.theepochtimes.com/irs-spent-10-million-on-weapons-since-covid-19-pandemic-began-watchdog_5238319.html?utm_source=partner&amp;utm_campaign=BonginoReport</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>IRS Spent $10 Million on Weapons Since COVID-19 Pandemic Began: Watchdog</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The Internal Revenue Service (IRS) has been splashing out millions stocking up on guns, ammunition, and combat gear since 2020, according to the findings of Open The Books, a watchdog group that tracks government spending.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">A report by the watchdog, published on April 27, found that the agency has spent a total of $10 million on weaponry and gear since the COVID-19 pandemic began, including $2.3 million on duty ammunition, $1.2 million on ballistic shields, and another $1.3 million on &ldquo;various other gear for criminal investigation agents.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Additionally, the agency has spent $474,000 on Smith &amp; Wesson rifles, $463,000 on Beretta 1301 tactical shotguns, and $243,000 on body armor vests since 2020.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Another $467,000 was reportedly spent on duty tactical lighting, $354,000 on tactical gear bags, and $267,000 on ballistic helmets in the same time.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The report, called &ldquo;The Militarization of Federal Bureaucracy,&rdquo; contains updated data through the end of March 2023.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Since 2006, the IRS has splashed out $35.2 million (adjusted for inflation) on guns, ammunition, and military-style equipment. The report found that 2020 and 2021 saw them spend increased amounts.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">In a statement to Open The Books in 2021, an IRS spokesperson said IRS Criminal Investigation special agents &ldquo;have been using weapons throughout their history as they have consistently found themselves investigating the most dangerous criminals involved in organized crime, drugs, and gangs.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The IRS Careers website for criminal investigation special agents states that applicants must be willing to &ldquo;carry a firearm, must be prepared to protect him/herself or others from physical attacks at any time and without warning and use firearms in life-threatening situations; must be willing to use force up to and including the use of deadly force.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://www.dailyfetched.com/san-francisco-loses-another-retail-giant-as-shops-continue-to-close-due-to-crime/"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.dailyfetched.com/san-francisco-loses-another-retail-giant-as-shops-continue-to-close-due-to-crime/</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>San Francisco Loses Another Retail Giant as Shops Continue To Close Due to Crime</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">According to a memo from Chief Stores Officer Jamie Nordstrom to employees, the company has decided not to renew its leases for its San Francisco Centre Nordstrom store and the Market Street Rack store.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&ldquo;We&rsquo;ve spent more than 35 years serving customers in downtown San Francisco, building relationships with them and investing in the local community,&rdquo; Nordstrom wrote.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&ldquo;But as many of you know, the dynamics of the downtown San Francisco market have changed dramatically over the past several years, impacting customer foot traffic to our stores and our ability to operate successfully.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The San Francisco Centre location will close at the end of August, and the Market Street Rack will close on July 1.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">the owner of the Westfield mall, told the San Francisco Standard that such closures &ldquo;underscores the deteriorating situation in Downtown San Francisco.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">A spokesperson for the mall added:</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&ldquo;A growing number of retailers and businesses are leaving the area due to the unsafe conditions for customers, retailers, and employees, coupled with the fact that these significant issues are preventing an economic recovery of the area.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The statement continued:</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">[Unibail-Rodamco-Westfield] has actively engaged with city leaders for many years to express our serious concerns, which are shared by our customers and retailers. We have urged the city to find solutions to the key issues and lack of enforcement again.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The news comes not long after San Francisco flagship Whole Foods retail store closed after just a year due to 568 emergency calls over 13 months amid soaring crime in the city.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Incidents included vagrants starting fights, throwing food, and defecating on the floor.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Twenty retailers have closed stores in the Union Square area since 2020, The Standard reports.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Last month, CashApp founder Bob Lee was fatally stabbed in the streets of San Fransisco, while former fire commissioner Don Carmignani was recently beaten over the head with a pipe by a vagrant.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Last October, The Daily Fetched reported that commuters were resorting to arming themselves with baseball bats and stun guns due to droves of violent drug addicts.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Residents of the SoMa, in northeast San Francisco, said the recent opening of the SoMa RISE drug sobering center, which opened in June, has plagued the neighborhood, making it unsafe.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Residents say the center, which aims to temper drug usage, has done nothing but draw heavy users to the neighborhood.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Residents said the influx of drug users had brought soaring crime, making the neighborhood more dangerous, Fox News reported.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">San Francisco Mayor London Breed touted the center as a safe haven for addicts looking to rebuild their lives.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">But according to SoMa resident and business owner Mark Sackett, the reality of the center in the neighborhood is much different.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://www.dailyfetched.com/joe-biden-offers-500k-grant-for-teachers-in-pakistan-to-help-transgender-youth/"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.dailyfetched.com/joe-biden-offers-500k-grant-for-teachers-in-pakistan-to-help-transgender-youth/</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Joe Biden Offers $500K Grant for Teachers in Pakistan to Help Transgender Youth</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">According to the State Department grant, it will teach English language skills to Pakistani transgender youth so they &ldquo;better participate in the global community and prepare them for success in the workplace.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The grant report aims to focus on three components:</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">(1) Professional Development for English Language Teachers from Non-Mainstream Institutions</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">(2) Professional Development for novice Pakistani English language teachers</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">(3) Professional Development for Transgender Youth and for Afghan Teachers, Students, and Young Professionals Residing in Pakistan.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The program component that includes a focus on transgender youth accepts proposals from applicants &ldquo;for a minimum of $25,000 and a maximum of $75,000 to implement: (1) intensive professional development courses for Pakistani transgender youth from the ages of 13-25, and (2) and intensive professional development courses for Afghan teachers, students, and young professionals residing in Pakistan.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The components aim to improve English language communication skills and connect trainees to a professional alumni network.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Applicants to the Biden grant program are encouraged to address, &ldquo;What is the most effective way to reach the greatest number of Pakistani transgender youth and Afghan teachers, students, and young professionals from diverse locations across Pakistan?&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">A spokesperson for the State Department said the education project from the agency focuses on transgender youth like it does with other &ldquo;marginalized communities.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">However, the spokesperson added that the grant funds won&rsquo;t be used for gender transitions.</span></p>]]></description>
   <author><![CDATA[Garrison Hardie]]></author>
   <enclosure url="https://app.dropwave.io/episode/1251c2aa-1900-4260-a78b-0bfeda16c36d/daily-news-brief-for-thursday-may-the-4th-be-with-you-2023-1.mp3" length="951" type="audio/mp3"/>
   <guid isPermaLink="false"><![CDATA[1251c2aa-1900-4260-a78b-0bfeda16c36d]]></guid>
   <pubDate>Thu, 04 May 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
   <source url=""><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></source>
   <itunes:author><![CDATA[Garrison Hardie]]></itunes:author>
   <itunes:image href="https://assets-cdn2.dropwave.io/2ab40ac0-e99d-4f25-a6d2-541d2c9b290a/cover-art/hUZu1H9lrRY0wXg66WHC8eLwYBA3hbRNTAHQmHt2.png"/>
   <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
   <itunes:duration>951</itunes:duration>
   <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
  
  </item><item>
   <title><![CDATA[Daily News Brief for Wednesday, May 3rd, 2023 [Daily News Brief]]]></title>
   <link>https://app.dropwave.io/episode/256dace2-7236-464e-8409-7180184ea69d/daily-news-brief-for-wednesday-may-3rd-2023.mp3</link>
   <description><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">This is Garrison Hardie with your CrossPolitic Daily News Brief for Wednesday, May 3rd, 2023.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>Club Membership Plug: (1/9)</strong></span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Ladies and gentleman, it&rsquo;s never been a better time to become a club member at CrossPolitic. This year, CrossPolitic will be dropping exclusive content into our club portal for club members ONLY. Some of this content will include a pilot TV Show called This America, a Bible study series with Pastor Toby, a special with New Saint Andrew&rsquo;s President, Ben Merkle, our backstage content, and our conference talks! You can grab a club membership for 10 bucks per month&hellip; that&rsquo;s two cups of coffee. So again, head on over to fightlaughfeast.com to get signed up today! That&rsquo;s fightlaughfeast.com.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://thefederalist.com/2023/05/02/in-reynosa-mexico-15000-haitian-immigrants-wait-for-key-biden-policy-to-end/"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://thefederalist.com/2023/05/02/in-reynosa-mexico-15000-haitian-immigrants-wait-for-key-biden-policy-to-end/</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>In Reynosa, Mexico, 15,000 Haitian Immigrants Wait For New Chaotic Biden Policy To Kick In</strong></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">An estimated 15,000 mostly Haitian immigrants have packed into every crevice of this northern Mexican city on the Rio Grande across from McAllen, Texas, and won&rsquo;t leave. At least not until after 11:59 p.m. on May 11.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">That&rsquo;s the moment when the pandemic-era &ldquo;Title 42&rdquo; rapid expulsion policy finally expires and is replaced by a new, untested Biden administration plan for keeping them in Reynosa as well as the &ldquo;volatile logjam,&rdquo; as The New York Times recently termed them, of tens of thousands of other immigrants now waiting for the policy change all over Mexico.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">But because of a powerful deterrent of Title 42 fairly unique to them, the 15,000 Haitians in Reynosa make for a good bellwether for if the administration&rsquo;s replacement strategy will hold them back as Title 42 has, or will invite the most chaotic rush on the U.S. southern border yet in this third long year of the most voluminous mass migration event in recorded American history.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The reason to watch Reynosa after May 12 is that most of its Haitians, long ago overflowing migrant camps all over town, will not dare cross the river while Title 42 is in effect, unlike other nationalities who have already disregarded it by crossing in large numbers. The Haitians of Reynosa won&rsquo;t go even as they enviously witness large numbers of Venezuelans nearby illegally cross in an overwhelming new surge despite Title 42 and see the American government admit them into the country.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Title 42&rsquo;s impact on them is why its ending makes Reynosa and its reticent population of Haitians almost the perfect bellwether to know if the Biden administration&rsquo;s plan for May 12 is going to work as sold. Either way, many hundreds of thousands, turning into millions by the end of the Biden term, will enter.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The question is whether it will be an orderly flow no one can see &mdash; or a schizophrenic rush that overflows border management preparations into towns and cities across the country, hurts the country, and poses a political liability for Democrats thinking about 2024 elections.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://time.com/6276438/biden-troops-border-title42/"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://time.com/6276438/biden-troops-border-title42/</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>Biden Sending 1,500 Troops to Southern Border Ahead of Expected Migration Surge</strong></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The Biden Administration will send 1,500 troops to the southern border of the U.S. to support immigration authorities facing tens of thousands of migrants expected to surge into the country once COVID-19 restrictions are lifted, U.S. officials said.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">At the request of the Department of Homeland Security (DHS), the U.S. service members will be sent on a 90-day temporary deployment assisting Customs and Border Patrol (CBP), the Pentagon announced on Tuesday. The troops will not carry out law enforcement work, but instead perform support duties that will free up CBP agents to detain and process migrants.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Homeland Security Secretary Alejandro Mayorkas said Sunday the government is bracing for a record tide of migration across the southwest border when pandemic restrictions, known as Title 42, end on May 11. The Trump-era authorities prevented migrants from requesting asylum and allowed U.S. border agents to quickly expel migrants out of public-health concerns.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Mayorkas emphasized the immigration system was stretched thin on resources and made a public case for federal relief.&ldquo;I just want to be clear that we are working within significant constraints,&rdquo; he said Sunday on &ldquo;Meet the Press.&rdquo; &ldquo;We need people. We need technology. We need facilities. We need transportation resources&mdash;all of the elements of addressing the needs of a large population of people arriving irregularly at our southern border.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Customs and Border Patrol (CBP) Commissioner Troy Miller told Congress last month his agency is preparing for about 10,000 migrant crossings every day once Title 42 ends. President Joe Biden signed an executive order April 27 to call-up active-duty troops to combat international drug trafficking, officials said. The DHS then formally asked for the Pentagon&rsquo;s support, which Defense Secretary Lloyd Austin approved on Tuesday.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Currently, there are about 2,500 troops&mdash;members of the National Guard on active-duty orders&mdash;deployed along the 2,000-mile-long southwest border supporting CBP&rsquo;s efforts. For years, U.S. forces have monitored &ldquo;Mobile Surveillance Cameras&rdquo; in all nine border sectors in each of the four states bordering Mexico. The devices are armed with infrared cameras, enabling service members to watch for illegal border crossings day or night.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://thepostmillennial.com/breaking-jay-inslee-will-not-seek-4th-term-as-washingtons-governor-in-2024?utm_campaign=64487"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://thepostmillennial.com/breaking-jay-inslee-will-not-seek-4th-term-as-washingtons-governor-in-2024?utm_campaign=64487</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>Jay Inslee will not seek 4th term as Washington's governor in 2024</strong></span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Washington state Governor Jay Inslee (D) announced Monday that he will not seek re-election in 2024.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">In a statement, Inslee said:</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">"Today I announced I will not be running for a fourth term. We've made Washington a beacon for progress, and now it's time to pass the torch," Gov Inslee said on Twitter. "I'm proud of the progress we've made on so many fronts: climate, financial aid, paid family leave, legal justice system reforms, gun safety, reproductive freedom... Now is the time to intensely focus on all we can accomplish in the next year and a half. I intend to do just that.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Inslee's announcement follows the conclusion of an "intense" and "controversial" legislative session where the democrat-controlled House and Senate voted to ban semi-automatic firearms, make Washington a sanctuary state for minors seeking gender affirming care and abortions, and legalized possession of illicit drugs, to name a few.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Governor Inslee became the second governor in state history to serve three consecutive terms after he was re-elected in 2020, and in his announcement Inslee called his tenure a "dynamic success."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Under Inslee's governance, Washington state has succumbed to criminal lawlessness as well as an existential homeless crisis rippling throug the evergreen state. Immediately following the announcement, critics of the governor took to social media to praise Inslee's decision to step down from his post, saying "good riddance."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://thenationalpulse.com/2023/05/01/carjackings-in-washington-dc-skyrocketing/"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://thenationalpulse.com/2023/05/01/carjackings-in-washington-dc-skyrocketing/</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>How Many Carjackings in Washington, D.C. in 2023? Here Are The Staggering Numbers&hellip;</strong></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Carjackings in Washington D.C. continue to skyrocket in line with a five-year trend that has the local police chief Robert Contee lamenting that crimes are happing &ldquo;at a pace that I have not seen in my 30-plus year career here with the Metropolitan Police Department.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Since the beginning of the year, there have been a staggering 228 carjackings in the District, 78 of which occurred in April alone, with 23 in the last week, according to the Washington D.C. Metropolitical Police Department (MPD). Despite 74 percent of this year&rsquo;s carjackings featuring a firearm, less than 35 percent of carjacking offenses are prosecuted.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">In 2018, there were 148 carjackings in D.C., and 152 in 2019. However, following the death of George Floyd, the D.C. city council announced its intention to slash $15 million from the MPD&rsquo;s annual budget. This resulted in an explosion in carjackings, amongst other crimes.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">In 2020, there were 360 carjackings, followed by 425 in 2021, and 485 last year. If carjackings continue to occur at the current rate, there may be as many as 600 by the end of 2023.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Republicans from the U.S. House of Representatives were forced to intervene earlier this year after the D.C. council wanted to reduce penalties for violent crimes such as carjacking and gun possession.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The D.C. council thought it better to lower the maximum jail time for carjackings, and eliminate most mandatory minimum sentences for crimes in the capitol than addressing the problem as the MPD demanded. The Criminal Code Act of 2022 was, however, blocked by the U.S. Congress from coming into force, with 33 Democrat Senators even voting against the bill.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Andrew Clyde, a House Representative from Georgia&rsquo;s 9th District, led the charge against the Criminal Code Act, arguing that Congress had to &ldquo;stop this insanity in its tracks.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The Democrat Mayor of Washington D.C., Muriel Bowser, has also promised free steering wheel locks for some cars after suggesting one of the reasons why carjackings are so common had something to do with a &ldquo;recent social media challenge.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">These actions, however, do not meet the demands of the local police force. A representative of the MPD Carjacking Task Force, Valkyrie Barnes, argues, &ldquo;It&rsquo;s ridiculous&hellip; unless there is some kind of deterrent to this, it&rsquo;s not going to stop&hellip; we need more [detectives].&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The District of Columbia and many of its residents currently support the notion of adding D.C. as a fully-fledged state, arguing that residents are taxed as citizens, but do not receive commensurate representation as a result. Opponents of this cause point out that D.C. residents often have far more political sway than ordinary voters around the country, and that the purpose of the District, per the nation&rsquo;s founders, was to be separate from the Congress and its machinations. Many of the latter group believe that much of D.C. should be given back to Virginia and Maryland as a means to create a compromise over representation.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/americas/vice-media-bankruptcy-journalism-layoffs-b2330554.html"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/americas/vice-media-bankruptcy-journalism-layoffs-b2330554.html</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>Vice heading for bankruptcy after once being worth $5.7bn, reports say</strong></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Vice, once heralded as the insurgent leader of a new generation of media companies, is heading for bankruptcy, according to The New York Times.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Two people familiar with Vice operations told the paper the media company is looking for a buyer. Otherwise, the company will have to file for bankruptcy, the unnamed sources said.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">&ldquo;Vice Media Group has been engaged in a comprehensive evaluation of strategic alternatives and planning,&rdquo; Vice said in a statement on Monday to the Times. &ldquo;The company, its board and stakeholders continue to be focused on finding the best path for the company.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The media company, which got its start as a Canadian alternative publication, eventually became a digital powerhouse known for its in-your-face, youth-focused stories about politics, music, and culture, told across a constellation of websites, films, podcasts, TV shows, the flagship magazine, and eventually a standalone TV network.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Vice News reporters filed memorable documentaries like a report from the Charlottesville &ldquo;Unite the Right&rdquo; rally in 2017, as well as reporting gonzo tales like chronicling NBA legend Dennis Rodman&rsquo;s visit to North Korea.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">A 2017 investment round led by TPG once valued the company at $5.7bn. More recently, the company was thought to be worth less than $1bn, according to reports earlier this year about the company&rsquo;s potential search for a buyer.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Despite receiving acclaim for its unique style of storytelling, as well investments from marquee names like Disney and Fox, the company has continued to struggle financially.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Last week, the company announced it would cancel its flagship &ldquo;Vice News Tonight&rdquo; show and lay off dozens of employees amid a larger corporate restructuring, the latest in a bruising season of media layoffs that saw cuts at Insider, NPR, Paper magazine, and the demise of Buzzfeed News.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">That follows reports that the Vice got an emergency $30m in financing to pay off a growing number of debts.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">In February, Vice Media chief executive Nancy Dubuc left the company.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The company fell short of a 2022 revenue goal by more than $100m, The Wall Street Journal reported in December.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The previous year, the company scuttled plans to go public through a special purpose acquisition company.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">In addition to its financial woes, Vice has been plagued by scandals, with critics charging the company&rsquo;s anti-establishment ethos at times covered up a corporate culture rife with abuse.</span></p>
<p><br /><br /><br /></p>]]></description>
   <author><![CDATA[Garrison Hardie]]></author>
   <enclosure url="https://app.dropwave.io/episode/256dace2-7236-464e-8409-7180184ea69d/daily-news-brief-for-wednesday-may-3rd-2023.mp3" length="780" type="audio/mp3"/>
   <guid isPermaLink="false"><![CDATA[256dace2-7236-464e-8409-7180184ea69d]]></guid>
   <pubDate>Wed, 03 May 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
   <source url=""><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></source>
   <itunes:author><![CDATA[Garrison Hardie]]></itunes:author>
   <itunes:image href="https://assets-cdn2.dropwave.io/2ab40ac0-e99d-4f25-a6d2-541d2c9b290a/cover-art/hUZu1H9lrRY0wXg66WHC8eLwYBA3hbRNTAHQmHt2.png"/>
   <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
   <itunes:duration>780</itunes:duration>
   <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
  
  </item>
 </channel>
</rss>
