<?xml version="1.0"?>
<?xml-stylesheet href="/storage/feed-stylesheet.xsl" type="text/xsl"?>

<rss xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
 <channel>
  <title>FLF - Daily News Brief</title>
  <link>https://dropwave.io</link>
  <description><![CDATA[FIGHT LAUGH FEAST PRESENTS SHOWS PROCLAIMING THE LORDSHIP OF CHRIST OVER ALL OF LIFE.
]]></description>
  <language>en</language>
  <managingEditor><![CDATA[fightlaughfeast@gmail.com (FLF, LLC)]]></managingEditor>
  <webMaster><![CDATA[support@dropwave.io (DropWave Support)]]></webMaster>
  <pubDate>Sat, 15 Apr 2023 07:25:46 +0000</pubDate>
  <lastBuildDate>Sat, 15 Apr 2023 07:25:46 +0000</lastBuildDate>
  <image>
   <url>https://is4-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Podcasts113/v4/58/56/52/5856525c-2973-cf29-3db9-21faa8595391/mza_1144696925612154085.png/1200x1200bb.jpg</url>
   <link>https://dropwave.io</link>
   <title><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></title>
  </image>
  <itunes:author><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></itunes:author>
  <itunes:image href="https://is4-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Podcasts113/v4/58/56/52/5856525c-2973-cf29-3db9-21faa8595391/mza_1144696925612154085.png/1200x1200bb.jpg"/>
  <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
  <itunes:owner>
   <itunes:name><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></itunes:name>
   <itunes:email>fightlaughfeast@gmail.com</itunes:email>
  </itunes:owner>
  <itunes:category text="News"/>
  <item>
   <title><![CDATA[Daily News Brief for Friday, April 14th, 2023 [Daily News Brief]]]></title>
   <link>https://app.dropwave.io/episode/76bb9a83-daa3-48f3-9a67-a9c01498f24d/daily-news-brief-for-friday-april-14th-2023.mp3</link>
   <description><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">&nbsp;This is Garrison Hardie with your CrossPolitic Daily News Brief for Friday, April 14th, 2023.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>Fight Laugh Feast Magazine</strong></span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Our Fight Laugh Feast Magazine is a quarterly issue that packs a punch like a 21 year Balvenie, no ice. We don&rsquo;t water down our scotch, why would we water down our theology? Order a yearly subscription for yourself and then send a couple yearly subscriptions to your friends who have been drinking luke-warm evangelical cool-aid. Every quarter we promise quality food for the soul, wine for the heart, and some Red Bull for turning over tables. Our magazine will include cultural commentary, a Psalm of the quarter, recipes for feasting, laughter sprinkled through out the glossy pages, and more. Sign up today, at fightlaughfeast.com.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://www.foxnews.com/us/texas-dairy-explosion-leaves-least-18000-cattle-dead-person-critically-injured"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.foxnews.com/us/texas-dairy-explosion-leaves-least-18000-cattle-dead-person-critically-injured</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>Texas dairy explosion leaves at least 18,000 cattle dead, 1 person critically injured</strong></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Approximately 18,000 cows were killed, and one person was critically injured, in an explosion at a dairy farm in the Texas Panhandle on Monday.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The Castro County Sheriff&rsquo;s Office confirmed with Fox News Digital that the cows were in a holding area before being brought in for milking when the blast occurred at the Southfork Dairy Farm in Dimmitt.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Very few cows in the holding area survived, officials told local outlet KFDA.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Police said they received eight calls just before 7:30 p.m. Monday about an explosion and fire. Callers said some employees were trapped inside the milking building.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">When law enforcement officials arrived at the dairy farm, they determined only a woman was trapped in the dairy building.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Officials said the trapped individual was rescued from the building and airlifted to UMC Hospital in Lubbock for treatment. Lubbock is located about 80 miles from Dimmitt.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Officials said all the other dairy employees were accounted for and were safe.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The Texas State Fire Marshal&rsquo;s Office is investigating the cause of the fire.</span></p>
<p><br /><br /><br /><br /><br /></p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/restoring-america/community-family/legal-abortions-fell-post-roe"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/restoring-america/community-family/legal-abortions-fell-post-roe</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>Legal abortions fell 6% in six months after Supreme Court overturned Roe</strong></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Legal abortions in the United States dropped more than 6% in the six months after the Supreme Court overturned Roe v. Wade , a testament to the new rules and regulations that now vary from state to state.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">A new report released by the Society of Family Planning, called the "#WeCount" report, determined that there were 32,260 fewer abortions from July to December 2022 when compared to data taken in April and May. In the months post-Dobbs v. Jackson's Women's Health Organization decision, which overturned Roe v. Wade in June, there were an average of 5,377 fewer abortions per month.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Telehealth abortions provided through virtual clinics have increased every month since pre-Dobbs in April, and by December, the appointments represented 9% of all abortions across the six months post-Dobbs.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The organization found that the effect of the Dobbs decision is based on state abortion policies. States with bans in place witnessed a total of 43,410 fewer people cumulatively having abortions. On the other side, states that permitted abortion access following the end of Roe v. Wade saw a total of 11,150 more people who had abortions.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">By Dec. 31, 13 states had banned abortion with almost no exceptions, and Georgia imposed a six-week ban. In Georgia, the number of abortions decreased by 40%, according to the report.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Florida saw 1,200 more abortions in the months post-Dobbs because state law currently permits abortions up to 15 weeks. The Sunshine State is inching closer to a six-week ban after the state Senate passed the legislation , sending it to the House, where it is also expected to pass, and eventually Gov. Ron DeSantis's (R-FL) desk, where he is likely to sign it.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The Dobbs decision also pushed thousands of women to travel long distances to obtain abortions if their home states had restrictions. The report showed that the number of abortions increased significantly in states that have solidified abortion access and are located near states with bans, the largest increases occurring in Florida, Illinois, and North Carolina.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Abortions declined significantly in places where the courts overturned proposed bans, such as Arizona and Ohio.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Several clinics in Arizona, which allows abortions up to 15 weeks, temporarily shut down while the court determined whether the near total ban that predated Arizona's statehood could be enforced. Eventually, the court ruled that the 15-week ban overruled the near-total ban and went into effect in December 2022. The number of abortions per month in Arizona dropped 85% to 230 between April and July and shot back up to 870 by December, according to the report.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">In Ohio, a six-week ban went into effect after the Dobbs decision. In that time, the number of abortions dropped 62% from before Dobbs to 790. However, a judge halted the six-week ban, and abortions are now legal up to 22 weeks of pregnancy.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The number of abortions now sits at over 1,400 per month. Pro-abortion activists in Ohio created a committee in December to explore putting abortion on the ballot , and in March, the Ohio Ballot Board certified the language of the proposed ballot initiative that would enshrine abortion in the state constitution.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://www.politico.eu/article/euco-eu-crosses-into-the-border-fence-game-migration/"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.politico.eu/article/euco-eu-crosses-into-the-border-fence-game-migration/</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>EU vows more cash for frontier policing as border fence debate revives</strong></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The EU that once largely dismissed border walls as a crude Trumpian solution is vowing to channel &ldquo;substantial&rdquo; funds into frontier guards and surveillance equipment, as countries ramp up calls for help paying for their border fences.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">For several hours at an EU Council summit on Thursday, the only show in town was Volodymyr Zelenskyy. Then the Ukrainian leader left, and a well-worn clash over migration instantly returned. There were stark signs that the bloc&rsquo;s stance is hardening.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Well into the early hours of Friday morning, EU leaders made proposal after proposal, all seeking to stem the rise in people arriving to the Continent outside legal channels. Some wanted Brussels to help pay for border fences. Others stressed a focus on returning rejected asylum seekers.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">German Chancellor Olaf Scholz at one point tried to calm passions, according to one official familiar with the discussion. Did the EU want to turn itself into a fortress? Walls, simply put, do not work, he said, pointing to the U.S.-Mexico border, where a fractious debate over a wall hasn&rsquo;t abated crossings.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Ultimately, however, Scholz and the other EU leaders did back more stringent EU border control methods &mdash; an indication of how the EU has toughened its stance on the subject since the apex of the 2015-2016 Syrian refugee crisis.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Border fences, especially, were once anathema in much of Europe, treated as a blunt instrument meant more for show than practical use. But a growing coalition of EU countries has now built such barriers, with some wanting Brussels to help pay for more. And while EU officials won&rsquo;t cross the red line into fence funding, they usually agree to fund surveillance technology and border guards.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">As EU leaders went round and round, Austria led the pack in pushing for more border resources from Brussels.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The country has experienced an increase in migrants arriving through the Western Balkans, often crossing from Serbia into Hungary and then into Austria.&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">At Thursday&rsquo;s summit, the country got its preferred language into the final statement, which implores the Commission &ldquo;to immediately mobilise substantial EU funds and means&rdquo; to help countries bolster their &ldquo;border protection capabilities and infrastructure.&rdquo; The statement specifically referenced &ldquo;surveillance, including aerial surveillance, and equipment.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">After the leaders broke up around 3 a.m., Austrian Chancellor Karl Nehammer lauded the result, which may be the EU&rsquo;s strongest language yet on the issue.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Bulgaria has been a particular focus for Austria. It wants the EU to help reinforce a fence between the EU border country and Turkey, a project it pegs at &euro;2 billion. But the Commission has cautioned that it only has &euro;3 billion left for all fence-related projects, according to multiple diplomats.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Austria was not the only country stumping for more border funding. A clutch of countries including Hungary, Denmark, Estonia, Lithuania, Latvia and Greece signed a letter backing tougher border measures on the eve of the summit. The missive echoed a similar letter from October 2021 that saw 12 member states asking the European Commission to let EU cash go toward border barriers.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Von der Leyen, who opposes the EU entering the fence-funding business, said after the meeting that leaders had only agreed to use EU money for infrastructure like cameras, watch towers and vehicles.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">She even made a point of mentioning that an existing fence the EU was looking to rehab &ldquo;doesn&rsquo;t function&rdquo; since it doesn&rsquo;t have adequate personnel and surveillance equipment. The effort is part of a series of &ldquo;pilot projects&rdquo; von der Leyen said the EU would launch to illustrate, among other things, how an ideal border would process asylum seekers.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://www.conservativereview.com/trans-teacher-allegedly-threatened-to-shoot-students-and-parents-say-the-middle-school-failed-to-notify-them-2659853038.html"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.conservativereview.com/trans-teacher-allegedly-threatened-to-shoot-students-and-parents-say-the-middle-school-failed-to-notify-them-2659853038.html</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>Trans teacher allegedly threatened to shoot students, and parents say the middle school failed to notify them</strong></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Parents with children attending Fox Chapel Middle School in Hernando County, Florida, told the Daily Caller News Foundation that school officials failed to notify them after a transgender teacher allegedly threatened to shoot and kill students.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Assistant Principal Kerry Thornton and guidance counselor Kimberly Walby contacted the middle school&rsquo;s resource officer on March 24 to file an incident report regarding a teacher allegedly expressing thoughts about suicidal ideation and possibly shooting students.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The report, obtained by Moms for Liberty&rsquo;s Hernando County chapter, stated that Alexander Renczkowski, a biologically male teacher who identifies as female and goes by the name Ashlee, had confessed to having &ldquo;bad thoughts&rdquo; but denied threatening to harm students. According to the report, the teacher stated that &ldquo;she does not want to harm herself.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Authorities then confiscated three firearms and ammunition from Renczkowski&rsquo;s home, the report noted. After conducting a threat assessment, Hernando County School District&rsquo;s mental health coordinator, Sandra Hurst, found that the teacher did not meet the criteria to be involuntarily institutionalized for mental illness under Florida&rsquo;s Baker Act law, the report added.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Renczkowski was reportedly allowed back into the classroom the next day.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Several parents told the DCNF that they learned about the incident from a local reporter, not the school.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">According to the parents, the school did not contact them until 17 days after the report was filed and the news had already circulated.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Hernando County Sheriff&rsquo;s Office released a statement Wednesday about the March incident.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">&ldquo;On 03-24-23, the HCSO was notified of, and did investigate, an event at Fox Chapel Middle School,&rdquo; the sheriff&rsquo;s office said. &ldquo;The investigation revealed that no criminal offense(s) occurred; therefore, no arrest(s) could be made. Further, deputies found that the individual did not, at that moment, meet the required criteria for involuntary commitment under the Baker Act.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The sheriff&rsquo;s office noted that the teacher cooperated with law enforcement to hand over all firearms.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The Hernando County School District, Fox Chapel Middle School, and Alexander Renczkowski did not respond to requests for comment, the DCNF reported.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://dailycaller.com/2023/04/12/south-korea-ammunition-biden-administraiton-ukraine/"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://dailycaller.com/2023/04/12/south-korea-ammunition-biden-administraiton-ukraine/</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>US Gets 500,000 Artillery Shells On Loan From South Korea To Fill Plummeting Stocks</strong></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The U.S. reached an agreement last month to obtain 500,000 rounds of 155 mm artillery shells on loan from South Korea, Reuters reported Wednesday, citing a South Korean newspaper.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">U.S. stocks of the 155 mm round, which see a high level of consumption on the battlefield in Ukraine, have fallen to critically low levels, and the Biden administration sought artillery ammunition from South Korea in March, according to documents seen by the DCNF. South Korea will &ldquo;lend&rdquo; the shells to the U.S. rather than selling to avoid the possibility of those shells being delivered to Ukraine in a future assistance package, thereby violating a South Korean policy against supplying lethal items to countries at war, the DongA Ilbo outlet reported, citing government sources, according to Reuters.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">South Korea&rsquo;s defense ministry told Reuters that Seoul and allies are exploring a variety of ways to provide Ukraine with much needed munitions but did not speak to specific discussions or agreements.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The U.S. for the first time struck a deal with South Korea to purchase 100,000 155 mm rounds for ultimate delivery to Ukraine in November. Routing the deal through the U.S. allowed South Korea to avoid complicity in Ukraine&rsquo;s attacks on Russian forces, Reuters and The Wall Street Journal reported, citing U.S. officials familiar with the matter.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The shells will primarily serve to backfill U.S. stockpiles, DongA Ilbo reported, according to Reuters.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">News of the agreement comes after leaked Pentagon documents from March described a conversation between two South Korean national security officials about potentially routing artillery through Poland &mdash; alarming officials and prompting Seoul to confront Washington about the disclosure, Reuters reported.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The South Korean president&rsquo;s office affirmed the leaked documents would not damage relations with the U.S., The New York Times reported. U.S. Defense Secretary Lloyd Austin and South Korean Defense Minister Lee Jong-sup agreed in a phone call Tuesday that &ldquo;quite a few of the documents in question were fabricated.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">So far, the country has declined to provide overt military assistance to Ukraine, citing its own precarious security situation as its northern neighbor has not relented on threats against Seoul&rsquo;s sovereignty, according to Reuters. However, Seoul is one of the U.S. key allies in Asia and a large ammunition producer.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The U.S. has sent more than 1.5 million 155 mm shells for the Howitzer system to Ukraine, as well as an additional 6,500 GPS-guided rounds, according to a fact sheet that was accurate as of April 4. For comparison, the U.S. produces about 15,000 rounds per month, the NYT reported.</span></p>]]></description>
   <author><![CDATA[Garrison Hardie]]></author>
   <enclosure url="https://app.dropwave.io/episode/76bb9a83-daa3-48f3-9a67-a9c01498f24d/daily-news-brief-for-friday-april-14th-2023.mp3" length="864" type="audio/mp3"/>
   <guid isPermaLink="false"><![CDATA[76bb9a83-daa3-48f3-9a67-a9c01498f24d]]></guid>
   <pubDate>Fri, 14 Apr 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
   <source url=""><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></source>
   <itunes:author><![CDATA[Garrison Hardie]]></itunes:author>
   <itunes:image href="https://assets-cdn2.dropwave.io/2ab40ac0-e99d-4f25-a6d2-541d2c9b290a/cover-art/hUZu1H9lrRY0wXg66WHC8eLwYBA3hbRNTAHQmHt2.png"/>
   <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
   <itunes:duration>864</itunes:duration>
   <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
  
  </item><item>
   <title><![CDATA[Daily News Brief for Thursday, April 13th, 2023 [Daily News Brief]]]></title>
   <link>https://app.dropwave.io/episode/9b467d7b-d044-480d-8dcd-4c2a7dbc089e/daily-news-brief-for-thursday-april-13th-2023.mp3</link>
   <description><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">This is Garrison Hardie with your CrossPolitic Daily News Brief for Thursday, April 13th, 2023.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>Fight Laugh Feast Conference - Ark Encounter</strong></span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">This year, our Fight Laugh Feast Conference is at the Ark Encounter in Kentucky on The Politics of Six Day Creation. The politics of six day creation is the difference between a fixed standard of justice and a careening standard of justice, the difference between the corrosive relativism that creates mobs and anarchy and the freedom of objectivity, truth, and due process. The politics of six day creation establishes the authority and sufficiency of God&rsquo;s Word for all of life: from what is a man or a woman, when does human life begin, and how is human society best organized?</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Come hear Ken Ham, Pastor Doug Wilson, Dr. Ben Merkle, Dr. Gordon Wilson, me and more, and of course a live CrossPolitic show! Mark your calendars for October 11th-14th, as we fight, laugh, and feast, with beer &amp; psalms, our amazing lineup of speakers, our Rowdy Christian Merch, and a Sabbath Feast to wrap up the occasion. Maybe an infant baptism while we&rsquo;re at it! Visit fightlaughfeast.com for more information!</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Now ladies and gentleman&hellip; I have some audio for you to listen to. Listen to this exchange between Elon Musk, and a BBC reporter. A warning&hellip; Elon slaughters this &ldquo;journalist&rdquo;. Seeing as this is audio, just know I use air quotes when I say journalist.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=XqJKAnN0-gM"><span style="font-weight: 400;" data-rich-links="{&quot;fple-t&quot;:&quot;'You Just Lied': Elon Musk Slaughters BBC Reporter In Live Interview&quot;,&quot;fple-u&quot;:&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=XqJKAnN0-gM&quot;,&quot;fple-mt&quot;:null,&quot;type&quot;:&quot;first-party-link&quot;}">'You Just Lied': Elon Musk Slaughters BBC Reporter In Live Interview</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;">-Play Video</span></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">That ladies and gentleman, is the state of journalism these days.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Now, let&rsquo;s get to the news:</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://www.foxnews.com/politics/farmers-score-victory-biden-admin-judge-pauses-controversial-eco-rules"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.foxnews.com/politics/farmers-score-victory-biden-admin-judge-pauses-controversial-eco-rules</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>Farmers score victory over Biden admin as judge pauses controversial eco rules</strong></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">A federal judge granted a request Wednesday from a coalition of 24 states and several industry groups to block environmental regulations redefining how water sources are protected.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Judge Daniel Hovland of the U.S. District Court for the District of North Dakota ruled that the so-called Waters of the United States (WOTUS) rule announced by the Environmental Protection Agency (EPA) in late December poses "great" risks to states. The judge also ruled that the federal government should wait until the Supreme Court soon rules on a related case pending before it.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">On Dec. 30, the final working day of 2022, the EPA and the U.S. Army Corps of Engineers quietly announced they had approved the WOTUS regulation and that it would be implemented in March. After announcing it, EPA Administrator Michael Regan said the rule "safeguards our nation&rsquo;s waters."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The rule ultimately opens the door for the federal government to regulate wetlands, lakes, ponds, streams and "relatively permanent" waterways, largely mimicking a pre-2015 environmental rule set during the Obama administration which implemented the changes in an effort to curb water pollution. The regulation is a broad interpretation of which water sources require protection under the Clean Water Act.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">However, in its lawsuit filed in February, the 24-state coalition &mdash; led by West Virginia, Georgia, Iowa and North Dakota &mdash; argued the regulations were an example of federal overreach and an attack on their sovereign authority regulating bodies of water and surrounding land.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">A series of industry groups &mdash; including the American Farm Bureau Federation, American Petroleum Institute, National Association of Realtors, National Cattlemen&rsquo;s Beef Association, National Corn Growers Association and National Mining Association &mdash; also entered the lawsuit as intervenor-plaintiffs.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Meanwhile, the Senate and House both passed a bipartisan resolution earlier this year overturning the WOTUS regulation. President Biden vetoed the bill on April 6.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://www.theepochtimes.com/biden-admin-unveils-rule-to-force-67-percent-of-cars-sold-to-be-electric-by-2032_5189758.html?utm_source=partner&amp;utm_campaign=BonginoReport"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.theepochtimes.com/biden-admin-unveils-rule-to-force-67-percent-of-cars-sold-to-be-electric-by-2032_5189758.html?utm_source=partner&amp;utm_campaign=BonginoReport</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>US Unveils Toughest-Ever Car Emissions Rule in Bid to Force Surge in EV Purchases</strong></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">President Joe Biden further accelerated the nation&rsquo;s switch to electric vehicles by announcing two proposed federal rule changes aimed at reducing greenhouse gases and other pollutants in motor vehicle emissions.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The changes, announced on April 12, would affect virtually all gasoline-powered vehicles on U.S. highways, save consumers an estimated $12,000 in fuel and maintenance costs over the life of a vehicle, and avoid almost 10 billion tons of carbon dioxide emissions through 2055, according to the Environmental Protection Agency (EPA).</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The move aims to further the president&rsquo;s goal of having 50 percent of all new cars and light trucks and 30 percent of new medium- and heavy-duty trucks sold in 2030 be zero-emission vehicles. Electric vehicles (EVs) are considered zero-emission vehicles.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The EPA estimates that approval of these rules would result in 67 percent of new passenger vehicles and light trucks being EVs by 2032, along with 50 percent of buses, 35 percent of short-haul freight tractors, and 25 percent of long-haul freight tractors.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Critics have claimed that the move, which will increase the price of new cars, was made without consideration of the ability of the nation&rsquo;s supply chain to meet the demand.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The Biden administration has spent roughly $31 billion on the development of so-called clean transportation over the past two years, including the development of a network of EV charging stations, improving the supply chain for materials needed to produce EV batteries, and making loans to companies that manufacture EVs and EV components in the United States.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">General Motors, Ford, and Stellantis&mdash;the maker of Chrysler, Fiat, Ram, and Jeep brands&mdash;stated in 2021 that they would aim to reach EV sales of at least 40 percent of all their new vehicle sales by 2030.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The rule change comes 10 months after six major automakers pledged to stop selling gas and diesel-powered cars worldwide by 2040.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Speaking of hemoraging money&hellip;&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://thepoliticalinsider.com/federal-government-borrowing-astronomical-6-billion-per-day/"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://thepoliticalinsider.com/federal-government-borrowing-astronomical-6-billion-per-day/</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>Federal Government Borrowing Astronomical $6 Billion Per Day</strong></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The U.S. Congressional Budget Office said Monday the federal government has accumulated more than a trillion dollars in debt only six months into the fiscal year.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The Committee for a Responsible Federal Budget released a report pointing out that those figures amount to an average of $6 billion per day so far in fiscal year 2023.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The data figures come as Republicans and Democrats approach a deadline to raise the debt ceiling or face defaulting on the national debt, an unprecedented event that would have huge ramifications for the U.S. and global economy.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Republicans have pointed to those figures as proof of the need for spending cuts.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">President Joe Biden, though, has shown no interest in negotiating. Democrats argue the fiscal deadline is too risky to play with in negotiations.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The CRFB said if nothing changes, the annual deficit will hit $3 trillion by the end of this decade.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Down to Florida we go&hellip;&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://www.dailyfetched.com/florida-lawmakers-prepare-to-pass-measure-to-permit-death-penalty-for-pedophiles/"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.dailyfetched.com/florida-lawmakers-prepare-to-pass-measure-to-permit-death-penalty-for-pedophiles/</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>Florida Lawmakers Prepare to Pass Measure to Permit DEATH PENALTY for Pedophiles</strong></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The House will consider its version of the bill (HB 1297) after (SB 1342) was cleared on Tuesday by the Rules Committee, as it readies for the bill to be presented to the full Senate.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">For decades, the U.S. Supreme Court and Florida Supreme Court rulings have prohibited the execution of child rapists and sexual abuse cases.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The last time someone was executed for a non-murder offense in the U.S. was 1964, according to a Senate staff analysis.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">However, the House and Senate bills argue that a Florida Supreme Court case in1981 and a U.S. Supreme Court case in 2008 were both &ldquo;wrongly decided.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The Senate version declared the cases represent an &ldquo;egregious infringement of the state&rsquo;s power to punish the most heinous of crimes.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The bill&rsquo;s sponsor, former prosecutor turned Republican state senator Jonathan Martin, said the legislation would allow for &ldquo;constitutional boundaries by providing a sentencing procedure for those heinous crimes.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">&ldquo;If an individual rapes an 11-year-old, a 10-year-old, a 2-year-old or a 5-year-old, they should be subject to the death penalty,&rdquo; Martin said Tuesday.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">As Red State reports:</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The legislation inevitably has drawn criticism, with Aaron Wyat of the Florida Association of Criminal Defense Lawyers pointing out that although people want &ldquo;vengeance&rdquo; against pedophiles, the death penalty would represent an overturning of decades of legal precedent.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">&ldquo;This bill invites a longer, costlier (legal) process for the victim and their family that they will endure,&rdquo; Wayt said.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">&ldquo;While this crime, anyone convicted of it is vile, heinous, the Constitution itself, the case law, the Supreme Court demands a maximum of life in prison. And so while it&rsquo;s not the vengeance we all want, it&rsquo;s the justice that the Constitution demands,&rdquo; Wayt added.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Meanwhile, left-leaning Slate Magazine argued a &ldquo;sentence of life without parole is a harsh and severe punishment,&rdquo; even for pedophiles.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Despite the media pushback, the bill has attracted support from some Democrats, including Senate Minority Leader Lauren Book, who suffered sexual abuse as a child and founded the advocacy organization Lauren&rsquo;s Kids.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Gov. Ron DeSantis is expected to sign off on this legislation after voicing support for the death penalty for pedophiles.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://www.foxnews.com/politics/trump-sues-michael-cohen-for-500-million"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.foxnews.com/politics/trump-sues-michael-cohen-for-500-million</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>Trump sues former attorney Michael Cohen for $500 million</strong></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Former President Donald Trump is suing his ex-lawyer Michael Cohen for more than $500 million, alleging a breach of his attorney-client relationship, unjust enrichment, and more, Fox News Digital has learned.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Trump&rsquo;s legal team filed the more-than 30-page federal lawsuit in U.S. District Court for the Southern District of Florida on Wednesday.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The lawsuit alleges Cohen breached his attorney-client relationship by "spreading falsehoods" about Trump that were "likely to be embarrassing or detrimental, and partook in other misconduct," while also breaching contractual terms of a confidentiality agreement he signed as a condition of employment with Trump.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The lawsuit alleges Cohen spread falsehoods about Trump "with malicious intent and to wholly self-serving ends."&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The lawsuit details Cohen&rsquo;s "myriad of public statements, including the publication of two books, a podcast series, and innumerable mainstream media appearances," while ignoring "cease and desist" orders.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">It claims Cohen has, in recent months, "increased the frequency and hostility of the illicit acts" and "appears to have become emboldened and repeatedly continues to make wrongful and false statements" about Trump through various platforms.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The lawsuit comes a week after the former president pleaded not guilty in Manhattan court to 34 felony counts of falsifying business records in New York, related to alleged hush money payments made ahead of the 2016 presidential election.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://www.breitbart.com/sports/2023/04/11/nc-state-senator-moves-to-ban-participation-trophies/"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.breitbart.com/sports/2023/04/11/nc-state-senator-moves-to-ban-participation-trophies/</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>NC State Senator Moves to Ban Participation Trophies</strong></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Coffee is for closers, and if a state senator in North Carolina has his way, trophies at state-sponsored events will be for winners and winners only.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">North Carolina State Senator Timothy Moffitt (R) introduced the &ldquo;Eliminate Participation Trophies Act&rdquo; on Thursday, known in the legislature as SB 430.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">If passed, the bill would ban the awarding of trophies to children at state-sponsored athletic events simply for participating in the event.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">&ldquo;Youth sports or other youth recreation activities operated under the authority of a local government shall not include awards for participants based solely on their participation in the sport or other activity,&rdquo; the proposed law states. &ldquo;Awards provided in connection with the activity, if any, shall be based on identified performance achievements.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Moffitt and the bill&rsquo;s co-sponsors, Republican Senators Bobby Hanig and Eddie Settle say the bill will apply only to state-sponsored youth events. Though, no ages are listed explicitly in the bill.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Many argue that participation trophies aren&rsquo;t that big of a deal. After all, awarding trophies for merely showing up tends to fade out once kids progress past pee-wees and enter the junior high ranks. However, proponents of laws such as Moffitt&rsquo;s will point to things like the Colts&rsquo; 2014 AFC Finalist Banner:</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Clearly, the participation trophy culture has made its way past pee-wees. Is it worth passing a law? The North Carolina legislature will soon decide.</span></p>]]></description>
   <author><![CDATA[Garrison Hardie]]></author>
   <enclosure url="https://app.dropwave.io/episode/9b467d7b-d044-480d-8dcd-4c2a7dbc089e/daily-news-brief-for-thursday-april-13th-2023.mp3" length="1106" type="audio/mp3"/>
   <guid isPermaLink="false"><![CDATA[9b467d7b-d044-480d-8dcd-4c2a7dbc089e]]></guid>
   <pubDate>Thu, 13 Apr 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
   <source url=""><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></source>
   <itunes:author><![CDATA[Garrison Hardie]]></itunes:author>
   <itunes:image href="https://assets-cdn2.dropwave.io/2ab40ac0-e99d-4f25-a6d2-541d2c9b290a/cover-art/hUZu1H9lrRY0wXg66WHC8eLwYBA3hbRNTAHQmHt2.png"/>
   <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
   <itunes:duration>1106</itunes:duration>
   <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
  
  </item><item>
   <title><![CDATA[Daily News Brief for Wednesday, April 12th, 2023 [Daily News Brief]]]></title>
   <link>https://app.dropwave.io/episode/e50cd14b-6490-40cb-9525-3870a78ef6da/daily-news-brief-for-wednesday-april-12th-2023.mp3</link>
   <description><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">This is Garrison Hardie with your CrossPolitic Daily News Brief for Wednesday, April 12th, 2023.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://nypost.com/2023/04/11/truck-carrying-soil-from-east-palestine-overturns-on-highway/"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://nypost.com/2023/04/11/truck-carrying-soil-from-east-palestine-overturns-on-highway/</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>Truck carrying toxic soil from East Palestine train derailment overturns on highway</strong></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">A truck carrying about 40,000 pounds of toxic soil from East Palestine, Ohio, overturned on Monday, spilling roughly half its contents onto the highway before it even got out of the state.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The open-top tractor-trailer was traveling north on SR-165 in Columbiana County when the accident occurred, CBS News reported.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Driver Phillip Falck, 74, went off the right side of the road and hit a ditch and a utility pole before overturning, the outlet said.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Officers who responded found the truck &ldquo;on its side,&rsquo;&rdquo; per the Ohio State Highway Patrol.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The local fire department and the Ohio Environmental Protection Agency also responded.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">It was decided that the 20,000 pounds of spilled soil was contained and did not threaten any waterways.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Falck sustained minor injuries and was cited for operating a vehicle without reasonable control, WFMJ reported.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The soil onboard was being transported away from East Palestine, where a Norfolk Southern train derailed on Feb. 3, releasing multiple hazardous substances into the surrounding area.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Residents were evacuated, and thousands of fish reportedly died from exposure to the toxins.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">More than two months later, the process of removing contaminated soil and water from the site remains ongoing.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">On Monday, state officials said approximately 11.4 million gallons of wastewater had been hauled out of the area, in addition to 19,900 tons of soil.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">A new health clinic, the East Liverpool City Hospital East Palestine Clinic, also opened in the area on Monday.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">It will replace the temporary assessment clinic that opened in the wake of the derailment.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://www.foxnews.com/politics/manhattan-da-alvin-bragg-sues-rep-jim-jordan-trump-indictment-subpoena"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.foxnews.com/politics/manhattan-da-alvin-bragg-sues-rep-jim-jordan-trump-indictment-subpoena</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>Manhattan DA Alvin Bragg sues Rep. Jim Jordan over Trump indictment subpoenas</strong></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Manhattan District Attorney Alvin Bragg on Tuesday filed a federal lawsuit against Rep. Jim Jordan, alleging that the Republican lawmaker is trying to wage a campaign of intimidation over his prosecution of former President Donald Trump.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">In his lawsuit, the Democratic D.A. said he's taking legal action "in response to an unprecedently brazen and unconstitutional attack by members of Congress on an ongoing New York State criminal prosecution and investigation of former President Donald J. Trump."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Bragg is asking a judge to invalidate subpoenas that Jordan, the chair of the House Judiciary Committee, has or plans to issue as part of an investigation of Bragg's handling of the Trump case.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">"The Manhattan D.A.'s Office focuses on the law and the evidence, not political gamesmanship or threats. We look forward to presenting our case in court to enjoin enforcement of the subpoena."&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The case is assigned to U.S. District Mary Kay Vyskocil, a Trump appointee who previously served as a federal bankruptcy court judge.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">In recent weeks, the Judiciary Committee issued a subpoena seeking testimony from a former prosecutor, Mark Pomerantz, who previously oversaw the Trump investigation. The committee has also sought documents and testimony about the case from Bragg and his office. Bragg has rejected those requests.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Trump was indicted late last month on 34 felony counts of falsifying business records related to hush-money payments made during the 2016 presidential campaign to bury allegations that he had extramarital sexual encounters. The 2024 presidential contender has denied wrongdoing and pleaded not guilty at an arraignment in Manhattan last week.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The House Judiciary Committee is scheduled to hold a hearing in Manhattan on Monday on crime in New York City and what it alleges are Bragg's "pro-crime, anti-victim" policies. The D.A.'s office, however, points to statistics showing that violent crime in Manhattan has dropped since Bragg took office in January 2022.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://justthenews.com/government/state-houses/newsom-stockpiles-2-million-abortion-pills-so-californians-can-access-them"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://justthenews.com/government/state-houses/newsom-stockpiles-2-million-abortion-pills-so-californians-can-access-them</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>Newsom stockpiles 2 million abortion pills so Californians can access them after judge's ruling</strong></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">California Democrat Gov. Gavin Newsom is stockpiling as much as 2 million misoprostol pills used to terminate a pregnancy &ndash; after a federal judge's ruling last week sought to halt the FDA's approval of another abortifacient, mifepristone.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">"We will not cave to extremists who are trying to outlaw these critical abortion services," Newsom said Monday in announcing his plan. "Medication abortion remains legal in California."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Mifepristone is used in conjunction with misoprostol to terminate a pregnancy through 10 weeks of gestation, according to the FDA. Misoprostol still can effectively terminate a pregnancy when used alone, according to a National Institutes of Health study but the Food and Drug Administration has not approved it for abortions.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The Biden administration is appealing the ruling from the Texas-based federal judge that brought mifepristone's status into question. The case is expected to be heard by the Supreme Court.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://bongino.com/15-days-to-slow-the-spread-ends-after-1120-days"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://bongino.com/15-days-to-slow-the-spread-ends-after-1120-days</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>"15 Days to Slow the Spread" Ends After 1,120 Days</strong></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://dailycaller.com/2023/04/11/governor-shut-down-church-pay-fee-kentucky-andrew-beshear/"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://dailycaller.com/2023/04/11/governor-shut-down-church-pay-fee-kentucky-andrew-beshear/</span></a></span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">On Monday, Joe Biden signed a GOP-led resolution that brought the national emergency over the COVID-19 pandemic to an end.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">And just like that, &ldquo;15 days to slow the spread&rdquo; was over&hellip;.. after 1120 days.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">As the New York Post reported:</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Biden signed the legislation behind closed doors on the eve of his trip Tuesday to Northern Ireland and the White House acknowledged the milestone without fanfare in a brief late-afternoon email that read: &ldquo;On Monday, April 10, 2023, the President signed into law: H.J.Res. 7, which terminates the national emergency related to the COVID-19 pandemic.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The legislation drafted by Rep. Paul Gosar (R-Ariz.) passed the House 229-197 in February, with a handful of Democratic supporters, and then the Senate 68-23 last month with about half of the chamber&rsquo;s Democrats voting in favor.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">In January, the White House said that Biden would end both the national emergency and a separate public health emergency on May 11 after more than 1 million Americans died from the respiratory disease that originated in Wuhan, China.</span></p>
<p><br /><br /></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">If the national emergency and the powers it afforded the government prevented even a single person from contracting COVID, the evidence has yet to be seen.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Matt Palumbo is the author of Fact-Checking the Fact-Checkers: How the Left Hijacked and Weaponized the Fact-Checking Industry and The Man Behind the Curtain: Inside the Secret Network of George Soros</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://dailycaller.com/2023/04/11/governor-shut-down-church-pay-fee-kentucky-andrew-beshear/"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://dailycaller.com/2023/04/11/governor-shut-down-church-pay-fee-kentucky-andrew-beshear/</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;">&nbsp;</span></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>Dem Governor Who Shut Down Churches During COVID Ordered To Pay Over $270,000 In Attorney&rsquo;s Fees</strong></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">A federal appeals court ruled Monday that three individuals who sued the Kentucky governor for their right to assemble for worship during COVID-19 must be paid over $270,000 in attorney&rsquo;s fees.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Randall Daniel, Theodore Roberts, and Sally O&rsquo;Boyle sued in August 2020 after they received notices logging their attendance at Maryville Baptist Church&rsquo;s Easter Service and informing them they must quarantine or face &ldquo;further enforcement measures.&rdquo; The group alleged Democratic Governor Andrew Beshear&rsquo;s bans on religious gatherings and interstate travel violated their constitutional rights, which the Sixth Circuit affirmed in May 2020, according to court documents.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">On Monday, the Sixth Circuit upheld a district court ruling awarding the congregants $272,142.50 in attorney&rsquo;s fees, rejecting the governor&rsquo;s challenges.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">&ldquo;I know a lot of people who are outraged that the TAXPAYER is on the hook for ANDY&rsquo;S constitutional violation,&rdquo; said Roberts in a tweet. &ldquo;I share this outrage, but this outrage must be aimed at Beshear. If the people of Kentucky want to quit being taxed to pay for these court judgments, Kentucky MUST elect a governor who will actually follow the constitution.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Republican Kentucky Rep. Thomas Massie responded to the ruling on Monday, congratulating attorney Chris Wiest and TJ Roberts on the win.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The Sixth Circuit previously barred the governor from enforcing a prohibition on in-person services, disputing the lower court&rsquo;s ruling which upheld the ban.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">&ldquo;[The] unexplained breadth of the ban on religious services, together with its haven for numerous secular exceptions, cannot co-exist with a society that places religious freedom in a place of honor in the Bill of Rights: the First Amendment,&rdquo; the court found in May 2020.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">&ldquo;Here in Kentucky, there are so many different ways to worship, and all but one church in this commonwealth are engaged in them,&rdquo; Beshear said after the initial lawsuit was filed, according to WDRB. &ldquo;You can do it virtually. You can do it in a drive-in service, and in many states they are not allowing those drive-in services like we are. So this work &mdash; this opportunity to worship, which is so important, is still there. We just ask people to choose one of the versions that doesn&rsquo;t spread the coronavirus, and I think that&rsquo;s what our faith calls us to do.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Beshear did not immediately respond to a request for comment.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>]]></description>
   <author><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></author>
   <enclosure url="https://app.dropwave.io/episode/e50cd14b-6490-40cb-9525-3870a78ef6da/daily-news-brief-for-wednesday-april-12th-2023.mp3" length="560" type="audio/mp3"/>
   <guid isPermaLink="false"><![CDATA[e50cd14b-6490-40cb-9525-3870a78ef6da]]></guid>
   <pubDate>Wed, 12 Apr 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
   <source url=""><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></source>
   <itunes:author><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></itunes:author>
   <itunes:image href="https://assets-cdn2.dropwave.io/2ab40ac0-e99d-4f25-a6d2-541d2c9b290a/cover-art/hUZu1H9lrRY0wXg66WHC8eLwYBA3hbRNTAHQmHt2.png"/>
   <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
   <itunes:duration>560</itunes:duration>
   <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
  
  </item><item>
   <title><![CDATA[Daily News Brief for Tuesday, April 11th, 2023 [Daily News Brief]]]></title>
   <link>https://app.dropwave.io/episode/c1135bad-139f-4e9c-82a3-d945fdfa9b7b/daily-news-brief-for-tuesday-april-11th-2023.mp3</link>
   <description><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">This is Garrison Hardie with your CrossPolitic Daily News Brief for Tuesday, April 11th, 2023.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Let&rsquo;s get straight to the news.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2023/04/10/us/louisville-kentucky-shooting.html"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.nytimes.com/2023/04/10/us/louisville-kentucky-shooting.html</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>5 Dead and 8 Injured in Shooting in Louisville, Ky., Police Say</strong></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">At least five people were killed and eight others were injured in a shooting at a bank in downtown Louisville, Ky., on Monday morning, the police said. The suspected gunman died at the scene.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Paul Humphrey, the deputy chief of the Louisville Metro Police Department, said that the police received calls around 8:30 a.m. about a shooting at Old National Bank and when they arrived on the scene, &ldquo;they encountered the suspect almost immediately, still firing gunshots.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Chief Humphrey said that the gunman, whose name was not immediately released, was confirmed dead at the scene. &ldquo;We do not know exactly the circumstances of his death at this time,&rdquo; he said. It was not immediately clear if the gunman was included among the five dead.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The police did not give a motive for the shooting, but they said that the gunman had a connection to the bank and may have been a current or former employee. &ldquo;We believe this is a lone gunman involved in this that did have a connection to the bank,&rdquo; Chief Humphrey said at a news conference.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Five people were killed inside the bank, the deputy chief said, and at least eight people, including a police officer, were taken to a nearby hospital. He said that two people were in critical condition, including a police officer who was in surgery on Monday morning.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">&ldquo;There is no active danger known to the public at this time,&rdquo; Chief Humphrey said.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The bank is across the street from Louisville Slugger Field, a minor-league baseball stadium where the Louisville Bats play. The area includes many hotels and apartment complexes.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The University of Louisville Hospital received nine patients, including two police officers, from the shooting, a spokeswoman, Heather Fountaine, said in an email. She said at least three of the patients had been discharged by early Monday afternoon.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Kentucky Gov. Andy Beshear spoke on the tragedy.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=m4I2Wltw0BI"><span style="font-weight: 400;" data-rich-links="{&quot;fple-t&quot;:&quot;Kentucky Gov. Beshear: 'I have a very close friend who didn't make it today'&quot;,&quot;fple-u&quot;:&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=m4I2Wltw0BI&quot;,&quot;fple-mt&quot;:null,&quot;type&quot;:&quot;first-party-link&quot;}">Kentucky Gov. Beshear: 'I have a very close friend who didn't make it today'</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;">- Play Video&nbsp;</span></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The Police Department was still investigating the shooting at the bank when one man was fatally shot and another person was injured in a shooting later on Monday morning outside Jefferson Community and Technical College, less than two miles from the bank. It was not immediately clear what led to that shooting, but the police said that the two shootings were not connected.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The college&rsquo;s technical campus was still on lockdown midday Monday, and the school closed all of its campuses and canceled classes &ldquo;out of reverence for those involved in shootings that have occurred today,&rdquo; it said.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://www.foxnews.com/world/taiwan-warns-chinese-misstep-could-lead-uncontrollable-world-war-outbreak"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.foxnews.com/world/taiwan-warns-chinese-misstep-could-lead-uncontrollable-world-war-outbreak</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>Taiwan warns Chinese misstep could lead to 'uncontrollable' world war outbreak</strong></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Taiwan is sounding alarms over Chinese military drills that it says could mistakenly spark an "uncontrollable war" that would draw in countries from around the world.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">"The Chinese military exercises this couple of days have been very serious," Taiwanese Foreign Minister Joseph Wu told Fox News Sunday. "If you look at the sorties of the Chinese air force, together with the ships, they're coming very close to Taiwan. And any accident might spark an uncontrollable war in between Taiwan and China. And if other countries are trying to intervene, it might be the start of a war of great scale."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The comments come as large scale Chinese military drills entered their third day Monday, with the Chinese military declaring that it is "ready to fight" if Taiwan were to attempt to declare its independence from the mainland.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">"The theater&rsquo;s troops are ready to fight at all times and can fight at any time to resolutely smash any form of &lsquo;Taiwan independence&rsquo; and foreign interference attempts," the military said Monday, according to The Associated Press.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The drills China has run played out similarly to those the country conducted in August after Taiwan received a visit from then-House Speaker Nancy Pelosi, D-Calif., this time coming on the heels of a meeting between Taiwanese officials and House Speaker Kevin McCarthy, R-Calif.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Like the previous incident in August, multiple warships and planes have reportedly crossed the median line of the Taiwan Strait, which for decades was understood by both sides as a boundary that military forces should not cross for fear of escalating to war. But China has disregarded the boundary in more recent military drills, insisting the line is "imaginary" in nature.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Wu warned that the recent drills have shown that the Chinese threat to the independently governed island have continued to increase, arguing that it will be crucial for the U.S. to continue to show support for Taiwan as a way to deter aggression from the mainland.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://www.theblaze.com/news/social-media-federal-agency-hiring"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.theblaze.com/news/social-media-federal-agency-hiring</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>Social media and big tech companies have hired hundreds from federal agencies, including CIA and FBI</strong></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Tech companies such as Google, Meta, TikTok, and Twitter hired nearly 250 employees from federal law enforcement agencies such as the Federal Bureau of Investigation, the Department of Justice, and the CIA, according to an investigation by the Daily Caller.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Silicon Valley and tech companies have recruited 248 employees from the Central Intelligence Agency, Department of Homeland Security, DOJ, and FBI, according to the report. Several of the employees fill top roles at the companies after having held positions in government agencies for more than two decades in many cases.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Much of the hiring came between 2017 and 2022. Google alone hired 130 former CIA, DHS, DOJ, and FBI employees. Meta hired 47. Even Chinese-owned TikTok has employed 25 former CIA, DHS, DOJ, or FBI employees.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The report states that Twitter directly recruited several employees of the FBI who had worked for the agency for over 20 years.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">An &ldquo;embedded security manager" worked for Twitter for 10 months after working 22 years in the FBI, but he now works for Chevron. A &ldquo;senior security manager" for Twitter also had a 22-year career with the FBI.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Twitter's director of information security for the insider threat program was an FBI employee of 23 years. Additionally, the tech company's corporate security manager and crisis manager had 25 and 23 years respectively of experience at the federal agency.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Other job titles at Twitter with FBI backgrounds include &ldquo;senior director,&rdquo; &ldquo;security specialist,&rdquo; &ldquo;director of corporate security/ risk,&rdquo; and &ldquo;director of corporate resilience.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Google, Meta, TikTok, and the former FBI employees mentioned in the report either did not respond to inquiries from the Daily Caller or declined to comment. Twitter reportedly responded with a poo emoji, which is standard practice for the company.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Twitter CEO Elon Musk is fighting battles on many fronts recently, with varying degrees of success.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Musk is battling media credibility claims after labeling National Public Radio as "state-affiliated media," before eventually adjusting the label to "government funded media," the same annotation given to outlet BBC.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">At the same time, Musk temporarily changed the Twitter logo on the website to the "doge," a widely used cartoon image of the dog breed Shiba Inu.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">As well, in late March 2023, Musk and 1,000 others from the tech industry urged a pause in the development of artificial intelligence due to "profound risks to society and humanity."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Speaking of social media &amp; marketing&hellip;&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://dailycaller.com/2023/04/10/viral-video-shows-bud-light-exec-trashing-brands-fratty-and-out-of-touch-marketing/"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://dailycaller.com/2023/04/10/viral-video-shows-bud-light-exec-trashing-brands-fratty-and-out-of-touch-marketing/</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>Viral Video Shows Bud Light Exec Trashing Brand&rsquo;s &lsquo;Fratty And Out-Of-Touch&rsquo; Marketing</strong></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Recently resurfaced video shows Alissa Heinerscheid, the vice president of marketing at Bud Light, trashing the beer company&rsquo;s customer base.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The video made the rounds after Bud Light partnered with Dylan Mulvaney, sending the transgender TikTok star a beer can with his face on it. Another Bud Light can features a rainbow and the phrase &ldquo;celebrate everyone&rsquo;s identity,&rdquo; with various pronouns printed on the can.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Dylan has posted several videos on social media advertising the beer. The advertising campaign sparked massive backlash from the Bud Light&rsquo;s customers.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://twitter.com/i/status/1645089521980280832"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://twitter.com/i/status/1645089521980280832</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> - Play Video&nbsp;</span></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Thanks Bud Light&hellip; nothing makes me feel more seen than seeing a man pretending to be a woman on your beer cans.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The video has been shared by several popular Twitter accounts, and has amassed million of views.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Bud Light parent company Anheuser-Busch defended the partnership in a statement issued on April 3.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">&ldquo;Anheuser-Busch works with hundreds of influencers across our brands as one of many ways to authentically connect with audiences across various demographics and passion points,&rdquo; the spokesperson said. &ldquo;From time to time, we produce unique commemorative cans for fans and for brand influencers, like Dylan Mulvaney. This commemorative can was a gift to celebrate a personal milestone and is not for sale to the general public.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>Dime Payments</strong></span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Dime Payments is a Christian owned processing payment business. Every business needs a payment process system, so please go to https://dimepayments.com/flf and sign your business up. Working with them supports us. They wont cancel you, like Stripe canceled President Trump. They wont cancel you, like Mailchimp canceled the Babylon Bee. Check them out. At least have a phone call and tell them that CrossPolitic sent you. Go to https://dimepayments.com/flf.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Now, let&rsquo;s bring this home for a landing&hellip; it&rsquo;s time for my favorite topic, sports!</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Over this Easter weekend, my friends and I hosted a fight night. It was UFC 287, which featured numerous fights.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Christian Rodriguez defeated the previously undefeated (and 18 year old) Raul Rosas Jr. by unanimous decision. But hey,&nbsp;</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Kevin Holland defeated Santiago Ponzinibbio by TKO</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Rob Font defeated Adrian Yanez by TKO</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Gilbert Burns took down the legend Jorge Masvidal by unanimous decision. Masvidal appeared to have retired after the fight as well, after 20 years of fighting.&nbsp;</span></li>
</ul>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">And then&hellip; this happend&hellip; </span><strong>PLAY AUDIO CLIP HERE</strong></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">That&rsquo;s right&hellip; the main event featured Alex Pereira, and Israel Adesanya, and Adesanya defeated his boogie man by KO&hellip; the background story is Pereira defeated Adesanya in their three previous fights, and Adesanya FINALLY came back and got him over the weekend in his fourth attempt&hellip; and for awhile, it looked like Pereira was going to win again, until Adesanya flipped the script, and walked away with the win.&nbsp;</span></p>]]></description>
   <author><![CDATA[Garrison Hardie]]></author>
   <enclosure url="https://app.dropwave.io/episode/c1135bad-139f-4e9c-82a3-d945fdfa9b7b/daily-news-brief-for-tuesday-april-11th-2023.mp3" length="927" type="audio/mp3"/>
   <guid isPermaLink="false"><![CDATA[c1135bad-139f-4e9c-82a3-d945fdfa9b7b]]></guid>
   <pubDate>Tue, 11 Apr 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
   <source url=""><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></source>
   <itunes:author><![CDATA[Garrison Hardie]]></itunes:author>
   <itunes:image href="https://assets-cdn2.dropwave.io/2ab40ac0-e99d-4f25-a6d2-541d2c9b290a/cover-art/hUZu1H9lrRY0wXg66WHC8eLwYBA3hbRNTAHQmHt2.png"/>
   <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
   <itunes:duration>927</itunes:duration>
   <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
  
  </item><item>
   <title><![CDATA[Daily News Brief for Friday, April 7th, 2023 [Daily News Brief]]]></title>
   <link>https://app.dropwave.io/episode/9ea58ecc-cff0-42ec-81f2-b22765cccc15/daily-news-brief-for-friday-april-7th-2023.mp3</link>
   <description><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">This is Garrison Hardie with your CrossPolitic Daily News Brief for Friday, April 7th, 2023.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Gravity Jack:</strong></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Gravity Jack is a full service digital agency specializing in the development of Virtual &amp; Augmented Reality experiences, mobile apps, blockchain and Web3 projects. Founded in 2009 as the first American agency to offer augmented reality, they even patented it; Gravity Jack's digital experiences have been a source of innovation for small business, Fortune 500 Companies, and the US Military. Get your vision in motion at </span><a href="http://www.gravityjack.com"><span style="font-weight: 400;">gravityjack.com</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://thepostmillennial.com/breaking-white-house-says-there-should-be-no-age-limit-on-child-sex-changes-up-to-child-parents-to-decide?utm_campaign=64487"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://thepostmillennial.com/breaking-white-house-says-there-should-be-no-age-limit-on-child-sex-changes-up-to-child-parents-to-decide?utm_campaign=64487</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>White House says there should be no age limit on child sex changes&mdash;up to child, parents to decide</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">During a White House press conference on Wednesday, Press Secretary Karine Jean-Pierre was questioned on what age Biden thinks medicalized gender transitions are appropriate for minors, to which she said that it was up to the "child and their parents to decide."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://rumble.com/v2gf8r6-a-reporter-asks-the-wh-press-sec-if-biden-has-a-position-on-at-what-age.html"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://rumble.com/v2gf8r6-a-reporter-asks-the-wh-press-sec-if-biden-has-a-position-on-at-what-age.html</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> - Play Video&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Following the fatal shooting at a Nashville Christian school carried out by Audrey Hale last month, who identified as transgender, Jean-Pierre proclaimed that the transgender community was "under attack" by so-called "anti-trans bills" across the nation.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://freebeacon.com/democrats/colorado-poised-to-become-haven-for-youth-gender-reassignment-surgeries/"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://freebeacon.com/democrats/colorado-poised-to-become-haven-for-youth-gender-reassignment-surgeries/</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Colorado Poised to Become Haven for Youth Gender Reassignment Surgeries</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Colorado Democrats over the weekend advanced a bill cosponsored by a transgender representative that would make their state a safe haven for teenagers seeking sex changes.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The Colorado House of Representatives on Saturday passed SB 188, which would require the state&rsquo;s courts and medical licensing boards to protect doctors who dispense hormones and perform sex changes on teens from states that restrict these surgeries, as well as those who provide abortions. The bill, which was cosponsored by Rep. Brianna Titone (D.), who identifies as transgender, was approved alongside two pieces of legislation that would expand abortion access in the state, all three of which have already passed the state senate.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Colorado is the latest blue state whose legislators have moved to enshrine protections to controversial medical procedures. Oregon Democrats last month passed a package designed to make their state a "haven" for people seeking sex changes and abortions, and Minnesota has passed similar legislation. California lawmakers have advanced a number of similar bills, including one bill that would allow children to check into group homes if their parents do not support their "gender identity."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The bill, which passed on party lines, was advanced late Saturday after 29-hours of contentious debate. Before passing the measure, House lawmakers added an amendment stating that the state&rsquo;s definition of "reproductive health care" includes sex change procedures and sterilization. This would ensure the legislation applies for minors under 19, according to Colorado Catholic Conference executive director Brittany Vessely.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">During the floor debate, Titone scolded a Republican colleague who questioned the safety of child sex changes, saying he lacked "empathy" and claimed no one would choose to change genders voluntarily.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">An increasing number of children are saying they are transgender, Reuters reported. In 2021, some 42,000 children and teens were told by therapists that they have gender dysphoria&mdash;almost triple the number given this diagnosis in 2017.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The bill could still face a legal challenge. The state assembly&rsquo;s non-partisan counsel said last week that SB 188 violates a provision in Colorado&rsquo;s constitution barring bills from regulating more than one subject, Colorado Politics reports. Colorado&rsquo;s Office of Legislative Legal Services found that the bill improperly welds the terms "reproductive health care" and "gender-affirming health care" into one entity, when they are actually separate.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Democrats say this was a technical issue they resolved in the amendment process. But Republicans say the constitutional problems persist and that the error points to a much larger problem.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The bill is expected to be sent to Gov. Jared Polis&rsquo;s desk for approval, along with the two abortion bills that passed Saturday. Those bills would empower state officials to target crisis pregnancy centers for promoting alleged "misinformation" about abortion and force insurance plans to cover abortion without copays. The bills would also make Colorado the first state to ban abortion pill reversals.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://www.breitbart.com/politics/2023/04/06/exclusive-jim-jordan-subpoenas-manhattan-prosecutor-who-resigned-over-suspended-trump-probe/"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.breitbart.com/politics/2023/04/06/exclusive-jim-jordan-subpoenas-manhattan-prosecutor-who-resigned-over-suspended-trump-probe/</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Jim Jordan Subpoenas Manhattan Prosecutor Who Resigned over Suspended Trump Probe</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">House Judiciary Committee chairman Rep. Jim Jordan (R-OH) escalated Republicans&rsquo; investigation into the Manhattan district attorney&rsquo;s indictment of former President Donald Trump by subpoenaing a prosecutor on Thursday who resigned from the office last year over the district attorney&rsquo;s initial reluctance to pursue Trump&rsquo;s case.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Jordan&rsquo;s subpoena, reviewed by Breitbart News, directs Mark Pomerantz, who resigned from Manhattan District Attorney Alvin Bragg&rsquo;s office in February 2022, to appear before the committee for a deposition on April 20.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Pomerantz, a former special assistant assigned to the years-long Trump case, exited the Manhattan district attorney&rsquo;s office right after Bragg took over. The move became a public affair when his resignation letter appeared in the New York Times last March.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Pomerantz wrote in the letter to Bragg that he believed Trump was &ldquo;guilty of numerous felony violations&rdquo; related to his financial statements and that he was quitting because he thought Bragg&rsquo;s decision at the time to &ldquo;indefinitely&rdquo; suspend the investigation into Trump was &ldquo;misguided.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Jordan observed, based on the resignation letter, that Pomerantz had &ldquo;prejudged the results&rdquo; of the investigation and that his critical words of Bragg seemingly sparked the district attorney to openly declare that the Trump investigation was &ldquo;far from over.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">In November 2022, one week after Trump announced he was running for president again, the Times reported that Bragg had revived the Trump investigation and had zeroed in on a hush money scheme involving porn star Stormy Daniels and Trump&rsquo;s former personal attorney Michael Cohen.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&ldquo;For Mr. Bragg, the hush-money developments suggest the first signs of progress since he took office at the beginning of the year, when he balked at indicting Mr. Trump in connection with his business practices,&rdquo; the outlet reported at the time.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Pomerantz later went on to publish a book about the matter, called People vs. Donald Trump: An Inside Account, in which Pomerantz discussed internal concerns people had about the investigation and worries about the credibility of Cohen, a convicted felon.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">He added that Pomerantz &ldquo;frivolously&rdquo; compared Trump to John Gotti, a notorious New York City mob boss, and described him as a &ldquo;malignant narcissist.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&ldquo;The depth of your personal animosity towards him is apparent in your writing,&rdquo; Jordan concluded.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The subpoena marks Republicans&rsquo; strongest move yet in its investigation of the New York County&rsquo;s indictment of Trump amid questions from some about Congress&rsquo;s authority to probe open state-level criminal matters.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://americanmilitarynews.com/2023/04/us-kills-isis-leader-who-planned-international-terrorist-attacks/"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://americanmilitarynews.com/2023/04/us-kills-isis-leader-who-planned-international-terrorist-attacks/</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>US kills ISIS leader who planned international terrorist attacks</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">A senior ISIS leader responsible for planning international terrorist attacks was killed in a U.S. strike on Monday in Syria, dealing another blow to the remnants of the Islamic State.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">U.S. Central Command, which oversees Middle East operations, said in a statement that the killing of the commander, al-Jabouri, will &ldquo;temporarily disrupt [ISIS&rsquo;] ability to plot external attacks.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Describing the operation as a &ldquo;unilateral strike,&rdquo; CENTCOM stated that al-Jabouri was a planner for attacks in Europe and Turkey, and had developed the leadership structure for ISIS in Turkey. CENTCOM said the strike did not injure or kill any civilians.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The Syrian Observatory for Human Rights, a U.K.-based nonprofit that tracks conflict in Syria, reported that a drone strike killed the commander while he was walking and making a phone call near his house.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The strike came two weeks after U.S. forces in Syria traded deadly strikes with Iranian proxies, raising fears of escalation in the region. The Iran-backed strikes killed an American contractor and gave six U.S. troops traumatic brain injuries, CNN reported.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Retaliatory strikes by the U.S. killed eight militants and targeted facilities used by groups associated with the Islamic Revolutionary Guard Corps, Iran&rsquo;s internal militia and its main force for operations beyond its borders.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">CENTCOM has stated that the U.S. has about 900 troops deployed in Syria, as well as about 170 contractors, Stars and Stripes reported. U.S. forces are stationed in Syria &ldquo;to keep an ISIS resurgence at bay,&rdquo; a military spokesman told the Washington Post in December.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">CENTCOM Commander Gen. Michael Kurilla told a congressional committee in March that &ldquo;ISIS would return within one to two years&rdquo; if the U.S. pulled out of Syria, Stars and Stripes reported. The House of Representatives recently voted down an effort to force the withdrawal of about 900 troops from Syria.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2023/apr/06/clarence-thomas-supreme-courts-gifts-republican-megadonor"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2023/apr/06/clarence-thomas-supreme-courts-gifts-republican-megadonor</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Clarence Thomas faces impeachment calls after reports of undisclosed gifts</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Clarence Thomas, the most conservative justice on the US supreme court, is facing renewed calls for impeachment after it was reported that for two decades he has accepted undisclosed luxury gifts from a Republican mega-donor.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Thomas may have violated financial disclosure rules when he failed to disclose travel on yachts and jets and other gifts funded by the property billionaire Harlan Crow and uncovered by ProPublica.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">It found that Thomas flies on Crow&rsquo;s Bombardier Global 5000 jet and holidays on Crow&rsquo;s 162ft super-yacht. He has enjoyed holidays at Crow&rsquo;s ranch in Texas and joined him at an exclusive all-male California retreat. The justice usually spends about a week each summer at Crow&rsquo;s private resort in the Adirondack mountains in New York.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The revelations prompted sharp criticism by Democrats of Thomas, who after 31 years is the longest-serving justice and an influential voice in the rightwing majority that last year ended the right to abortion.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Dick Durbin, a Democrat from Illinois and chair of the Senate judiciary committee, said: &ldquo;This behavior is simply inconsistent with the ethical standards the American people expect of any public servant, let alone a justice on the supreme court.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&ldquo;Today&rsquo;s report demonstrates, yet again, that supreme court justices must be held to an enforceable code of conduct, just like every other federal judge. The ProPublica report is a call to action, and the Senate judiciary committee will act.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Alexandria Ocasio-Cortez, a progressive congresswoman from New York, tweeted: &ldquo;This is beyond party or partisanship. This degree of corruption is shocking &ndash; almost cartoonish. Thomas must be impeached. Barring some dramatic change, this is what the [chief justice John] Roberts court will be known for: rank corruption, erosion of democracy, and the stripping of human rights.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Impeachment remains unlikely, even given other calls regarding the pro-Trump activities of Thomas&rsquo;s wife, the rightwing activist Ginni Thomas, and not just because Republicans hold the House. Only one supreme court justice has ever been impeached: Samuel Chase, in 1804-05. He was acquitted in the Senate.</span></p>]]></description>
   <author><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></author>
   <enclosure url="https://app.dropwave.io/episode/9ea58ecc-cff0-42ec-81f2-b22765cccc15/daily-news-brief-for-friday-april-7th-2023.mp3" length="800" type="audio/mp3"/>
   <guid isPermaLink="false"><![CDATA[9ea58ecc-cff0-42ec-81f2-b22765cccc15]]></guid>
   <pubDate>Fri, 07 Apr 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
   <source url=""><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></source>
   <itunes:author><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></itunes:author>
   <itunes:image href="https://assets-cdn2.dropwave.io/2ab40ac0-e99d-4f25-a6d2-541d2c9b290a/cover-art/hUZu1H9lrRY0wXg66WHC8eLwYBA3hbRNTAHQmHt2.png"/>
   <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
   <itunes:duration>800</itunes:duration>
   <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
  
  </item><item>
   <title><![CDATA[Daily News Brief for Thursday, April 6th, 2023 [Daily News Brief]]]></title>
   <link>https://app.dropwave.io/episode/95a82f4f-a7ec-4fb8-9fb0-03520de903ba/daily-news-brief-for-thursday-april-6th-2023.mp3</link>
   <description><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">This is Garrison Hardie with your CrossPolitic Daily News Brief for Thursday, April 6th, 2023.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Hi Contrast Hymn Books</strong></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">If you don&rsquo;t teach your kids the Lord&rsquo;s songs, the world will teach them its songs.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The brand-new Hi-Contrast Hymn Book is designed to help you teach your children the most beloved songs of the Christian faith.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Its captivating illustrations will create special moments of truth, goodness, and beauty in your home every day.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">To get a copy for your family, go to</span><a href="http://www.hicontrasthymnbooks.com/FLF"><span style="font-weight: 400;"> </span><span style="font-weight: 400;">www.hicontrasthymnbooks.com/FLF</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;">.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">That&rsquo;s www. &ldquo;H&rdquo; &ldquo;I&rdquo;</span><a href="http://contrasthymnbooks.com/FLF"><span style="font-weight: 400;"> </span><span style="font-weight: 400;">contrasthymnbooks.com/FLF</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;">.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://thepostmillennial.com/breaking-nashville-police-find-trans-school-shooters-suicide-note-refuse-to-release-details?utm_campaign=64487"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://thepostmillennial.com/breaking-nashville-police-find-trans-school-shooters-suicide-note-refuse-to-release-details?utm_campaign=64487</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Nashville police find trans school shooter's suicide note&mdash;refuse to release details</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The Metropolitan Nashville Police Department reportedly found a suicide note left by trans-identifying school shooter Audrey Hale during their search of the now deceased assailant's home.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">While authorities have confirmed that the note exists, its contents have not disclosed what it contains.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">According to NBC News, on Tuesday authorities released a list of items discovered at the home following the shooting. Among them were several journals, a shotgun, cellphones, laptops, and a suicide note. Old photos and yearbooks from The Covenant School, where Hale was a former student, were also recovered.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The MNPD declined to provide further details regarding the contents of the note, a document which many have suggested could shine some light on the potential motive behind the mass shooting, which left six people dead.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Officers did reveal, however, that many of the othe documents they found included notes about firearms courses and school shootings of the past.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">On Monday, police revealed that Hale planned the attack "over a period of months," and that she fired 152 rounds from the time she shot her way into the school until being killed by police.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">"The writings remain under careful review by the MNPD and the FBI's Behavioral Analysis Unit based in Quantico, Virginia. The motive for Hale&rsquo;s actions has not been established and remains under investigation by the Homicide Unit in consultation with the FBI&rsquo;s Behavioral Analysis Unit," MNPD wrote.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Hale's manifesto has also been recovered, and its contents will reportedly be released to the public as soon as the FBI has analyzed it.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://www.theepochtimes.com/another-biden-administration-covid-19-vaccine-mandate-struck-down-by-court_5172256.html?utm_source=partner&amp;utm_campaign=BonginoReport&amp;src_src=partner&amp;src_cmp=BonginoReport"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.theepochtimes.com/another-biden-administration-covid-19-vaccine-mandate-struck-down-by-court_5172256.html?utm_source=partner&amp;utm_campaign=BonginoReport&amp;src_src=partner&amp;src_cmp=BonginoReport</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Another Biden Administration COVID-19 Vaccine Mandate Struck Down by Court</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">President Joe Biden&rsquo;s administration did not have the authority to impose a COVID-19 vaccine mandate on workers and volunteers in a federal childcare program, a U.S. judge has ruled.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The Department of Health and Human Services (HHS) forced Head Start workers, and some volunteers, to get a COVID-19 vaccine starting in early 2022. Head Start provides childcare to children from low-income families.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">HHS cited the Head Start Act, which says the health secretary can add &ldquo;administrative and financial management standards,&rdquo; &ldquo;standards relating to the condition and location of facilities (including indoor air quality assessment standards, where appropriate),&rdquo; and &ldquo;such other standards as the secretary finds to be appropriate.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Texas Attorney General Ken Paxton argued that the mandate was outside of the power granted by the act. The law &ldquo;does not mention vaccinations,&rdquo; he and other plaintiffs said in a brief.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">U.S. District Judge James Wesley Hendrix agreed.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&ldquo;The wisdom of Head Start&rsquo;s rule is not before the Court&mdash;only its legality. If the people, through Congress, wish to impose a vaccine mandate on Head Start programs, they may do so by passing a law. But an agency can do only what Congress authorizes it to do,&rdquo; Hendrix, a Trump appointee, said in his ruling.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&ldquo;Regardless of how well intentioned, HHS&rsquo;s attempt here to shoehorn the vaccine mandate into statutory language authorizing modification of Head Start&rsquo;s administrative, financial, and facility-management standards goes too far. Equally fatal to the rule is the agency&rsquo;s decision to implement it without the necessary public notice and comment, consultation with stakeholders, and reasonable explanation,&rdquo; he added.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The ruling strikes down the mandate, which Biden&rsquo;s administration had refused to rescind. The mandate had already been struck down in 24 states, per a 2022 ruling by a different judge.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">HHS and the U.S. Department of Justice did not respond to requests for comment.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&ldquo;I&rsquo;m proud to announce that the Biden Administration&rsquo;s attempt to use the Head Start program to mask toddlers and force the vaccine on staff and volunteers has now been permanently defeated,&rdquo; Texas Attorney General Ken Paxton, a Republican and one of the plaintiffs, said in an emailed statement to The Epoch Times.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">In court filings, defendants had urged the judge not to block the mandate.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The COVID-19 vaccines do not prevent transmission or infection, according to data from the U.S. Centers for Disease Control and Prevention, though observational data have indicated they have a small effect on both that might turn negative over time.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The National Head Start Association, a nonprofit, welcomed the judge&rsquo;s ruling.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Head Start previously rescinded its mask mandate after months of lobbying from the nonprofit and others. It had mandated masks for children, workers, and volunteers.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://www.foxnews.com/politics/doj-reaches-ettlement-in-sutherland-springs-texas-shooting-civil-cases/"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.foxnews.com/politics/doj-reaches-ettlement-in-sutherland-springs-texas-shooting-civil-cases/</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>DOJ agrees to $144M settlement in Sutherland Springs shooting civil cases alleging background check negligence</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The Justice Department announced Wednesday it has reached a $144 million agreement in principle to settle civil cases stemming from a 2017 mass shooting at the First Baptist Church of Sutherland Springs, Texas, which left 26 dead.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Officials said the settlements will resolve claims from more than 75 plaintiffs, who alleged "the Air Force was negligent when it failed to transmit to the National Instant Criminal Background Check System information about the shooter that would have prevented him from purchasing guns from a federally licensed firearms dealer."&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The gunman in the November 2017 attack, Devin Patrick Kelly, served in the Air Force. He died of an apparent self-inflicted gunshot wound.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">"No words or amount of money can diminish the immense tragedy of the mass shooting in Sutherland Springs," said Associate Attorney General Vanita Gupta. "Today&rsquo;s announcement brings the litigation to a close, ending a painful chapter for the victims of this unthinkable crime."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The Justice Department said Wednesday that a "federal district court in Texas concluded that the United States was liable for damages caused by the shooting."&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">"The agreement in principle would settle all claims for a total of $144.5 million. The settlement agreement has been approved, subject to the plaintiffs&rsquo; securing the required court approvals," it added. "Under applicable law, a court must approve some aspects of the settlements."&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The Justice Department also said the "NICS plays a critical role in combatting gun violence, and the federal government is always striving to improve the functioning of that system."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Kelley had served nearly five years in the Air Force before being discharged in 2014 for bad conduct, after he was convicted of assaulting a former wife and stepson, cracking the child&rsquo;s skull. The Air Force has publicly acknowledged that the felony conviction for domestic violence, had it been put into the FBI database, could have prevented Kelley from buying guns from licensed firearms dealers, and also from possessing body armor.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">U.S. District Judge Xavier Rodriguez said in 2021 that had the government done its job and entered Kelley&rsquo;s history into the database, "it is more likely than not that Kelley would have been deterred from carrying out the Church shooting."&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Kelley was shot at by two churchgoers who later pursued him.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Officials said an autopsy determined Kelley was shot by Willeford twice.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Now this!!!</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://thenationalpulse.com/2023/04/03/city-council-considering-sale-of-biblical-roman-art-for-lack-of-diversity/"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://thenationalpulse.com/2023/04/03/city-council-considering-sale-of-biblical-roman-art-for-lack-of-diversity/</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>City Council Considering Sale of Biblical, Roman Art for &lsquo;Lack of Diversity&rsquo;</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Acouncil in the English city of Oxford has announced that it will consider selling some of its Biblical art that decorates the town hall in an effort to &ldquo;better reflect the gender and ethnic diversity of [the] city&rdquo;.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">On Monday, March 20th, a Liberal Democratic councillor, Katherine Miles, submitted a motion to the council to have the artworks either removed or sold. The two paintings she demands be removed or sold are the Rape of the Sabine Women and Salome and Head of John the Baptist. The former depicts Roman mythology, whereas the latter is a biblical tale.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Ms. Miles has been working on an initiative to increase the diversity and representation of the artwork in Oxford City Council since June 2021. She claims that the paintings depict &ldquo;animal cruelty and gender-based violence&rdquo;, as well as a lack of diversity. More specifically, she argues the artwork contains fox hunting, representations of death, and depictions of rape.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">In an interview with Oxford Mail, the newspaper that first reported the story, Ms. Miles reflected on the &ldquo;lack of diversity,&rdquo; stating, &ldquo;[with] only three portraits in the town hall of women, it is high time the council redresses the existing lack of diversity within the town hall portraits to better reflect the gender and ethnic diversity of our city.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Therefore, in her words, the collection has &ldquo;no practical value to the city&rdquo; nor a &ldquo;clear link to Oxford&rdquo;.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Another Liberal Democrat councillor, Lawrence Fouweather, announced his support of the motion. He argues that the artwork could be sold to assist local residents in financial difficulties. &ldquo;The Council,&rdquo; he argues, &ldquo;is running short of cash, and at the same time the cost of living crisis is thrusting many of our residents into tremendous hardship and poverty&hellip;this proposed one-off sale of select artworks from the city&rsquo;s collection would help alleviate the dire plight of some of our most deprived residents&rdquo;.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Ms. Miles, on the other hand, has stated that &ldquo;[s]elling any existing artwork not on display, and not becoming of a public institution, may be [sic] one way to fund the costs of any initiative to improve the decorations in the town hall&rdquo;.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">One critic, Peter Whittle of the New Culture Forum in London, criticized the move, stating, &ldquo;our culture continues to be dismantled by nobodies, morons and philistines&rdquo;.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">No verdict has been made on the sale. A spokesman for Oxford City Council has publicly stated that, as for now, &ldquo;there is no council position on this matter&rdquo;.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">According to the Telegraph, &ldquo;[d]iscussions about the diversity of public art in Oxford come after the city council created an &ldquo;Anti-Racism Charter&rdquo; in 2021, after pledging to tackle discrimination following Black Lives Matter protests the previous year.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://www.foxnews.com/us/cash-app-founder-bob-lee-fatally-stabbed-san-francisco-report"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.foxnews.com/us/cash-app-founder-bob-lee-fatally-stabbed-san-francisco-report</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Cash App founder Bob Lee fatally stabbed in San Francisco</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Tech executive Bob Lee, founder of Cash App and the former chief technology officer of Square, was stabbed to death in San Francisco, California, according to reports.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">A 43-year-old man was attacked Tuesday at around 2:35 a.m., San Francisco Police said in a statement. Officers arrived at the scene on the 300 block of Main Street in response to the stabbing.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The San Francisco medical examiner has not yet identified the victim, but Lee was later identified by his friends as the person stabbed, according to KPIX.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Lee was rushed to the hospital to receive treatment for his life-threatening wounds, but he later succumbed to his injuries.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">No arrests have been made in connection with the stabbing as of Wednesday morning. The incident remains under investigation.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Lee was the chief product officer of San Francisco-based cryptocurrency company MobileCoin.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">He previously worked at Google, where he led Android's core library team and launched "the world&rsquo;s most used operating system," his profile on MobileCoin&rsquo;s official website reads.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The tech mogul also founded the social network Present, and invested in and advised other companies, including Figma, Clubhouse, Beeper and Faire.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">During the coronavirus pandemic, Lee helped the World Health Organization with their mobile app and led development for an at-home testing company.</span></p>]]></description>
   <author><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></author>
   <enclosure url="https://app.dropwave.io/episode/95a82f4f-a7ec-4fb8-9fb0-03520de903ba/daily-news-brief-for-thursday-april-6th-2023.mp3" length="720" type="audio/mp3"/>
   <guid isPermaLink="false"><![CDATA[95a82f4f-a7ec-4fb8-9fb0-03520de903ba]]></guid>
   <pubDate>Thu, 06 Apr 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
   <source url=""><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></source>
   <itunes:author><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></itunes:author>
   <itunes:image href="https://assets-cdn2.dropwave.io/2ab40ac0-e99d-4f25-a6d2-541d2c9b290a/cover-art/hUZu1H9lrRY0wXg66WHC8eLwYBA3hbRNTAHQmHt2.png"/>
   <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
   <itunes:duration>720</itunes:duration>
   <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
  
  </item><item>
   <title><![CDATA[Daily News Brief for Wednesday, April 5th, 2023 [Daily News Brief]]]></title>
   <link>https://app.dropwave.io/episode/d60170fd-ee83-4792-a814-14a1016f85b9/daily-news-brief-for-wednesday-april-5th-2023.mp3</link>
   <description><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">This is Garrison Hardie with your CrossPolitic Daily News Brief for Wednesday, April 5th, 2023.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>Alps Precious Metals Group</strong></span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">THE PAST WEEK HAS BROUGHT SOME &ldquo;EXCITEMENT&rdquo; TO THE MARKETS.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">BANK RUNS.&nbsp; STOCK COLLAPSES.&nbsp; WHAT WAS THOUGHT TO BE STABLE SUDDENLY APPEARS UNSTABLE.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">AND YET, GOLD&rsquo;S PRICE *WENT UP* AS THE HEADLINES BECAME MORE OMINOUS.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">ALPS PRECIOUS METALS WAS ESTABLISHED BECAUSE WE BELIEVE THE BEST WAY TO PROTECT ONE&rsquo;S HARD-EARNED WEALTH FROM THE SERIOUS FINANCIAL PROBLEMS THAT ARE UPON US IS BY OWNING PHYSICAL GOLD AND SILVER.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">CALL JAMES HUNTER OF ALPS AT 251-377-2197, AND VISIT OUR WEBSITE AT WWW.ALPSPMG.COM TO DISCOVER HOW YOU CAN BUY PHYSICAL PRECIOUS METALS FOR YOUR INVESTMENT AND IRA PORTFOLIOS.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">OWN THE ASSET GOD SPECIFICALLY MENTIONED AS &ldquo;GOOD&rdquo; IN THE 2ND CHAPTER OF GENESIS, AND OBTAIN A PEACE OF MIND THAT CAN BE HAD WITH FEW OTHER INVESTMENTS.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">AGAIN, CALL JAMES HUNTER OF ALPS PRECIOUS METALS AT 251-377-2197, AND VISIT WWW.ALPSPMG.COM TO LEARN HOW TO OWN THE BEDROCK ASSET OF THE AGES.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://www.newsweek.com/donald-trump-could-sentenced-more-100-years-prison-1792487"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.newsweek.com/donald-trump-could-sentenced-more-100-years-prison-1792487</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>Donald Trump Could be Sentenced to More Than 100 Years in Prison</strong></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Donald Trump could be sentenced to more than 100 years in prison if found guilty of the over 30 charges of business fraud in the indictment from a Manhattan grand jury for which he'll be arraigned on Tuesday in New York, according to attorney Lisa Bloom.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">According to an exclusive report by Yahoo News correspondent Michael Isikoff on Monday, the former president will face 34 class E felonies for falsification of business records in the case which revolves around the $130,000 payment of hush money to adult film star Stormy Daniels by Trump's then-lawyer Michael Cohen ahead of the 2016 presidential election. Trump has consistently denied any wrongdoing and called the probe a political "witch hunt."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">"If this report is correct, Trump will be arraigned tomorrow on 34 FELONIES. Each carries a possible prison term of 4 years. Bragg would not bring this case without strong evidence," she wrote about the Manhattan District Attorney leading the grand jury investigation, Alvin Bragg.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">"Remember, this is the same DA's office that recently convicted the Trump Org for criminal fraud."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Bloom, who since 2015 has been a vocal critic of Trump and in 2016 represented pro-bono four women accusing him of sexual harassment or sexual assault, said she's convinced that the case against Trump is strong, going to the point of calling it "a prosecutor's dream" because there's a record of the former president giving conflicting versions of the story.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Based on these premises, Bloom expects the 34 felony charges to be about Trump's attempts to "cover up evidence of an underlying crime, in this case the campaign nondisclosures."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Most experts looking at the case against Trump expect the chance of Trump actually serving prison time if found guilty close to zero. The charges against him would also not disqualify him from running for the presidency in 2024.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">It's also uncertain whether Bragg would actually recommend Trump serve time in prison. The sentence will be eventually decided by the judge.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2023/04/04/jolts-february-2023-.html"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.cnbc.com/2023/04/04/jolts-february-2023-.html</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>Job openings tumbled below 10 million in February for the first time in nearly two years</strong></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Job openings fell below 10 million in February for the first time in nearly two years, in a sign that the Federal Reserve&rsquo;s efforts to slow the labor market may be having some impact.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Available positions totaled 9.93 million, a drop of 632,000 from January&rsquo;s downwardly revised number, the Labor Department reported Tuesday in its monthly Job Openings and Labor Turnover Survey. Wall Street had been looking for 10.4 million, according to FactSet.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">It was the first time vacancies fell below 10 million since May 2021.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The Fed has targeted the red-hot labor market in its quest to bring down inflation, which had been running at a 41-year high in the summer of 2022. The central bank has raised benchmark interest rates nine times since March 2022, but those moves had been appearing to have little impact on the jobs situation.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Prior to the February data, job openings had been outnumbering available workers by nearly 2 to 1. The latest figures bring that ratio down to less than 1.7 to 1.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Treasury yields fell following the release as the data could help dissuade the Fed from further rate hikes. Stocks moved lower.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">&ldquo;The labor market is starting to loosen as the number of job openings declined in most sectors. As the economy slows, firms will likely cut openings and workers will be less likely to quit in search of better hours and higher pay,&rdquo; said Jeffrey Roach, chief economist at LPL Financial. &ldquo;The Fed could consider pausing rate hikes at the next meeting but only if the upcoming employment report shows signs of material weakness and the March [consumer price index] report reveals lower inflation.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Though the numbers run a month behind, the Fed watches the JOLTS data closely for signs of labor slack.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Along with the decline in job openings, hires and separations also decreased slightly. Quits, a sign of labor confidence in the ability to switch jobs, rose by 146,000 to just over 4 million.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Professional and business services saw a slide of 278,000 job openings on the month, while trade, transportation and utilities decreased 210,000. Accommodation and food services, an important sector to gauge consumer demand, dropped 125,000.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">On the positive side, there were 129,000 new construction jobs available, though that was the only category that saw a noticeable bump.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The JOLTS release comes three days ahead of fresh nonfarm payroll numbers for March. The Friday Labor Department count is expected to show a gain of 238,000, with the unemployment rate holding steady at 3.6%.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://www.dailywire.com/news/wisconsin-voters-head-to-the-polls-to-decide-balance-of-state-supreme-court"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.dailywire.com/news/wisconsin-voters-head-to-the-polls-to-decide-balance-of-state-supreme-court</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>Wisconsin Voters Head To The Polls To Decide Balance Of State Supreme Court</strong></span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Voters in Wisconsin head to the polls on Tuesday to decide the balance of the state Supreme Court in one of the most expensive court races in history.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Neither candidate running for the open seat belongs to a political party. Conservative candidate and former Justice Dan Kelly, backed by most Republicans, is facing off against liberal candidate Judge Janet Protasiewicz (Pro-Tuh-Say-Witz), the preferred candidate of most Democrats, with the winner determining the ideological slant of the divided court and earning a 10-year term on the court.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Protasiewicz has reportedly been backed by donations from left-wing billionaire George Soros and Gov. J.B Pritzker (D-IL), while Kelly has received support from groups like Fair Courts America, a conservative judicial organization. Total spending has exceeded $40 million, an astronomical amount compared to previous years when total spending was only around $10 million.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Hollywood has even thrown its weight behind Protasiewicz, with director Steven Speilberg contributing to her campaign and actor Mark Ruffalo encouraging voters to &ldquo;change the future of Wisconsin by electing Janet Protasiewicz &amp; flipping the state supreme court.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Both candidates have suggested that the other is unfit to serve, with Kelly pointing to Protasiewicz&rsquo;s left-wing ties and claiming she has a soft-on-crime sentencing history, while Protasiewicz linked Kelly to attempts to challenge the 2020 presidential election in the Badger State.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">During a debate earlier this year, Protasiewicz claimed that she was &ldquo;running against probably one of the most extreme partisan characters in the history of the state.&rdquo;&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Though officially non-partisan, the candidates have nearly polar opposite views, with Protasiewicz openly championing her support for abortion and Kelly receiving the endorsements of key pro-life groups in the state. Protasiewicz had an ad featuring a woman celebrating an abortion because the child could have been born with disabilities.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The election could be a deciding factor in a case over Wisconsin&rsquo;s 1849 abortion ban, which became relevant after Roe v. Wade was overturned last summer.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The candidates could also play a key role in deciding the fate of other laws in the state, including election integrity measures, election maps, and gun laws. Last year, the state made a bombshell ruling, saying that Wisconsin voters could not turn their ballots into unmanned drop boxes and that voters would not be allowed to give them to others to drop off for them. This case, decided 4-3, would likely have been different with a different balance on the court.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Republicans currently control the state&rsquo;s general assembly, but Democrat Gov. Tony Evers won re-election in November, meaning lawmakers are limited in what laws they can get passed.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/restoring-america/fairness-justice/los-angeles-decarceration-release-inmates"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/restoring-america/fairness-justice/los-angeles-decarceration-release-inmates</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>Los Angeles floats 'decarceration' policy to release large number of inmates</strong></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The Los Angeles County Board of Supervisors is floating a "decarceration" policy that would drastically reduce the number of people in jails, releasing many current inmates.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The agenda item , added to Tuesday's meeting, is titled "Los Angeles County to Take Actionable Next Steps to Depopulate and Decarcerate the Los Angeles County Jails: Granting Local Authority, Advocating for Court and State Support, and Legislative Changes."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The proposal, to be discussed during the meeting, would "declare the State of mental health services and overcrowding in the Los Angeles County jails a humanitarian crisis, requiring the County to move with all deliberate speed on meaningful solutions; and prioritize decreasing the number of individuals entering the Los Angeles County Jails" through a number of measures.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">In order to "reaffirm the Board&rsquo;s commitment to depopulate and decarcerate," the proposal would require law enforcement to "cite and release individuals with aggregate bail amounts set at $50,000 or below" and "adopt a zero-bail schedule for individuals accused of low-level offenses, infractions, misdemeanors, and some felony offenses."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The push comes as crime, including violent crime, has risen in the past few years, particularly since the start of the COVID-19 pandemic . An analysis found that crime increased 11% in 2022, with 60 reported crimes per 1,000 residents, compared to 2021, which saw 54 crimes per 1,000 residents. In some areas, crime has skyrocketed; downtown experienced 372 crimes per 1,000 residents in 2022.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The vice president of the Los Angeles Association of Deputy District Attorneys, Eric Siddall, denounced the proposal, speaking with Fox News, arguing that it would make crime in the city even worse.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">"The Los Angeles County Board of Supervisors&rsquo; motion to gut parts of the criminal justice system without input from stakeholders is dangerous and recklessness," he told the outlet. "The authors sought no advice from those who know and understand public safety issues. They seek to lower the jail population without addressing the root causes of crime or protecting the public."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">He condemned the "catch-and-release" part of the proposal.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Now this!</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://www.theblaze.com/news/gone-with-the-wind-to-include-trigger-warning-intro-that-addresses-white-supremacy-in-latest-print"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.theblaze.com/news/gone-with-the-wind-to-include-trigger-warning-intro-that-addresses-white-supremacy-in-latest-print</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>'Gone with the Wind' to include trigger warning, intro that addresses 'white supremacy' in latest print</strong></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The publishers of the classic American novel "Gone with the Wind" will include a "harmful" trigger warning and an introduction that addresses "white supremacy," the Telegraph reported.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Pan Macmillan, a publishing house based in London, has decided to affix a trigger warning to Margaret Mitchell's 1936 novel. The book, which takes place in 1861, follows the story of Scarlett O'Hara, the daughter of a southern plantation owner, and her romance with Captain Rhett Butler during the Civil War.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The cautionary note at the front of the new edition of the book will warn readers that it contains "racist" themes that could be "hurtful or indeed harmful."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">"Gone with the Wind is a novel which includes problematic elements including the romanticisation of a shocking era in our history and the horrors of slavery," the trigger warning states. "The novel includes the representation of unacceptable practices, racist and stereotypical depictions and troubling themes, characterisation, language and imagery."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Pan Macmillan noted that the new edition of Mitchell's novel would remain original. New editions of works from Agatha Christie and Ian Fleming were recently altered to remove potentially offensive passages with racial references.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">"The text of this book remains true to the original in every way and is reflective of the language and period in which it was originally written," the cautionary note continued. "We want to alert readers that there may be hurtful or indeed harmful phrases and terminology that were prevalent at the time this novel was written and which are true to the context of the historical setting of this novel."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">"Pan Macmillan believes changing the text to reflect today&rsquo;s world would undermine the authenticity of the original, so has chosen to leave the text in its entirety."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Pan Macmillan added, "This does not, however, constitute an endorsement of the characterisation, content or language used."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The cautionary note affixed to the start of the novel was written by Philippa Gregory, the author of "The Other Boleyn Girl." According to the publisher, Gregory was chosen to pen the introduction because "we believed it was important that no author from a minority background should be asked to undertake the emotional labour of being responsible for educating the majority."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Gregory argued that Mitchell's novel "effectively promoted the racist planter view of the history of the South." She claimed it "defends racism" and "glamorizes and preaches white supremacy."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">According to Gregory, "It tells us, unequivocally, that African people are not of the same species as white people."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">"This is the lie that spoils the novel," Gregory adds.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">All I can say to the publisher is, Frankly my dear&hellip; I don&rsquo;t give a damn.&nbsp;</span></p>]]></description>
   <author><![CDATA[Garrison Hardie]]></author>
   <enclosure url="https://app.dropwave.io/episode/d60170fd-ee83-4792-a814-14a1016f85b9/daily-news-brief-for-wednesday-april-5th-2023.mp3" length="829" type="audio/mp3"/>
   <guid isPermaLink="false"><![CDATA[d60170fd-ee83-4792-a814-14a1016f85b9]]></guid>
   <pubDate>Wed, 05 Apr 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
   <source url=""><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></source>
   <itunes:author><![CDATA[Garrison Hardie]]></itunes:author>
   <itunes:image href="https://assets-cdn2.dropwave.io/2ab40ac0-e99d-4f25-a6d2-541d2c9b290a/cover-art/hUZu1H9lrRY0wXg66WHC8eLwYBA3hbRNTAHQmHt2.png"/>
   <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
   <itunes:duration>829</itunes:duration>
   <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
  
  </item>
 </channel>
</rss>
