<?xml version="1.0"?>
<?xml-stylesheet href="/storage/feed-stylesheet.xsl" type="text/xsl"?>

<rss xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
 <channel>
  <title>FLF - Daily News Brief</title>
  <link>https://dropwave.io</link>
  <description><![CDATA[FIGHT LAUGH FEAST PRESENTS SHOWS PROCLAIMING THE LORDSHIP OF CHRIST OVER ALL OF LIFE.
]]></description>
  <language>en</language>
  <managingEditor><![CDATA[fightlaughfeast@gmail.com (FLF, LLC)]]></managingEditor>
  <webMaster><![CDATA[support@dropwave.io (DropWave Support)]]></webMaster>
  <pubDate>Mon, 10 Apr 2023 19:25:46 +0000</pubDate>
  <lastBuildDate>Mon, 10 Apr 2023 19:25:46 +0000</lastBuildDate>
  <image>
   <url>https://is4-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Podcasts113/v4/58/56/52/5856525c-2973-cf29-3db9-21faa8595391/mza_1144696925612154085.png/1200x1200bb.jpg</url>
   <link>https://dropwave.io</link>
   <title><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></title>
  </image>
  <itunes:author><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></itunes:author>
  <itunes:image href="https://is4-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Podcasts113/v4/58/56/52/5856525c-2973-cf29-3db9-21faa8595391/mza_1144696925612154085.png/1200x1200bb.jpg"/>
  <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
  <itunes:owner>
   <itunes:name><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></itunes:name>
   <itunes:email>fightlaughfeast@gmail.com</itunes:email>
  </itunes:owner>
  <itunes:category text="News"/>
  <item>
   <title><![CDATA[Daily News Brief for Friday, April 7th, 2023 [Daily News Brief]]]></title>
   <link>https://app.dropwave.io/episode/9ea58ecc-cff0-42ec-81f2-b22765cccc15/daily-news-brief-for-friday-april-7th-2023.mp3</link>
   <description><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">This is Garrison Hardie with your CrossPolitic Daily News Brief for Friday, April 7th, 2023.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Gravity Jack:</strong></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Gravity Jack is a full service digital agency specializing in the development of Virtual &amp; Augmented Reality experiences, mobile apps, blockchain and Web3 projects. Founded in 2009 as the first American agency to offer augmented reality, they even patented it; Gravity Jack's digital experiences have been a source of innovation for small business, Fortune 500 Companies, and the US Military. Get your vision in motion at </span><a href="http://www.gravityjack.com"><span style="font-weight: 400;">gravityjack.com</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://thepostmillennial.com/breaking-white-house-says-there-should-be-no-age-limit-on-child-sex-changes-up-to-child-parents-to-decide?utm_campaign=64487"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://thepostmillennial.com/breaking-white-house-says-there-should-be-no-age-limit-on-child-sex-changes-up-to-child-parents-to-decide?utm_campaign=64487</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>White House says there should be no age limit on child sex changes&mdash;up to child, parents to decide</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">During a White House press conference on Wednesday, Press Secretary Karine Jean-Pierre was questioned on what age Biden thinks medicalized gender transitions are appropriate for minors, to which she said that it was up to the "child and their parents to decide."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://rumble.com/v2gf8r6-a-reporter-asks-the-wh-press-sec-if-biden-has-a-position-on-at-what-age.html"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://rumble.com/v2gf8r6-a-reporter-asks-the-wh-press-sec-if-biden-has-a-position-on-at-what-age.html</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> - Play Video&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Following the fatal shooting at a Nashville Christian school carried out by Audrey Hale last month, who identified as transgender, Jean-Pierre proclaimed that the transgender community was "under attack" by so-called "anti-trans bills" across the nation.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://freebeacon.com/democrats/colorado-poised-to-become-haven-for-youth-gender-reassignment-surgeries/"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://freebeacon.com/democrats/colorado-poised-to-become-haven-for-youth-gender-reassignment-surgeries/</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Colorado Poised to Become Haven for Youth Gender Reassignment Surgeries</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Colorado Democrats over the weekend advanced a bill cosponsored by a transgender representative that would make their state a safe haven for teenagers seeking sex changes.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The Colorado House of Representatives on Saturday passed SB 188, which would require the state&rsquo;s courts and medical licensing boards to protect doctors who dispense hormones and perform sex changes on teens from states that restrict these surgeries, as well as those who provide abortions. The bill, which was cosponsored by Rep. Brianna Titone (D.), who identifies as transgender, was approved alongside two pieces of legislation that would expand abortion access in the state, all three of which have already passed the state senate.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Colorado is the latest blue state whose legislators have moved to enshrine protections to controversial medical procedures. Oregon Democrats last month passed a package designed to make their state a "haven" for people seeking sex changes and abortions, and Minnesota has passed similar legislation. California lawmakers have advanced a number of similar bills, including one bill that would allow children to check into group homes if their parents do not support their "gender identity."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The bill, which passed on party lines, was advanced late Saturday after 29-hours of contentious debate. Before passing the measure, House lawmakers added an amendment stating that the state&rsquo;s definition of "reproductive health care" includes sex change procedures and sterilization. This would ensure the legislation applies for minors under 19, according to Colorado Catholic Conference executive director Brittany Vessely.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">During the floor debate, Titone scolded a Republican colleague who questioned the safety of child sex changes, saying he lacked "empathy" and claimed no one would choose to change genders voluntarily.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">An increasing number of children are saying they are transgender, Reuters reported. In 2021, some 42,000 children and teens were told by therapists that they have gender dysphoria&mdash;almost triple the number given this diagnosis in 2017.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The bill could still face a legal challenge. The state assembly&rsquo;s non-partisan counsel said last week that SB 188 violates a provision in Colorado&rsquo;s constitution barring bills from regulating more than one subject, Colorado Politics reports. Colorado&rsquo;s Office of Legislative Legal Services found that the bill improperly welds the terms "reproductive health care" and "gender-affirming health care" into one entity, when they are actually separate.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Democrats say this was a technical issue they resolved in the amendment process. But Republicans say the constitutional problems persist and that the error points to a much larger problem.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The bill is expected to be sent to Gov. Jared Polis&rsquo;s desk for approval, along with the two abortion bills that passed Saturday. Those bills would empower state officials to target crisis pregnancy centers for promoting alleged "misinformation" about abortion and force insurance plans to cover abortion without copays. The bills would also make Colorado the first state to ban abortion pill reversals.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://www.breitbart.com/politics/2023/04/06/exclusive-jim-jordan-subpoenas-manhattan-prosecutor-who-resigned-over-suspended-trump-probe/"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.breitbart.com/politics/2023/04/06/exclusive-jim-jordan-subpoenas-manhattan-prosecutor-who-resigned-over-suspended-trump-probe/</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Jim Jordan Subpoenas Manhattan Prosecutor Who Resigned over Suspended Trump Probe</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">House Judiciary Committee chairman Rep. Jim Jordan (R-OH) escalated Republicans&rsquo; investigation into the Manhattan district attorney&rsquo;s indictment of former President Donald Trump by subpoenaing a prosecutor on Thursday who resigned from the office last year over the district attorney&rsquo;s initial reluctance to pursue Trump&rsquo;s case.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Jordan&rsquo;s subpoena, reviewed by Breitbart News, directs Mark Pomerantz, who resigned from Manhattan District Attorney Alvin Bragg&rsquo;s office in February 2022, to appear before the committee for a deposition on April 20.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Pomerantz, a former special assistant assigned to the years-long Trump case, exited the Manhattan district attorney&rsquo;s office right after Bragg took over. The move became a public affair when his resignation letter appeared in the New York Times last March.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Pomerantz wrote in the letter to Bragg that he believed Trump was &ldquo;guilty of numerous felony violations&rdquo; related to his financial statements and that he was quitting because he thought Bragg&rsquo;s decision at the time to &ldquo;indefinitely&rdquo; suspend the investigation into Trump was &ldquo;misguided.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Jordan observed, based on the resignation letter, that Pomerantz had &ldquo;prejudged the results&rdquo; of the investigation and that his critical words of Bragg seemingly sparked the district attorney to openly declare that the Trump investigation was &ldquo;far from over.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">In November 2022, one week after Trump announced he was running for president again, the Times reported that Bragg had revived the Trump investigation and had zeroed in on a hush money scheme involving porn star Stormy Daniels and Trump&rsquo;s former personal attorney Michael Cohen.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&ldquo;For Mr. Bragg, the hush-money developments suggest the first signs of progress since he took office at the beginning of the year, when he balked at indicting Mr. Trump in connection with his business practices,&rdquo; the outlet reported at the time.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Pomerantz later went on to publish a book about the matter, called People vs. Donald Trump: An Inside Account, in which Pomerantz discussed internal concerns people had about the investigation and worries about the credibility of Cohen, a convicted felon.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">He added that Pomerantz &ldquo;frivolously&rdquo; compared Trump to John Gotti, a notorious New York City mob boss, and described him as a &ldquo;malignant narcissist.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&ldquo;The depth of your personal animosity towards him is apparent in your writing,&rdquo; Jordan concluded.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The subpoena marks Republicans&rsquo; strongest move yet in its investigation of the New York County&rsquo;s indictment of Trump amid questions from some about Congress&rsquo;s authority to probe open state-level criminal matters.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://americanmilitarynews.com/2023/04/us-kills-isis-leader-who-planned-international-terrorist-attacks/"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://americanmilitarynews.com/2023/04/us-kills-isis-leader-who-planned-international-terrorist-attacks/</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>US kills ISIS leader who planned international terrorist attacks</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">A senior ISIS leader responsible for planning international terrorist attacks was killed in a U.S. strike on Monday in Syria, dealing another blow to the remnants of the Islamic State.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">U.S. Central Command, which oversees Middle East operations, said in a statement that the killing of the commander, al-Jabouri, will &ldquo;temporarily disrupt [ISIS&rsquo;] ability to plot external attacks.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Describing the operation as a &ldquo;unilateral strike,&rdquo; CENTCOM stated that al-Jabouri was a planner for attacks in Europe and Turkey, and had developed the leadership structure for ISIS in Turkey. CENTCOM said the strike did not injure or kill any civilians.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The Syrian Observatory for Human Rights, a U.K.-based nonprofit that tracks conflict in Syria, reported that a drone strike killed the commander while he was walking and making a phone call near his house.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The strike came two weeks after U.S. forces in Syria traded deadly strikes with Iranian proxies, raising fears of escalation in the region. The Iran-backed strikes killed an American contractor and gave six U.S. troops traumatic brain injuries, CNN reported.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Retaliatory strikes by the U.S. killed eight militants and targeted facilities used by groups associated with the Islamic Revolutionary Guard Corps, Iran&rsquo;s internal militia and its main force for operations beyond its borders.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">CENTCOM has stated that the U.S. has about 900 troops deployed in Syria, as well as about 170 contractors, Stars and Stripes reported. U.S. forces are stationed in Syria &ldquo;to keep an ISIS resurgence at bay,&rdquo; a military spokesman told the Washington Post in December.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">CENTCOM Commander Gen. Michael Kurilla told a congressional committee in March that &ldquo;ISIS would return within one to two years&rdquo; if the U.S. pulled out of Syria, Stars and Stripes reported. The House of Representatives recently voted down an effort to force the withdrawal of about 900 troops from Syria.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2023/apr/06/clarence-thomas-supreme-courts-gifts-republican-megadonor"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2023/apr/06/clarence-thomas-supreme-courts-gifts-republican-megadonor</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Clarence Thomas faces impeachment calls after reports of undisclosed gifts</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Clarence Thomas, the most conservative justice on the US supreme court, is facing renewed calls for impeachment after it was reported that for two decades he has accepted undisclosed luxury gifts from a Republican mega-donor.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Thomas may have violated financial disclosure rules when he failed to disclose travel on yachts and jets and other gifts funded by the property billionaire Harlan Crow and uncovered by ProPublica.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">It found that Thomas flies on Crow&rsquo;s Bombardier Global 5000 jet and holidays on Crow&rsquo;s 162ft super-yacht. He has enjoyed holidays at Crow&rsquo;s ranch in Texas and joined him at an exclusive all-male California retreat. The justice usually spends about a week each summer at Crow&rsquo;s private resort in the Adirondack mountains in New York.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The revelations prompted sharp criticism by Democrats of Thomas, who after 31 years is the longest-serving justice and an influential voice in the rightwing majority that last year ended the right to abortion.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Dick Durbin, a Democrat from Illinois and chair of the Senate judiciary committee, said: &ldquo;This behavior is simply inconsistent with the ethical standards the American people expect of any public servant, let alone a justice on the supreme court.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&ldquo;Today&rsquo;s report demonstrates, yet again, that supreme court justices must be held to an enforceable code of conduct, just like every other federal judge. The ProPublica report is a call to action, and the Senate judiciary committee will act.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Alexandria Ocasio-Cortez, a progressive congresswoman from New York, tweeted: &ldquo;This is beyond party or partisanship. This degree of corruption is shocking &ndash; almost cartoonish. Thomas must be impeached. Barring some dramatic change, this is what the [chief justice John] Roberts court will be known for: rank corruption, erosion of democracy, and the stripping of human rights.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Impeachment remains unlikely, even given other calls regarding the pro-Trump activities of Thomas&rsquo;s wife, the rightwing activist Ginni Thomas, and not just because Republicans hold the House. Only one supreme court justice has ever been impeached: Samuel Chase, in 1804-05. He was acquitted in the Senate.</span></p>]]></description>
   <author><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></author>
   <enclosure url="https://app.dropwave.io/episode/9ea58ecc-cff0-42ec-81f2-b22765cccc15/daily-news-brief-for-friday-april-7th-2023.mp3" length="800" type="audio/mp3"/>
   <guid isPermaLink="false"><![CDATA[9ea58ecc-cff0-42ec-81f2-b22765cccc15]]></guid>
   <pubDate>Fri, 07 Apr 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
   <source url=""><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></source>
   <itunes:author><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></itunes:author>
   <itunes:image href="https://assets-cdn2.dropwave.io/2ab40ac0-e99d-4f25-a6d2-541d2c9b290a/cover-art/hUZu1H9lrRY0wXg66WHC8eLwYBA3hbRNTAHQmHt2.png"/>
   <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
   <itunes:duration>800</itunes:duration>
   <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
  
  </item><item>
   <title><![CDATA[Daily News Brief for Thursday, April 6th, 2023 [Daily News Brief]]]></title>
   <link>https://app.dropwave.io/episode/95a82f4f-a7ec-4fb8-9fb0-03520de903ba/daily-news-brief-for-thursday-april-6th-2023.mp3</link>
   <description><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">This is Garrison Hardie with your CrossPolitic Daily News Brief for Thursday, April 6th, 2023.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Hi Contrast Hymn Books</strong></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">If you don&rsquo;t teach your kids the Lord&rsquo;s songs, the world will teach them its songs.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The brand-new Hi-Contrast Hymn Book is designed to help you teach your children the most beloved songs of the Christian faith.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Its captivating illustrations will create special moments of truth, goodness, and beauty in your home every day.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">To get a copy for your family, go to</span><a href="http://www.hicontrasthymnbooks.com/FLF"><span style="font-weight: 400;"> </span><span style="font-weight: 400;">www.hicontrasthymnbooks.com/FLF</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;">.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">That&rsquo;s www. &ldquo;H&rdquo; &ldquo;I&rdquo;</span><a href="http://contrasthymnbooks.com/FLF"><span style="font-weight: 400;"> </span><span style="font-weight: 400;">contrasthymnbooks.com/FLF</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;">.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://thepostmillennial.com/breaking-nashville-police-find-trans-school-shooters-suicide-note-refuse-to-release-details?utm_campaign=64487"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://thepostmillennial.com/breaking-nashville-police-find-trans-school-shooters-suicide-note-refuse-to-release-details?utm_campaign=64487</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Nashville police find trans school shooter's suicide note&mdash;refuse to release details</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The Metropolitan Nashville Police Department reportedly found a suicide note left by trans-identifying school shooter Audrey Hale during their search of the now deceased assailant's home.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">While authorities have confirmed that the note exists, its contents have not disclosed what it contains.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">According to NBC News, on Tuesday authorities released a list of items discovered at the home following the shooting. Among them were several journals, a shotgun, cellphones, laptops, and a suicide note. Old photos and yearbooks from The Covenant School, where Hale was a former student, were also recovered.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The MNPD declined to provide further details regarding the contents of the note, a document which many have suggested could shine some light on the potential motive behind the mass shooting, which left six people dead.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Officers did reveal, however, that many of the othe documents they found included notes about firearms courses and school shootings of the past.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">On Monday, police revealed that Hale planned the attack "over a period of months," and that she fired 152 rounds from the time she shot her way into the school until being killed by police.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">"The writings remain under careful review by the MNPD and the FBI's Behavioral Analysis Unit based in Quantico, Virginia. The motive for Hale&rsquo;s actions has not been established and remains under investigation by the Homicide Unit in consultation with the FBI&rsquo;s Behavioral Analysis Unit," MNPD wrote.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Hale's manifesto has also been recovered, and its contents will reportedly be released to the public as soon as the FBI has analyzed it.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://www.theepochtimes.com/another-biden-administration-covid-19-vaccine-mandate-struck-down-by-court_5172256.html?utm_source=partner&amp;utm_campaign=BonginoReport&amp;src_src=partner&amp;src_cmp=BonginoReport"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.theepochtimes.com/another-biden-administration-covid-19-vaccine-mandate-struck-down-by-court_5172256.html?utm_source=partner&amp;utm_campaign=BonginoReport&amp;src_src=partner&amp;src_cmp=BonginoReport</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Another Biden Administration COVID-19 Vaccine Mandate Struck Down by Court</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">President Joe Biden&rsquo;s administration did not have the authority to impose a COVID-19 vaccine mandate on workers and volunteers in a federal childcare program, a U.S. judge has ruled.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The Department of Health and Human Services (HHS) forced Head Start workers, and some volunteers, to get a COVID-19 vaccine starting in early 2022. Head Start provides childcare to children from low-income families.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">HHS cited the Head Start Act, which says the health secretary can add &ldquo;administrative and financial management standards,&rdquo; &ldquo;standards relating to the condition and location of facilities (including indoor air quality assessment standards, where appropriate),&rdquo; and &ldquo;such other standards as the secretary finds to be appropriate.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Texas Attorney General Ken Paxton argued that the mandate was outside of the power granted by the act. The law &ldquo;does not mention vaccinations,&rdquo; he and other plaintiffs said in a brief.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">U.S. District Judge James Wesley Hendrix agreed.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&ldquo;The wisdom of Head Start&rsquo;s rule is not before the Court&mdash;only its legality. If the people, through Congress, wish to impose a vaccine mandate on Head Start programs, they may do so by passing a law. But an agency can do only what Congress authorizes it to do,&rdquo; Hendrix, a Trump appointee, said in his ruling.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&ldquo;Regardless of how well intentioned, HHS&rsquo;s attempt here to shoehorn the vaccine mandate into statutory language authorizing modification of Head Start&rsquo;s administrative, financial, and facility-management standards goes too far. Equally fatal to the rule is the agency&rsquo;s decision to implement it without the necessary public notice and comment, consultation with stakeholders, and reasonable explanation,&rdquo; he added.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The ruling strikes down the mandate, which Biden&rsquo;s administration had refused to rescind. The mandate had already been struck down in 24 states, per a 2022 ruling by a different judge.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">HHS and the U.S. Department of Justice did not respond to requests for comment.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&ldquo;I&rsquo;m proud to announce that the Biden Administration&rsquo;s attempt to use the Head Start program to mask toddlers and force the vaccine on staff and volunteers has now been permanently defeated,&rdquo; Texas Attorney General Ken Paxton, a Republican and one of the plaintiffs, said in an emailed statement to The Epoch Times.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">In court filings, defendants had urged the judge not to block the mandate.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The COVID-19 vaccines do not prevent transmission or infection, according to data from the U.S. Centers for Disease Control and Prevention, though observational data have indicated they have a small effect on both that might turn negative over time.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The National Head Start Association, a nonprofit, welcomed the judge&rsquo;s ruling.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Head Start previously rescinded its mask mandate after months of lobbying from the nonprofit and others. It had mandated masks for children, workers, and volunteers.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://www.foxnews.com/politics/doj-reaches-ettlement-in-sutherland-springs-texas-shooting-civil-cases/"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.foxnews.com/politics/doj-reaches-ettlement-in-sutherland-springs-texas-shooting-civil-cases/</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>DOJ agrees to $144M settlement in Sutherland Springs shooting civil cases alleging background check negligence</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The Justice Department announced Wednesday it has reached a $144 million agreement in principle to settle civil cases stemming from a 2017 mass shooting at the First Baptist Church of Sutherland Springs, Texas, which left 26 dead.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Officials said the settlements will resolve claims from more than 75 plaintiffs, who alleged "the Air Force was negligent when it failed to transmit to the National Instant Criminal Background Check System information about the shooter that would have prevented him from purchasing guns from a federally licensed firearms dealer."&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The gunman in the November 2017 attack, Devin Patrick Kelly, served in the Air Force. He died of an apparent self-inflicted gunshot wound.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">"No words or amount of money can diminish the immense tragedy of the mass shooting in Sutherland Springs," said Associate Attorney General Vanita Gupta. "Today&rsquo;s announcement brings the litigation to a close, ending a painful chapter for the victims of this unthinkable crime."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The Justice Department said Wednesday that a "federal district court in Texas concluded that the United States was liable for damages caused by the shooting."&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">"The agreement in principle would settle all claims for a total of $144.5 million. The settlement agreement has been approved, subject to the plaintiffs&rsquo; securing the required court approvals," it added. "Under applicable law, a court must approve some aspects of the settlements."&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The Justice Department also said the "NICS plays a critical role in combatting gun violence, and the federal government is always striving to improve the functioning of that system."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Kelley had served nearly five years in the Air Force before being discharged in 2014 for bad conduct, after he was convicted of assaulting a former wife and stepson, cracking the child&rsquo;s skull. The Air Force has publicly acknowledged that the felony conviction for domestic violence, had it been put into the FBI database, could have prevented Kelley from buying guns from licensed firearms dealers, and also from possessing body armor.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">U.S. District Judge Xavier Rodriguez said in 2021 that had the government done its job and entered Kelley&rsquo;s history into the database, "it is more likely than not that Kelley would have been deterred from carrying out the Church shooting."&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Kelley was shot at by two churchgoers who later pursued him.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Officials said an autopsy determined Kelley was shot by Willeford twice.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Now this!!!</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://thenationalpulse.com/2023/04/03/city-council-considering-sale-of-biblical-roman-art-for-lack-of-diversity/"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://thenationalpulse.com/2023/04/03/city-council-considering-sale-of-biblical-roman-art-for-lack-of-diversity/</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>City Council Considering Sale of Biblical, Roman Art for &lsquo;Lack of Diversity&rsquo;</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Acouncil in the English city of Oxford has announced that it will consider selling some of its Biblical art that decorates the town hall in an effort to &ldquo;better reflect the gender and ethnic diversity of [the] city&rdquo;.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">On Monday, March 20th, a Liberal Democratic councillor, Katherine Miles, submitted a motion to the council to have the artworks either removed or sold. The two paintings she demands be removed or sold are the Rape of the Sabine Women and Salome and Head of John the Baptist. The former depicts Roman mythology, whereas the latter is a biblical tale.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Ms. Miles has been working on an initiative to increase the diversity and representation of the artwork in Oxford City Council since June 2021. She claims that the paintings depict &ldquo;animal cruelty and gender-based violence&rdquo;, as well as a lack of diversity. More specifically, she argues the artwork contains fox hunting, representations of death, and depictions of rape.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">In an interview with Oxford Mail, the newspaper that first reported the story, Ms. Miles reflected on the &ldquo;lack of diversity,&rdquo; stating, &ldquo;[with] only three portraits in the town hall of women, it is high time the council redresses the existing lack of diversity within the town hall portraits to better reflect the gender and ethnic diversity of our city.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Therefore, in her words, the collection has &ldquo;no practical value to the city&rdquo; nor a &ldquo;clear link to Oxford&rdquo;.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Another Liberal Democrat councillor, Lawrence Fouweather, announced his support of the motion. He argues that the artwork could be sold to assist local residents in financial difficulties. &ldquo;The Council,&rdquo; he argues, &ldquo;is running short of cash, and at the same time the cost of living crisis is thrusting many of our residents into tremendous hardship and poverty&hellip;this proposed one-off sale of select artworks from the city&rsquo;s collection would help alleviate the dire plight of some of our most deprived residents&rdquo;.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Ms. Miles, on the other hand, has stated that &ldquo;[s]elling any existing artwork not on display, and not becoming of a public institution, may be [sic] one way to fund the costs of any initiative to improve the decorations in the town hall&rdquo;.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">One critic, Peter Whittle of the New Culture Forum in London, criticized the move, stating, &ldquo;our culture continues to be dismantled by nobodies, morons and philistines&rdquo;.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">No verdict has been made on the sale. A spokesman for Oxford City Council has publicly stated that, as for now, &ldquo;there is no council position on this matter&rdquo;.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">According to the Telegraph, &ldquo;[d]iscussions about the diversity of public art in Oxford come after the city council created an &ldquo;Anti-Racism Charter&rdquo; in 2021, after pledging to tackle discrimination following Black Lives Matter protests the previous year.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://www.foxnews.com/us/cash-app-founder-bob-lee-fatally-stabbed-san-francisco-report"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.foxnews.com/us/cash-app-founder-bob-lee-fatally-stabbed-san-francisco-report</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Cash App founder Bob Lee fatally stabbed in San Francisco</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Tech executive Bob Lee, founder of Cash App and the former chief technology officer of Square, was stabbed to death in San Francisco, California, according to reports.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">A 43-year-old man was attacked Tuesday at around 2:35 a.m., San Francisco Police said in a statement. Officers arrived at the scene on the 300 block of Main Street in response to the stabbing.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The San Francisco medical examiner has not yet identified the victim, but Lee was later identified by his friends as the person stabbed, according to KPIX.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Lee was rushed to the hospital to receive treatment for his life-threatening wounds, but he later succumbed to his injuries.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">No arrests have been made in connection with the stabbing as of Wednesday morning. The incident remains under investigation.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Lee was the chief product officer of San Francisco-based cryptocurrency company MobileCoin.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">He previously worked at Google, where he led Android's core library team and launched "the world&rsquo;s most used operating system," his profile on MobileCoin&rsquo;s official website reads.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The tech mogul also founded the social network Present, and invested in and advised other companies, including Figma, Clubhouse, Beeper and Faire.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">During the coronavirus pandemic, Lee helped the World Health Organization with their mobile app and led development for an at-home testing company.</span></p>]]></description>
   <author><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></author>
   <enclosure url="https://app.dropwave.io/episode/95a82f4f-a7ec-4fb8-9fb0-03520de903ba/daily-news-brief-for-thursday-april-6th-2023.mp3" length="720" type="audio/mp3"/>
   <guid isPermaLink="false"><![CDATA[95a82f4f-a7ec-4fb8-9fb0-03520de903ba]]></guid>
   <pubDate>Thu, 06 Apr 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
   <source url=""><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></source>
   <itunes:author><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></itunes:author>
   <itunes:image href="https://assets-cdn2.dropwave.io/2ab40ac0-e99d-4f25-a6d2-541d2c9b290a/cover-art/hUZu1H9lrRY0wXg66WHC8eLwYBA3hbRNTAHQmHt2.png"/>
   <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
   <itunes:duration>720</itunes:duration>
   <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
  
  </item><item>
   <title><![CDATA[Daily News Brief for Wednesday, April 5th, 2023 [Daily News Brief]]]></title>
   <link>https://app.dropwave.io/episode/d60170fd-ee83-4792-a814-14a1016f85b9/daily-news-brief-for-wednesday-april-5th-2023.mp3</link>
   <description><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">This is Garrison Hardie with your CrossPolitic Daily News Brief for Wednesday, April 5th, 2023.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>Alps Precious Metals Group</strong></span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">THE PAST WEEK HAS BROUGHT SOME &ldquo;EXCITEMENT&rdquo; TO THE MARKETS.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">BANK RUNS.&nbsp; STOCK COLLAPSES.&nbsp; WHAT WAS THOUGHT TO BE STABLE SUDDENLY APPEARS UNSTABLE.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">AND YET, GOLD&rsquo;S PRICE *WENT UP* AS THE HEADLINES BECAME MORE OMINOUS.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">ALPS PRECIOUS METALS WAS ESTABLISHED BECAUSE WE BELIEVE THE BEST WAY TO PROTECT ONE&rsquo;S HARD-EARNED WEALTH FROM THE SERIOUS FINANCIAL PROBLEMS THAT ARE UPON US IS BY OWNING PHYSICAL GOLD AND SILVER.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">CALL JAMES HUNTER OF ALPS AT 251-377-2197, AND VISIT OUR WEBSITE AT WWW.ALPSPMG.COM TO DISCOVER HOW YOU CAN BUY PHYSICAL PRECIOUS METALS FOR YOUR INVESTMENT AND IRA PORTFOLIOS.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">OWN THE ASSET GOD SPECIFICALLY MENTIONED AS &ldquo;GOOD&rdquo; IN THE 2ND CHAPTER OF GENESIS, AND OBTAIN A PEACE OF MIND THAT CAN BE HAD WITH FEW OTHER INVESTMENTS.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">AGAIN, CALL JAMES HUNTER OF ALPS PRECIOUS METALS AT 251-377-2197, AND VISIT WWW.ALPSPMG.COM TO LEARN HOW TO OWN THE BEDROCK ASSET OF THE AGES.  </span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://www.newsweek.com/donald-trump-could-sentenced-more-100-years-prison-1792487"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.newsweek.com/donald-trump-could-sentenced-more-100-years-prison-1792487</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>Donald Trump Could be Sentenced to More Than 100 Years in Prison</strong></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Donald Trump could be sentenced to more than 100 years in prison if found guilty of the over 30 charges of business fraud in the indictment from a Manhattan grand jury for which he'll be arraigned on Tuesday in New York, according to attorney Lisa Bloom.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">According to an exclusive report by Yahoo News correspondent Michael Isikoff on Monday, the former president will face 34 class E felonies for falsification of business records in the case which revolves around the $130,000 payment of hush money to adult film star Stormy Daniels by Trump's then-lawyer Michael Cohen ahead of the 2016 presidential election. Trump has consistently denied any wrongdoing and called the probe a political "witch hunt."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">"If this report is correct, Trump will be arraigned tomorrow on 34 FELONIES. Each carries a possible prison term of 4 years. Bragg would not bring this case without strong evidence," she wrote about the Manhattan District Attorney leading the grand jury investigation, Alvin Bragg.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">"Remember, this is the same DA's office that recently convicted the Trump Org for criminal fraud."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Bloom, who since 2015 has been a vocal critic of Trump and in 2016 represented pro-bono four women accusing him of sexual harassment or sexual assault, said she's convinced that the case against Trump is strong, going to the point of calling it "a prosecutor's dream" because there's a record of the former president giving conflicting versions of the story.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Based on these premises, Bloom expects the 34 felony charges to be about Trump's attempts to "cover up evidence of an underlying crime, in this case the campaign nondisclosures."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Most experts looking at the case against Trump expect the chance of Trump actually serving prison time if found guilty close to zero. The charges against him would also not disqualify him from running for the presidency in 2024.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">It's also uncertain whether Bragg would actually recommend Trump serve time in prison. The sentence will be eventually decided by the judge.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2023/04/04/jolts-february-2023-.html"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.cnbc.com/2023/04/04/jolts-february-2023-.html</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>Job openings tumbled below 10 million in February for the first time in nearly two years</strong></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Job openings fell below 10 million in February for the first time in nearly two years, in a sign that the Federal Reserve&rsquo;s efforts to slow the labor market may be having some impact.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Available positions totaled 9.93 million, a drop of 632,000 from January&rsquo;s downwardly revised number, the Labor Department reported Tuesday in its monthly Job Openings and Labor Turnover Survey. Wall Street had been looking for 10.4 million, according to FactSet.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">It was the first time vacancies fell below 10 million since May 2021.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The Fed has targeted the red-hot labor market in its quest to bring down inflation, which had been running at a 41-year high in the summer of 2022. The central bank has raised benchmark interest rates nine times since March 2022, but those moves had been appearing to have little impact on the jobs situation.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Prior to the February data, job openings had been outnumbering available workers by nearly 2 to 1. The latest figures bring that ratio down to less than 1.7 to 1.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Treasury yields fell following the release as the data could help dissuade the Fed from further rate hikes. Stocks moved lower.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">&ldquo;The labor market is starting to loosen as the number of job openings declined in most sectors. As the economy slows, firms will likely cut openings and workers will be less likely to quit in search of better hours and higher pay,&rdquo; said Jeffrey Roach, chief economist at LPL Financial. &ldquo;The Fed could consider pausing rate hikes at the next meeting but only if the upcoming employment report shows signs of material weakness and the March [consumer price index] report reveals lower inflation.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Though the numbers run a month behind, the Fed watches the JOLTS data closely for signs of labor slack.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Along with the decline in job openings, hires and separations also decreased slightly. Quits, a sign of labor confidence in the ability to switch jobs, rose by 146,000 to just over 4 million.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Professional and business services saw a slide of 278,000 job openings on the month, while trade, transportation and utilities decreased 210,000. Accommodation and food services, an important sector to gauge consumer demand, dropped 125,000.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">On the positive side, there were 129,000 new construction jobs available, though that was the only category that saw a noticeable bump.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The JOLTS release comes three days ahead of fresh nonfarm payroll numbers for March. The Friday Labor Department count is expected to show a gain of 238,000, with the unemployment rate holding steady at 3.6%.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://www.dailywire.com/news/wisconsin-voters-head-to-the-polls-to-decide-balance-of-state-supreme-court"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.dailywire.com/news/wisconsin-voters-head-to-the-polls-to-decide-balance-of-state-supreme-court</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>Wisconsin Voters Head To The Polls To Decide Balance Of State Supreme Court</strong></span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Voters in Wisconsin head to the polls on Tuesday to decide the balance of the state Supreme Court in one of the most expensive court races in history.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Neither candidate running for the open seat belongs to a political party. Conservative candidate and former Justice Dan Kelly, backed by most Republicans, is facing off against liberal candidate Judge Janet Protasiewicz (Pro-Tuh-Say-Witz), the preferred candidate of most Democrats, with the winner determining the ideological slant of the divided court and earning a 10-year term on the court.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Protasiewicz has reportedly been backed by donations from left-wing billionaire George Soros and Gov. J.B Pritzker (D-IL), while Kelly has received support from groups like Fair Courts America, a conservative judicial organization. Total spending has exceeded $40 million, an astronomical amount compared to previous years when total spending was only around $10 million.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Hollywood has even thrown its weight behind Protasiewicz, with director Steven Speilberg contributing to her campaign and actor Mark Ruffalo encouraging voters to &ldquo;change the future of Wisconsin by electing Janet Protasiewicz &amp; flipping the state supreme court.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Both candidates have suggested that the other is unfit to serve, with Kelly pointing to Protasiewicz&rsquo;s left-wing ties and claiming she has a soft-on-crime sentencing history, while Protasiewicz linked Kelly to attempts to challenge the 2020 presidential election in the Badger State.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">During a debate earlier this year, Protasiewicz claimed that she was &ldquo;running against probably one of the most extreme partisan characters in the history of the state.&rdquo;&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Though officially non-partisan, the candidates have nearly polar opposite views, with Protasiewicz openly championing her support for abortion and Kelly receiving the endorsements of key pro-life groups in the state. Protasiewicz had an ad featuring a woman celebrating an abortion because the child could have been born with disabilities.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The election could be a deciding factor in a case over Wisconsin&rsquo;s 1849 abortion ban, which became relevant after Roe v. Wade was overturned last summer.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The candidates could also play a key role in deciding the fate of other laws in the state, including election integrity measures, election maps, and gun laws. Last year, the state made a bombshell ruling, saying that Wisconsin voters could not turn their ballots into unmanned drop boxes and that voters would not be allowed to give them to others to drop off for them. This case, decided 4-3, would likely have been different with a different balance on the court.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Republicans currently control the state&rsquo;s general assembly, but Democrat Gov. Tony Evers won re-election in November, meaning lawmakers are limited in what laws they can get passed.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/restoring-america/fairness-justice/los-angeles-decarceration-release-inmates"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/restoring-america/fairness-justice/los-angeles-decarceration-release-inmates</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>Los Angeles floats 'decarceration' policy to release large number of inmates</strong></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The Los Angeles County Board of Supervisors is floating a "decarceration" policy that would drastically reduce the number of people in jails, releasing many current inmates.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The agenda item , added to Tuesday's meeting, is titled "Los Angeles County to Take Actionable Next Steps to Depopulate and Decarcerate the Los Angeles County Jails: Granting Local Authority, Advocating for Court and State Support, and Legislative Changes."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The proposal, to be discussed during the meeting, would "declare the State of mental health services and overcrowding in the Los Angeles County jails a humanitarian crisis, requiring the County to move with all deliberate speed on meaningful solutions; and prioritize decreasing the number of individuals entering the Los Angeles County Jails" through a number of measures.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">In order to "reaffirm the Board&rsquo;s commitment to depopulate and decarcerate," the proposal would require law enforcement to "cite and release individuals with aggregate bail amounts set at $50,000 or below" and "adopt a zero-bail schedule for individuals accused of low-level offenses, infractions, misdemeanors, and some felony offenses."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The push comes as crime, including violent crime, has risen in the past few years, particularly since the start of the COVID-19 pandemic . An analysis found that crime increased 11% in 2022, with 60 reported crimes per 1,000 residents, compared to 2021, which saw 54 crimes per 1,000 residents. In some areas, crime has skyrocketed; downtown experienced 372 crimes per 1,000 residents in 2022.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The vice president of the Los Angeles Association of Deputy District Attorneys, Eric Siddall, denounced the proposal, speaking with Fox News, arguing that it would make crime in the city even worse.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">"The Los Angeles County Board of Supervisors&rsquo; motion to gut parts of the criminal justice system without input from stakeholders is dangerous and recklessness," he told the outlet. "The authors sought no advice from those who know and understand public safety issues. They seek to lower the jail population without addressing the root causes of crime or protecting the public."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">He condemned the "catch-and-release" part of the proposal.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Now this!</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://www.theblaze.com/news/gone-with-the-wind-to-include-trigger-warning-intro-that-addresses-white-supremacy-in-latest-print"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.theblaze.com/news/gone-with-the-wind-to-include-trigger-warning-intro-that-addresses-white-supremacy-in-latest-print</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>'Gone with the Wind' to include trigger warning, intro that addresses 'white supremacy' in latest print</strong></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The publishers of the classic American novel "Gone with the Wind" will include a "harmful" trigger warning and an introduction that addresses "white supremacy," the Telegraph reported.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Pan Macmillan, a publishing house based in London, has decided to affix a trigger warning to Margaret Mitchell's 1936 novel. The book, which takes place in 1861, follows the story of Scarlett O'Hara, the daughter of a southern plantation owner, and her romance with Captain Rhett Butler during the Civil War.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The cautionary note at the front of the new edition of the book will warn readers that it contains "racist" themes that could be "hurtful or indeed harmful."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">"Gone with the Wind is a novel which includes problematic elements including the romanticisation of a shocking era in our history and the horrors of slavery," the trigger warning states. "The novel includes the representation of unacceptable practices, racist and stereotypical depictions and troubling themes, characterisation, language and imagery."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Pan Macmillan noted that the new edition of Mitchell's novel would remain original. New editions of works from Agatha Christie and Ian Fleming were recently altered to remove potentially offensive passages with racial references.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">"The text of this book remains true to the original in every way and is reflective of the language and period in which it was originally written," the cautionary note continued. "We want to alert readers that there may be hurtful or indeed harmful phrases and terminology that were prevalent at the time this novel was written and which are true to the context of the historical setting of this novel."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">"Pan Macmillan believes changing the text to reflect today&rsquo;s world would undermine the authenticity of the original, so has chosen to leave the text in its entirety."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Pan Macmillan added, "This does not, however, constitute an endorsement of the characterisation, content or language used."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The cautionary note affixed to the start of the novel was written by Philippa Gregory, the author of "The Other Boleyn Girl." According to the publisher, Gregory was chosen to pen the introduction because "we believed it was important that no author from a minority background should be asked to undertake the emotional labour of being responsible for educating the majority."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Gregory argued that Mitchell's novel "effectively promoted the racist planter view of the history of the South." She claimed it "defends racism" and "glamorizes and preaches white supremacy."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">According to Gregory, "It tells us, unequivocally, that African people are not of the same species as white people."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">"This is the lie that spoils the novel," Gregory adds.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">All I can say to the publisher is, Frankly my dear&hellip; I don&rsquo;t give a damn.&nbsp;</span></p>]]></description>
   <author><![CDATA[Garrison Hardie]]></author>
   <enclosure url="https://app.dropwave.io/episode/d60170fd-ee83-4792-a814-14a1016f85b9/daily-news-brief-for-wednesday-april-5th-2023.mp3" length="829" type="audio/mp3"/>
   <guid isPermaLink="false"><![CDATA[d60170fd-ee83-4792-a814-14a1016f85b9]]></guid>
   <pubDate>Wed, 05 Apr 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
   <source url=""><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></source>
   <itunes:author><![CDATA[Garrison Hardie]]></itunes:author>
   <itunes:image href="https://assets-cdn2.dropwave.io/2ab40ac0-e99d-4f25-a6d2-541d2c9b290a/cover-art/hUZu1H9lrRY0wXg66WHC8eLwYBA3hbRNTAHQmHt2.png"/>
   <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
   <itunes:duration>829</itunes:duration>
   <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
  
  </item><item>
   <title><![CDATA[Daily News Brief for Friday, March 31st, 2023 [Daily News Brief]]]></title>
   <link>https://app.dropwave.io/episode/0a9739e3-6106-4bc0-a1df-c7370871a55e/daily-news-brief-for-friday-march-31st-2023.mp3</link>
   <description><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">This is Garrison Hardie with your CrossPolitic Daily News Brief for Friday, March 31st, 2023.</span></p>
<p class="p1">&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>Hi Contrast Hymn Books</strong></span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">If you don&rsquo;t teach your kids the Lord&rsquo;s songs, the world will teach them its songs.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The brand-new Hi-Contrast Hymn Book is designed to help you teach your children the most beloved songs of the Christian faith.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Its captivating illustrations will create special moments of truth, goodness, and beauty in your home every day.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">To get a copy for your family, go to</span><a href="http://www.hicontrasthymnbooks.com/FLF"><span style="font-weight: 400;"> </span><span style="font-weight: 400;">www.hicontrasthymnbooks.com/FLF</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;">.&nbsp;</span></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">That&rsquo;s www. &ldquo;H&rdquo; &ldquo;I&rdquo;</span><a href="http://contrasthymnbooks.com/FLF"><span style="font-weight: 400;"> </span><span style="font-weight: 400;">contrasthymnbooks.com/FLF</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;">.&nbsp;</span></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://www.huffpost.com/entry/trump-stormy-daniels-hush-money-indictment_n_640f5b35e4b0fef1523fa996"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.huffpost.com/entry/trump-stormy-daniels-hush-money-indictment_n_640f5b35e4b0fef1523fa996</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>Trump Indicted Over $130,000 Hush Money Payment To Stormy Daniels</strong></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Former President Donald Trump, already under multiple criminal investigations for his coup attempt, has been indicted by a Manhattan grand jury for his role in a $130,000 hush money payment to a porn star in the days before the 2016 election.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The New York Times was the first to report on the still-sealed indictment.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Trump&rsquo;s campaign staff did not immediately respond to a HuffPost query Thursday. But Taylor Budowich, a former Trump aide and now the head of a pro-Trump super PAC, claimed in a Twitter post that the indictment is evidence of a &ldquo;failed nation,&rdquo; and predicted it would actually help Trump.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Trump, who is running again for the Republican nomination for the presidency, has in recent days ramped up his appeals to supporters to rise up against prosecutors in New York and elsewhere ― reminiscent of his inflammatory language leading up to the Jan. 6, 2021, assault on the U.S. Capitol by a mob of his followers.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">In another post, Trump predicted he would be arrested on Tuesday, March 21, forcing New York City police to increase security at the courthouse. Then, when no indictment came, Trump and others suggested that District Attorney Alvin Bragg must have backed down.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">As of late Thursday afternoon, Trump had not posted anything following the news of the indictment.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The indictment in New York City gives Trump, who frequently claimed that his actions as president were &ldquo;historic,&rdquo; another claim to history: He is now the first of the 44 ex-chief executives to be charged with a crime. He had previously entered the history books by becoming the only president to be impeached twice.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">One of his lawyers at the time, Michael Cohen, already pleaded guilty to a federal charge of violating campaign finance laws with the check to Stormy Daniels to buy her silence about the affair she says she had with Trump in 2006. Cohen served 13 months in prison and another year and a half under home confinement for that and various unrelated charges.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Cohen is likely to be a key witness against Trump in District Attorney Alvin Bragg&rsquo;s prosecution. He has said Trump reimbursed him for the $130,000, as well as $150,000 to a second woman, with a series of payments, and evidence during his case showed the money came from Trump&rsquo;s business as a supposed &ldquo;legal expense.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Trump has claimed that Bragg&rsquo;s probe is a part of a &ldquo;witch hunt&rdquo; against him</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The former president is also under investigation by the Fulton County District Attorney in Atlanta and the U.S. Department of Justice about his attempts to overturn the 2020 election he lost by pressuring his own vice president into throwing out the results from key states and awarding Trump a second term ― an effort that culminated in the violence he incited on Jan. 6, 2021.</span></p>
<p class="p1">&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://thepostmillennial.com/far-left-activists-students-storm-state-house-to-demanding-more-gun-control-in-tennessee?utm_campaign=64487"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://thepostmillennial.com/far-left-activists-students-storm-state-house-to-demanding-more-gun-control-in-tennessee?utm_campaign=64487</span></a></span></p>
<p class="p1">&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>Far-left activists, students storm state house to demand more gun control in Tennessee</strong></span></p>
<p class="p1">&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">On Thursday, a large number of individuals congregated at the Tennessee State Capitol, with the situation quickly turning chaotic as leftist activists entered the building and were seen shouting at lawmakers, demanding more gun control measures.</span></p>
<p class="p1">&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Among those present were parents with their children and members of the community demonstrating following the Covenant School shooting, which resulted in the deaths of six individuals, including three children.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">"We&rsquo;re here because we still believe that we can make change. We can. It&rsquo;s a tough state, I get it,&rdquo; said organizer Maryam Abolfazli, to local news outlet WKRN.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p class="p1">&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The Republican-majority Legislature gathered at the Capitol on Thursday to start the legislative session for the first time since the shooting. Protestors stormed the building and filled the hallways while chanting slogans.</span></p>
<p class="p1">&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Demonstrators took over both indoor and outdoor spaces, video shows.</span></p>
<p class="p1">&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The Senate chamber gallery was filled with protesters, including children holding signs with the age of the victims of the recent attack.</span></p>
<p class="p1">&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Some of the protestors interrupted the lawmakers with their shouts of "Children are dead!" resulting in their removal from the gallery.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p class="p1">&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Meanwhile, in the House, two Democratic lawmakers caused a temporary disruption by using a megaphone to yell, "Power to the people."</span></p>
<p class="p1">&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The protests followed a candlelight vigil held in Nashville the previous night, where Republican lawmakers, alongside First Lady Jill Biden, Democratic lawmakers, and musicians, including Sheryl Crow, gathered to honor the victims and advocate for stricter gun control.</span></p>
<p class="p1">&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://dailycaller.com/2023/03/30/el-paso-southern-border-mexico/"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://dailycaller.com/2023/03/30/el-paso-southern-border-mexico/</span></a></span></p>
<p class="p1">&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>Caravan Of More Than 1,000 Migrants Crosses Into El Paso Illegally As Chaos Erupts In Mexico</strong></span></p>
<p class="p1">&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">A caravan of more than 1,000 migrants crossed illegally into El Paso, Texas, Wednesday as chaos erupted in recent days on the Mexican side in Juarez.</span></p>
<p class="p1">&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Agents apprehended the group, which was mostly comprised of Venezuelans, Wednesday, El Paso Border Patrol Chief Anthony Good said late Thursday. The incident follows chaos in Juarez, where nearly 40 migrants died Monday in a shelter fire.</span></p>
<p class="p1">&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Hundreds of migrants also amassed at the Paso del Norte bridge on March 15 leading into Juarez to demand entry into the U.S.</span></p>
<p class="p1">&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Venezuelans are expelled under Title 42, a public health order invoked by the Trump administration during COVID-19. They are, however, offered exemptions through a humanitarian parole program and Customs and Border Protection (CBP) One, a phone app used to request an entry interview.</span></p>
<p class="p1">&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Migrants have expressed frustrations with the CBP One process having glitches and lacking appointment availability.</span></p>
<p class="p1">&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">&ldquo;Migrants that are still arriving at the southern border from the original surge invitation by the president are becoming impatient with extended processing times and turning frustrations against CBP personnel,&rdquo; a Border Patrol agent, who requested anonymity because they weren&rsquo;t authorized to speak publicly, recently told the Daily Caller News Foundation.</span></p>
<p class="p1">&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://justthenews.com/nation/states/center-square/los-angeles-cook-counties-post-biggest-population-losses-us-2022"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://justthenews.com/nation/states/center-square/los-angeles-cook-counties-post-biggest-population-losses-us-2022</span></a></span></p>
<p class="p1">&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>Blue flight: Los Angeles, Cook counties post biggest population losses in U.S. in 2022</strong></span></p>
<p class="p1">&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The number of people who used to live in Los Angeles County and Cook County in Illinois continues to plummet.</span></p>
<p class="p1">&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Los Angeles County posted the largest population decline of all counties in the United States in 2022, falling by 90,704 and continuing a downward trend. It lost nearly twice that amount (180,394) in 2021, according to the U.S. Census Bureau&rsquo;s Vintage 2022 estimates released Thursday.</span></p>
<p class="p1">&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Cook County, home to Chicago, lost 68,314 people from July 2021 to July of last year.</span></p>
<p class="p1">&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Los Angeles County was still the most populous county in the U.S. That was followed by Cook County in Illinois at 5,109,292, which declined by 68,314 from the prior year. Rounding out the top five were Harris County, Texas (4,780,913); Maricopa County, Arizona (4,551,524); and San Diego County, California (3,276,208).</span></p>
<p class="p1">&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Eight of the top 10 most populous counties in the U.S. were located in the South and West. The two exceptions were Cook County in Illinois and Kings County in New York.</span></p>
<p class="p1">&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">"Reflecting longstanding regional population shifts, the nation&rsquo;s most populous counties are increasingly located in the South and West," the bureau reported. "In 2022, 63 of the country&rsquo;s 100 most populous counties were located in the South and West, up from 61 in the prior year."</span></p>
<p class="p1">&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The 10 counties in the U.S. that gained the most people were located in three states: Texas, Arizona and Florida. Maricopa County in Arizona topped the growth list, adding 56,831 people in 2022. It was followed by Harris County, Texas (added 45,626); Collin County, Texas (44,246); Denton County, Texas (33,424); and Polk County, Florida (32,225).</span></p>
<p class="p1">&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The biggest losers were Los Angeles County, California (-90,704); Cook County, Illinois (-68,314); Queens County, New York (-50,112); Kings County, New York (-46,970); and Bronx County, New York (-41,143).</span></p>
<p class="p1">&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">"The migration and growth patterns for counties edged closer to pre-pandemic levels this year," said Christine Hartley, assistant division chief for estimates and projections in the Census Bureau&rsquo;s population division. "Some urban counties, such as Dallas and San Francisco, saw domestic outmigration at a slower pace between 2021 and 2022, compared to the prior year."</span></p>
<p class="p1">&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Deaths outnumbered births in most U.S. counties in 2022. Nearly three-quarters of all U.S. counties had natural decrease in 2022, which means they recorded more deaths than births.</span></p>
<p class="p1">&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">"The incidence of natural decrease remains historically high," the bureau reported. "Natural decrease counties are found nationwide but are especially prevalent in some states."</span></p>
<p class="p1">&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Maine was the only state in the nation where all counties had natural decrease. Deaths outnumbered births in 54 or the 55 counties in West Virginia. And seven of the 10 counties with the highest amount of natural decrease were in Florida. Pinellas County topped the list with -6,468.</span></p>
<p class="p1">&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Births exceeded deaths in 791 counties (or 25.2% of all counties) in 2022. Five of the top 10 counties where births exceeded deaths, called natural increase, were in Texas. Harris County had the highest in the nation with 30,117.</span></p>
<p class="p1"><br /><br /><br /></p>]]></description>
   <author><![CDATA[Garrison Hardie]]></author>
   <enclosure url="https://app.dropwave.io/episode/0a9739e3-6106-4bc0-a1df-c7370871a55e/daily-news-brief-for-friday-march-31st-2023.mp3" length="614" type="audio/mp3"/>
   <guid isPermaLink="false"><![CDATA[0a9739e3-6106-4bc0-a1df-c7370871a55e]]></guid>
   <pubDate>Fri, 31 Mar 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
   <source url=""><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></source>
   <itunes:author><![CDATA[Garrison Hardie]]></itunes:author>
   <itunes:image href="https://assets-cdn2.dropwave.io/2ab40ac0-e99d-4f25-a6d2-541d2c9b290a/cover-art/hUZu1H9lrRY0wXg66WHC8eLwYBA3hbRNTAHQmHt2.png"/>
   <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
   <itunes:duration>614</itunes:duration>
   <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
  
  </item><item>
   <title><![CDATA[Daily News Brief for Thursday, March 30th, 2023 [Daily News Brief]]]></title>
   <link>https://app.dropwave.io/episode/d9c34491-690d-4971-a4c1-9a62e84046e0/daily-news-brief-for-thursday-march-30th-2023.mp3</link>
   <description><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">This is Garrison Hardie with your CrossPolitic Daily News Brief for Thursday, March 30th, 2023.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Alps Precious Metals Group</strong></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">THE PAST WEEK HAS BROUGHT SOME &ldquo;EXCITEMENT&rdquo; TO THE MARKETS.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">BANK RUNS.&nbsp; STOCK COLLAPSES.&nbsp; WHAT WAS THOUGHT TO BE STABLE SUDDENLY APPEARS UNSTABLE.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">AND YET, GOLD&rsquo;S PRICE *WENT UP* AS THE HEADLINES BECAME MORE OMINOUS.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">ALPS PRECIOUS METALS WAS ESTABLISHED BECAUSE WE BELIEVE THE BEST WAY TO PROTECT ONE&rsquo;S HARD-EARNED WEALTH FROM THE SERIOUS FINANCIAL PROBLEMS THAT ARE UPON US IS BY OWNING PHYSICAL GOLD AND SILVER.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">CALL JAMES HUNTER OF ALPS AT 251-377-2197, AND VISIT OUR WEBSITE AT WWW.ALPSPMG.COM TO DISCOVER HOW YOU CAN BUY PHYSICAL PRECIOUS METALS FOR YOUR INVESTMENT AND IRA PORTFOLIOS.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">OWN THE ASSET GOD SPECIFICALLY MENTIONED AS &ldquo;GOOD&rdquo; IN THE 2ND CHAPTER OF GENESIS, AND OBTAIN A PEACE OF MIND THAT CAN BE HAD WITH FEW OTHER INVESTMENTS.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">AGAIN, CALL JAMES HUNTER OF ALPS PRECIOUS METALS AT 251-377-2197, AND VISIT WWW.ALPSPMG.COM TO LEARN HOW TO OWN THE BEDROCK ASSET OF THE AGES.  </span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://www.foxnews.com/us/dna-half-eaten-burrito-ties-wisconsin-doctoral-student-pro-life-center-firebombing-attack"><strong>https://www.foxnews.com/us/dna-half-eaten-burrito-ties-wisconsin-doctoral-student-pro-life-center-firebombing-attack</strong></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>DNA from half-eaten burrito ties ex-Wisconsin doctoral student to pro-life center firebombing attack</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">DNA found in a half-eaten burrito helped exposed a former Wisconsin university research assistant now accused of firebombing a pro-life center last Mother's Day.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The attack on the headquarters of Wisconsin Family Action in Madison, Wisconsin, came about a week after the leak of a Supreme Court draft opinion that would later overturn Roe v. Wade.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">About 10 months after a Molotov cocktail was tossed inside the office and the message, "If abortions aren&rsquo;t safe then you aren&rsquo;t either," was scrawled on the building's side, Hridindu Sankar Roychowdhury, 29, of Madison, was arrested in Boston on Tuesday and charged with one count of attempting to cause damage by means of fire or an explosive.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The Justice Department said he traveled from Madison to Portland, Maine, and he purchased a one-way ticket from Boston to Guatemala City, Guatemala, departing Tuesday morning.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Law enforcement arrested Roychowdhury at Boston Logan International Airport.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">"According to the complaint, Mr. Roychowdhury used an incendiary device in violation of federal law in connection with his efforts to terrorize and intimidate a private organization," Assistant Attorney General Matthew G. Olsen of the Justice Department&rsquo;s National Security Division said in a statement. "I commend the commitment and professionalism of law enforcement personnel who worked exhaustively to ensure that justice is served."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">"Violence is never an acceptable way for anyone to express their views or their disagreement," Assistant Director Robert R. Wells of the FBI&rsquo;s Counterterrorism Division said. "Today&rsquo;s arrest demonstrates the FBI&rsquo;s commitment to vigorously pursue those responsible for this dangerous attack and others across the country, and to hold them accountable for their criminal actions."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">According to the complaint, on Mother&rsquo;s Day, Sunday, May 8, 2022, at approximately 6:06 a.m., law enforcement responded to an active fire at an office building located in Madison.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Once inside the building, police observed a mason jar under a broken window. The jar was broken, and the lid and screw top were burned black, the Justice Department said.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The police also saw a purple disposable lighter near the mason jar. On the opposite wall from the window, the police saw another mason jar with the lid on and a blue cloth tucked into the top, and the cloth was singed. The jar was about half full of a clear fluid that smelled like an accelerant, the complaint says.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Outside the building, someone spray-painted on one wall, "If abortions aren&rsquo;t safe then you aren&rsquo;t either" and, on another wall, a large "A" with a circle around it and the number "1312," according to the Justice Department. During the investigation, law enforcement collected DNA from the scene of the attack.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">In March 2023, law enforcement identified Roychowdhury as a possible suspect. The affidavit said officers conducting surveillance on a protest at the Wisconsin State Capitol over the construction of an Atlanta public safety center dubbed "Cop City," observed an individual later identified as Roychowdhury.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Local police officers later observed Roychowdhury dispose of food in a public trash can, and the officers recovered the leftover food and related items, and law enforcement collected DNA from the food. The affidavit says officers recovered a paper bag filled with "a quarter portion of a partially eaten burrito wrapped in waxed paper, a soiled napkin, a crumpled napkin, a stack of napkins, the wrapper of the burrito, a crumpled food wrapper, [and] four unopened hot sauce packets."</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">"On March 17, 2023, law enforcement advised that a forensic biologist examined the DNA evidence recovered from the attack scene and compared it to the DNA collected from the food contents. The forensic biologist found the two samples matched and likely were the same individual," the Justice Department said.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">State Rep. Barbara Dittrich, a Republican, shared screenshots to Twitter Tuesday showing that the University of Wisconsin-Madison's website listed Roychowdhury as a trainee/research assistant for the Biophysics Interdisciplinary PhD in Structural and Computational Biology and Quantitative Biosciences.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">A LinkedIn profile for Roychowdhury also listed a UWMadison Doctor of Philosophy - PhD Biochemistry under education.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">"This man should be charged with domestic terrorism, and the good taxpayers of this state should not be paying his salary," Dittrich tweeted.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">In an update, the lawmaker said UWMadison campus "notified us after this post that Mr. Roychowdhurdy ended his affiliation with the UW System the year that this incident occurred.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">If convicted, Roychowdhury faces a mandatory minimum penalty of five years and a maximum of 20 years in prison, prosecutors said.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Transition:</strong></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">In world news&hellip;&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://www.breitbart.com/europe/2023/03/28/former-general-calls-for-eu-military-in-north-africa-to-defeat-russian-mercenaries/"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.breitbart.com/europe/2023/03/28/former-general-calls-for-eu-military-in-north-africa-to-defeat-russian-mercenaries/</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Former General Calls for EU Military in North Africa to Defeat Russian Mercenaries</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">A former Italian General has called on the European Union to act militarily in Northern Africa, blaming the Russian mercenary PMC Wagner Group for the current wave of illegal immigrants.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">General Carlo Jean, former commander of the Italian unit of the NATO Mobile Force and Alpine Brigade &ldquo;Cadore&rdquo;, is the latest Italian official to blame Private Military Company Wagner &mdash; Russian mercenaries, in other words &mdash; for the surge of illegals that have arrived in Italy so far this year.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">According to General Jean, local governments in African countries have become too weak in the face of ethnic and tribal groups making cash from illegal migration, preventing European nations from making effective deals with governments to halt illegal migration.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">General Jean added that the solution to the problem is military force saying, &ldquo;something that is against the values of which we are very proud. That is, force would be needed, a massive intervention, to field a colonial-type army in Africa to stabilize regimes and regions.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&ldquo;The big problem is that Europe is not a state, it has neither military nor political capacity to do something that can only be achieved with rather harsh methods, with occupation and strengthening of the governments of North Africa and the Sahel. We should operate like Wagner,&rdquo; he said and added that if Europe does not act military then it should resign itself to becoming a &ldquo;mestizo continent.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The statements from General Jean come just weeks after Italian Foreign Minister Antonio Tajani blamed PMC Wagner for the rise in illegal migration, which has close to tripled since last year.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&ldquo;We have indications that they are very active and in contact with gangs of traffickers and militiamen interested in the smuggling of migrants,&rdquo; Tajani said of the Russian private military group.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Tajani was joined in his view by Defence Minister Guido Crosetto, who PMC Wagner allegedly has a $15 million bounty on, according to Italian media reports.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://nypost.com/2023/03/29/pope-francis-hospitalized-for-lung-infection-vatican/"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://nypost.com/2023/03/29/pope-francis-hospitalized-for-lung-infection-vatican/</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Pope Francis hospitalized for lung infection: Vatican</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Pope Francis was hospitalized with a lung infection Wednesday after experiencing difficulty breathing in recent days and will remain in the hospital for several days of treatment, the Vatican said.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The 86-year-old pope doesn&rsquo;t have COVID-19, spokesman Matteo Bruni said in a statement late Wednesday.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The hospitalization was the first since Francis spent 10 days at the Gemelli hospital in July 2021 to have 33 centimeters (13 inches) of his colon removed.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">It immediately raised questions about Francis&rsquo; overall health, and his ability to celebrate the busy Holy Week events that are due to begin this weekend with Palm Sunday.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Bruni said Francis had been suffering breathing troubles in recent days and went to the Gemelli for tests.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&ldquo;The tests showed a respiratory infection (COVID-19 infection excluded) that will require some days of medical therapy,&rdquo; Bruni&rsquo;s statement said.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Francis appeared in relatively good form during his regularly scheduled general audience earlier Wednesday, though he grimaced strongly while getting in and out of the &ldquo;popemobile.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Francis had part of one lung removed when he was a young man due to a respiratory infection, and he often speaks in a whisper.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">But he got through the worst phases of the COVID-19 pandemic without at least any public word of ever testing positive.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Francis had been due to celebrate Palm Sunday this weekend, kicking off the Vatican&rsquo;s Holy Week observances: Holy Thursday, Good Friday, the Easter Vigil and finally Easter Sunday on April 9.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">He has canceled all audiences through Friday, but it wasn&rsquo;t clear whether he could keep the Holy Week plans.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Francis has used a wheelchair for over a year due to strained ligaments in his right knee and a small knee fracture. He has said the injury was healing and has been walking more with a cane of late.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Francis also has said he resisted having surgery for the knee problems because he didn&rsquo;t respond well to general anesthesia during the 2021 intestinal surgery.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">He said soon after the surgery that he had recovered fully and could eat normally.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://www.foxnews.com/politics/elon-musk-apple-co-founder-tech-experts-call-pause-giant-ai-experiments"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.foxnews.com/politics/elon-musk-apple-co-founder-tech-experts-call-pause-giant-ai-experiments</span></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Elon Musk, Apple co-founder, other tech experts call for pause on 'giant AI experiments': 'Dangerous race'</strong></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Elon Musk, Steve Wozniak, and a host of other tech leaders and artificial intelligence experts are urging AI labs to pause development of powerful new AI systems in an open letter citing potential risks to society.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The letter asks AI developers to "immediately pause for at least 6 months the training of AI systems more powerful than GPT-4." It was issued by the Future of Life Institute and signed by more than 1,000 people, including Musk, who argued that safety protocols need to be developed by independent overseers to guide the future of AI systems. GPT-4 is the latest deep learning model from OpenAI, which "exhibits human-level performance on various professional and academic benchmarks," according to the lab.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">"Powerful AI systems should be developed only once we are confident that their effects will be positive and their risks will be manageable," the letter said.</span><span style="font-weight: 400;"><br /><br /></span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The letter warns that at this stage, no one "can understand, predict, or reliably control" the powerful new tools developed in AI labs. The undersigned tech experts cite the risks of propaganda and lies spread through AI-generated articles that look real, and even the possibility that Ai programs can outperform workers and make jobs obsolete.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">"AI labs and independent experts should use this pause to jointly develop and implement a set of shared safety protocols for advanced AI design and development that are rigorously audited and overseen by independent outside experts," the letter states.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">"In parallel, AI developers must work with policymakers to dramatically accelerate development of robust AI governance systems."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The signatories, which include Stability AI CEO Emad Mostaque, researchers at Alphabet-owned DeepMind, as well as AI heavyweights Yoshua Bengio and Stuart Russell, emphasize that AI development in general should be not paused, writing that their letter is calling for "merely a stepping back from the dangerous race to ever-larger unpredictable black-box models with emergent capabilities."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">According to the European Union's transparency register, the Future of Life Institute is primarily funded by the Musk Foundation, as well as London-based effective altruism group Founders Pledge, and Silicon Valley Community Foundation.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Musk, whose electric car company Tesla uses AI for its autopilot system, has previously raised concerns about the rapid development of AI.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Since its release last year, Microsoft-backed OpenAI's ChatGPT has prompted rivals to accelerate developing similar large language models, and companies to integrate generative AI models into their products.</span></p>]]></description>
   <author><![CDATA[Garrison Hardie]]></author>
   <enclosure url="https://app.dropwave.io/episode/d9c34491-690d-4971-a4c1-9a62e84046e0/daily-news-brief-for-thursday-march-30th-2023.mp3" length="834" type="audio/mp3"/>
   <guid isPermaLink="false"><![CDATA[d9c34491-690d-4971-a4c1-9a62e84046e0]]></guid>
   <pubDate>Thu, 30 Mar 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
   <source url=""><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></source>
   <itunes:author><![CDATA[Garrison Hardie]]></itunes:author>
   <itunes:image href="https://assets-cdn2.dropwave.io/2ab40ac0-e99d-4f25-a6d2-541d2c9b290a/cover-art/hUZu1H9lrRY0wXg66WHC8eLwYBA3hbRNTAHQmHt2.png"/>
   <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
   <itunes:duration>834</itunes:duration>
   <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
  
  </item>
 </channel>
</rss>
