<?xml version="1.0"?>
<?xml-stylesheet href="/storage/feed-stylesheet.xsl" type="text/xsl"?>

<rss xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
 <channel>
  <title>FLF - Daily News Brief</title>
  <link>https://dropwave.io</link>
  <description><![CDATA[FIGHT LAUGH FEAST PRESENTS SHOWS PROCLAIMING THE LORDSHIP OF CHRIST OVER ALL OF LIFE.
]]></description>
  <language>en</language>
  <managingEditor><![CDATA[fightlaughfeast@gmail.com (FLF, LLC)]]></managingEditor>
  <webMaster><![CDATA[support@dropwave.io (DropWave Support)]]></webMaster>
  <pubDate>Sun, 04 Jun 2023 07:25:45 +0000</pubDate>
  <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Jun 2023 07:25:45 +0000</lastBuildDate>
  <image>
   <url>https://is4-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Podcasts113/v4/58/56/52/5856525c-2973-cf29-3db9-21faa8595391/mza_1144696925612154085.png/1200x1200bb.jpg</url>
   <link>https://dropwave.io</link>
   <title><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></title>
  </image>
  <itunes:author><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></itunes:author>
  <itunes:image href="https://is4-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Podcasts113/v4/58/56/52/5856525c-2973-cf29-3db9-21faa8595391/mza_1144696925612154085.png/1200x1200bb.jpg"/>
  <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
  <itunes:owner>
   <itunes:name><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></itunes:name>
   <itunes:email>fightlaughfeast@gmail.com</itunes:email>
  </itunes:owner>
  <itunes:category text="News"/>
  <item>
   <title><![CDATA[Daily News Brief for Thursday, June 1st, 2023 [Daily News Brief]]]></title>
   <link>https://app.dropwave.io/episode/9362c7c6-17ba-4d6e-b65f-db49b0702a14/daily-news-brief-for-thursday-june-1st-2023.mp3</link>
   <description><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">This is Garrison Hardie with your CrossPolitic Daily News Brief for Thursday, June 1st, 2023.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://www.theepochtimes.com/chick-fil-a-faces-growing-backlash-over-diversity-equity-and-inclusion-efforts_5300643.html?utm_source=partner&amp;utm_campaign=BonginoReport"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.theepochtimes.com/chick-fil-a-faces-growing-backlash-over-diversity-equity-and-inclusion-efforts_5300643.html?utm_source=partner&amp;utm_campaign=BonginoReport</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>Chick-fil-A Faces Growing Backlash Over &lsquo;Diversity, Equity, and Inclusion&rsquo; Efforts</strong></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Some conservatives have suggested a boycott of Chick-fil-A after the fast-food chain was discovered to have a vice president of &ldquo;diversity, equity, [and] inclusion,&rdquo; or DEI.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">In a previously issued Chick-fil-A news release, the company said that Erick McReynolds serves as its vice president of DEI, saying: &ldquo;Chick-fil-A restaurants have long been recognized as a place where people know they will be treated well. Modeling care for others starts in the restaurant, and we are committed to ensuring mutual respect, understanding, and dignity everywhere we do business.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">DEI is a set of principles that large corporations, government agencies, and schools have increasingly incorporated into their work environments, often mandating employees receive such training. However, these principles are rooted in Marxism, according to prominent critics including Christopher Rufo and James Lindsay, that are essentially vehicles for &ldquo;left-wing racialist ideology and partisan political activism.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">&ldquo;They are designed to replace the system of academic merit with a system of race-based preferences and discrimination&mdash;which, in many cases, explicitly violates federal civil rights law,&rdquo; wrote Rufo for his Substack page earlier this year.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The Chick-fil-A announcement was highlighted this week by several prominent conservative accounts. According to McReynolds&rsquo;s LinkedIn page, he was hired as Chick-fil-A&rsquo;s vice president for &ldquo;Diversity, Equity [and] Inclusion&rdquo; in late 2021.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The chicken-based fast-food chain has been generally well respected among conservatives due to the company&rsquo;s religious values and its prior support for religious groups. In the McReynolds DEI announcement, Chick-fil-A makes reference to its corporate purpose, which is &ldquo;to glorify God by being a faithful steward of all that is entrusted to us&rdquo; and &ldquo;to have a positive influence on all who come into contact with Chick-fil-A.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">In recent weeks, a number of companies have faced backlash for embracing what critics say are left-wing values or a pro-LGBT agenda. Since early April, Bud Light has seen a significant backlash after it produced a beer can with transgender activist and influencer Dylan Mulvaney&rsquo;s face and as Mulvaney suggested a partnership with the brand.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Sales of Bud Light have dropped significantly year-over-year, with consumers opting to drink brands like Coors or Miller in its place, according to data released by industry analysts. Data published by Bump Williams Consulting and Nielsen IQ shows that by the week ending May 20, Bud Light sales declined 29.5 percent year-over-year, while revenue is down 25.7 percent.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The CEO of Anheuser-Busch has, on multiple occasions, said that Bud Light did not partner with Mulvaney, a man who identifies as a woman, and that only &ldquo;one can&rdquo; with Mulvaney&rsquo;s face was produced. Local distributors in some areas also released advertisements saying as much in a bid to lure back customers, while Bud Light has marketed several deals to move cases of beer.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Another major boycott was directed at Target after the company released a line of LGBT clothing for children&mdash;including onesies for infants&mdash;for its &ldquo;pride collection,&rdquo; according to its website. Other companies, like Kohl&rsquo;s and PetSmart, have similarly been criticized for selling similar products.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Last week, Target said in a news release that it would be moving its &ldquo;pride&rdquo; merchandise to other areas of the store. The company, meanwhile, has seen its stock drop considerably since mid-May, falling another 3.5 percentage points on Tuesday.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://www.dailywire.com/news/9-teenagers-arrested-over-brutal-assault-of-3-u-s-marines"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.dailywire.com/news/9-teenagers-arrested-over-brutal-assault-of-3-u-s-marines</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>9 Teenagers Arrested Over Brutal Assault Of 3 U.S. Marines</strong></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Sheriff&rsquo;s deputies in San Clemente, California, arrested nine teenagers over the brutal assault of three U.S. Marines last Saturday.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">San Clemente Mayor Chris Duncan announced that Orange County Sheriff&rsquo;s Department had charged the teenagers, five of whom were accused of assault with a deadly weapon and the other four with misdemeanor assault and battery.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">&ldquo;They think they have the people they are looking for,&rdquo; Duncan stated. &ldquo;Not to say that there might not be a few others out there. They feel pretty confident that they have the main perpetrators. &hellip; They had some videotape that wasn&rsquo;t readily available to the public that had a lot better images of the individuals involved.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">&ldquo;In today&rsquo;s age, you&rsquo;re going to get caught &mdash; people are going to record it,&rdquo; Duncan continued. &ldquo;I hope this serves as a learning lesson for young folks in the community not to let themselves get out of control when something like this happens.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">As many as 40 young people were involved when the three U.S. Marines near a California beach Saturday night were attacked in a horrific moment caught on now-viral video.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The Marines were enjoying time off from their service at Camp Pendleton in Oceanside at approximately 10 p.m. along the beach in San Clemente. One of the Marines, Hunter Antonino, said a piece of debris hit him in the face, prompting him to ask the group to stop lighting fireworks.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">&ldquo;They were lighting off fireworks, they were being belligerent and obnoxious and annoying other people, so I went up to them and told them to stop,&rdquo; he recalled. Antonio said the group then followed the Marines as they returned to the pier, whereupon Antonio and another Marine informed the group that they were Marines so the group would leave them alone.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Instead, the group savagely attacked the Marines. One individual punched a Marine in the back, prompting the Marine to turn and charge at him, sparking the melee. Video shows two of the Marines lying in the fetal position on the ground as the group kicked them and hurled racial epithets at them. The Marines were kicked in the head and upper body.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Although the Marines were injured, they refused to go to a hospital, according to Orange County Sheriff&rsquo;s deputies. Antonio thought he may have suffered a concussion.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/policy/healthcare/anti-abortion-protesters-beaten-baltimore-planned-parenthood"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/policy/healthcare/anti-abortion-protesters-beaten-baltimore-planned-parenthood</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>Two anti-abortion protesters beaten outside Planned Parenthood in Baltimore</strong></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Two senior citizen anti-abortion protesters were attacked outside of a Planned Parenthood clinic in North Baltimore on Friday morning, sending one to the University of Maryland Medical Center.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">&ldquo;Please pray for my dear friend, Mark Crosby,&rdquo; President of the Baltimore County Right to Life organization Jay Walton said on Facebook Friday. &ldquo;He was viciously attacked yesterday, May 26, 2023 while he was praying in front of Planned Parenthood in Baltimore City. He and another prolifer were attacked from behind and the thug ran away.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Mark Crosby and Dick Shafer have been confirmed as the victims in Friday's attack. Both men are over the age of 70, according to police reports.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">WMAR reported that surveillance video shows the suspect tackling Shafer, disturbing a large flower planter outside of the abortion facility. When Crosby came to Shafer&rsquo;s aid, the assailant shoved Crosby to the ground, and the person was seen punching and kicking him in the face.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Baltimore anti-abortion advocate John Roswell told LifeSiteNews that while Shafer is recovering well, Crosby &ldquo;is bleeding from some unidentified area behind his eye and the bone eye orbit is completely shattered.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Walton said on Monday morning that Crosby, who had been released from the hospital, had to be transported back to the emergency room due to further complications.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Roswell told LifeSiteNews that a Planned Parenthood escort, who guides abortion patients into the organization's facilities, was present at the scene and engaged with the assailant prior to the attack. In his experience, Roswell said that escorts are usually present in the rare cases that pro-abortion rights activists engage in violent altercations with anti-abortion advocates.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Investigators told local news outlets WBAL and WMAR that they are searching for the suspect.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://www.theblaze.com/news/tony-holford-us-canada-border-explosives-sign"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.theblaze.com/news/tony-holford-us-canada-border-explosives-sign</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>Police open fire on driver at US-Canada border; truck had 'sign' indicating 'explosive device on- board'</strong></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Police opened fire on a truck driver on Memorial Day as the driver aproached the U.S.-Canadian border with a sign indicating he had an explosive device on board.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The motorist, 42-year-old Tony Holford of Providence, Rhode Island, faces charges of aggravated reckless conduct, a class B crime; terrorizing, a Class D crime, and failure to stop, a class E crime, the Maine State Police Major Crimes Unit said in a press release.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">At 10:39 a.m. Monday, Maine State Police Trooper Denver Roy attempted to stop a vehicle heading north on Interstate 95 in Houlton, Maine. The driver did not stop, instead continuing north.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Trooper Roy "observed a sign indicating that the operator had an explosive device on-board," the MSP wrote. It is not clear what sort of sign was displayed.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">When the vehicle eventually stopped between the U.S. and Canadian ports of entry, troopers commanded him to get out of the vehicle.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">When the vehicle's operator reportedly maneuvered the truck toward the Canadian port of entry, Corporal Eric Paquette shot at him.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Holford, who was uninjured, surrendered to Main State Police troopers and was taken to the Aroostook County Jail after being medically cleared.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">MSP say the scene is contained and there is no ongoing danger to the public.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Authorities in Canada and the United States are collaborating on an investigation into the incident.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The Maine State Police Bomb Squad and crime scene technicians advised motorists to use alternative points of entry as they processed the scene. The Woodstock, New Brunswick, border crossing was reopened Monday night, according to a tweet posted by the Canada Border Services Agency's Atlantic Region.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The Office of the Maine Attorney General and the Maine State Police will work together "in the coming days to continue the investigation and the events that led up to the officer-involved shooting."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://justthenews.com/politics-policy/education/virginia-eliminates-degree-requirements-most-state-jobs"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://justthenews.com/politics-policy/education/virginia-eliminates-degree-requirements-most-state-jobs</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>Virginia eliminates degree requirements for most state jobs</strong></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Virginia Republican Gov. Glenn Youngkin on Tuesday announced a change in state hiring practices that would eliminate requirements or preferences that applicants for most state positions have a college degree.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">A press release from Youngkin indicated that the change will take effect on July 1 and affect roughly 90% of state positions. The Old Dominion's myriad agencies post as many as 20,000 job listings per year.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">"On day one we went to work reimagining workforce solutions in government and this key reform will expand opportunities for qualified applicants who are ready to serve Virginians," Youngkin said in a statement.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">State Secretary of Labor Bryan Slater further, in the same release, indicated that the state was looking into heavily regulated private industries to streamline the professional certification processes.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The move comes as American high school graduates increasingly opt against pursuing college degrees to due affordability and return on investment concerns.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">President Joe Biden has moved to lessen the financial burden of incurring debt to pay for college by offering up to $10,000 in repayment relief for most loan recipients and up to $20,000 for those who received a Pell Grant, though that plan has faced legal scrutiny and may well end up permanently blocked by the judiciary. The proposed deal to raise the debt limit facing Congress includes a measure to end a temporary freeze on student loan repayments.</span></p>]]></description>
   <author><![CDATA[Garrison Hardie]]></author>
   <enclosure url="https://app.dropwave.io/episode/9362c7c6-17ba-4d6e-b65f-db49b0702a14/daily-news-brief-for-thursday-june-1st-2023.mp3" length="687" type="audio/mp3"/>
   <guid isPermaLink="false"><![CDATA[9362c7c6-17ba-4d6e-b65f-db49b0702a14]]></guid>
   <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
   <source url=""><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></source>
   <itunes:author><![CDATA[Garrison Hardie]]></itunes:author>
   <itunes:image href="https://assets-cdn2.dropwave.io/2ab40ac0-e99d-4f25-a6d2-541d2c9b290a/cover-art/hUZu1H9lrRY0wXg66WHC8eLwYBA3hbRNTAHQmHt2.png"/>
   <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
   <itunes:duration>687</itunes:duration>
   <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
  
  </item><item>
   <title><![CDATA[Daily News Brief for Wednesday, May 31st, 2023 [Daily News Brief]]]></title>
   <link>https://app.dropwave.io/episode/d3dd0c7c-0e15-4226-bbf7-a7ee772f1207/daily-news-brief-for-wednesday-may-31st-2023.mp3</link>
   <description><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">This is Garrison Hardie with your CrossPolitic Daily News Brief for Wednesday, May 31st, 2023.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://www.christiantoday.com/article/archbishop.distressed.by.attacks.on.christians.in.india/140278.htm"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.christiantoday.com/article/archbishop.distressed.by.attacks.on.christians.in.india/140278.htm</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>Archbishop 'distressed' by attacks on Christians in India</strong></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The Archbishop of Canterbury has lamented violent attacks on indigenous tribal Christians in north-eastern India.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Archbishop Justin Welby said he was "distressed" by the reports of violence coming out of Manipur state in recent weeks.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Writing on Twitter, the Archbishop said he was praying that "justice and peace would prevail" in the region.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The violence, carried out by Hindu nationalists, has killed dozens and displaced around 10,000 people, mostly Christians.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Many churches and buildings belonging to Christians have also been destroyed.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The Archbishop said he was praying "that regional authorities would protect all minority groups, including Christians and their places of worship, and that justice and peace would prevail".&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Open Doors last week shared reports from Christian partners on the ground fear that the violence will lead to a civil war.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">They have expressed disappointment at what they see as a lack of action by the Indian government and local authorities to quell the violence.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">According to Open Doors, at least 300 churches have been burned or demolished and 1,000 Christian homes have been destroyed in Manipur in the last few weeks.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The NGO is providing support to Christians caught up in the violence but has warned that conditions are "grim", and many are still fearing for their lives.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">"If the situation continues civil war is inevitable," said an Open Doors partner who cannot be named for security reasons.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">"If there is a civil war the situation will only become more gruesome, more lives lost, properties destroyed and further open persecution of religious minorities."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://taskandpurpose.com/news/taliban-humvee-m240-iran-fight/"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://taskandpurpose.com/news/taliban-humvee-m240-iran-fight/</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>The Taliban is using leftover American gear to fight a border skirmish with Iran</strong></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">A gunfight broke out between Iranian border guards and Taliban fighters along the border between Iran and Afghanistan this weekend. Fighting killed three people in the biggest escalation between the two countries over water. And the Taliban brought out a big gun to help.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Video posted to social media offered an up-close view of the skirmish, inside an unexpected place: an Humvee kitted out with an M240 machine gun. If that looks familiar it&rsquo;s because those are some of the pieces of military equipment captured by the Taliban, now put into use for fighting other parties.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Other accounts shared online reported heavy machine gun fire, as well as purported use of mortars and other explosives. Outside of the Humvee, Taliban fighters were spotted using AK-style rifles and RPGs to attack the Iranian position on the border.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">At least three people are confirmed to have died in Saturday&rsquo;s gunfight, although accounts vary on how many belonged to each side. The Taliban claimed at least one of its fighters was killed, while an Iranian paper said all deaths were on Iran&rsquo;s side, per al-Jazeera. The fighting took place in the Nimroz province of Afghanistan. As a result, the border crossing between Milak and Zaranj in Iran and Afghanistan, respectively, closed (it was not where the fighting took place). Both nations accused the other of starting the gunfight.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The fighting between the two nations broke out amid political fights over water rights. Drought has been a serious issue in Afghanistan for the last three years. The Helmand River flows from Afghanistan into Iran and is dammed on the Afghan side. Earlier in May, Iranian President Ebrahim Raisi called on the Taliban not to restrict the flow of water.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">More than a year since the Taliban took control of Afghanistan, the group is using all kinds of seized American and NATO weapons.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">It&rsquo;s not a new development. The Taliban regularly used captured American-provided equipment when fighting the U.S.-backed government. In the later years of the war, special Taliban units were spotted wearing American-style driving Humvees and even wielding weapons belonging to special operations units. During the fall of Kabul in 2021, Los Angeles Times reporter Nabih Bulos captured footage of Taliban fighters in the city dressed like special operations forces.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">When the U.S.-backed government fell and the Afghan security forces collapsed, the Taliban got its hand on a lot of leftover weapons and equipment. A 2022 report from the Pentagon&rsquo;s lead inspector general for Operation Enduring Sentinel and Operation Freedom&rsquo;s Sentinel found that approximately $7.12 billion in equipment was still in the country when the Taliban took over. That included everything from rifles to aircraft.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://www.newsmax.com/world/globaltalk/africa-uganda-gay-rights/2023/05/29/id/1121533/"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.newsmax.com/world/globaltalk/africa-uganda-gay-rights/2023/05/29/id/1121533/</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>Uganda Signs Anti-gay Law With Death Penalty for 'Aggravated Homosexuality'</strong></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Uganda's president has signed into law tough new anti-gay legislation supported by many in this East African country but widely condemned by rights activists and others abroad.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The version of the bill signed by President Yoweri Museveni does not criminalize those who identify as LGBTQ, a key concern for campaigners who condemned an earlier draft of the legislation as an egregious attack on human rights.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">But the new law still prescribes the death penalty for "aggravated homosexuality," which is defined as cases of sexual relations involving people infected with HIV as well as with minors and other categories of vulnerable people.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">A suspect convicted of "attempted aggravated homosexuality" can be imprisoned for up to 14 years, according to the legislation.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Parliamentary Speaker Anita Among said in a statement the president had "answered the cries of our people" in signing the bill.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">"With a lot of humility, I thank my colleagues the Members of Parliament for withstanding all the pressure from bullies and doomsday conspiracy theorists in the interest of our country," the statement said.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Museveni had returned the bill to the national assembly in April, asking for changes that would differentiate between identifying as LGBTQ and actually engaging in homosexual acts. That angered some lawmakers, including some who feared the president would proceed to veto the bill amid international pressure. Lawmakers passed an amended version of the bill earlier in May.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Homosexuality was already illegal in Uganda under a colonial-era law criminalizing sexual activity "against the order of nature." The punishment for that offense is life imprisonment.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The U.S. has warned of economic consequences over legislation described by Amnesty International as "draconian and overly broad."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The leaders of the U.N. AIDS program, the U.S. President's Emergency Plan for AIDS Relief and the Global Fund in a joint statement Monday said they "are deeply concerned about the harmful impact" of the legislation on public health and the HIV response.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">"Uganda's progress on its HIV response is now in grave jeopardy," the statement said. "The Anti-Homosexuality Act 2023 will obstruct health education and the outreach that can help end AIDS as a public health threat."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">That statement noted that "stigma and discrimination associated with the passage of the Act has already led to reduced access to prevention as well as treatment services" for LGBTQ people.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Anti-gay sentiment in Uganda has grown in recent weeks amid news coverage alleging sodomy in boarding schools, including a prestigious one for boys where a parent accused a teacher of abusing her son.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The February decision of the Church of England 's national assembly to continue banning church weddings for same-sex couples while allowing priests to bless same-sex marriages and civil partnerships inflamed many in Uganda and elsewhere in Africa.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Homosexuality is criminalized in more than 30 of Africa's 54 countries. Some Africans see it as behavior imported from abroad and not a sexual orientation.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://www.foxnews.com/politics/house-oversight-committee-taking-steps-to-hold-fbi-director-wray-in-contempt-of-congress-over-biden-document"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.foxnews.com/politics/house-oversight-committee-taking-steps-to-hold-fbi-director-wray-in-contempt-of-congress-over-biden-document</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>Republicans to hold FBI Director Wray in contempt of Congress over Biden document</strong></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">House Oversight Committee Chairman James Comer is taking steps to hold FBI Director Christopher Wray in contempt of Congress after the Bureau notified the panel it will not comply with its subpoena related to a possible criminal scheme involving then-Vice President Joe Biden.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The FBI, though, said Tuesday evening it remains committed to cooperating with Congress, and will provide access to the document "in a format and setting that maintains confidentiality and protects important security interests and the integrity of FBI investigations."&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Comer, R-Ky., has subpoenaed the FBI for a document that allegedly describes a criminal scheme involving Biden and a foreign national and relating to the exchange of money for policy decisions. The document is an FBI-generated FD-1023 form.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Comer first subpoenaed the document earlier this month. The FBI did not turn it over and instead explained that it needed to protect the Bureau's confidential human source program.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Comer set another deadline last week, giving Wray until Tuesday, May 30, to turn over the document. After the deadline was set, Wray set up a call with Comer for Wednesday, May 31.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">However, the FBI notified the panel it would not provide the document to the committee by the Tuesday afternoon deadline.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">He added, "Americans deserve the truth, and the Oversight Committee will continue to demand transparency from this nation&rsquo;s chief law enforcement agency."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">In response, the FBI told Fox News Digital that the bureau "remains committed to cooperating with the Committee in good faith."</span></p>]]></description>
   <author><![CDATA[Garrison Hardie]]></author>
   <enclosure url="https://app.dropwave.io/episode/d3dd0c7c-0e15-4226-bbf7-a7ee772f1207/daily-news-brief-for-wednesday-may-31st-2023.mp3" length="578" type="audio/mp3"/>
   <guid isPermaLink="false"><![CDATA[d3dd0c7c-0e15-4226-bbf7-a7ee772f1207]]></guid>
   <pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
   <source url=""><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></source>
   <itunes:author><![CDATA[Garrison Hardie]]></itunes:author>
   <itunes:image href="https://assets-cdn2.dropwave.io/2ab40ac0-e99d-4f25-a6d2-541d2c9b290a/cover-art/hUZu1H9lrRY0wXg66WHC8eLwYBA3hbRNTAHQmHt2.png"/>
   <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
   <itunes:duration>578</itunes:duration>
   <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
  
  </item><item>
   <title><![CDATA[Daily News Brief for Tuesday, May 30th, 2023 [Daily News Brief]]]></title>
   <link>https://app.dropwave.io/episode/94afbd19-7c7b-4f4d-abaf-2081b62eb8b5/daily-news-brief-for-tuesday-may-30th-2023.mp3</link>
   <description><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">This is Garrison Hardie with your CrossPolitic Daily News Brief for Tuesday, May 30th, 2023.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>Fight Laugh Feast Conference - Ark Encounter</strong></span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">This year, our Fight Laugh Feast Conference is at the Ark Encounter in Kentucky on The Politics of Six Day Creation. The politics of six day creation is the difference between a fixed standard of justice and a careening standard of justice, the difference between the corrosive relativism that creates mobs and anarchy and the freedom of objectivity, truth, and due process. The politics of six day creation establishes the authority and sufficiency of God&rsquo;s Word for all of life: from what is a man or a woman, when does human life begin, and how is human society best organized?</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Come hear Ken Ham, Pastor Doug Wilson, Dr. Ben Merkle, Dr. Gordon Wilson, me and more, and of course a live CrossPolitic show! Mark your calendars for October 11th-14th, as we fight, laugh, and feast, with beer &amp; psalms, our amazing lineup of speakers, our Rowdy Christian Merch, and a Sabbath Feast to wrap up the occasion. Maybe an infant baptism while we&rsquo;re at it! Visit fightlaughfeast.com for more information!</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://nypost.com/2023/05/28/mccarthys-debt-ceiling-deal-with-biden-comes-up-short-on-vow-to-reign-in-irs/"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://nypost.com/2023/05/28/mccarthys-debt-ceiling-deal-with-biden-comes-up-short-on-vow-to-reign-in-irs/</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>McCarthy&rsquo;s debt-ceiling deal with Biden comes up short on his vow to rein in IRS</strong></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">It struck a chord with voters, wary of funding a new &ldquo;army&rdquo; of armed IRS agents to harass middle-class families and small business owners and abuse their powers to target political dissidents, Soviet-style.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">&ldquo;Our very first bill will repeal the funding for 87,000 new IRS agents,&rdquo; McCarthy vowed.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">&ldquo;You see, we believe government should be to help you, not go after you.&rdquo;&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Sure enough, the House voted 221-210 to repeal the extra IRS funding.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">&ldquo;Promises made,&rdquo; the newly minted speaker said Jan. 9, banging the gavel on the first bill of the Republican-controlled House.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">What about promises kept?&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">In the debt-ceiling deal outlined Sunday and due to be inked later this week, McCarthy has allowed the lion&rsquo;s share of that extra IRS funding to remain unmolested: preserving $78.1 billion of the $80 billion.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">As rebel GOP Rep Dan Bishop put it: &ldquo;So there will be 85,260 more IRS agents rather than 87,000 to eat you alive. Big win.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Overpromising and underdelivering is what turns voters off the GOP.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">You don&rsquo;t mount a powerful six-month fear campaign about 87,000 new, armed IRS agents ready to break down people&rsquo;s doors, and then meekly capitulate at the first sign of resistance.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Even if those fears were exaggerated, your credibility rests on delivering a lot more than 2% of what you promised.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">In any case the fears about a weaponized IRS targeting Biden&rsquo;s opponents are very real.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">If anything, the IRS is worse today than it was during the Obama administration, when Lois Lerner presided over the targeted harassment of Tea Party groups and other conservatives.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Not a single IRS employee was held accountable for the scandal. Lerner retired on a full pension without even a slap on the wrist.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">This is the same IRS which went after journalist Matt Taibbi last December, three weeks after he started reporting on the so-called &ldquo;Twitter Files,&rdquo; which revealed that censorship on the social-media platform had been coordinated by federal government agencies such as the FBI and CIA.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">On March 9, when Taibbi was testifying in Congress about, ironically enough, the weaponization of the federal government, IRS agents showed up unannounced at his New Jersey home.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The IRS file on Taibbi was opened the day he posted his ninth and most explosive Twitter file, detailing how agencies including the Pentagon and the State Department had colluded with Twitter to stifle dissent.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">It was Christmas Eve, a Saturday, which shows what an unusual priority it was for an agency that normally goes to sleep for two weeks over Christmas and whose standard work week is Monday through Friday.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Under questioning from Judiciary Committee Chairman Jim Jordan, the IRS has claimed it had concerns about &ldquo;identity fraud&rdquo; with Taibbi&rsquo;s 2018 and 2021 tax returns, and that he was sent two letters before the home visit. Yet Taibbi says he and his accountant never received any letters.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Even more &ldquo;unnerving&rdquo; as Taibbi puts it, was the fact that an IRS case agent had compiled a dossier on him which included personal information such as his voter registration records and whether he had a concealed-weapons permit or a hunting or fishing license.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Unlike Hunter Biden, Taibbi didn&rsquo;t owe the IRS any taxes and in fact was due a refund.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">And yes, this is the same IRS which removed its entire investigative team from the Hunter Biden case on DOJ orders after two senior agents complained about DOJ interference.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://thepostmillennial.com/blm-co-founder-loses-multi-platform-warner-brothers-deal-after-delivering-no-content-on-contract?utm_campaign=64487"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://thepostmillennial.com/blm-co-founder-loses-multi-platform-warner-brothers-deal-after-delivering-no-content-on-contract?utm_campaign=64487</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>BLM co-founder loses multi-platform Warner Brothers deal after delivering no content on contract</strong></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">In October 2020, 39-year-old Black Lives Matter co-founder and former leader Patrisse Cullors signed a multi-year contract with Warner Bros Television Group to create content for the entertainment giant, but the studio quietly ended then relationship last year with no material produced, reports the New York Post.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">On Friday, a source familiar with the situation told the outlet, "The studio signed an overall deal with BLM co-founder Patrisse Cullors at some point in 2020" but the "Deal expired at end of October 2022."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">"The deal unfortunately did not result in any produced shows," the source added.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The agreement was a multi-year, multi-platform deal in which Cullors would produce original material, including scripted comedies and dramas, animated shows, and documentary series, that would focus on black stories. The content would go out on the distributor's broadcast, cable, and streaming platforms.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Variety first reported on the deal in 2020 but did not disclose its value.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Previously, Cullors said in an interview that she was working on material for Warner Bros, including documentaries focused on reparations and social mobility of black Americans as well as a scripted program on marijuana.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Patrisse Cullors, who helped found BLM in 2013, stepped down from the organization after a real-estate scandal emerged in May 2021 when it was revealed she spent $3.2 million on four different homes in Georgia and California. Soon after more reports started to emerge of Black Lives Matter leadership using company funds for personal luxury.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Upon stepping down, Cullors claimed she was doing so in order to focus on her book and TV deal.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">In April 2022, Cullors said that 990 tax forms required for charities were "triggering" and that the forms were being "weaponized" against organizations like hers.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The IRS 990 is a routine document charities must fill out annually to disclose their financial activities.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Now this!!!</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://www.theepochtimes.com/eu-issues-waring-after-elon-musk-pulls-twitter-out-of-anti-disinformation-agreement_5296657.html?utm_source=partner&amp;utm_campaign=BonginoReport"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.theepochtimes.com/eu-issues-waring-after-elon-musk-pulls-twitter-out-of-anti-disinformation-agreement_5296657.html?utm_source=partner&amp;utm_campaign=BonginoReport</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>EU Issues Warning After Elon Musk Pulls Twitter Out of Anti-&lsquo;Disinformation&rsquo; Agreement</strong></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Senior European Union officials were furious over the weekend after Twitter owner Elon Musk pulled the social media platform out of the bloc&rsquo;s &ldquo;Code of Practice,&rdquo; which critics say is tantamount to a censorship regime.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The EU&rsquo;s internal market commissioner, Thierry Breton, wrote that Twitter left the bloc&rsquo;s Code of Practice, after reports claimed the platform would do so. Breton warned that Twitter would face some legal liabilities.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">&ldquo;Twitter leaves EU voluntary Code of Practice against disinformation. But obligations remain. You can run, but you can&rsquo;t hide,&rdquo; Breton wrote. &ldquo;Beyond voluntary commitments, fighting disinformation will be legal obligation under #DSA as of August 25. Our teams will be ready for enforcement.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">An EU official also told Euractiv that the bloc is &ldquo;waiting for this,&rdquo; and &ldquo;it was purely a matter of time&rdquo; before reports surfaced that Musk would withdraw.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The rules known as the Digital Services Act (DSA) require companies to do risk management, conduct external and independent auditing, share data with authorities and researchers, and adopt a code of conduct by August.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The 19 companies that are subject to the rules include Alphabet&rsquo;s Google Maps, Google Play, Google Search, Google Shopping, YouTube, Meta&rsquo;s Facebook and Instagram, Amazon&rsquo;s Marketplace, Apple&rsquo;s App Store, and Twitter. The others are Microsoft&rsquo;s two units LinkedIn and Bing, booking.com, Pinterest, Snap Inc&rsquo;s Snapchat, TikTok, Wikipedia, Zalando, and Alibaba&rsquo;s AliExpress.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Breton said he was checking to see whether another four to five companies fall under the DSA, with a decision expected in the next few weeks. Breton singled out Facebook&rsquo;s content moderation system for criticism because of its role in building opinions on key issues.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Twitter had agreed earlier to a stress test, and Breton said he and his team would travel to the company&rsquo;s headquarters in San Francisco at the end of June of this year to carry out the voluntary mock exercise. Breton didn&rsquo;t detail what the test would entail.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">There are guardrails for content generated by artificial intelligence, like deep fake videos and synthetic images, which will have to be clearly labeled when they come up in search results, Breton said. He&rsquo;s also said that under the Digital Services Act, violations could be punished with hefty fines of up to 6 percent of a company&rsquo;s annual revenue.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Platforms will have to &ldquo;completely redesign&rdquo; their systems to ensure a high level of privacy and safety for children, including verifying users&rsquo; ages, Breton said.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Big Tech companies also will have to revamp their systems to &ldquo;prevent algorithmic amplification of disinformation,&rdquo; he said, saying he was particularly concerned about Facebook&rsquo;s content moderation systems ahead of September elections in Slovakia.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Now for my favorite topic&hellip; sports!</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://www.foxnews.com/sports/actor-will-ferrell-to-portray-nfl-legend-john-madden-in-upcoming-feature-film-report"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.foxnews.com/sports/actor-will-ferrell-to-portray-nfl-legend-john-madden-in-upcoming-feature-film-report</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>Actor Will Ferrell to portray NFL legend John Madden in upcoming feature film</strong></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Actor and comedian Will Ferrell will play the lead role of an upcoming film about NFL icon John Madden, according a report from Deadline.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The movie "Madden" will be directed by five-time Oscar nominee David O. Russell, who previously served as director of the critically acclaimed film "Silver Linings Playbook," among others.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The film is expected to touch on Madden's time as head coach of the Raiders, his television broadcasting career and how he became the creative force behind one of the most popular video game franchises of all-time.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">This project is independent of a separate limited series about Madden's life, with Tom Brady as executive producer, Deadline previously reported.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">It remains unclear when filming on "Madden" will begin. An official release date for the film has not been announced.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">New York Giants co-owner Steve Tisch is listed as one of the "Madden" producers. It is widely expected the NFL "will embrace the feature film on one of the sport's most beloved figures," according to Deadline.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Ferrell is a California native and attended the University of Southern California, where he studied sports information.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">He makes frequent appearances at USC Trojans football games and is a diehard Los Angeles Kings fan.</span></p>]]></description>
   <author><![CDATA[Garrison Hardie]]></author>
   <enclosure url="https://app.dropwave.io/episode/94afbd19-7c7b-4f4d-abaf-2081b62eb8b5/daily-news-brief-for-tuesday-may-30th-2023.mp3" length="677" type="audio/mp3"/>
   <guid isPermaLink="false"><![CDATA[94afbd19-7c7b-4f4d-abaf-2081b62eb8b5]]></guid>
   <pubDate>Tue, 30 May 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
   <source url=""><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></source>
   <itunes:author><![CDATA[Garrison Hardie]]></itunes:author>
   <itunes:image href="https://assets-cdn2.dropwave.io/2ab40ac0-e99d-4f25-a6d2-541d2c9b290a/cover-art/hUZu1H9lrRY0wXg66WHC8eLwYBA3hbRNTAHQmHt2.png"/>
   <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
   <itunes:duration>677</itunes:duration>
   <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
  
  </item><item>
   <title><![CDATA[Daily News Brief for Friday, May 26th, 2023 [Daily News Brief]]]></title>
   <link>https://app.dropwave.io/episode/57c33252-d98b-47a4-8902-e0602e35a1ea/daily-news-brief-for-friday-may-26th-2023.mp3</link>
   <description><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">This is Garrison Hardie with your CrossPolitic Daily News Brief for Friday, May 26th, 2023.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://www.dailywire.com/news/college-enrollment-keeps-sliding-even-three-years-after-lockdowns"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.dailywire.com/news/college-enrollment-keeps-sliding-even-three-years-after-lockdowns</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>College Enrollment Keeps Sliding Even Three Years After Lockdowns</strong></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Enrollment for most forms of postsecondary education in the United States continued to decline three years after nationwide lockdowns forced many students to temporarily continue their degrees online, according to a new analysis from the National Student Clearinghouse.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Public four-year institutions saw a 0.8% enrollment decline as of spring 2023, a somewhat less severe decrease than the 1.2% decline recorded in 2022 but more pronounced than the 0.3% decline in 2021 and the 0.2% decline in 2020. Private four-year nonprofit institutions meanwhile witnessed a 1.0% decrease in 2023, compared to the 1.2% decrease in 2022, the 0.4% decrease in 2021, and the 0.6% decrease in 2020.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">There are currently 7.1 million students enrolled in public four-year colleges and 3.9 million students enrolled in private four-year nonprofit colleges, marking drops from 7.3 million and 4.0 million enrolled students, respectively, from spring 2019, the last year which was not affected by the lockdowns.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">&ldquo;Undergraduates at public and private nonprofit four-year institutions are still declining but at slower rates,&rdquo; the analysis from the National Student Clearinghouse summarized. &ldquo;Total postsecondary enrollment remains well below pre-pandemic levels.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Community college enrollment nevertheless increased 0.5% as of spring 2023, a phenomenon driven by &ldquo;dual enrolled high school students and freshmen,&rdquo; while the number of students pursuing graduate or professional degrees plummeted 2.2% from last year.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The postsecondary education marketplace has been critically disrupted by the lockdowns and the advent of virtual instruction, realities which increasingly prompted students to question the time and funds they devote toward their college degrees.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Elevated levels of student debt, which officials in the Biden administration are seeking to address through an executive order to cancel $10,000 in loans for every borrower earning less than $125,000, have also prompted many students to pause or discontinue their education. The debt forgiveness policy was recently examined by the Supreme Court, which is expected to release an opinion on the controversial move within the next month.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Lockdowns also severely diminished learning outcomes at the primary and secondary levels. The most recent National Assessment of Educational Progress showed that average reading scores for nine-year-olds plummeted five points and average mathematics scores dropped seven points, marking the first score decline for reading in three decades and the first score decline for mathematics in the history of the initiative. Stanford University economist and Hoover Institution senior fellow Eric Hanushek revealed in a recent study that learning losses could cause affected students to lose between 2% and 9% of their lifetime earnings as they miss the opportunity to learn critical skills, reducing prospects for future nationwide economic growth.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Parents concerned about the impact of lockdowns on education have removed their children from government schools at an unprecedented rate. The number of homeschooled students increased from 2.7 million in 2020 to 3.1 million in 2023, according to a study from the National Home Education Research Institute.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>New Saint Andrews:</strong></span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Today&rsquo;s culture shifts like sand, but New Saint Andrews College is established on Christ, the immovable rock. The college is a premier institution that forges evangelical leaders who don&rsquo;t fear or hate the world. Guided by God&rsquo;s word, equipped with the genius of classical liberal arts and God-honoring wisdom, with a faculty dedicated to academic rigor and to God&rsquo;s kingdom, New Saint Andrews College offers an education that frees people.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Logic and language, hard work and joyful courage, old books and godly professors &mdash; New Saint Andrews Colleges provides time-tested resources that can equip your student for any vocation. To find out more, visit: nsa.edu</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://www.theblaze.com/news/member-group-of-coalition-pushing-extreme-abortion-initiative-in-ohio-fighting-to-undercut-parental-rights"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.theblaze.com/news/member-group-of-coalition-pushing-extreme-abortion-initiative-in-ohio-fighting-to-undercut-parental-rights</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>Coalition pushing extreme abortion initiative in Ohio says it isn't trying to undermine parental rights. A member group's explicit agenda suggests otherwise.</strong></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">A leftist coalition is working to roll back Ohio's few remaining abortion restrictions by way of a proposed constitutional amendment.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Some opposition groups have suggested that this craftily worded proposal will not only enable late-term abortions, but undermine parental rights on these and other matters of life and death, including the ability to protect children from sex-change mutilations.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">While proponents of member groups in the coalition have claimed the amendment will not undermine parental rights, recently highlighted remarks made by a key player behind the abortion initiative have done little to inspire confidence.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Ohio Physicians for Reproductive Rights and Ohioans for Reproductive Freedom PAC are leading the charge to enshrine abortion rights in the state constitution by way of an initiated constitutional amendment called the "Ohio Right to Make Reproductive Decisions Including Abortion Initiative."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The proposal to put this abortion initiative on the November 2023 ballot was certified in March by the state attorney general.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The proposed amendment further states that the "state shall not, directly or indirectly, burden, penalize, prohibit, interfere with, or discriminate against either: 1. An individual's voluntary exercise of this right or 2. A person or entity that assists an individual exercising this right, unless the State demonstrates that it is using the least restrictive means to advance the individual's health in accordance with widely accepted and evidence-based standards of care."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The only ostensible restriction on abortion admitted in the amendment leaves determinations as to whether a viable human being can be exterminated up to abortionists.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Parental rights are implicated and eroded under the amendment, argued the pro-life activists, because "'reproductive decisions' is a very broad term, and is intentionally included to stop any effort to put reasonable restrictions or enforce parental rights on a wide array of other destructive decisions&mdash;potentially including sex change surgeries."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Carrie Severino and Frank Scaturro of the Judicial Crisis Network concurred, noting in National Review that "'reproductive decisions' ... is a very broad term. By explicitly defining such decisions as 'not limited to' the enumerated categories, the proposal establishes its scope as sweeping. A natural reading would extend to any medical procedure that involves the human reproductive system, including sex-change surgery."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Extra to potentially affecting parents' ability to protect their children from sex-change mutilations and devastating puberty blockers, Dannenfelser and Sekulow highlighted how "if Ohio adopts the amendment, the state's supreme court can be expected to go even farther than the U.S. Supreme Court ever did in undoing the state's parental consent laws," in part by "outlawing any legal requirement for a parent to be notified about or consent before an abortion&mdash;or any other procedure related to 'reproduction decisions'&mdash;is performed on their child."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://twitter.com/i/status/1636019433578672130"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://twitter.com/i/status/1636019433578672130</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> - Play Video</span></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://www.military.com/daily-news/2023/05/23/va-cant-account-187-million-emergency-covid-19-funding.html"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.military.com/daily-news/2023/05/23/va-cant-account-187-million-emergency-covid-19-funding.html</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>VA Can't Account for $187 Million in Emergency COVID-19 Funding</strong></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The Department of Veterans Affairs can&rsquo;t account for at least $187 million in supplementary COVID-19 funding spread across more than 10,000 transactions related to the pandemic, according to a House oversight committee.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Congress and the VA are at odds over the department's handling of nearly $37 billion in additional funding it received to address the COVID-19 pandemic, with House Veterans Affairs Committee leaders on both sides of the aisle critical of its failure to account for every dime.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Chairman Mike Bost, R-Ill., and ranking member Rep. Mark Takano, D-Calif., praised the department for its pandemic response overall but called the VA out for its inability to account for the money, during a hearing sidetracked by GOP rancor over the department's messaging on debt ceiling legislation.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Between 2020 and 2021, the VA received roughly $37 billion to address COVID-19 response, including an initial $60 million, followed by $19.6 billion in the Coronavirus Aid, Relief, and Economic Security Act and another $17 billion in the American Rescue Plan.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">As part of the deal to receive the funding, the department was required to account for its spending, a mandate underscored by passage in November 2021 of the VA Transparency and Trust Act.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Across a series of 40 reviews and reports, the VA Office of Inspector General found numerous accounting issues involving the COVID-19 funds, including a lack of visibility over payroll, some contracts and medical supplies.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The IG said the problems are attributable to the department's decentralized management structure, as well as an outdated financial information technology software &ndash; that it doesn't expect to modernize for another decade.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">It determined that the department was challenged by inaccurate payroll accounting; used manual transfers and adjustments to its financial management systems that led to at least 53 reporting errors; had problems with supply acquisition, such as duplicate purchases; and failed to properly oversee its efforts to provide telehealth hardware to veterans, namely distributing tablet computers and cell phones so they could access health care but not recouping the equipment when the veteran failed to use it.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Given the issues, both Bost and Takano said they have concerns for the $2.1 billion remaining in American Rescue Plan funds, with Bost and fellow Republicans saying the money should be returned, while Takano pressed the VA to be more transparent as it continues using the funding.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">VA officials told the committee Tuesday that the department will spend the remaining American Rescue Plan money by the end of the fiscal year for programs initiated during the pandemic such as housing and telehealth for homeless veterans; prosthetics and medical research, including studies of long COVID; and on preventing the spread of contagious diseases in hospital and administrative settings.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://www.outkick.com/matt-araiza-jets-workout-allegations-cleared-up/"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.outkick.com/matt-araiza-jets-workout-allegations-cleared-up/</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>NEW YORK JETS WORKING OUT MATT ARAIZA TWO WEEKS AFTER PUNTER&rsquo;S NAME WAS CLEARED OF GANG RAPE ALLEGATIONS</strong></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Matt Araiza has landed his first workout with an NFL team since being cut by the Buffalo Bills ahead of last season over gang rape allegations. The New York Jets are giving the free-agent punter a look, according to Adam Schefter.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Matt Araiza was cut by the Bills in August 2022 shortly after an allegation was made public that he had taken part in the gang rape of a minor while attending San Diego State.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Fast-forward nine months to May of this year, and it has been determined that he was not present at the time of the incident that allegedly took place in October 2021.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The transcript of a meeting between the accuser and prosecutors was brought to light just over two weeks ago in which investigators explained that they do not believe Araiza was present at the time of the alleged assault.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Prosecutors in the San Diego District Attorney&rsquo;s Office declined to file criminal charges, but Araiza is still facing a civil suit that he has no plans of settling anytime soon.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Despite that there wasn&rsquo;t a single fact was known about the alleged incident, the Bills caved to the portion of the public who had already deemed the punter guilty and cut him shortly before the start of the 2022 NFL regular season.</span></p>]]></description>
   <author><![CDATA[Garrison Hardie]]></author>
   <enclosure url="https://app.dropwave.io/episode/57c33252-d98b-47a4-8902-e0602e35a1ea/daily-news-brief-for-friday-may-26th-2023.mp3" length="738" type="audio/mp3"/>
   <guid isPermaLink="false"><![CDATA[57c33252-d98b-47a4-8902-e0602e35a1ea]]></guid>
   <pubDate>Fri, 26 May 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
   <source url=""><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></source>
   <itunes:author><![CDATA[Garrison Hardie]]></itunes:author>
   <itunes:image href="https://assets-cdn2.dropwave.io/2ab40ac0-e99d-4f25-a6d2-541d2c9b290a/cover-art/hUZu1H9lrRY0wXg66WHC8eLwYBA3hbRNTAHQmHt2.png"/>
   <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
   <itunes:duration>738</itunes:duration>
   <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
  
  </item><item>
   <title><![CDATA[Daily News Brief for Wednesday, May 24th, 2023 [Daily News Brief]]]></title>
   <link>https://app.dropwave.io/episode/3bff24f1-e7d1-4e75-9545-7e5687844fd5/daily-news-brief-for-wednesday-may-24th-2023.mp3</link>
   <description><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">This is Garrison Hardie with your CrossPolitic Daily News Brief for Wednesday, May 24th, 2023.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://www.zerohedge.com/covid-19/who-warns-unusual-surge-severe-myocarditis-babies"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.zerohedge.com/covid-19/who-warns-unusual-surge-severe-myocarditis-babies</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>WHO Warns Of 'Unusual' Surge in Severe Myocarditis in Babies</strong></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">On Tuesday, the WHO issued an alert that there had been a rise in &ldquo;severe myocarditis&rdquo; in newborns and infants between June 2022 and March 2023 in Wales and England.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">It said that this was associated with the enterovirus infection, which rarely affects the heart.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">A UK Health Security Agency (UKHSA) spokesperson confirmed to The Epoch Times that 10 babies have been diagnosed in Wales and five have been diagnosed in England.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The WHO said that &ldquo;although enterovirus infections are common in neonates and young infants, the reported increase in myocarditis with severe outcomes in neonates and infants associated with enterovirus infection is unusual.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">It said that in the same hospital (covering the South Wales region) over the previous six years, &ldquo;only one other similar case has been identified.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">WHO assessed the public health risk as low, but added that in certain situations, it &ldquo;may be advisable to close child-care facilities and schools to reduce the intensity of transmission.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">However, the WHO took down the alert on Wednesday. The Epoch Times understands that this could be because some of the numbers were not correct.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The WHO did not respond to The Epoch Times&rsquo; request for comment.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Dr. Shamez Ladhani, Consultant Paediatrician at UKHSA, told The Epoch Times by email that &ldquo;given a higher than average number of cases in Wales in the autumn/winter months in very young babies, UKHSA is investigating the situation in England to see if any similar cases have been observed here and whether there are any factors driving the increase in cases.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The UKHSA did not respond to questions about ruling out any links to the effects of the COVID-19 vaccine.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Public Health Wales at the start of May announced that it was investigating a cluster of severe enterovirus infections with myocarditis occurring in very young babies from the South Wales region.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The cases occurred from June 2022 with a peak in November 2022 involving babies under 28 days old.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Ten babies have developed myocarditis within this cluster. One baby remains in hospital, eight are being managed as outpatients, and one baby has died.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Consultant pathologist and HART member Dr. Clare Craig told The Epoch Times that there&rsquo;s &ldquo;a massive question about whether or not these babies or the mums are vaccinated.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">HART is an organisation that was set up to share concerns about policy and guidance recommendations relating to the COVID-19 pandemic.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/restoring-america/community-family/nebraska-governor-signs-ban-abortion-and-child-transitions"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/restoring-america/community-family/nebraska-governor-signs-ban-abortion-and-child-transitions</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>Nebraska governor signs ban on abortion and child transitions</strong></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Nebraska became the latest state to enact bans on abortion and child gender transitions as Gov. Jim Pillen (R-NE) signed a dual measure Monday afternoon.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Nebraska 's legislature passed the measure Friday, which will prohibit abortion at 12 weeks of pregnancy and ban genital and nongenital mutilation surgeries on children. The bill also gives the state's chief medical officer, Dr. Timothy Tesmer, the authority to determine restrictions on puberty blockers and cross-sex hormones.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Pillen called child gender transitions "Lucifer at its finest" at the signing ceremony.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">"All children deserve a chance to grow and live happy, fruitful lives," Pillen said in a press release before the signing. "This includes pre-born boys and girls, and it includes children struggling with their gender identity. These kids deserve the opportunity to grow and explore who they are and want to be, and they can do so without making irreversible decisions that should be made when they are fully grown."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">While the abortion ban goes into effect immediately upon Pillen's signature, the ban on transgender procedures will go into effect on Oct. 1.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The abortion ban includes exceptions for rape, incest, and instances in which the life of the mother is at risk. Eighty-six percent of abortions in Nebraska occur before 12 weeks, according to state statistics.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Primary sponsor state Sen. Joni Albrecht, fighting through tears, said, "I look forward to the day when every child is protected from elective abortions in our state."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Nebraska joins a growing list of states that have passed abortion restrictions since the overturn of Roe v. Wade. Twenty-seven states have attempted to pass such laws, but some states have been either held up by courts or hindered by a divided government.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Last week, North Carolina and South Carolina took action to restrict abortion.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">From Nebraska to Texas we go&hellip;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://townhall.com/tipsheet/madelineleesman/2023/05/23/texas-bans-diversity-offices-at-colleges-n2623589"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://townhall.com/tipsheet/madelineleesman/2023/05/23/texas-bans-diversity-offices-at-colleges-n2623589</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>Texas Moves a Step Closer to Banning Diversity Programs in Higher Education</strong></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">On Monday, Texas lawmakers passed a bill to end Diversity, Equity and Inclusion (DEI) programs at state colleges and universities. If the bill were to become law, it would be the second state in the nation with such legislation, following Florida.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">According to The Hill, the measure requires the governors of each state university to ensure that there is no DEI office at the school and that preferential treatment is not given for &ldquo;diversity hires.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Rep. John Kuempel, a Republican, said that &ldquo;DEI is present in some form in almost every Texas campus&rdquo; and that schools &ldquo;must recruit the best people in every field regardless of race and gender,&rdquo; according to the Dallas Morning News. The Texas House voted 83-60 in support of S.B. 17. The legislation heads back to the Senate, where it will decide to accept or deny changes made by members of the House.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Last month, when the Senate passed its version of the bill, Lt. Gov. Dan Patrick described the legislation as the &ldquo;strongest pushback on woke policies in higher education.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">&ldquo;For far too long, academia has been poisoned by woke policies and faculty seeking to indoctrinate our students. Professors did not believe we would push back on their advances, but they were wrong. Students should be taught how to think critically, not what to think," Patrick said in a statement.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://freebeacon.com/energy/majority-of-united-states-faces-elevated-risk-of-summer-power-blackouts-amid-green-energy-push/"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://freebeacon.com/energy/majority-of-united-states-faces-elevated-risk-of-summer-power-blackouts-amid-green-energy-push/</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>Majority of United States Faces 'Elevated Risk' of Summer Power Blackouts Amid Green Energy Push</strong></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">America's increased reliance on green energy in favor of coal and gas has a majority of the United States facing an "elevated risk" of summer power blackouts, according to a leading grid reliability watchdog.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The North American Electric Reliability Corporation (NERC) last week published its 2023 summer reliability assessment, which found that two-thirds of North America could face power shortages this summer during periods of extreme heat. That vulnerability, the watchdog group said, stems from America's increase in green power generation and decrease in fossil fuel power plants. While coal and natural gas plants can be turned on and off at the flip of a switch, green alternatives such as wind and solar rely on favorable weather conditions to operate at full capacity. If those conditions aren't met, power demand can outpace supply.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">"The system is closer to the edge," NERC director of reliability assessment and performance analysis John Moura said last week. "More needs to be done."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Moura is far from the only expert sounding the alarm on America's unreliable power grid. Both state and federal officials in recent weeks have warned that high summer temperatures, combined with low nightly winds, could bring power blackouts across the country. "I'm afraid to say it, but I think the United States is heading towards a catastrophic situation," Federal Energy Regulatory Commission member Mark Christie said during a May Senate hearing.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Despite those warnings, President Joe Biden has moved forward with plans to accelerate U.S. coal plant retirements. With nearly half of America's coal power already set to disappear by 2030, Biden's Environmental Protection Agency earlier this month unveiled new standards that force coal and gas power plants to slash their carbon emissions by a whopping 90 percent between 2035 and 2040. In order to meet the near-impossible standards, those plants will have to spend big on infrastructure upgrades&mdash;costs that may prompt the plants to shut down rather than comply.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">"Coal is more than five times as dependable as wind and more than twice as dependable as solar when electricity demand is greatest," America's Power CEO Michelle Bloodworth said in a statement, "yet bad public policy and EPA regulations are forcing the closure of coal plants."</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">In addition to his far-reaching fossil fuel regulations, Biden has spent hundreds of billions of dollars on tax breaks and subsidies aimed at increasing electric car use. And in April, Biden's Environmental Protection Agency announced a new rule that imposes strict tailpipe emission limits on vehicles sold&mdash;so strict that it effectively forces automakers to ensure that two-thirds of the cars they sell are electric by 2032.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Those moves could also put strain on the nation's power grid. As more Americans plug in their cars instead of filling them up with gasoline, grids across the country will need to put out more power to keep up. The issue has already plagued some U.S. states&mdash;in September, for example, California urged electric car drivers to stop charging their vehicles due to power grid strain. Still, the ordeal did not stop state officials from moving full steam ahead with plans to outlaw gas-powered vehicles and eradicate fossil fuel power plants.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/news/house/mccarthy-warns-nowhere-near-deal-on-debt-ceiling"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/news/house/mccarthy-warns-nowhere-near-deal-on-debt-ceiling</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>McCarthy warns White House and GOP &lsquo;nowhere near a deal&rsquo; on debt ceiling</strong></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">House Speaker Kevin McCarthy (R-CA) warned Republican lawmakers that his team is &ldquo;nowhere near a deal&rdquo; with the White House on the debt ceiling, ramping up pressure on President Joe Biden just nine days before the default deadline.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">In a closed-door meeting with GOP lawmakers on Tuesday, McCarthy told members a compromise on the debt ceiling was still far off, reiterating his position that he would not increase spending or raise the debt ceiling without conditions. Republicans emerged from the meeting wary of negotiators&rsquo; progress, telling reporters the talks are not going well so far.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">As part of the negotiations, the White House proposed late last week to limit next year&rsquo;s spending to 2023 levels &mdash; an idea that was rejected by Republicans, who wish to return to 2022 levels. McHenry and Rep. Garret Graves (R-LA), the top negotiators for McCarthy, emphasized that stance on Tuesday by calling on the White House to agree to cut spending.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Meanwhile, some Republicans remain skeptical of Treasury Secretary Janet Yellen&rsquo;s warnings that the country could default on its payments as soon as June 1, calling that date a manufactured deadline set by the Biden administration to accelerate a deal.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Gaetz argued the United States is not at risk of missing its payments, noting the country has strong revenue that will continue coming in over the next few weeks. Instead, the Florida Republican said Yellen should appear before Congress to present &ldquo;receipts and deposits&rdquo; that prove the country is on track to default.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">McCarthy&rsquo;s warning comes after the speaker met with Biden on Monday evening, marking the third meeting the two have held since restarting negotiations earlier this month. McCarthy called the meeting &ldquo;productive&rdquo; but noted the two are still far apart on finalizing a deal.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Now for the rundown&hellip;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://thepostmillennial.com/breaking-suspect-in-custody-after-allegedly-crashing-u-haul-truck-into-barriers-near-white-house?utm_campaign=64487"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://thepostmillennial.com/breaking-suspect-in-custody-after-allegedly-crashing-u-haul-truck-into-barriers-near-white-house?utm_campaign=64487</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">On Monday night, the driver of a U-Haul truck was taken into custody after allegedly slamming into security barriers near the White House. According to Secret Service spokesperson Anthony Guglielmi, the truck crashed on the northern side of Lafayette Square at around 10 pm.</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Guglielmi said in a statement, "Shortly before 10:00 p.m. Monday, Secret Service Uniformed Division officers detained the driver of a box truck after the vehicle collided with security barriers on the north side of Lafayette Square at 16th Street."</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">He added that there were no injuries to any Secret Service or White House personnel and that the crash is under investigation but that the preliminary investigation reveals the driver may have intentionally crashed into the barriers.</span></li>
</ul>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://thepostmillennial.com/uc-berkeley-holds-segregated-graduation-ceremony-for-black-students-only?utm_campaign=64487"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://thepostmillennial.com/uc-berkeley-holds-segregated-graduation-ceremony-for-black-students-only?utm_campaign=64487</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The University of California Berkeley hosted a black-only graduation ceremony for its non-white students at Zellerbach Hall on Saturday. In March, UC Berkeley&rsquo;s African American Studies Department announced they would be holding their annual &ldquo;Black Graduation&rdquo; ceremony for students in May.</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">According to the announcement, &ldquo;The Department of African American Studies plans on hosting our annual Black Graduation ceremony, which is open to all majors and degree programs across the campus."</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://twitter.com/i/status/1660362211636969473"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://twitter.com/i/status/1660362211636969473</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> - Play Video&nbsp;</span></span></li>
</ul>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://redstate.com/mike_miller/2023/05/22/super-woke-target-partners-on-its-new-gay-pride-line-with-designer-who-insists-satan-loves-you-n749804"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://redstate.com/mike_miller/2023/05/22/super-woke-target-partners-on-its-new-gay-pride-line-with-designer-who-insists-satan-loves-you-n749804</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">So let&rsquo;s check them off. By &ldquo;them,&rdquo; I mean just the latest corporations to put their &ldquo;woke&rdquo; beliefs ahead of customer loyalty, profits, and shareholders: Disney, Nike, Bud Light, BlackRock, Ford, and Miller Lite. The complete list is long &mdash; and it just got longer with the addition of the super-woke Target Corporation.</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Target has partnered with UK-based Satanist designer Abprallen on its new &ldquo;Pride&rdquo; collection, which features a &ldquo;Cure Transphobia&rdquo; sweatshirt, which bears the message &ldquo;Cure transphobia, not trans people,&rdquo; and other related items. Did I mention that Abprallen insists &ldquo;Satan loves you,&rdquo; &ldquo;Satan respects pronouns,&rdquo; and other uplifting [sarc] trash for your shopping pleasure? As reported by Breitbart, Abprallen mixes its affinity for satanism with its pro-LGBT activism, boasting on its Instagram page: &ldquo;Satan loves you and respects who you are; you&rsquo;re important and valuable in this world and you deserve to treat yourself with love and respect.&rdquo;</span></li>
</ul>]]></description>
   <author><![CDATA[Garrison Hardie]]></author>
   <enclosure url="https://app.dropwave.io/episode/3bff24f1-e7d1-4e75-9545-7e5687844fd5/daily-news-brief-for-wednesday-may-24th-2023.mp3" length="890" type="audio/mp3"/>
   <guid isPermaLink="false"><![CDATA[3bff24f1-e7d1-4e75-9545-7e5687844fd5]]></guid>
   <pubDate>Wed, 24 May 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
   <source url=""><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></source>
   <itunes:author><![CDATA[Garrison Hardie]]></itunes:author>
   <itunes:image href="https://assets-cdn2.dropwave.io/2ab40ac0-e99d-4f25-a6d2-541d2c9b290a/cover-art/hUZu1H9lrRY0wXg66WHC8eLwYBA3hbRNTAHQmHt2.png"/>
   <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
   <itunes:duration>890</itunes:duration>
   <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
  
  </item><item>
   <title><![CDATA[Daily News Brief for Tuesday, May 23rd, 2023 [Daily News Brief]]]></title>
   <link>https://app.dropwave.io/episode/bc3a25a3-61d5-4dad-9435-49fcc84f03dc/daily-news-brief-for-tuesday-may-23rd-2023.mp3</link>
   <description><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">This is Garrison Hardie with your CrossPolitic Daily News Brief for Tuesday, May 23rd, 2023.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>Concordis Education Partners:</strong></span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Classical Christian education has reminded us to aim education at truth, but the trivium has been used as a formula rather than a way of training students in discernment.&nbsp;&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">To teach well, you must coach.&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">&nbsp;</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Concordis Foundation is offering their third annual BOOT CAMP &ndash; a faculty summit &ndash; July 11-13th in Moscow, Idaho.&nbsp; This is a three-day intensive teaching training where you learn to coach students, using the trivium, so that you can meet students at all learning levels.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">&nbsp;</span></p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Learn more at</span><a href="https://concordispartners.com/"><span style="font-weight: 400;"> </span><span style="font-weight: 400;">concordispartners.com</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;">&nbsp;&nbsp;</span></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://www.westernjournal.com/two-women-told-broken-law-criticizing-male-attempting-breastfeed-child-report/"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.westernjournal.com/two-women-told-broken-law-criticizing-male-attempting-breastfeed-child-report/</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>Two Women Are Told They've Broken the Law by Criticizing Male Attempting to Breastfeed a Child: Report</strong></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Two Australian women were reportedly given notices informing them that they committed a crime by criticizing a male, who identifies as a woman, that was trying to breastfeed a baby.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The news was first reported by the &ldquo;Pro-Woman, Pro-Child Safeguarding, Anti-Bullsh*t,&rdquo; media outlet Reduxx.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">According to the outlet, Twitter contacted the two women &mdash; Jasmine Sussex and Leah Whiston &mdash; on May 16, notifying them that they had violated Australian law in several of their tweets.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The platform told the two that a &ldquo;government entity or law enforcement agency&rdquo; had informed them of their alleged crime, and that the platform had been forced to hide the content from Australian users.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The posts in question had been critical of Jennifer Buckley, a female-identified male.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Buckley had previously announced online that, after two years of transitioning, he had induced lactation and had begun breastfeeding his newborn son, who his wife had given birth to.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Sussex was heavily critical of this, telling the U.K.&rsquo;s Daily Mail that &ldquo;men shouldn&rsquo;t breastfeed because breastfeeding [is] for the baby,&rdquo; and that &ldquo;there is no evidence that any male-induced milk is equivalent to mother&rsquo;s milk.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">&ldquo;We have no idea if the substance is even milk. It&rsquo;s absolutely a human experiment on babies,&rdquo; she told the outlet.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">As a volunteer breastfeeding counselor, Sussex was reportedly fired from her job in 2021 for failing to comply with the adoption of &ldquo;gender neutral&rdquo; language in breastfeeding care &mdash; a claim which the ABA denied to the Daily Mail.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">A year after, she was removed from the Australian Breastfeeding Association (ABA), Reduxx reported.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">&ldquo;I was sacked for. &hellip; &lsquo;Engaging in Sectarian Controversy&rsquo; in breach of the ABA constitution,&rdquo; she told Reduxx. &ldquo;In other words, continuing to talk about the dangers of gender identity ideology for mothers and babies, including how men were forcing their way into the breastfeeding relationship by attempting to induce lactation.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Whiston, meanwhile, is the representative for the Standing for Women Queensland (SFWQ) page.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">She had posted a Twitter thread on the page, revealing that an LGBT lobby group had allegedly given the ABA $20,000 for them to create an educational booklet about &ldquo;chest feeding.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://www.dailysignal.com/2023/05/22/exclusive-leaked-policy-exposes-fox-news-stances-on-woke-ideology/?fbclid=IwAR36KJiUko85jY6nRrQSX4DH2XOZAwUdyaTl-iEhQIfZe9w-ZPnsTY3cAnA"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.dailysignal.com/2023/05/22/exclusive-leaked-policy-exposes-fox-news-stances-on-woke-ideology/?fbclid=IwAR36KJiUko85jY6nRrQSX4DH2XOZAwUdyaTl-iEhQIfZe9w-ZPnsTY3cAnA</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>Leaked Policy Exposes Fox News Stances on Woke Ideology</strong></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Fox News employees are allowed to use bathrooms that align with their gender identity, rather than their biological sex, and permitted to dress in alignment with their preferred gender. They must also be addressed by their preferred name and pronouns in the workplace.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">These are just a few of the policies outlined in the company handbook, dated January 2021, a copy of which was shared with The Daily Signal. Fox also offers to help employees come up with a &ldquo;Workplace Transition Plan&rdquo; to ease their gender transition at work.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The revelations comes amid conservative consternation at Fox Digital&rsquo;s use of activist language like &ldquo;gender affirming care&rdquo; in stories on its website, as well as the site&rsquo;s consistent use of female pronouns for biological males like TikTok celebrity Dylan Mulvaney and swimmer Lia Thomas (formerly known as Will Thomas).</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Fox also drew strong backlash for a June 2022 on-air segment praising a child&rsquo;s gender transition as an &ldquo;inspiration to others.&rdquo; That segment briefly depicted California state Sen. Scott Weiner, a far-left Democrat who led the move to soften sex offender registry requirements for sodomy with minors, and highlighted the activist claim that a child might commit suicide if he or she is not permitted to transition.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Carlson&rsquo;s show was canceled April 24, days after he delivered a viral speech at The Heritage Foundation&rsquo;s 50th anniversary gala. Fox News Media has not given a reason, simply stating that the two parties &ldquo;agreed to part ways.&rdquo;&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">A source who still works at Fox News told The Daily Signal that after Carlson&rsquo;s show was canceled in April, producers for the new 8 p.m. &ldquo;Fox News Tonight&rdquo; program were told not to bash Mulvaney. That directive came from high-level executives, the source said.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Fox News did not respond to The Daily Signal&rsquo;s multiple requests for comment.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Under the category &ldquo;Gender Transition,&rdquo; Fox&rsquo;s employee handbook promises that the company is dedicated to &ldquo;expanding and strengthening&rdquo; efforts to &ldquo;sustain a more inclusive work environment.&rdquo; The Fox employee handbook is posted on Workday, where employees can see company guidelines or policies, a former employee told The Daily Signal.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">&ldquo;Employees who are transitioning their gender have the right to be open about their transition if they so choose, and to work in an environment free of harassment, discrimination, or retaliation, and without fear of consequences or transphobia for living openly,&rdquo; the policy says.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Citing the Human Rights Campaign, one of the most prominent LGBTQ organization in the country, the Fox handbook defines a slew of LGBTQ terms, including cisgender, gender expression, gender-fluid, gender identity, gender non-conforming, gender transition, LGBTQ, non-binary, and transgender.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">For the past several years, Fox received a perfect score on the Human Rights Campaign&rsquo;s Corporate Equality Index, &ldquo;the nation&rsquo;s foremost benchmarking survey and report measuring corporate policies and practices related to LGBTQ+ workplace equality.&rdquo; A former Fox News employee told The Daily Signal that the company frequently mentions this perfect score in employee training materials.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">&ldquo;Fox News devotes hours of programming to attacking &lsquo;woke companies,&rsquo; but ironically Fox is as woke as the rest of them,&rdquo; another former Fox News employee told The Daily Signal, emphasizing that Fox viewers would be &ldquo;astonished to find out what the company is like.&rdquo;&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Fox&rsquo;s policies appear to be aligned with the legal requirements in New York City, where the company is headquartered, as well as California, where a large number of its employees work.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The handbook explicitly states that any employee &ldquo;may access the restroom corresponding to their gender identity.&rdquo;&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">&ldquo;If a transitioning employee expresses a desire for increased privacy they will be provided access to a single occupancy restroom where available,&rdquo; the handbook says. &ldquo;However, no employee shall be required to use a single occupancy restroom if they do not wish to do so.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">When trans-identifying TikTok star Mulvaney was first gaining prominence last year, producers for &ldquo;Tucker Carlson Tonight&rdquo; had to fight to be able to refer to Mulvaney with male pronouns in the show&rsquo;s chyrons, the former &ldquo;Tucker Carlson Tonight&rdquo; producer told The Daily Signal.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Carlson&rsquo;s team also fought to be able to host The Daily Wire&rsquo;s Matt Walsh on trans issues, the producer said, but the team was repeatedly met with resistance from Fox on this due to Walsh&rsquo;s frank condemnation of transgender ideology. This may have also been due in part to Fox&rsquo;s view of The Daily Wire as a competitor, the former producer suggested.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://www.based-politics.com/2023/05/22/this-public-college-is-giving-out-paid-internships-that-openly-exclude-white-people/"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.based-politics.com/2023/05/22/this-public-college-is-giving-out-paid-internships-that-openly-exclude-white-people/</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>This public college is giving out paid internships that openly exclude white people</strong></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Martin Luther King Jr. famously dreamed of a day when Americans would be judged not by the color of their skin but by the content of their character. Well, keep dreaming, MLK, because segregation and open race discrimination are making a comeback&mdash;this time, in progressive bastions like our higher education system and in the name of &ldquo;Diversity, Equity, and Inclusion.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The University of Minnesota just got hit with a federal civil rights complaint because it&rsquo;s openly conditioning a paid internship program on the basis of race. Their &ldquo;Multicultural Summer Research Opportunities Program&rdquo; is &ldquo;an intensive 10 week summer program in which undergraduate students of color work full-time with a faculty mentor on a research project.&rdquo; It aims to help in &ldquo;preparing students for graduate school and developing research skills,&rdquo; and pays students a $6,000 stipend. A condition of the program is that it is only open to students who &ldquo;identify&rdquo; as &ldquo;a student of color or Native American.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">This program&rsquo;s legality is being challenged by the Legal Insurrection Foundation&rsquo;s Equal Protection Project (EPP), which &ldquo;seeks to ensure equal protection under the law and non-discrimination by the government&rdquo; and &ldquo;opposes racial discrimination in any form.&rdquo; They just filed a complaint with the&nbsp; Office of Civil Rights of the U.S. Department of Education arguing that this internship program violates the Civil Rights Act and the Equal Protection clause of the Constitution.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">&ldquo;The U. Minnesota segregated summer program is inexcusable, and it&rsquo;s shocking that a major university would so openly make educational opportunities open only to students of a certain skin color,&rdquo; EPP President Bill told Fox News Digital. &ldquo;There is no good form of racial discrimination. Depriving white students of educational opportunities does not promote racial or any other form of justice.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://www.breitbart.com/politics/2023/05/21/census-new-york-city-loses-nearly-half-a-million-residents-in-two-years/"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.breitbart.com/politics/2023/05/21/census-new-york-city-loses-nearly-half-a-million-residents-in-two-years/</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><strong>New York City Loses Nearly Half a Million Residents in Two Years</strong></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">New York City has lost nearly half a million residents over the course of just two years, newly released United States Census Bureau data reveals.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The Census Bureau data, which shows population estimates for mid-2022, finds that fewer than 8.4 million residents remain living in New York City &mdash; still making the Big Apple the nation&rsquo;s most populous city by several million.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">In April 2020, the very start of the Chinese coronavirus pandemic, more than 8.8 million residents lived in New York City. This figure indicates a population loss of more than five percent from April 2020 to July 2022 with almost half a million residents leaving the city.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Americans moving out of deep blue cities is widespread, the Census Bureau data shows.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The second largest city, Los Angeles, California, and the third largest city, Chicago, Illinois, also lost residents over the course of two years. In Los Angeles, for instance, about 3.8 million residents remain in the city as of July 2022 compared to about 3.9 million residents in April 2020, a loss of about 100,000 residents.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Similarly, Chicago had about 2.67 million residents as of July 2022 but in April 2020, the city had about three percent more residents. Over the two years, about 85,000 residents left Chicago.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">And now for the rundown&hellip;&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://andmagazine.substack.com/p/china-is-building-killer-robots-using"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://andmagazine.substack.com/p/china-is-building-killer-robots-using</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Many of us have seen The Terminator, a 1984 film starring Arnold Schwarzenegger. It depicts an almost unstoppable robot sent back in time from 2029 to 1984. Its mission was to kill a woman whose unborn son will save humanity from Skynet, a 2029 artificial intelligence system that had become self-aware and then decided to destroy all of mankind because humans were interfering in their plans and programs.</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The Chinese Communist Party, the CCP, is now creating their version of the Terminator -- an army of battlefield killer robots that will not be managed by humans in any way and, instead, will be controlled by an artificial intelligence (AI) system. The Chinese plan for building such lethal autonomous robots was revealed by Zeng Yi, an executive in a Chinese government-owned company named Norinco. He said, &ldquo;In future battlegrounds, there will be no people fighting,&rdquo; adding that autonomous AI platforms are &ldquo;inevitable.&rdquo;</span></li>
</ul>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/news/washington-secrets/explosion-of-ap-climate-change-stories-following-8m-enviro-grant"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/news/washington-secrets/explosion-of-ap-climate-change-stories-following-8m-enviro-grant</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">In the year following a grant of more than $8 million to the Associated Press from key climate change advocates, the news service has poured out at least 64 stories warning of environmental calamity, according to a new media study.Media Research Center Business charted the stories and language used following the multimillion-dollar grant and found that AP also used over 500 environmental extremism buzzwords in the stories.</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The media giant, which feeds news outlets worldwide, received grants totaling $8 million from the William and Flora Hewlett Foundation, the Howard Hughes Medical Institute, Quadrivium, the Rockefeller Foundation, and the Walton Family Foundation in February 2022. AP said it would hire 20 new environmental writers with the money to create a climate swat team to &ldquo;enhance the global understanding of climate change and its impact across the world.&rdquo;</span></li>
</ul>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://www.outkick.com/trans-high-school-track-runner-robs-female-athlete-of-state-championship-bid/"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.outkick.com/trans-high-school-track-runner-robs-female-athlete-of-state-championship-bid/</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Another day, another biological male taking opportunities from deserving females.Athena Ryan took second place Saturday in the high school women&rsquo;s 1600 meter race at the North Coast Meet of Champions in California. The top three athletes advance to the CIF State Track &amp; Field Championships next week. So the fourth-place finisher, Adeline Johnson, missed her chance to compete in State by just one spot. A spot taken by a boy.</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Ryan, a junior at Sonoma Academy, competed on the men&rsquo;s team in 2021. But he&rsquo;s been running in women&rsquo;s events for the past two seasons. In Saturday&rsquo;s meet, he clocked a season-record 4:55:91 in the 1600m finals. He would have finished last in the male category. The slowest male time in the preliminaries was 4:46:54. The slowest male time in the finals was 4:35:12.</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">A group of advocates held a banner at the event that simply read, &ldquo;Protect Female Sports.&rdquo; They were eventually asked to leave and then escorted off the premises. But not before they had an interesting exchange with an angry passerby.</span></li>
</ul>
<p><br /><br /></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">How about we end with some cool news&hellip;</span></p>
<p><span style="font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;"><a href="https://www.dailyfetched.com/soldier-who-lost-both-legs-in-afghanistan-does-the-unimaginable-and-climbs-everest-anything-is-possible/"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.dailyfetched.com/soldier-who-lost-both-legs-in-afghanistan-does-the-unimaginable-and-climbs-everest-anything-is-possible/</span></a></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">British army soldier Gurkha veteran Hari Budha Magar, who lost both his legs while serving in Afghanistan, has successfully climbed to the top of the world&rsquo;s tallest mountain, Mount Everest.</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">Magar, a father of three, served as a corporal in the Gurkha regiment in the British Army. After Magar lost his legs to an improvised explosive device in 2010, he thought his life was &ldquo;completely finished.&rdquo;</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">The veteran, who now lives in Canterbury, England, battled depression and alcoholism following the explosion.</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400; font-family: 'book antiqua', palatino, serif;">But Magar persevered. The veteran helped strike down a ban on both double amputees and blind people climbing Everest, ensuring he would have a chance at overcoming both nature and his injuries. According to the BBC, Magar hoped to &ldquo;inspire others&rdquo; and &ldquo;change perceptions on disability&rdquo; and set off with a team of Nepalese climbers to combat Everest. He&rdquo; set off on May 6 with a team of Nepalese climbers led by Krish Thapa, a fellow Gurkha veteran and British special forces mountain troop leader. Magar announced he &ldquo;stood victorious&rdquo; atop Everest around 3 p.m. on May 19, noting, &ldquo;Disability is no barrier to reaching the 8,849-metre peak.&rdquo;</span></li>
</ul>]]></description>
   <author><![CDATA[Garrison Hardie]]></author>
   <enclosure url="https://app.dropwave.io/episode/bc3a25a3-61d5-4dad-9435-49fcc84f03dc/daily-news-brief-for-tuesday-may-23rd-2023.mp3" length="937" type="audio/mp3"/>
   <guid isPermaLink="false"><![CDATA[bc3a25a3-61d5-4dad-9435-49fcc84f03dc]]></guid>
   <pubDate>Tue, 23 May 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
   <source url=""><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></source>
   <itunes:author><![CDATA[Garrison Hardie]]></itunes:author>
   <itunes:image href="https://assets-cdn2.dropwave.io/2ab40ac0-e99d-4f25-a6d2-541d2c9b290a/cover-art/hUZu1H9lrRY0wXg66WHC8eLwYBA3hbRNTAHQmHt2.png"/>
   <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
   <itunes:duration>937</itunes:duration>
   <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
  
  </item>
 </channel>
</rss>
