<?xml version="1.0"?>
<?xml-stylesheet href="/storage/feed-stylesheet.xsl" type="text/xsl"?>

<rss xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
 <channel>
  <title>FLF - Pastor Toby’s Blog</title>
  <link>https://dropwave.io</link>
  <description><![CDATA[FIGHT LAUGH FEAST PRESENTS SHOWS PROCLAIMING THE LORDSHIP OF CHRIST OVER ALL OF LIFE.
]]></description>
  <language>en</language>
  <managingEditor><![CDATA[fightlaughfeast@gmail.com (FLF, LLC)]]></managingEditor>
  <webMaster><![CDATA[support@dropwave.io (DropWave Support)]]></webMaster>
  <pubDate>Wed, 15 Mar 2023 13:25:45 +0000</pubDate>
  <lastBuildDate>Wed, 15 Mar 2023 13:25:45 +0000</lastBuildDate>
  <image>
   <url>https://is4-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Podcasts113/v4/58/56/52/5856525c-2973-cf29-3db9-21faa8595391/mza_1144696925612154085.png/1200x1200bb.jpg</url>
   <link>https://dropwave.io</link>
   <title><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></title>
  </image>
  <itunes:author><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></itunes:author>
  <itunes:image href="https://is4-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Podcasts113/v4/58/56/52/5856525c-2973-cf29-3db9-21faa8595391/mza_1144696925612154085.png/1200x1200bb.jpg"/>
  <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
  <itunes:owner>
   <itunes:name><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></itunes:name>
   <itunes:email>fightlaughfeast@gmail.com</itunes:email>
  </itunes:owner>
  <itunes:category text="News"/>
  <item>
   <title><![CDATA[Having Two Legs: Tucker Carlson & A Case Study in Christian Nationalism & Theocratic Conservatism [Pastor Toby’s Blog]]]></title>
   <link>https://app.dropwave.io/episode/55470ef5-66b3-497a-86e8-f2e4a2231e59/having-two-legs-tucker-carlson-a-case-study-in-christian-nationalism-theocratic-conservatism-1.mp3</link>
   <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Tucker Carlson &amp; A Case Study in Christian Nationalism &amp; Theocratic Conservatism&nbsp;</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Introduction</strong></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">One may wonder how the algorithmic gods of the medias mutter and chirp and old clips of Tucker Carlson and Ben Shapiro emerge from the ancient shadows, but be assured that they do and when they do, they provide one with opportunities to pull your son aside, like Solomon in Proverbs and say, do you see that man? Yeah, not like that.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Now the particular clip that is currently making the rounds is from 2018, and a great deal of water has gone under the old proverbial bridge and has flowed many miles hence, even to the wild lands of Wuhan and beyond. And so one might hope that greater light has come into the great Tucker Carlson&rsquo;s eyes. I mean, if they can lock us down, close our churches, foist useless, perhaps even harmful masks on our faces, and demand injections or else you&rsquo;re a hater, a bigot, and a scoundrel, perhaps he&rsquo;s had a change of heart.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">But the clip is from when a Ben Shapiro interview of Tucker Carlson, where Tucker argues that since family is the foundational building block of society and an unmitigated good, society ought to take steps to protect it and defend it. And certain technological advances that threaten that good ought to be curbed and perhaps even prohibited. Tucker says that if we don&rsquo;t we may very soon end up with a situation where a reasonably well-adjusted college graduate (one who doesn&rsquo;t smoke pot) may not have the means to provide for himself, much less take a wife, and raise a family with her. And when pressed by Ben Shapiro about the possibility of Artificial Intelligence driving trucks on American highways, Tucker says that if he was President he would absolutely order the Department of Transportation to ban all AI on federal highways because if they didn&rsquo;t millions of jobs would be lost. And truck driving is one of the most common jobs for high school educated men in America.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Setting the Table</strong></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Now let&rsquo;s set the table carefully here. First, it&rsquo;s absolutely true that the natural family is the foundational building block of society. Second, let&rsquo;s agree that society should do everything lawfully in its power to protect and encourage family formation and flourishing. But here is where the questions begin to array themselves. What actually is &ldquo;lawfully in its power?&rdquo; Can the state simply do anything that appears to contribute to some notion of the &ldquo;common good?&rdquo; How should society protect and encourage natural family formation? My previously stated proposal is that as Protestant Christians we must begin with the clear instructions given in Scripture and then work our way out from those by good and necessary consequence, by the light of nature and Christian prudence. So I don&rsquo;t think we need an explicit Bible verse about AI and truck drivers, but I do think we need clear-eyed biblical principles.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">There are multiple problems with Tucker&rsquo;s proposal, beginning with him acting like a socialist. The assumption of socialism/Marxism is that there is no God, and therefore the state must take His place. Since there is no God to do justice, rendering unto each man what he deserves, the State takes unto itself this responsibility. Fascism need not be dark and bloody at first. It simply claims the right to command commerce and markets for the &ldquo;common good&rdquo; of society, for the good of families and family values. But it&rsquo;s still fascism and socialism for all that, even if the state is commanding Bible reading and church attendance. Don&rsquo;t misunderstand: I&rsquo;m not saying that Tucker&rsquo;s second presidential fiat would be compulsory Bible reading and church attendance. But why exactly not?&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Furthermore, these soft-socialist/fascist policies claim a kind omniscience. Tucker claims that millions of jobs will be lost in a matter of years. But this sounds like the conservative equivalent of the environmental doomsdayers. If you don&rsquo;t ban plastic bags today, the oceans will rise in five years and millions will die! Or sometimes they even notice real problems, like for example, air pollution. But as Alex Epstein has helpfully catalogued, over and over again, there&rsquo;s a certain simplistic and narrow mindset that looks at one factor and multiplies it by a million without accounting for all the other possibilities and concludes that the apocalyptic outcome is inevitable! And that&rsquo;s trying to be god while sucking at it. So when environmentalists have projected air pollution from coal and oil and other fossil fuels, what they have consistently not accounted for is adaptation, creativity, ingenuity, and improvements in technology which mitigate, minimize, and sometimes completely undo the dangers and potential harms. People, made in the image of God, are like God, and despite our fallen natures, they are generally trying to improve things.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Tucker&rsquo;s comments struck me as not only tapping into that false socialist omniscience, but they were demeaning and condescending to the very human beings he was claiming to want to protect and help, while apparently completely forgetting about other human beings in the equation. Now, it&rsquo;s an entirely open question as to whether it would ever actually work to have AI drive trucks in this country. At the very least, we would want to have a chain of liability clearly articulated, and like the goring ox in Exodus 21, require restitution and harsh penalties for any harm or damage that occurs. But why does Tucker paint the drug free college graduate like a helpless victim? Why are working class high school graduates being described as completely dependent on truck driving jobs? Can they not do anything else? A few decades ago they worked in American factories, but after the government got involved in &ldquo;helping&rdquo; them, they all got sent overseas. And here we are suggesting more Big Government involvement to help &ldquo;fix&rdquo; inequities. &ldquo;We&rsquo;re the government and we&rsquo;re here to help,&rdquo; are still the most terrifying words in the English language, even when they are in the mouth of so-called &ldquo;common good&rdquo; conservatives.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Now, the fact of the matter is that even if the tech and liabilities all got sufficiently sorted, and people started experimenting with AI truck drivers, the change wouldn&rsquo;t happen overnight. But as it started to happen (if it ever did), you would immediately be funding all the developers, troubleshooters, repairment, maintenance, and updates needed to grow and improve that new technology. The other part of the &ldquo;inevitability-omniscience&rdquo; complex is a failure to see that new technology only ever depends upon human beings creating it, maintaining, fixing it, improving, and so on. Read </span><em><span style="font-weight: 400;">Life After Google</span></em><span style="font-weight: 400;"> by George Gilder and repent of your implicit Darwinism. Artificial intelligence will always be completely dependent upon human intelligence. So just as a new technology begins to break into markets, new human jobs come into being. And this is how it has always worked. As technology changes, some folks are laid off and find new creative outlets, but all of that new technology also always creates new needs for human workers.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>The Biblical Common Good</strong></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The Biblical vision of the common good is each sphere of government exercising the power delegated to it by Christ obediently. The Magisterial Reformers were working in a particular historical moment where church government had way overreached its bounds, and part of the way you begin to limit overweening powers is by reinvigorating the balance of powers. In the days of Luther and Calvin it was absolutely necessary to call the magistrates to take up the sword of justice and push back the encroachments of the Papal See. However, we now live in an era where the state has become the Infallible Mouth of God, and it&rsquo;s high time ministers of the gospel declared the Lordship of Christ and commanded magistrates back into their own lane, while insisting that husbands and fathers, wives and mothers step up to the plate and take back their authority in the home and marketplace. Until a crime has been actually committed, it is an unjust use of violence to manipulate markets. I understand that when you live in a snake pit of market regulations the temptation is to simply join the mafia and release your own &ldquo;good&rdquo; snakes into the mix, but as we learn from one of those lesser known Mosaic principles, never bring more snakes to a snake pit unless your snake will swallow all of them and turn back into a walking stick when it&rsquo;s done.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">God has established three governments among men: the family, the church, and the state. These governments are not water-tight jurisdictions, but function more like a Venn diagram with clear differences and some overlap. God has assigned to the family the jurisdiction of health, welfare, and education. God has assigned to the church the ministry of worship and discipleship, the administration of Word and sacrament. God has assigned to the state the ministry of the sword of justice. Closely related is the difference between sins and crimes. We see this distinction beginning in the differing ministries of Abraham and Melchizedek, Moses and Aaron, as well as the differing penalties provided in the Mosaic law. When the law says that someone will be &ldquo;cut off from among his people,&rdquo; this is the ordinary discipline of Old Testament family and &ldquo;church.&rdquo; When the penalty prescribed is restitution or stripes or death, this the ministry of the sword. Now granted these are not pristine, Euclidian categories. Many of the laws in the Mosaic code have moral, ceremonial, and civil elements to them. Nevertheless, ceremonial laws were under the jurisdiction of the priests and civil laws were under the jurisdiction of the judges and magistrates. But the fact that family law was also being established in the Mosaic law is profound. Laws surrounding marriage and divorce and remarriage within families, with instructions for what might be appealed to civil magistrates for civil penalties begin to establish these jurisdictional differences.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">In other words, not all sins are or should be crimes. Covetousness is a sin but not a crime. Lying is always a sin, but not all lies should be adjudicated as crimes. Lust is a sin, even adultery in the heart, but until the lust is acted upon in fornication or adultery, there is no crime to adjudicate. A rebellious son ought to be disciplined by his own parents for many years before they determine to appeal to the civil magistrate for criminal penalties. But here is where the jurisdictions overlap: if a true biblical crime has been committed in a family or church, the civil magistrate is authorized by God to intervene. A civil magistrate my seek a warrant to arrest a father and pastor for sexual abuse. But by the same token, a father may resist or ignore tyrannical orders given a magistrate and a pastor may rebuke a magistrate and command him to repent of his sin, just as John did and lost his head for it. When a church excommunicates a professing Christian, barring them from the Lord&rsquo;s Supper and fellowship in the local church, the church is exercising its power to protect truth and morality in a society. When a family disciplines its young children teaching them Christian virtues the family government is doing its part to cultivate families and work ethics and morality. The family has the power to ultimately disinherit a son or daughter for gross immorality or apostasy. And it is the job of the state to punish crimes as defined by Scripture. No crime has been committed if a trucking company fires a driver in favor of an AI driver.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Conclusion</strong></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">In the clip mentioned, Tucker Carlson says that even though he believes in free markets it&rsquo;s not an absolute or religious commitment or requirement. He says there&rsquo;s no &ldquo;Nicene Creed of Capitalism&rdquo; he has to subscribe to. Now he&rsquo;s absolutely right if he means that free markets may not be used to justify committing crimes (e.g. theft, murder, etc.). But what Tucker is actually proposing is denying jobs and livelihoods to those working in AI, and by the making it a law, he&rsquo;s threatening the use of violence for those who try. In the name of doing good and protecting families, Tucker is proposing that he be the one who gets to choose the winners and the losers. Truckers are the winners; programmers and new tech are the losers. Sorry, the gods have spoken. We know what&rsquo;s best for you. And actually, we&rsquo;ve decided that cars have taken too many jobs away from horses and mules. So yeah, we&rsquo;re going back to the Middle Ages, you greedy capitalist pigs. But seriously, where&rsquo;s the line?&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Ok, I&rsquo;ll stop here. Tucker says there&rsquo;s no Nicene Creed of capitalism, and that&rsquo;s true enough, but there is a Nicene Creed that says that God is the &ldquo;Father Almighty, Maker of Heaven and earth, and of all things visible and invisible&hellip;&rdquo; Invisible things would include market forces, the creativity and ingenuity of men, as well as their created needs and desires.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Until or unless God gives a government the authority to step in, it is a violation of the Nicene Creed to grasp power for yourself and violently or coercively prohibit the free actions and creativity of people.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">It must always be remembered that if the primary power of the state is the power of the sword, then whenever you call for a &ldquo;ban,&rdquo; you are simultaneously calling for the use of violent, coercive force to be used if someone disregards the ban. I&rsquo;m sorry, but we just had a few years of a police state trial run in the West with law enforcement fining churches for being open, for mandated gags on peoples&rsquo; faces, and frog marching decent law-abiding citizens off to jail for singing songs in public.&nbsp;&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">I do believe in the &ldquo;common good,&rdquo; but the common good is determined by God&rsquo;s Word and not simplistic, short-sighted calculations. It was those kinds of simplistic, short-sighted calculations that the Imperial College of London used to insight the COVID panic. So, no thanks. God&rsquo;s world is more resilient, more complex, more glorious than that.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p><br /><br /><br /><br /></p>]]></description>
   <author><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></author>
   <enclosure url="https://app.dropwave.io/episode/55470ef5-66b3-497a-86e8-f2e4a2231e59/having-two-legs-tucker-carlson-a-case-study-in-christian-nationalism-theocratic-conservatism-1.mp3" length="1084" type="audio/mp3"/>
   <guid isPermaLink="false"><![CDATA[55470ef5-66b3-497a-86e8-f2e4a2231e59]]></guid>
   <pubDate>Mon, 27 Feb 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
   <source url=""><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></source>
   <itunes:author><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></itunes:author>
   <itunes:image href="https://prod-assets-spc1.nyc3.digitaloceanspaces.com/20dde981-157e-4504-b38f-dd9d7b0e4c50/cover-art/ZdXVos6595FpTNoyp6qYqu16EQyUrG0zPvsBPzMA.png"/>
   <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
   <itunes:duration>1084</itunes:duration>
   <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
  
  </item><item>
   <title><![CDATA[Having Two Legs: Real Communion [Pastor Toby’s Blog]]]></title>
   <link>https://app.dropwave.io/episode/cf94952b-29fc-4433-bb0e-cfc8aceadaf2/having-two-legs-real-communion.mp3</link>
   <description><![CDATA[<p dir="ltr">Real Communion</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The table of the Lord&rsquo;s is a table of communion and fellowship. This is why we call it Communion. It is communion with God, and it is communion with God&rsquo;s people. This is why Paul told the Corinthians that when they came together to eat this meal it was not really the Lord&rsquo;s Supper. There were divisions among the Corinthians, rivalries, resentments, and elbows being thrown. You can&rsquo;t celebrate communion while being out of communion with God or your neighbor, your husband, your wife, your parents, your kids, or roommates. It says that when the Corinthians tried to do that many of them got sick and some had even died.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">In the Old Testament, when the Israelites complained against God that there was no meat to eat in the wilderness, He gave them quail, but that meat became poison to all those with evil hearts. Likewise, God told Israel that if a man suspected his wife of adultery, he could bring her to the tabernacle and the priest could give her a drink that would function as a jealousy test. In some ways, the Lord&rsquo;s table functions like that. If you are in fellowship with God and one another, the bread and cup are grace and strength and blessing. But if you come to the table harboring secret sins, or grievances or out of fellowship with someone, you need to know that by eating and drinking, you are inviting Christ in. Christ is there, and it is communion with Christ. But if you eat and drinking communion while trying to preserve disunion, divisions, and strife, the meal will be a curse.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The answer is not to abstain from the table. If you are baptized, you really must come.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Don&rsquo;t cling to your sin and abstain from the meal. Rather, let go of your sin now. Drop your sin now. Determine in your heart right now to kill that sin, to confess it, to forsake it, to be reconciled to your brother or sister as soon as possible. If you do that, then the Lord&rsquo;s Supper will strengthen you for that fight, strengthen you to do what needs to be done to restore fellowship.&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">So consider your wife, your husband, your kids, your parents, your roommates, your friends. Is all well? Or do you need to go find them right now, call them, text them an apology and ask for forgiveness? Then do it. Then the Lord&rsquo;s supper will truly be communion, communion with the Lord Jesus Christ, whose blood reconciles every sin.&nbsp;</p>
<p><br /><br /><br /></p>]]></description>
   <author><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></author>
   <enclosure url="https://app.dropwave.io/episode/cf94952b-29fc-4433-bb0e-cfc8aceadaf2/having-two-legs-real-communion.mp3" length="176" type="audio/mp3"/>
   <guid isPermaLink="false"><![CDATA[cf94952b-29fc-4433-bb0e-cfc8aceadaf2]]></guid>
   <pubDate>Sat, 25 Feb 2023 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
   <source url=""><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></source>
   <itunes:author><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></itunes:author>
   <itunes:image href="https://prod-assets-spc1.nyc3.digitaloceanspaces.com/20dde981-157e-4504-b38f-dd9d7b0e4c50/cover-art/ZdXVos6595FpTNoyp6qYqu16EQyUrG0zPvsBPzMA.png"/>
   <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
   <itunes:duration>176</itunes:duration>
   <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
  
  </item><item>
   <title><![CDATA[Having Two Legs: Theonomy & Classical Reformed Christian Nationalism: A Modest Proposal [Pastor Toby’s Blog]]]></title>
   <link>https://app.dropwave.io/episode/3fd9e97d-1f11-4276-b95c-eb0e45b8bcef/having-two-legs-theonomy-classical-reformed-christian-nationalism-a-modest-proposal.mp3</link>
   <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>&nbsp;Theonomy &amp; Classical Reformed Christian Nationalism: A Modest Proposal</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Introduction</strong></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The conversation swirling around Christian Nationalism, the classical liberal order, and how Christians ought to think about particular policy proposals continues apace. These issues are in play with the current push for &ldquo;school choice&rdquo; and Education Savings Accounts, and they are in play with Senator Josh Hawley&rsquo;s recent proposal to ban social media use for children under 16.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">To which I tweeted out: &ldquo;Yikes. No. This is the kind of folly that conservatives propose in the name of "the common good" that gives me the creeping fantods. This is why Kuyper's sphere sovereignty and old fashioned theonomy are so necessary. God has not established the state/power of the sword to raise/train our children. Same goes for alcohol, tobacco, and firearms. As soon as you start letting the civil magistrate act like your mom, you will only get more of the Karen State that we currently have.&rdquo;&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">And that seems to have stirred the waters. At this point, I&rsquo;m hoping I&rsquo;ve stirred the waters of Bethsaida and not something more shark infested, but that remains to be seen.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Part of the fun of the last few weeks was the honor of having Timon Cline on CrossPolitic, and we had a great time debating and discussing the differences between theonomy and what I think he and others would call classical reformed political theology &ndash; although I&rsquo;m still not convinced that they are that far apart. Meanwhile, other conversations have continued behind the scenes with friendly critics of theonomy. And then we had the follow up honor of talking to David Bahnsen about his misgivings surrounding the &ldquo;Christian Nationalism&rdquo; conversation and his preference for the &ldquo;classical liberal order.&rdquo;&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Some related factors are that sometimes advocates of &ldquo;classical liberal order&rdquo; *sound* a bit cavalier about our current cultural moment, and some, like David French, seem to have sold the whole farm to the leftists in the name of his version of the &ldquo;classical liberal order&rdquo; which seems to be code for &ldquo;surrendering slowly.&rdquo; But David Bahnsen insists that is not at all what he means or thinks. He envisions an explicitly Christian public square, but he is concerned not to make the civil sphere the central or primary actor in such an endeavor. The role of the Church and the family also need to be reinvigorated and reinforced, otherwise, you have a semi-conservative version of the current regime. And to his credit, there are some in the Reformed Christian Nationalism conversation that think it&rsquo;s perfectly reasonable for Josh Hawley to propose age limits for social media, and others have suggested taking over the public schools and turning them into explicitly Christian schools funded by tax dollars and run by departments of education. All of which, I repeat, gives me the creeping fantods.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Warm Theonomic Fuzzies</strong></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The old Puritans and Scottish Presbyterians and Genevans who first sought reinvigorate civil magistrates under the spell of Papist supremacy (hence the name &ldquo;magisterial&rdquo; Reformers) affirmed that the specific civil laws of old Israel had expired with that particular state, except for the &ldquo;general equity thereof.&rdquo; While many modern Reformed types have concluded that this means something akin to &ldquo;cute metaphors and warm fuzzy feelings,&rdquo; the actual authors of the Westminster Confession and their immediate heirs functioned as though the Old Testament civil laws had a lot more to teach us than that. The fact that the early American colonies had Sabbath civil laws and blasphemy laws and laws prohibiting sodomy and adultery and fornication and divorce, tell you that they understood &ldquo;general equity&rdquo; as including the eternal moral and ethical principles resident in those civil laws and penalties.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Now first off I want to emphasize that I think we need to have this conversation. And by &ldquo;this conversation,&rdquo; I mean, I think we need to have those of you steeped in the Reformed political tradition talking with those of us who are more steeped in the biblical studies and theonomy. Some of us need to be reading Franciscus Junius and some us need to be reading Rushdoony. I really appreciated the olive branch of sorts from Stephen Wolfe on this topic (his article on &ldquo;Classical Reformed Theonomy&rdquo;), and I also really appreciated Bahnsen&rsquo;s demeanor toward the whole thing as well.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Look, we&rsquo;ve got men in lingerie twerking in front of little kids in public parks and libraries; I think this is the moment for us to work together, not splinter into a million pieces because we didn&rsquo;t get exactly what we wanted. So first, off, I want to issue a general invite to anyone interested in recovering a truly Christian America to join the conversation in good faith. The leftist progressives rally around their common hatred of our Lord and His people, and they are frequently able to get more done together because of that shared hatred than conservatives because we throw elbows and knife one another in the back in the name of truth and morality and justice. Look, if you want to see drag queens banned from the public square, and our nation submit to the Lordship of Jesus Christ, you are most welcome to the table, even if our philosophical categories and methodologies are different. Let&rsquo;s talk. Let&rsquo;s work together. Let&rsquo;s spar, debate, and brainstorm.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>A Chastened Classical Reformed Theonomy</strong></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">And toward that end, I want to propose one way of pushing the conversation forward. One trusted and friendly critic of theonomy lamented theonomy because biblical law, he said, simply doesn&rsquo;t have enough substance to fill out a complete law code or public policy system. And I don&rsquo;t have any problem acknowledging that we need more than what is written in Scripture. As the Westminster Confession says, &ldquo;Nevertheless we acknowledge&hellip; that there are some circumstances concerning the worship of God, and the government of the church, common to human actions and societies, which are to be ordered by the light of nature and Christian prudence, according to the general rules of the Word, which are always to be observed&rdquo; (WCF 1.6). While this is primarily addressing the worship of God and the government of the church, I would argue that those activities that are &ldquo;common to human actions and societies&rdquo; would include the rational ordering of public policy and civil government, and therefore, those arrangements are to be &ldquo;according to the general rules of the Word,&rdquo; but must also &ldquo;be ordered by the light of nature and Christian prudence.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">So here&rsquo;s a practical question for my &ldquo;classical Reformed&rdquo; brothers: Since I believe that we agree that wherever Scripture establishes transcendent morality or universal principles of justice, those principles are universally binding on all societies and governments, regardless of time or place, can we agree that since we are Reformed and Protestant, those principles are &ldquo;First Principles?&rdquo; In other words, </span><em><span style="font-weight: 400;">Sola Scriptura</span></em><span style="font-weight: 400;"> (understood rightly) applies here as much as anywhere else. Sola Scriptura does not mean that Scripture is the </span><em><span style="font-weight: 400;">only</span></em><span style="font-weight: 400;"> authority, but rather, it means that Scripture is the only ultimate and infallible authority. Tradition, creeds, common law, parents, and pastors all play true authoritative roles in the life of Christians and Christian society. Nevertheless, the First Principles of Scripture are foundational, and wherever any other true authority bumps up against one of them, Scripture always wins. Are we on the same page so far?&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Now here&rsquo;s the proposal: I propose that we agree that wherever Scripture speaks on matters of universal morality and justice, those principles be nailed into the ground with enormous steel stakes (yuge ones). At that point, I would be happy to concede that all by itself, those general principles of justice are not enough to build out a modern civil law code, but since we are Protestants, we are agreed that whatever else ought to go into that law code, it must be deduced from those principles by good and necessary consequence, according to the light of nature and reason, and be consistent with them.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Now this might be where I run into trouble with critics of theonomy, but as a fiercely loyal Protestant, I also want to insist on a sort of regulative principle of power. Since all power is derived from God (Rom. 13), all power is wielded by His blessing and in submission to His ultimate power or else it is wielded in defiance of His blessing and power. Furthermore, this fits with what the Confession says regarding worship, that what is clearly stated must be explicitly obeyed, and whatever else is necessary for a flourishing society must be deduced from those principles and the light of nature. This need not be taken as tight-shoed regulative principle, but simply, as my old seminary professor, Hughes Oliphant Old, like to say, it must be &ldquo;according to Scripture,&rdquo; obedient to the commands and consistent with its principles and examples.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>A Few Stakes in the Ground</strong></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">What follows is certainly not an exhaustive list, but this will do for a start.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">First, while I do believe that civil government was instituted before the Fall and would have developed as families filled the earth, organizing society with a body of customary laws to maximize their good (deciding which side of the road to drive on, for example), the primary postlapsarian instruction and picture we are given of civil justice in the Bible captured well in the paintings and statues of Lady Justice: she is blind (or blindfolded), holding balances in one hand, and a sword in the other. This accords with the repeated instructions to the judges, &ldquo;Ye shall not respect persons in judgment; but ye shall hear the small as well as the great; ye shall not be afraid of the face of man; for the judgment is God&rsquo;s&hellip;&rdquo; (Dt. 1:17). Justice requires diligent inquiry, but that inquiry is primarily for the purpose of putting all the facts in the scales of justice. While justice requires wisdom, it is not primarily a &ldquo;creative&rdquo; task. The judgment of justice is God&rsquo;s. Diligent inquiry puts all the facts that we have in the scales, and it is the job of civil magistrates to deliver verdicts of equity, which is primarily punitive (as indicated by the sword).&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Now when I said that Josh Hawley ought not be leading the way in banning teenagers from social media since that is family/parental jurisdiction, some friends pointed out that the Bible on one occasion refers to magistrates as nursing fathers and mothers (Is. 49:23). And so it does. But that one image (which we should not abandon) cannot be made the normative image without doing great damage to the rest of Scripture. The key question of course is: how are civil magistrates to be faithful fathers and mothers? The answer is: by doing justice according to God&rsquo;s law. Isaiah 49:23 is no more a defense of Social Security, Medicare, and government schools than is Paul&rsquo;s description of himself as a father default permission for him to tell parents which breakfast cereal is right for their kids. The church is the household and family of God, but that doesn&rsquo;t mean that the church is the first line of defense for widows. Paul insists that a man that doesn&rsquo;t provide for his own family is worse than an unbeliever (1 Tim. 5:7). These natural affections, natural obligations remain firmly in place, including then the fact that the civil magistrate has no role in health, welfare, and education, unless you simply mean the role of punishing criminals and cheering churches and families on in their tasks.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Another stake to drive into the ground is the most basic principle of biblical justice: the </span><em><span style="font-weight: 400;">lex talionis</span></em><span style="font-weight: 400;">: &ldquo;Eye for eye, tooth for tooth, hand for hand, foot for foot, burning for burning, wound for wound, stripe for stripe&rdquo; (Ex. 21:24-25). A number of case laws are laid out in the biblical law that give is a lot of information about how this principle is to play out (e.g. slaves that are struck and lose an eye or tooth must be set free). Related is the principle of restitution: a thief caught stealing must return double (Ex. 22:4). Because what he sought to do his neighbor ought to be done to him to restore balance to the scales of society. If the theft is of a particularly great value, perhaps including the ability of a man/business to do his productive labor, or if the stolen item has been sold for profit that restitution may be increased to four or five-fold (Ex. 22:1).&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The penalties in the Mosaic law should also be taken seriously, and they should be understood as maximum penalties. The only required death penalty is for murder (Gen. 9). Related to this is the principle that only civil magistrates have the power of the sword, and so church and family government may not execute criminals or heretics. This is part of the glory of Dt. 21:18-19 regarding the rebellious son. In some ancient societies, a father claimed the right to execute his own children, but God&rsquo;s law forbids it. Perhaps a pagan father might have even argued &ldquo;from nature&rdquo; that since he had brought the life into the world, it was his to adjudicate, but God&rsquo;s law prohibits it. The law provides that the family government may appeal to the civil government for adjudication and potential capital punishment. But notice that until an actual crime has been committed, the civil magistrate has no jurisdiction, and the civil magistrate is only involved upon appeal from the family government. This would be one such biblical principle that would render Sen. Hawley&rsquo;s proposed social media legislation null and void.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">One of the most often cited laws in the Old Testament for explaining the continuing relevance or &ldquo;general equity&rdquo; of Mosaic law is Dt. 22:8: &ldquo;When thou buildest a new house, then thou shalt make a battlement for thy roof, that thou bring not blood upon thine house, if any man fall from thence.&rdquo; On the one hand, this certainly is an extension of the sixth commandment forbidding murder, and it certainly establishes the notion of liability for negligent homicide or battery. The general equity of this law would be rightly applied to people who refuse to put a fence around their swimming pool or a deep pit or their upstairs balcony (and arguably, reckless driving): if someone falls and dies or is injured, the home owner/driver can be held negligently liable. And the overarching principle is certainly the duty of all to take reasonable precautions to protect and preserve life.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">At the same time, some want to reason from this principle that health and building codes are therefore a reasonable application of this justice. But while it would certainly be a &ldquo;sin&rdquo; to act in high-handed negligent ways, it was not a &ldquo;crime.&rdquo; The </span><em><span style="font-weight: 400;">lex talionis</span></em><span style="font-weight: 400;"> principle requires that actual harm be measured for appropriate penalties to be exacted. But if a man built a balcony and refused to build a railing or drove recklessly through town, he may very well be in sin, but until actual damages have occurred, what penalty would truly be &ldquo;eye for eye?&rdquo; We also shouldn&rsquo;t underestimate the power and influence of the family and church governments and their related communities. Not every problem must be solved with guns and fines. Many problems should be solved by community pressures and influence.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Conclusion</strong></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The fear of the classical reformed Christian Nationalist types is that &ldquo;the classical liberal order&rdquo; is code for more liberalism, more false offers of a seat at the table of a neutral public square, and defeatism and apathy, but let us be done with all offers of neutrality, secularism, and the like.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Jesus is Lord of the public square, and the Great Commission requires us to preach and make disciples of all the nations.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">So America must confess that Jesus is Lord formally, and our laws must reflect is eternal law, as derived from Scripture and nature and reason, but with Scripture firmly ensconced as the Chief authority.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">On the other hand, my friends of the theonomic Kuyperian classical order flavor are understandably nervous that if we do not firmly root our &ldquo;Christian order&rdquo; in Rutherford&rsquo;s axiom, that the </span><em><span style="font-weight: 400;">Lex</span></em><span style="font-weight: 400;"> really is </span><em><span style="font-weight: 400;">Rex</span></em><span style="font-weight: 400;">, and that justice and the &ldquo;common good&rdquo; must be grounded in God&rsquo;s Special Revelation in Scripture, then in the name of &ldquo;the tradition&rdquo; and &ldquo;the common good&rdquo; and &ldquo;reason&rdquo; and the &ldquo;light of nature&rdquo; we will end up right back where are, a Machiavellian power grab that happens to have Christian symbols and phrases attached to it.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">It's true that the &ldquo;classical liberal order&rdquo; guys sometimes sound like power is only icky and bad, but in our determination to take responsibility for this mess of country, we must have clearly defined limits to that power. And it&rsquo;s also true that sometimes the Christian Nationalists sound like they would be willing to do anything to punch the liberals and score points. But tyranny is still tyranny even you try to defend it in the name of &ldquo;the common good.&rdquo; The &ldquo;common good&rdquo; is whatever God says it is, and nothing else. And if God has given the authority and power to wield, then we should not be afraid of it. We should take it up with boldness and joy in the name of Christ.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p><br /><br /><br /><br /></p>]]></description>
   <author><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></author>
   <enclosure url="https://app.dropwave.io/episode/3fd9e97d-1f11-4276-b95c-eb0e45b8bcef/having-two-legs-theonomy-classical-reformed-christian-nationalism-a-modest-proposal.mp3" length="1236" type="audio/mp3"/>
   <guid isPermaLink="false"><![CDATA[3fd9e97d-1f11-4276-b95c-eb0e45b8bcef]]></guid>
   <pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
   <source url=""><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></source>
   <itunes:author><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></itunes:author>
   <itunes:image href="https://prod-assets-spc1.nyc3.digitaloceanspaces.com/20dde981-157e-4504-b38f-dd9d7b0e4c50/cover-art/ZdXVos6595FpTNoyp6qYqu16EQyUrG0zPvsBPzMA.png"/>
   <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
   <itunes:duration>1236</itunes:duration>
   <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
  
  </item><item>
   <title><![CDATA[Having Two Legs: Tucker Carlson & A Case Study in Christian Nationalism & Theocratic Conservatism [Pastor Toby’s Blog]]]></title>
   <link>https://app.dropwave.io/episode/e903a7be-958f-408e-81d6-0d3f8b158fb3/having-two-legs-tucker-carlson-a-case-study-in-christian-nationalism-theocratic-conservatism.mp3</link>
   <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Tucker Carlson &amp; A Case Study in Christian Nationalism &amp; Theocratic Conservatism&nbsp;</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Introduction</strong></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">One may wonder how the algorithmic gods of the medias mutter and chirp and old clips of Tucker Carlson and Ben Shapiro emerge from the ancient shadows, but be assured that they do and when they do, they provide one with opportunities to pull your son aside, like Solomon in Proverbs and say, do you see that man? Yeah, not like that.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Now the particular clip that is currently making the rounds is from 2018, and a great deal of water has gone under the old proverbial bridge and has flowed many miles hence, even to the wild lands of Wuhan and beyond. And so one might hope that greater light has come into the great Tucker Carlson&rsquo;s eyes. I mean, if they can lock us down, close our churches, foist useless, perhaps even harmful masks on our faces, and demand injections or else you&rsquo;re a hater, a bigot, and a scoundrel, perhaps he&rsquo;s had a change of heart.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">But the clip is from when a Ben Shapiro interview of Tucker Carlson, where Tucker argues that since family is the foundational building block of society and an unmitigated good, society ought to take steps to protect it and defend it. And certain technological advances that threaten that good ought to be curbed and perhaps even prohibited. Tucker says that if we don&rsquo;t we may very soon end up with a situation where a reasonably well-adjusted college graduate (one who doesn&rsquo;t smoke pot) may not have the means to provide for himself, much less take a wife, and raise a family with her. And when pressed by Ben Shapiro about the possibility of Artificial Intelligence driving trucks on American highways, Tucker says that if he was President he would absolutely order the Department of Transportation to ban all AI on federal highways because if they didn&rsquo;t millions of jobs would be lost. And truck driving is one of the most common jobs for high school educated men in America.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Setting the Table</strong></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Now let&rsquo;s set the table carefully here. First, it&rsquo;s absolutely true that the natural family is the foundational building block of society. Second, let&rsquo;s agree that society should do everything lawfully in its power to protect and encourage family formation and flourishing. But here is where the questions begin to array themselves. What actually is &ldquo;lawfully in its power?&rdquo; Can the state simply do anything that appears to contribute to some notion of the &ldquo;common good?&rdquo; How should society protect and encourage natural family formation? My previously stated proposal is that as Protestant Christians we must begin with the clear instructions given in Scripture and then work our way out from those by good and necessary consequence, by the light of nature and Christian prudence. So I don&rsquo;t think we need an explicit Bible verse about AI and truck drivers, but I do think we need clear-eyed biblical principles.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">There are multiple problems with Tucker&rsquo;s proposal, beginning with him acting like a socialist. The assumption of socialism/Marxism is that there is no God, and therefore the state must take His place. Since there is no God to do justice, rendering unto each man what he deserves, the State takes unto itself this responsibility. Fascism need not be dark and bloody at first. It simply claims the right to command commerce and markets for the &ldquo;common good&rdquo; of society, for the good of families and family values. But it&rsquo;s still fascism and socialism for all that, even if the state is commanding Bible reading and church attendance. Don&rsquo;t misunderstand: I&rsquo;m not saying that Tucker&rsquo;s second presidential fiat would be compulsory Bible reading and church attendance. But why exactly not?&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Furthermore, these soft-socialist/fascist policies claim a kind omniscience. Tucker claims that millions of jobs will be lost in a matter of years. But this sounds like the conservative equivalent of the environmental doomsdayers. If you don&rsquo;t ban plastic bags today, the oceans will rise in five years and millions will die! Or sometimes they even notice real problems, like for example, air pollution. But as Alex Epstein has helpfully catalogued, over and over again, there&rsquo;s a certain simplistic and narrow mindset that looks at one factor and multiplies it by a million without accounting for all the other possibilities and concludes that the apocalyptic outcome is inevitable! And that&rsquo;s trying to be god while sucking at it. So when environmentalists have projected air pollution from coal and oil and other fossil fuels, what they have consistently not accounted for is adaptation, creativity, ingenuity, and improvements in technology which mitigate, minimize, and sometimes completely undo the dangers and potential harms. People, made in the image of God, are like God, and despite our fallen natures, they are generally trying to improve things.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Tucker&rsquo;s comments struck me as not only tapping into that false socialist omniscience, but they were demeaning and condescending to the very human beings he was claiming to want to protect and help, while apparently completely forgetting about other human beings in the equation. Now, it&rsquo;s an entirely open question as to whether it would ever actually work to have AI drive trucks in this country. At the very least, we would want to have a chain of liability clearly articulated, and like the goring ox in Exodus 21, require restitution and harsh penalties for any harm or damage that occurs. But why does Tucker paint the drug free college graduate like a helpless victim? Why are working class high school graduates being described as completely dependent on truck driving jobs? Can they not do anything else? A few decades ago they worked in American factories, but after the government got involved in &ldquo;helping&rdquo; them, they all got sent overseas. And here we are suggesting more Big Government involvement to help &ldquo;fix&rdquo; inequities. &ldquo;We&rsquo;re the government and we&rsquo;re here to help,&rdquo; are still the most terrifying words in the English language, even when they are in the mouth of so-called &ldquo;common good&rdquo; conservatives.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Now, the fact of the matter is that even if the tech and liabilities all got sufficiently sorted, and people started experimenting with AI truck drivers, the change wouldn&rsquo;t happen overnight. But as it started to happen (if it ever did), you would immediately be funding all the developers, troubleshooters, repairment, maintenance, and updates needed to grow and improve that new technology. The other part of the &ldquo;inevitability-omniscience&rdquo; complex is a failure to see that new technology only ever depends upon human beings creating it, maintaining, fixing it, improving, and so on. Read </span><em><span style="font-weight: 400;">Life After Google</span></em><span style="font-weight: 400;"> by George Gilder and repent of your implicit Darwinism. Artificial intelligence will always be completely dependent upon human intelligence. So just as a new technology begins to break into markets, new human jobs come into being. And this is how it has always worked. As technology changes, some folks are laid off and find new creative outlets, but all of that new technology also always creates new needs for human workers.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>The Biblical Common Good</strong></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The Biblical vision of the common good is each sphere of government exercising the power delegated to it by Christ obediently. The Magisterial Reformers were working in a particular historical moment where church government had way overreached its bounds, and part of the way you begin to limit overweening powers is by reinvigorating the balance of powers. In the days of Luther and Calvin it was absolutely necessary to call the magistrates to take up the sword of justice and push back the encroachments of the Papal See. However, we now live in an era where the state has become the Infallible Mouth of God, and it&rsquo;s high time ministers of the gospel declared the Lordship of Christ and commanded magistrates back into their own lane, while insisting that husbands and fathers, wives and mothers step up to the plate and take back their authority in the home and marketplace. Until a crime has been actually committed, it is an unjust use of violence to manipulate markets. I understand that when you live in a snake pit of market regulations the temptation is to simply join the mafia and release your own &ldquo;good&rdquo; snakes into the mix, but as we learn from one of those lesser known Mosaic principles, never bring more snakes to a snake pit unless your snake will swallow all of them and turn back into a walking stick when it&rsquo;s done.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">God has established three governments among men: the family, the church, and the state. These governments are not water-tight jurisdictions, but function more like a Venn diagram with clear differences and some overlap. God has assigned to the family the jurisdiction of health, welfare, and education. God has assigned to the church the ministry of worship and discipleship, the administration of Word and sacrament. God has assigned to the state the ministry of the sword of justice. Closely related is the difference between sins and crimes. We see this distinction beginning in the differing ministries of Abraham and Melchizedek, Moses and Aaron, as well as the differing penalties provided in the Mosaic law. When the law says that someone will be &ldquo;cut off from among his people,&rdquo; this is the ordinary discipline of Old Testament family and &ldquo;church.&rdquo; When the penalty prescribed is restitution or stripes or death, this the ministry of the sword. Now granted these are not pristine, Euclidian categories. Many of the laws in the Mosaic code have moral, ceremonial, and civil elements to them. Nevertheless, ceremonial laws were under the jurisdiction of the priests and civil laws were under the jurisdiction of the judges and magistrates. But the fact that family law was also being established in the Mosaic law is profound. Laws surrounding marriage and divorce and remarriage within families, with instructions for what might be appealed to civil magistrates for civil penalties begin to establish these jurisdictional differences.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">In other words, not all sins are or should be crimes. Covetousness is a sin but not a crime. Lying is always a sin, but not all lies should be adjudicated as crimes. Lust is a sin, even adultery in the heart, but until the lust is acted upon in fornication or adultery, there is no crime to adjudicate. A rebellious son ought to be disciplined by his own parents for many years before they determine to appeal to the civil magistrate for criminal penalties. But here is where the jurisdictions overlap: if a true biblical crime has been committed in a family or church, the civil magistrate is authorized by God to intervene. A civil magistrate my seek a warrant to arrest a father and pastor for sexual abuse. But by the same token, a father may resist or ignore tyrannical orders given a magistrate and a pastor may rebuke a magistrate and command him to repent of his sin, just as John did and lost his head for it. When a church excommunicates a professing Christian, barring them from the Lord&rsquo;s Supper and fellowship in the local church, the church is exercising its power to protect truth and morality in a society. When a family disciplines its young children teaching them Christian virtues the family government is doing its part to cultivate families and work ethics and morality. The family has the power to ultimately disinherit a son or daughter for gross immorality or apostasy. And it is the job of the state to punish crimes as defined by Scripture. No crime has been committed if a trucking company fires a driver in favor of an AI driver.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Conclusion</strong></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">In the clip mentioned, Tucker Carlson says that even though he believes in free markets it&rsquo;s not an absolute or religious commitment or requirement. He says there&rsquo;s no &ldquo;Nicene Creed of Capitalism&rdquo; he has to subscribe to. Now he&rsquo;s absolutely right if he means that free markets may not be used to justify committing crimes (e.g. theft, murder, etc.). But what Tucker is actually proposing is denying jobs and livelihoods to those working in AI, and by the making it a law, he&rsquo;s threatening the use of violence for those who try. In the name of doing good and protecting families, Tucker is proposing that he be the one who gets to choose the winners and the losers. Truckers are the winners; programmers and new tech are the losers. Sorry, the gods have spoken. We know what&rsquo;s best for you. And actually, we&rsquo;ve decided that cars have taken too many jobs away from horses and mules. So yeah, we&rsquo;re going back to the Middle Ages, you greedy capitalist pigs. But seriously, where&rsquo;s the line?&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Ok, I&rsquo;ll stop here. Tucker says there&rsquo;s no Nicene Creed of capitalism, and that&rsquo;s true enough, but there is a Nicene Creed that says that God is the &ldquo;Father Almighty, Maker of Heaven and earth, and of all things visible and invisible&hellip;&rdquo; Invisible things would include market forces, the creativity and ingenuity of men, as well as their created needs and desires.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Until or unless God gives a government the authority to step in, it is a violation of the Nicene Creed to grasp power for yourself and violently or coercively prohibit the free actions and creativity of people.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">It must always be remembered that if the primary power of the state is the power of the sword, then whenever you call for a &ldquo;ban,&rdquo; you are simultaneously calling for the use of violent, coercive force to be used if someone disregards the ban. I&rsquo;m sorry, but we just had a few years of a police state trial run in the West with law enforcement fining churches for being open, for mandated gags on peoples&rsquo; faces, and frog marching decent law-abiding citizens off to jail for singing songs in public.&nbsp;&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">I do believe in the &ldquo;common good,&rdquo; but the common good is determined by God&rsquo;s Word and not simplistic, short-sighted calculations. It was those kinds of simplistic, short-sighted calculations that the Imperial College of London used to insight the COVID panic. So, no thanks. God&rsquo;s world is more resilient, more complex, more glorious than that.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p><br /><br /><br /><br /></p>]]></description>
   <author><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></author>
   <enclosure url="https://app.dropwave.io/episode/e903a7be-958f-408e-81d6-0d3f8b158fb3/having-two-legs-tucker-carlson-a-case-study-in-christian-nationalism-theocratic-conservatism.mp3" length="1084" type="audio/mp3"/>
   <guid isPermaLink="false"><![CDATA[e903a7be-958f-408e-81d6-0d3f8b158fb3]]></guid>
   <pubDate>Mon, 20 Feb 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
   <source url=""><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></source>
   <itunes:author><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></itunes:author>
   <itunes:image href="https://prod-assets-spc1.nyc3.digitaloceanspaces.com/20dde981-157e-4504-b38f-dd9d7b0e4c50/cover-art/ZdXVos6595FpTNoyp6qYqu16EQyUrG0zPvsBPzMA.png"/>
   <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
   <itunes:duration>1084</itunes:duration>
   <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
  
  </item><item>
   <title><![CDATA[Having Two Legs: The Dignity of Guilt [Pastor Toby’s Blog]]]></title>
   <link>https://app.dropwave.io/episode/fb3f8628-6d3e-444d-a19e-ef6ea8588e58/having-two-legs-the-dignity-of-guilt.mp3</link>
   <description><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The Dignity of Guilt</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">One of the most loving and dignifying things God does for human beings is insist that they take responsibility for their sin. This is one of the fundamental meanings of the words of Christ: If anyone tries to save his life, he will lose it, but if he loses it for my sake, he will find it.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">We live in a world that makes excuses for everything, blames other people, circumstances, and wants to constantly play the victim, but the deep irony is that all excuse making is dehumanizing. Every time you blame someone else you sell your soul, you become less human. In our effort to save our life, our dignity, our value we actually cheapen the impact of our own choices, decisions, thoughts, words, and reactions. The end result of blaming others is that your actions don&rsquo;t matter, you don&rsquo;t matter. How could you matter? By that standard, nothing you do does anything. You were angry because of the kids. You lied because of that other person. You&rsquo;re depressed because of your dad. You snapped because you didn&rsquo;t get enough sleep or you missed breakfast. But what you&rsquo;re doing with every one of those excuses is selling your dignity as a human being, and fundamentally you are defying the God who made you in His image.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">You do not have the right to be offended. You do not have the right to sin. And so, one of the kindest, most loving things God comes to do is to dignify every human being with the sentence of guilty. No, you are not nothing. You are not worthless. You are not a mere victim of circumstances. No, you are a man; you are woman made with intelligence and the power of choice, and you have sinned. You have loved evil and hated good. You have hurt yourself and you have hurt others. And yes, you have been hurt and wronged, but you always had the responsibility to choose to respond with patience, kindness, and love. We are guilty. We deserve death. We are sinful and unclean. And the moment we tell the truth and take responsibility for our sins, Christ offers to take our sins away and promises to raise us up with the dignifying power of His grace.</span></p>
<p><br /><br style="font-weight: 400;" /></p>]]></description>
   <author><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></author>
   <enclosure url="https://app.dropwave.io/episode/fb3f8628-6d3e-444d-a19e-ef6ea8588e58/having-two-legs-the-dignity-of-guilt.mp3" length="167" type="audio/mp3"/>
   <guid isPermaLink="false"><![CDATA[fb3f8628-6d3e-444d-a19e-ef6ea8588e58]]></guid>
   <pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
   <source url=""><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></source>
   <itunes:author><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></itunes:author>
   <itunes:image href="https://prod-assets-spc1.nyc3.digitaloceanspaces.com/20dde981-157e-4504-b38f-dd9d7b0e4c50/cover-art/ZdXVos6595FpTNoyp6qYqu16EQyUrG0zPvsBPzMA.png"/>
   <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
   <itunes:duration>167</itunes:duration>
   <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
  
  </item><item>
   <title><![CDATA[Having Two Legs: Real School Choice & Conservative Chimpanzees [Pastor Toby’s Blog]]]></title>
   <link>https://app.dropwave.io/episode/929fbe3f-8f11-4ff7-809a-23b23c943f26/having-two-legs-real-school-choice-conservative-chimpanzees.mp3</link>
   <description><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Blog Post</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Real School Choice &amp; Conservative Chimpanzees</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Introduction</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Joe Biden recently got a bunch of Republicans to do what Democrats have been trying to do for decades: get them to embrace socialism. Ok, most Republicans are soft-socialists nowadays anyway, but Sleepy Joe got most of the Republican side of Congress to stand up and cheer for socialism during his recent State of the Union address. He got them to boo his accusation that they weren&rsquo;t true blue socialists, and then when he asked if they were in, they stood up and cheered. Biden played them like a drum, and the next day CNN had Republican representatives doubling and tripling down on it. It was masterful, if it wasn&rsquo;t so sad.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Of course the topic was Social Security and whether the Federal Government should take care of our parents and grandparents. Republicans are idiots. Republicans are fools. There was a masterful opportunity to take and they missed it. They took the bait. They bowed and scraped at the altar of the Almighty Sugar Daddy State, almost as if they had already completely forgotten about 2020. It would have been a glorious moment for conservatives to stand up and speak clearly into the microphone. How many of our parents and grandparents died alone in nursing homes? How many were locked down, isolated, deprived of personal care, familial affection, and honor? Don&rsquo;t you understand that our twisted nursing home culture is a direct result of looking to the state to take care of our parents and grandparents?&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Yes, we absolutely want to sunset Social Security. Absolutely. All day long, every day of the week. Is there no conservative willing to stand up for our parents and grandparents, who will insist that everything the Federal government does that is outside of its God-ordained assignment is inefficient, cumbersome, and ultimately sucks at whatever it is they are trying to do? All you need to do is go down to your local DMV. OK, how about the IRS? Biden had the audacity to claim that as the (apparently) new CEO of every major industry in America he was ordering sweeping changes, prohibiting various fees and surcharges, particularly for the airline industry, including for the privilege of having your family sit together. Biden is tired, he says, of treating children like baggage. But of course if a mother wanted to treat one of her more challenging children like baggage, why couldn&rsquo;t she? I mean, an unborn child requires a whole lot of energy and care, and with Biden&rsquo;s help, he believes she ought to be able to go down to the local Planned Parenthood (and for a small fee), unload that so-called &ldquo;baggage.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Where was I? Sorry, I got a bit distracted. But the point is that the same goons who can&rsquo;t tell the difference between baggage and children want to take care of your elderly parents and grandparents, and the whole Republican side of congress stood up and cheered, like a bunch of chimpanzees clapping for bananas.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Arizona ESAs &amp; My Vigorous Misgivings</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Ok, but here&rsquo;s the real point of this post: a whole bunch of conservatives are doing the same thing with &ldquo;school choice&rdquo; and Educational Savings Accounts (ESAs). I posted a lengthy thread last week after reading through the Arizona ESA program which is currently being heralded by many conservatives and school choice advocates as the &ldquo;model&rdquo; legislation. But the really short version can be summarized by the immortal words of Admiral Ackbar in Star Wars: &ldquo;It&rsquo;s a trap!&rdquo;&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">But I don&rsquo;t merely want to repeat what I said previously about all my misgivings. All those misgivings are still alive and well and they&rsquo;ve even grown a third eye and developed a vigorous twitch. But what I want to do is quickly review my findings from the Arizona ESA legislation and then bring this thing in for a landing with a plea for conservatives to see a really glorious opportunity in the &ldquo;school choice&rdquo; discussion if only we don&rsquo;t act like most of our Republican leaders in congress, so long as we don&rsquo;t bark and clap like a seal simply because they say some conservative-ish sounding words. Don&rsquo;t get sucked into embracing more socialism by Joe Biden or his Republican colleagues. Yeah, as the kids like to say, that was a pretty sick burn.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">So first, my findings: While the Arizona ESA program claims that &ldquo;each student&rsquo;s funding follows the student,&rdquo; the legislation only actually allows for $6,500 of the student&rsquo;s funding to follow the student. I might have a tiny ounce of hope that this was at least moving in the right direction, except that more than $11,000 is spent by the state and local taxpayers on each public school student, and that doesn&rsquo;t count all federal dollars on top of that, all of which continue going to the government schools. For every student that opts into the Arizona ESA program, over $600 additional dollars are immediately added back to the public school that they left, even though that student no longer attends that school. So tips galore. And if that weren&rsquo;t enough, the fact sheet defending the Arizona ESAs boasts: &ldquo;In fact, the rapid growth in Arizona&rsquo;s ESA program has tracked closely with major increases in per pupil funding for public schools over the past decade&hellip;&rdquo; As proof of that trajectory continuing, the fact sheet assures us that a companion bill has been introduced in the Arizona legislature to add $400 million additional funds to public schools, designated for all public school districts and charter schools.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Pause here for just a moment for me to make a comment about conservatives and rhetoric. When I posted these findings on Facebook, a friend from another state pushed back a bit about my Debby-downer appraisal of the program and linked to several conservative sites praising the Arizona legislation. I cheerfully clicked on the link, and the first sentence I read was this: &ldquo;First, the left told us that school choice would decimate the funding of public education. But then, Arizona passed the nation&rsquo;s first universal education savings account (ESA) program last year, and funding for the state&rsquo;s public schools still went up nearly a billion dollars even as tens of thousands of kids have joined the ESA program.&rdquo;&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Now regardless of the exact details of the ESA program or where the funding is coming from, you just lost me. This website is a Republican clapping like a seal for Joe Biden socialism. At the very least, this website doesn&rsquo;t understand what conservatives actually want. I don&rsquo;t want to increase funding for government schools. I want to </span><em><span style="font-weight: 400;">decrease</span></em><span style="font-weight: 400;"> funding for government schools. I want to dismantle government schools. I want to see them closed down. What&rsquo;s the word I&rsquo;m looking for? Ah right, I want to see government schools </span><em><span style="font-weight: 400;">sunset</span></em><span style="font-weight: 400;">.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Why? Because I&rsquo;m not a communist.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">I&rsquo;m not sure how to break this to you, but one of the central tenets of Marxism in the Communist Manifesto is &ldquo;Free education for all children in public schools.&rdquo; And of course by &ldquo;free&rdquo; Marx meant &ldquo;pounded out of your flesh in taxes whether you use them or not.&rdquo;&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Now, I&rsquo;m not a communist so that is also why I am not a revolutionary, and I would be happy to slowly sunset public education. I would be happy to nickel and dime the damn thing to death. But what I don&rsquo;t want to do is to take incremental steps to invigorate, strengthen, and expand government education corruption and power. When some of my more revolutionary friends wondered why I&rsquo;m willing to end abortion incrementally but not public education, I replied: &ldquo;I actually would support true incremental steps toward school choice, but if a 15wk abortion ban gave $400mil to Planned Parenthood, I would oppose it for the same reason.&rdquo; You don&rsquo;t dismantle something by giving it more money.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">When I asked my friend about this massive increase in spending on education, the reply said that this represents the ordinary increases in education budgets, which might be true, but if so, I&rsquo;m still against that. If an educational system has fewer students, they should have fewer dollars, not more. The incentives here are perverse. Less for more? That isn&rsquo;t capitalism. That isn&rsquo;t a free market. And ultimately all that money has to come from taxes. If this continues, tax payers could find themselves paying the same amount of money as before (or more) even with the $6500 dollar ESA boost.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Ok, back to the Arizona ESA program.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Not only is millions and perhaps a billion more dollars in public school funding a massive increase in the government school budget and funding in Arizona, the program is also the beginning of government oversight of private schools and homeschooling. The text of the Arizona ESA expansion bill explicitly requires that the curriculum ESAs are spent on must be approved by the Arizona department of education. Perhaps this approval will begin as something relatively benign, but if you think it&rsquo;s going to stay that way, you haven&rsquo;t been paying attention. Next, a &ldquo;qualified school&rdquo; includes your standard government &ldquo;non-discrimination&rdquo; clause, currently specifying race, color, or national origin. But if you don&rsquo;t think that will soon include sexual orientation, sexual identity, and puppy-lovers, I&rsquo;ve got a beachfront property in Kansas to sell you.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">I firmly believe in school choice, and I also believe that our actual education dollars should follow the students, but I&rsquo;m not aware of any &ldquo;school choice&rdquo; program that is honestly allowing the actual student funding to follow the student wherever their parents choose to send them to school. Of course, it should be remembered that tax dollars actually belong to the tax payers, and if we&rsquo;re talking about money for education, real school choice would include the freedom not to pay taxes for schools we don&rsquo;t use. I know this is a really radical notion, but I think it&rsquo;s a winning point: people shouldn&rsquo;t be forced to pay for goods and services they don&rsquo;t use. Parents shouldn&rsquo;t be forced to pay for schools they have decided are not best for their children. We don&rsquo;t force parents to send checks to certain doctors and medical providers, regardless of where they receive their medical care. Why would we do that with education? The name of this is socialism.&nbsp;&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">At the very least, if we cannot completely opt out (monetarily) of schools that we have decided are not best for our children, how about tax credits that simply refund our real tax dollars that we didn&rsquo;t actually use on government schools? I don&rsquo;t think they should have taken our money for a service we don&rsquo;t use in the first place, but I would certainly be OK with at least getting that money back. That would seem to me to be an incremental step in the right direction.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">All of this demonstrates that government education is a mafia with a monopoly using our tax-payer dollars to rig the system and make it more difficult for hard working Americans to provide the education they believe is best for their kids. Perhaps the one silver lining in all of this is simply the indication that government school mobsters can be bought off. I would urge somebody with connections to broker a deal with some big tech company (where you at Elon?), offering to infuse some state coffers with bazillions of dollars in exchange for two things: a number of seats on the state board of education and the real freedom of choice for parents to completely opt out of the system: keeping their tax dollars and spending their money on whatever educational program they desire.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Thus far my diatribe on Twitter, closing with &ldquo;In the meantime, remember that everything the government funds is inefficient, corrupt, has strings attached, and ultimately goes woke and bad.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Now I really don&rsquo;t mean this post as merely a whine-session, and I know there are many well-meaning conservatives (that are not Chimpanzees) that are simply interested in seeing the government monopoly broken. And count me as a reasonable incrementalist. I don&rsquo;t need a perfect bill to support. I&rsquo;m no perfectionist. I&rsquo;m a reformer; not a revolutionary. All I need is a bill that actually nudges us in the direction of real school choice, real educational freedom, and a truly free market for education.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Conclusion</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">So I&rsquo;ll end here simply with a plea for conservative rhetoric. I think we really do have an important opportunity right in front of us with the school choice discussion. And I am not at all calling for conservatives to be purists who can&rsquo;t be pleased with any compromise. But we also need to have a very clear idea of what we are aiming for. If we are not aiming for true educational freedom, true school choice, which means parents having the true freedom to use their own money to pay for whatever education they deem best for their children, then we will not know which direction we&rsquo;re going or even if we&rsquo;re making any progress at all. When you have no destination in mind, anywhere seems like progress.&nbsp;&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">I think there&rsquo;s a glorious opportunity for real progress in terms of practical policies, and I think with that opportunity is an opportunity to change the conversation. Let&rsquo;s talk about real educational choice and freedom. Let&rsquo;s talk about the sovereignty of parents over the educational choices of their children. Virginia Governor Youngkin was arguably elected partially on the steam of the claims of educational fascists who claimed that the experts and school boards and departments of education trumped parents, especially in the wake of a transgender bathroom assault. Do you see that opening? They are cramming CRT and sexual confusion down the throats of preschoolers. If Christian and conservative parents stand up and say enough is enough, we can make a difference. But the goal needs to be clear: we are not socialists; we are not communists.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">We believe in freedom of choice, parental sovereignty, and we refuse to be charged for an education system that hates us and hates our values. We want to keep our hard earned money and spend it on the education that we believe is best for our children. We want a level playing field, a truly free market for education, with schools competing without government intrusion, without the government putting its fingers on the scales. Let&rsquo;s change the conversation. Let&rsquo;s brainstorm. Let&rsquo;s invite our brightest minds and legislators together, and let&rsquo;s craft something better. Let&rsquo;s craft something that is actually moving towards freedom. And I&rsquo;m not just saying this, I&rsquo;m having conversations with key players to do this very thing, and I hope to have more to share on this very soon.&nbsp;&nbsp;</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&nbsp;</span></p>
<p><br /><br /></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Read it all for yourself:</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://azsbe.az.gov/empowerment-scholarship-account-esa-program</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.azleg.gov/legtext/55leg/2R/summary/H.HB2853_061422_WM.DOCX.htm</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://www.azleg.gov/legtext/55leg/2R/bills/HB2853P.pdf</span></p>
<p><br /><br /></p>]]></description>
   <author><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></author>
   <enclosure url="https://app.dropwave.io/episode/929fbe3f-8f11-4ff7-809a-23b23c943f26/having-two-legs-real-school-choice-conservative-chimpanzees.mp3" length="964" type="audio/mp3"/>
   <guid isPermaLink="false"><![CDATA[929fbe3f-8f11-4ff7-809a-23b23c943f26]]></guid>
   <pubDate>Tue, 14 Feb 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
   <source url=""><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></source>
   <itunes:author><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></itunes:author>
   <itunes:image href="https://prod-assets-spc1.nyc3.digitaloceanspaces.com/20dde981-157e-4504-b38f-dd9d7b0e4c50/cover-art/ZdXVos6595FpTNoyp6qYqu16EQyUrG0zPvsBPzMA.png"/>
   <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
   <itunes:duration>964</itunes:duration>
   <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
  
  </item><item>
   <title><![CDATA[Having Two Legs: Tyre Nichols & Systemic Oppression & Blessing [Pastor Toby’s Blog]]]></title>
   <link>https://app.dropwave.io/episode/a5ecbfbc-5927-43f4-a2c5-d5d866e9e9ee/having-two-legs-tyre-nichols-systemic-oppression-blessing.mp3</link>
   <description><![CDATA[<p>In this episode of Having Two Legs, Pastor Toby Sumpter lays out a Biblical stand on Tyre Nichols, Systemic Oppression, and the blessings of Covenant.<span class="Apple-converted-space">&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&ldquo;But in the real world, the world that God made, all authority and power is derived from God. God is over all.&rdquo;</p>]]></description>
   <author><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></author>
   <enclosure url="https://app.dropwave.io/episode/a5ecbfbc-5927-43f4-a2c5-d5d866e9e9ee/having-two-legs-tyre-nichols-systemic-oppression-blessing.mp3" length="676" type="audio/mp3"/>
   <guid isPermaLink="false"><![CDATA[a5ecbfbc-5927-43f4-a2c5-d5d866e9e9ee]]></guid>
   <pubDate>Mon, 06 Feb 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
   <source url=""><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></source>
   <itunes:author><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></itunes:author>
   <itunes:image href="https://prod-assets-spc1.nyc3.digitaloceanspaces.com/20dde981-157e-4504-b38f-dd9d7b0e4c50/cover-art/ZdXVos6595FpTNoyp6qYqu16EQyUrG0zPvsBPzMA.png"/>
   <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
   <itunes:duration>676</itunes:duration>
   <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
  
  </item><item>
   <title><![CDATA[Having Two Legs: Table Fellowship [Pastor Toby’s Blog]]]></title>
   <link>https://app.dropwave.io/episode/da27a960-2d07-46cd-9bf6-f44c90f61ed8/having-two-legs-table-fellowship.mp3</link>
   <description><![CDATA[<p dir="ltr">Table Fellowship</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">This is a table of communion and fellowship. This is why we call it Communion. It is communion with God, and it is communion with God&rsquo;s people. This is why Paul told the Corinthians that when they came together to eat this meal it was not really the Lord&rsquo;s Supper. There were divisions among the Corinthians, rivalries, resentments, and elbows being thrown. You can&rsquo;t celebrate communion while being out of communion with God or your neighbor. It says that when the Corinthians tried to do that many of them got sick and some had even died.&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">In the Old Testament, when the Israelites complained against God that there was no meat to eat in the wilderness, He gave them quail, but that meat became poison to all those with evil hearts. Likewise, God told Israel that if a man suspected his wife of adultery, he could bring her to the tabernacle and the priest could give her a drink that would function as a jealousy test. In some ways, this table functions like that. If you are in fellowship with God and one another, this bread and cup are grace and strength and blessing. But if you come to this table harboring secret sins, or grievances or out of fellowship with someone, you need to know that by eating and drinking, you are inviting Christ in. Christ is here, and this is communion with Christ. But if you eat and drink communion while trying to preserve disunion, divisions, and strife, this meal will be a curse.&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">The answer is not to abstain from this table. If you are baptized, you really must come. Don&rsquo;t cling to your sin and abstain from the meal. Rather, let go of your sin now. Drop your sin now. Determine in your heart right now to kill that sin, to confess it, to forsake it, to be reconciled to your brother or sister as soon as possible. If you do that, then this meal will strengthen you for that fight, strengthen you to do what needs to be done.&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p dir="ltr">So look around as you share this meal. Smile at your wife, your husband, your kids, your parents, your roommates, your friends. Is all well? Or do you need to lean over and whisper an apology and forgiveness to someone? Do it. This is communion. This is the communion of the Lord Jesus Christ, whose blood reconciles every sin. So come and welcome to Jesus Christ.&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>]]></description>
   <author><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></author>
   <enclosure url="https://app.dropwave.io/episode/da27a960-2d07-46cd-9bf6-f44c90f61ed8/having-two-legs-table-fellowship.mp3" length="167" type="audio/mp3"/>
   <guid isPermaLink="false"><![CDATA[da27a960-2d07-46cd-9bf6-f44c90f61ed8]]></guid>
   <pubDate>Sat, 04 Feb 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
   <source url=""><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></source>
   <itunes:author><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></itunes:author>
   <itunes:image href="https://prod-assets-spc1.nyc3.digitaloceanspaces.com/20dde981-157e-4504-b38f-dd9d7b0e4c50/cover-art/ZdXVos6595FpTNoyp6qYqu16EQyUrG0zPvsBPzMA.png"/>
   <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
   <itunes:duration>167</itunes:duration>
   <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
  
  </item><item>
   <title><![CDATA[Having Two Legs: Dressing for The King [Pastor Toby’s Blog]]]></title>
   <link>https://app.dropwave.io/episode/fc2952de-8dca-424a-a1bb-adb9ca2a4719/having-two-legs-dressing-for-the-king.mp3</link>
   <description><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Exhortation</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Dressing for the King</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">God meets us where we are, not where we should have been. This means that when someone walks into church off the street smelling and looking like the world, they are most welcome. Jesus welcomed us in our sins, and therefore, sinners of every stripe are most welcome. Come and welcome to Jesus Christ. But part of the glory of this grace is that it doesn&rsquo;t leave us there. God&rsquo;s grace changes us; it restores us and glorifies us to the kind of human beings we were created to be.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">This is part of why historically, the church has sought to dress for the occasion. We dress up for church because we are meeting with our King, and we dress up because we believe that this is part of what the King is doing in us and for us. He is taking our old sinful rags and giving us His royal robes of righteousness. He has done this definitively in Jesus Christ, but He is doing this progressively as we are changed from glory to glory, as we grow into Jesus Christ. We have no interest in turning this into any kind of fashion show: whether the hypocrisy of Pharisees in their long robes or the hypocrisy of showboating, with fancy suits or gaudy jewelry. What we are aiming for is simplicity and thoughtfulness. Giving thought to simple, modest dressing up for church can be one easy way to show honor for God and the occasion of worship and show kindness to one another.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p><br /><br /></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The focal point of worship is Jesus, not you, and not your comfort. Of course in our world tastes, preferences, and styles vary, and we really don&rsquo;t want to be cranky or legalistic at all. But flipflops and sweatpants generally communicate that something is casual and not very important, while tuxedos and low cut blouses or short skirts communicate &ldquo;hey everybody, look at me.&rdquo; It&rsquo;s striking that in Timothy, Paul says that men need to make sure that they are worshiping free of all wrath and doubting and women need to make sure they are worshiping modestly, without showing off their bodies or jewelry or hair. As Hebrews says, let us worship acceptably with reverence and fear; for our God is a consuming fire.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p><br /><br style="font-weight: 400;" /></p>]]></description>
   <author><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></author>
   <enclosure url="https://app.dropwave.io/episode/fc2952de-8dca-424a-a1bb-adb9ca2a4719/having-two-legs-dressing-for-the-king.mp3" length="160" type="audio/mp3"/>
   <guid isPermaLink="false"><![CDATA[fc2952de-8dca-424a-a1bb-adb9ca2a4719]]></guid>
   <pubDate>Wed, 01 Feb 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
   <source url=""><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></source>
   <itunes:author><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></itunes:author>
   <itunes:image href="https://prod-assets-spc1.nyc3.digitaloceanspaces.com/20dde981-157e-4504-b38f-dd9d7b0e4c50/cover-art/ZdXVos6595FpTNoyp6qYqu16EQyUrG0zPvsBPzMA.png"/>
   <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
   <itunes:duration>160</itunes:duration>
   <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
  
  </item><item>
   <title><![CDATA[Having Two Legs: School Choice [Pastor Toby’s Blog]]]></title>
   <link>https://app.dropwave.io/episode/65a595b2-e943-413b-a00a-eddf48965d53/having-two-legs-school-choice.mp3</link>
   <description><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">School Choice</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Introduction</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Whenever something sounds too good to be true, the rule of any sane person should be to consider it a scam until proven otherwise. When you get that email from that Saudi Arabian Prince wanting to share his inheritance with you, I&rsquo;m no financial advisor or Middle Eastern political dilettante, but I advise you to use your trash button vigorously.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">So when a movement begins picking up steam calling for &ldquo;school choice,&rdquo; thoughtful Christians and conservatives should have all their hackles done up for a party and their rhetorical guns at the ready. Remember, we live in a land that celebrates &ldquo;choice,&rdquo; and that means murdering babies. We live in a land that celebrates &ldquo;choice,&rdquo; and grooms little kids into sexual confusion and madness, secretly castrates teenagers without parental knowledge or consent, and demands you take injections of unspecified content because&hellip; shut up, you bigot.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">That&rsquo;s the world we live in. So when people begin heralding a new found freedom of choice, freedom to choose whatever school you want your children to attend, dollars following kids, and so on, it would be good, healthy even, to get all of your defenses up, and maybe even pull out a few knives. This is the exact same scene of many crimes in our land. Your cursor should be hovering over that trash button.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Don&rsquo;t get me wrong. I think we should exploit every opportunity to dismantle the government education monopoly. I think we should ride every bit of this wave to press for real educational freedom and parental sovereignty and responsibility, but conservative Christians have a bad habit of being manipulated through soundbites and ending up in worse positions than before.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">So let&rsquo;s review. Currently, as far as I know, the way government education works in the United States is that everyone who owns property pays into a state fund, that state fund is augmented by various federal programs and subsidies, which are taken of course from federal income taxes, and then those moneys are redistributed to counties and school districts based on various state guidelines, including number of children enrolled in school.&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">This means that parents who do not want to send their children to public schools, must pay into the government education programs via property taxes even though you don&rsquo;t use the program, and don&rsquo;t forget that if you pay rent, you are still paying into the program via your monthly rent. Your landlord is making sure that your rent covers all his property taxes. This is educational welfare, redistribution, and unjust taxation. Millions of Americans have defied this educational socialism and Marxism by bearing the costs of home schooling and private schooling on top of the taxes they are already paying for government schools they don&rsquo;t use.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">This is why I tweeted recently: &ldquo;One of the greatest modern rebellions has been the homeschool/private school movement: millions of Americans making the sacrifice to pay tuition/costs on top of their taxes, effectively paying tuition twice. The next step is getting our tax money back with no strings attached.&rdquo;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Which brings us to the so-called &ldquo;school choice&rdquo; movement. I would love to be wrong about this. I would love to find out that some state really is letting parents completely opt out of government regulation, government coercion, and government redistribution for education. But as far as I know, the &ldquo;school choice&rdquo; programs being pushed are actually an expansion of government regulation and redistribution and no lessening of the foundational coercion involved in the unjust taxation.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The most common program being championed by &ldquo;school choice&rdquo; advocates right now are ESA&rsquo;s &ndash; Education Savings Accounts. In these programs, the state agrees to deposit money in a savings account for qualified parents to use on qualified educational programs. The key words in that last sentence are &ldquo;state&rdquo; and &ldquo;qualified&rdquo; and &ldquo;qualified.&rdquo; This tells you most of what you need to know. In these schemes, the &ldquo;state&rdquo; is still claiming sovereignty over the educational venture, and this is proven by the fact that the state is determining which families are &ldquo;qualified&rdquo; to have some of their money back and which educational programs are &ldquo;qualified&rdquo; to receive those monies.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Now I&rsquo;m happy to grant that there may be some short term wins for parents in these programs. A poor, single mom that wants to send her kids to a Classical Christian school suddenly has the tuition dollars and doesn&rsquo;t feel trapped in the public school where her kids are being brainwashed all day long. I totally get it. But we are Christians, and we have to think further ahead than the next five minutes.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">But first, while I have all kinds of compassion for that single mom, I want to insist that a community that has not already given her all kinds of resources to pull her kids out of government schools and enroll them in a Christian option of her choice is a community that is not ready for a gush of greenbacks from the government teat. The community that has not already declared war on the communism inherent in government schools and made the great sacrifices to evacuate their children from those occupied territories is not a community that has proven to have the wisdom, discernment, or compassion necessary to see through this minefield.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Second, consider the fallout of expanded government redistribution and regulation. We&rsquo;ve already seen this in higher education. What happened over the last forty years with Pell grants and government loans? Our higher education system has gone to Hell. And I mean that literally. Even most of the so-called Christian colleges and universities are loaded up with Diversity Inclusion and Equity clowns. The current is so strong that even Grove City College, one of the only colleges in the nation that doesn&rsquo;t take government money, is in the thick of controversy over diversity and woke policies. I know of a young woman personally who was forced to leave during COVID because she refused to comply with their anti-science masking regime.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">What will the result be of government funding through ESAs? Mass compromise. Why? Because money ill-gotten corrupts. That money being put in your ESA? That&rsquo;s blood money. Property taxes are an evil and immoral stain on our land since they imply that if you don&rsquo;t pay taxes on the land and home that you &ldquo;own,&rdquo; they may be seized to pay for your back taxes, which essentially means that you are in a long term lease agreement with the government for your so-called property. So much for private property.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The impact of these wicked laws is wide ranging, but landing on the elderly and others with fixed incomes the hardest. As communities grow and develop, home and property values tend to rise, and with values rising, taxes rise. An elderly widow whose husband faithfully provided for her will often find it difficult to continue paying rising property taxes and be forced to sell her family estate. This is nothing short of Ahab&rsquo;s theft of Naboth&rsquo;s Vineyard in slow motion. If Ahab offers to let you use some of Naboth&rsquo;s vineyard for a garden, is it moral to take him up on that offer?&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Please don&rsquo;t misunderstand me. I am not arguing that all taxation is theft. I&rsquo;m simply arguing that taxation of property, with the implicit threat of seizing assets if you don&rsquo;t pay, is highway robbery in a bureaucratic business suit, even if the measure passed by 99% of the vote.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">It&rsquo;s never OK to demand someone pay you something they don&rsquo;t want or use with the threat of stealing their stuff if they don&rsquo;t pay you.Everything the government funds ends up costing more and driving quality down. If you don&rsquo;t think that will happen with ESAs there&rsquo;s a Saudi Arabian prince I&rsquo;d like to introduce you to.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">When money is more easily gotten, the pressure to raise prices increases. But when the money easily gotten is not based on real goods and services (real values), those price increases are simply inflation. And when you start down a path of incrementally accepting more money without a corresponding demand for increasing quality or quantity, you are already accepting a downgrade of quality. Again, I refer you to the American college scene, where billions of dollars are not only being spent to brainwash future teachers, doctors, and lawyers into believing Darwinian and Marxist lies, but they are also doing so with waterslides, climbing walls, jacuzzis, and dormitory amenities that keep STD rates high and virginity rates low.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Conclusion</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">I&rsquo;ve heard some proposing &ldquo;school choice&rdquo; in the form of tax credits. The plus side of tax credits would be relative lack of strings attached. The downside would still be the government pretending to have the authority to take our money in the first place. This would also likely continue to include some measure of redistribution since tax credits are often awarded based on income levels, granting larger credits to those with lower incomes. If tax credits were matched to actual taxation payments that would be even closer to giving people back the money stolen from them, but then why do we continue to allow our money to be taken in the first place? On what planet is it OK for the government to require you to pay for services that you object to, that you refuse, that you aren&rsquo;t using? If Christians have gotten their heads around the need to defund Planned Parenthood because we object to our tax dollars funding the murder of little babies, why can&rsquo;t we get our heads around the right of parents to decide how to spend their own money on the education of their own children? Why can&rsquo;t we simply demand the right to opt out?</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The cry and hue goes up that unless the state provides education, the poor will suffer, and the social and economic impact will be disastrous. But this really is ridiculous, government programs have the worst track records. They are bloated with regulations, red tape, and nuisance bureaucracy. The government insisting that if they don&rsquo;t take care of education, the poor will suffer, is like an obese man insisting that if he doesn&rsquo;t run the exercise and nutrition programs everyone will be sick and unhealthy. Just look at San Fransisco, Seattle, Portland. Look at those Marxist utopian paradises. Our answer needs to simply be that we will take care of our own poor, thank you very much. You have done quite enough, Mr. Fat Ass Government. Get your greasy paws off our schools.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">I suspect that there are backroom deals being made with these &ldquo;school choice&rdquo; programs. I suspect that Big Tech and Big Business are somewhere in those backrooms pulling strings.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Education is a massive business (like health care), and if you don&rsquo;t think there&rsquo;s corruption involved have I told you that I&rsquo;m a Saudi Arabian prince with a gold mine I need to unload? While there is some resistance on the Left that might make &ldquo;school choice&rdquo; seem like a real suckerpunch to their beloved Democrat training centers, er, I mean schools, Christians must understand that they do not have any real &ldquo;school choice,&rdquo; until they have full and complete choice over how to spend their own money for their own children.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">If we&rsquo;re going to make some kind of deal, the deal has to include the right of parents to opt out of the government education system. Since the god of Big Tech and Big Government is Mammon, I would suggest trying to broker a deal between some corporate fat cats and government fat cats. Could we convince the true believers in government education to let us leave this Egypt if they could give all their teachers a raise and every student a laptop and lifetime supply of condoms because Google is buying a few seats on the State Education board? Short of a radical gospel Reformation in our land, we need to be thinking and praying strategically. Can we off them a deal they can&rsquo;t refuse so that we can get out? But convincing them to let us use some of the money they stole isn&rsquo;t really a jailbreak; it&rsquo;s more like building an addition on the jail and letting you invite your school to use the new &ldquo;wing.&rdquo;&nbsp;</span></p>
<p><br /><br /><br /><br /></p>]]></description>
   <author><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></author>
   <enclosure url="https://app.dropwave.io/episode/65a595b2-e943-413b-a00a-eddf48965d53/having-two-legs-school-choice.mp3" length="774" type="audio/mp3"/>
   <guid isPermaLink="false"><![CDATA[65a595b2-e943-413b-a00a-eddf48965d53]]></guid>
   <pubDate>Mon, 30 Jan 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
   <source url=""><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></source>
   <itunes:author><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></itunes:author>
   <itunes:image href="https://prod-assets-spc1.nyc3.digitaloceanspaces.com/20dde981-157e-4504-b38f-dd9d7b0e4c50/cover-art/ZdXVos6595FpTNoyp6qYqu16EQyUrG0zPvsBPzMA.png"/>
   <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
   <itunes:duration>774</itunes:duration>
   <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
  
  </item><item>
   <title><![CDATA[Having Two Legs: Morbid Introspection vs. Godly Introspection [Pastor Toby’s Blog]]]></title>
   <link>https://app.dropwave.io/episode/2d4d111b-68f0-4bc5-bd8c-d9375e98aeb4/having-two-legs-morbid-introspection-vs-godly-introspection.mp3</link>
   <description><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Morbid Introspection vs. Godly Introspection</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">One of the instructions we are given at the Lord&rsquo;s table is to examine ourselves: &ldquo;But let a man examine himself and so let him eat of that bread, and drink of that cup. For he that eateth and drinketh unworthily, eateth and drinketh damnation to himself, not discerning the Lord&rsquo;s body&rdquo; (1 Cor. 11:28-29). In the surrounding context we learn that the Corinthians were coming to the table with factions and divisions, some were eating while others were not, and some were even getting drunk, and so they were eating and drinking unworthily, and the bread and wine were not a blessing but a curse.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">So we need to heed this warning too, but we need to heed this warning without falling into other ditches. One of those ditches is what might be called morbid introspection.&nbsp;</span><span style="font-weight: 400;">We believe in godly, joyful introspection, but we reject and warn against morbid introspection.</span><span style="font-weight: 400;">What&rsquo;s the difference? The difference is faith in God versus faith in yourself. Think of your heart like a house: Morbid introspection imagines that in order to do the job right, you have to explore your &ldquo;house-heart&rdquo; pretending that Christ is not there. This is like insisting that you have to explore a house blindfolded in the middle of the night. But Godly introspection begins and ends with your eyes fixed on Christ in your heart the whole time. These two approaches will result in two very different results:&nbsp;</span><span style="font-weight: 400;">We might call morbid introspection the haunted house approach and the godly introspection approach the happy home approach.</span><span style="font-weight: 400;">&nbsp;And the difference is whether you are keeping your eyes open to the light of Christ or not.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">In godly introspection, you should regularly find things that need tidying, sins that need confessing, but the house is not in danger of being condemned because Christ has taken up residence in your house.&nbsp;</span><span style="font-weight: 400;">Christ is in your heart. He is there, and He makes all the difference.&nbsp;</span><span style="font-weight: 400;">But if he is not there, or if you insist on only pretending He is not there, coming to this table will be a regular terror. So, let a man examine himself, beginning with fixing his eyes on Christ. Is Christ there? Is Christ in You? Now with Christ in You ask Him to show you anything you need to deal with. But do it joyfully because Christ is with you. He is the Light of the World, and He is in your hearts.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p><br /><br /></p>]]></description>
   <author><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></author>
   <enclosure url="https://app.dropwave.io/episode/2d4d111b-68f0-4bc5-bd8c-d9375e98aeb4/having-two-legs-morbid-introspection-vs-godly-introspection.mp3" length="175" type="audio/mp3"/>
   <guid isPermaLink="false"><![CDATA[2d4d111b-68f0-4bc5-bd8c-d9375e98aeb4]]></guid>
   <pubDate>Sat, 28 Jan 2023 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
   <source url=""><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></source>
   <itunes:author><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></itunes:author>
   <itunes:image href="https://prod-assets-spc1.nyc3.digitaloceanspaces.com/20dde981-157e-4504-b38f-dd9d7b0e4c50/cover-art/ZdXVos6595FpTNoyp6qYqu16EQyUrG0zPvsBPzMA.png"/>
   <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
   <itunes:duration>175</itunes:duration>
   <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
  
  </item><item>
   <title><![CDATA[Having Two Legs: Morbid Introspection vs. Godly Introspection [Pastor Toby’s Blog]]]></title>
   <link>https://app.dropwave.io/episode/706e32d9-9692-4bf6-9d8f-2cd8050ced66/having-two-legs-morbid-introspection-vs-godly-introspection-1.mp3</link>
   <description><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Morbid Introspection vs. Godly Introspection</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">One of the instructions we are given at the Lord&rsquo;s table is to examine ourselves: &ldquo;But let a man examine himself and so let him eat of that bread, and drink of that cup. For he that eateth and drinketh unworthily, eateth and drinketh damnation to himself, not discerning the Lord&rsquo;s body&rdquo; (1 Cor. 11:28-29). In the surrounding context we learn that the Corinthians were coming to the table with factions and divisions, some were eating while others were not, and some were even getting drunk, and so they were eating and drinking unworthily, and the bread and wine were not a blessing but a curse.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">So we need to heed this warning too, but we need to heed this warning without falling into other ditches. One of those ditches is what might be called morbid introspection.&nbsp;</span><span style="font-weight: 400;">We believe in godly, joyful introspection, but we reject and warn against morbid introspection.</span><span style="font-weight: 400;">What&rsquo;s the difference? The difference is faith in God versus faith in yourself. Think of your heart like a house: Morbid introspection imagines that in order to do the job right, you have to explore your &ldquo;house-heart&rdquo; pretending that Christ is not there. This is like insisting that you have to explore a house blindfolded in the middle of the night. But Godly introspection begins and ends with your eyes fixed on Christ in your heart the whole time. These two approaches will result in two very different results:&nbsp;</span><span style="font-weight: 400;">We might call morbid introspection the haunted house approach and the godly introspection approach the happy home approach.</span><span style="font-weight: 400;">&nbsp;And the difference is whether you are keeping your eyes open to the light of Christ or not.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">In godly introspection, you should regularly find things that need tidying, sins that need confessing, but the house is not in danger of being condemned because Christ has taken up residence in your house.&nbsp;</span><span style="font-weight: 400;">Christ is in your heart. He is there, and He makes all the difference.&nbsp;</span><span style="font-weight: 400;">But if he is not there, or if you insist on only pretending He is not there, coming to this table will be a regular terror. So, let a man examine himself, beginning with fixing his eyes on Christ. Is Christ there? Is Christ in You? Now with Christ in You ask Him to show you anything you need to deal with. But do it joyfully because Christ is with you. He is the Light of the World, and He is in your hearts.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p><br /><br /></p>]]></description>
   <author><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></author>
   <enclosure url="https://app.dropwave.io/episode/706e32d9-9692-4bf6-9d8f-2cd8050ced66/having-two-legs-morbid-introspection-vs-godly-introspection-1.mp3" length="175" type="audio/mp3"/>
   <guid isPermaLink="false"><![CDATA[706e32d9-9692-4bf6-9d8f-2cd8050ced66]]></guid>
   <pubDate>Sat, 28 Jan 2023 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
   <source url=""><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></source>
   <itunes:author><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></itunes:author>
   <itunes:image href="https://prod-assets-spc1.nyc3.digitaloceanspaces.com/20dde981-157e-4504-b38f-dd9d7b0e4c50/cover-art/ZdXVos6595FpTNoyp6qYqu16EQyUrG0zPvsBPzMA.png"/>
   <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
   <itunes:duration>175</itunes:duration>
   <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
  
  </item><item>
   <title><![CDATA[Having Two Legs: Worship is Warfare [Pastor Toby’s Blog]]]></title>
   <link>https://app.dropwave.io/episode/a3fcf1f5-9f1c-48a4-b93b-98355cba8b26/having-two-legs-worship-is-warfare.mp3</link>
   <description><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Worship is Warfare</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Worship is warfare. The Apostle says that we are to take up the full armor of God in order to do battle with principalities and powers in heavenly places (Eph. 6). Hebrews says that we have not come to a mountain that can be touched, but to the Heavenly Mt. Zion, the city of the Living God, to the saints made perfect, to Jesus the Mediator of the New Covenant, whose blood speaks better things than that of Abel (Heb. 12). And from this Mountain, God shakes Heaven and Earth. He shakes all things so that what cannot be shaken will remain. God is the consuming fire that engulfs this Heavenly Mt. Zion, and therefore we worship with reverence and awe.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">In the Book of Revelation, John is granted a vision of the heavenly places by the Holy Spirit on the Lord&rsquo;s Day. And what he sees is worship in the heavenly places. He sees the elders falling down in worship. He sees the four living creatures crying Holy, Holy, Holy! He sees an eschatological vision of the purified churched, a myriad of peoples from every tongue and tribe worshiping the Lamb who was slain, and as this worship takes place, we see judgments falling on the earth. The horses of God&rsquo;s judgement riding forth, the cups of God&rsquo;s wrath poured out, and the New Jerusalem coming down out of Heaven, as a bride adorned for her Wedding Feast.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Therefore, the central thing we do every week is gather for worship here. We gather here in order to struggle against the principalities and powers in heavenly places.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">We gather here, lifted up by the Spirit on the Lord&rsquo;s Day to join the heavenly hosts of angels and spirits of just men made perfect, in order to ask God to shake everything that can be shaken, all the sin and idols that remain in us and all the sin and idols out in the world, so that we, like Moses may have the light of Christ shine on our faces, changing us from glory to glory, that we might be sent back out into the world to take dominion for His glory, asking God that His Kingdom might come and His will be done, on earth as it is in Heaven.</span></p>
<p><br style="font-weight: 400;" /><br style="font-weight: 400;" /></p>]]></description>
   <author><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></author>
   <enclosure url="https://app.dropwave.io/episode/a3fcf1f5-9f1c-48a4-b93b-98355cba8b26/having-two-legs-worship-is-warfare.mp3" length="151" type="audio/mp3"/>
   <guid isPermaLink="false"><![CDATA[a3fcf1f5-9f1c-48a4-b93b-98355cba8b26]]></guid>
   <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jan 2023 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
   <source url=""><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></source>
   <itunes:author><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></itunes:author>
   <itunes:image href="https://prod-assets-spc1.nyc3.digitaloceanspaces.com/20dde981-157e-4504-b38f-dd9d7b0e4c50/cover-art/ZdXVos6595FpTNoyp6qYqu16EQyUrG0zPvsBPzMA.png"/>
   <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
   <itunes:duration>151</itunes:duration>
   <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
  
  </item><item>
   <title><![CDATA[Having Two Legs: Big Tech Buying Big Con, Crowder, the Daily Wire, and the Ethics of Tapping [Pastor Toby’s Blog]]]></title>
   <link>https://app.dropwave.io/episode/4d025fc7-a0e2-4f07-b02f-dfff977493ed/having-two-legs-big-tech-buying-big-con-crowder-the-daily-wire-and-the-ethics-of-tapping.mp3</link>
   <description><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Big Tech Buying Big Con</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Crowder, the Daily Wire, and the Ethics of Tapping</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Introduction</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">So Steven Crowder has collided with Jeremy Boreing and the Daily Wire. What began as what appeared to be what one friend called Crowder&rsquo;s &ldquo;Jerry McGuire Moment&rdquo; (which I admit I had to look up to understand the reference), quickly turned a bit ugly with the revelation of an apparently secret recording of a private conversation between Crowder and DW CEO Jeremy Boreing discussing differing philosophies of doing business.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">In what follows, I would like to briefly outline the case for Crowder&rsquo;s point, and then I want to address the ethics of conversation recording.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Crowder&rsquo;s Point</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">First, Crowder&rsquo;s initial claim was that &ldquo;Big Con&rdquo; is in bed with Big Tech. Reviewing an anonymous contract offer, Crowder warned in a video that provisions for salary cuts based on censorship from Big Tech companies (such as Youtube, Facebook, Twitter, Instagram) essentially leave conservative commentators out to dry on their own. Jeremy Boreing came out shortly thereafter explaining that the contract was an initial start-the-conversation offer with Crowder and he was happy to claim it as his own. Boreing argued that something like the salary cuts for losing social media platforms is necessary simply because of the math involved in the business venture. A platform like Daily Wire has to be able to count on certain amounts of revenue from social media in order to pay its partners; if that revenue dries up, they won&rsquo;t be able to pay their partners, hence the proposed pay cuts.&nbsp;&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">I get the math, and on a purely business level, I understand why it seems like a reasonable, utilitarian proposal. There&rsquo;s nothing monstrous or insidious about that sort of deal, all by itself. However, I&rsquo;m definitely sympathetic to Crowder&rsquo;s overall point, which he claims was never about the money but simply about Big Con (Big Conservatism) standing up for free speech and pushing back against Big Tech. If we&rsquo;re going to have multi-million dollar conservative news and commentary outlets, what good are they if they are not actively pushing back against Big Tech and seeking to protect their partners from cancel culture? Maybe Jeremy Boreing thinks he&rsquo;s playing the long game, but I happen to think they are already halfway over the waterfall that will soon take them down the FOX News drain. Denise McAlister is on record claiming that she was fired from the Daily Wire for being outspoken about the sinfulness of homosexuality. Ben Shapiro reportedly told her that he didn&rsquo;t want to rock that boat because they happen to be big donors/sponsors.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">I&rsquo;ve also written previously that Jeremy Boreing&rsquo;s razor ad was a pretty significant faceplant: pushing back against woke cancel culture by weaponizing proto-woke motifs isn&rsquo;t a winning strategy. While I don&rsquo;t really care if Jeremy wants to joke around about being the Daily Wire &ldquo;god king,&rdquo; strutting around his offices with four boobs (two on either side of him) is what got us here in the first place. And by &ldquo;here,&rdquo; I mean that you cannot objectify women, turning them into objects to be used for &ldquo;conservative&rdquo; ends, and then complain when some men decide they would like to cut them off teenage girls or put some fake ones on themselves. I certainly grant that men lusting after women is more &ldquo;natural&rdquo; than men lusting to </span><em><span style="font-weight: 400;">be</span></em><span style="font-weight: 400;"> women or </span><em><span style="font-weight: 400;">deform</span></em><span style="font-weight: 400;"> women. But that&rsquo;s like saying it&rsquo;s more natural to steal steak than trash. Stealing is still a sin, and sin is the kind of poison that always destroys and warps. Sin is insanity, and there aren&rsquo;t any brakes on that car. Why was Boreing cool with his Razor Ad? Because sex sells. It makes money. Of course, Boreing thinks he&rsquo;s making conservatism sexy, and I&rsquo;m all for the alternative economy and pushing back against woke razors. But you can&rsquo;t put a little bit of eyeliner on and insist that you&rsquo;re sticking it to the Drag Queens. Even if all your fans go along with it, that&rsquo;s still utilitarianism. Doing whatever &ldquo;works&rdquo; is not taking a sledgehammer to leftism; it&rsquo;s actually getting a sledgehammer ready for leftism.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Finally, Crowder&rsquo;s point seems legitimate to me because of Jordan Peterson&rsquo;s interview with Dave Rubin concerning his boutique, test-tube &ldquo;family.&rdquo; The atrocity of that conversation, as Peterson&rsquo;s grand welcome to the Daily Wire still astonishes me. And as I noted at the time, it was right around the same time that the Daily Wire announced that they were working on children&rsquo;s programming since Disney has gone woker than an angry Karen at a BLM rally in Seattle. Given the way Peterson handled Rubin&rsquo;s homosexuality, claims of &ldquo;marriage&rdquo; to his sodomite lover, the rented uteruses, the eggs purchased from a Sears catalogue, and his freezers full of breastmilk, I believe Jeremy Boreing and the Daily Wire also still owe the whole world an apology for presenting that steaming pile as anything close to conservative.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The juxtaposition of that interview with the announcement of children&rsquo;s programming colored me nonplussed. The same Daily Wire that had just stroked its three thoughtful philosophical chin hairs contemplating the purchase of eggs, renting of wombs, and freezers full of breastmilk would like to provide children&rsquo;s programming. At this point, they have lost all credibility (Matt Walsh&rsquo;s documentary notwithstanding) on the subject of what is a woman, a family, a marriage, children, or appropriate content.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Thus far, my concerns with the Daily Wire, and why Crowder&rsquo;s warning that Big Con might be getting sodomized by Big Tech seems reasonable to me. Sorry, let me say it nicer. Big Tech might be buying Big Con&rsquo;s eggs and inseminating them in test tubes in order to grow good liberal citizens in the Daily Wire&rsquo;s rented womb, looking a little conservative (with cleavage like their mom), but definitely ideologically of their father.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">I have no idea if these sorts of compromises are even on Crowder&rsquo;s radar. But I would hope they are, and if they aren&rsquo;t, maybe he has his own list of free speech compromises.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The Ethics of Secret Recordings</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">At the same time, unless another shoe drops, and some massive scandal is revealed at the Daily Wire, it looks to me that Crowder made a major blunder in secretly recording a phone call he had with Jeremy Boreing about the Daily Wire business model and releasing snippets of it publicly. I think Crowder was free to talk about his concerns with the proposed contract and business philosophy, but recording someone without their knowledge or consent is an act of war. Recording someone without their knowledge or consent is to identify them as your enemy.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">This is because recording someone without their knowledge or consent is a form of deception. When we talk to one another, we generally assume the context of our conversations, and it is a form of deception to allow someone to assume one context (friendly, informal discussion/debate) when another is actually in mind (every word is being examined, fishing for dirt/sabotage). Of course if you want to ask for permission to record or announce that a recording is in progress for the sake of keeping a faithful record of the conversation, that is certain permissible, and can be perfectly friendly, but that openness keeps the conversation friendly because it is honest, straightforward, and not at all duplicitous. But secret recordings are duplicitous.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Of course in a world of modern technology, it is incredibly easy to record or be recorded. We often joke that with iPhones and Siri and Alexa, all of our homes are bugged, all of our conversations are being recorded. I mean, we&rsquo;ve all had the eerie experience of talking to someone about spatulas, and then five minutes later, scrolling on Facebook there&rsquo;s an ad for spatulas. I mean, it&rsquo;s not even very subtle.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Nevertheless, in the ordinary course of things, when you call someone up on the phone or go to coffee with them, even when you&rsquo;re negotiating a potential business deal, good faith, means, well, good faith. It means that while people certainly may have multiple loyalties and responsibilities to juggle, what is being discussed and debated is what is being discussed and debated.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">As a pastor, I&rsquo;ve had situations where an aggrieved spouse has secretly recorded conversations or arguments with their spouse. While I can sympathize with the instinct (e.g. I want my pastor to hear exactly what she/he sounds like in private), unless we are talking about actual criminal activity that needs to be taken to the police, it is almost always like pulling out a nuke at a fist fight. Don&rsquo;t do it. While a relationship can be severely strained by arguments, losing tempers, harsh words, people do not understand the damage that can be done by duplicity, by deceptive recording. It is one thing to simply disagree, to disagree vehemently. It is another thing to submarine all trust.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&ldquo;A brother offended</span><em><span style="font-weight: 400;"> is harder to be won</span></em><span style="font-weight: 400;"> than a strong city: and </span><em><span style="font-weight: 400;">their</span></em><span style="font-weight: 400;"> contentions</span><em><span style="font-weight: 400;"> are</span></em><span style="font-weight: 400;"> like the bars of a castle&rdquo; (Prov. 18:19).</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The only other category the Bible admits would be lies/deception that trick people into doing the right thing. We see this with Jacob and Rebecca deceiving Isaac, tricking him into obeying God and giving Jacob the blessing. Tamar, the daughter in-law of Judah, deceives her father in-law into providing for her, and there are some court intrigues under David, where Joab sends the wise old woman in to plead before David, and later, even Bathsheba&rsquo;s plea for the throne for Solomon included some sleight of hand, calculated to prod David to do what needed to be done. But that doesn&rsquo;t appear to be what is going on in the Crowder/Daily Wire collision. This appears to me to be a legitimate conflict of visions and principles that got personal. The collision would have already made the personal relationships that existed more strained as it is, but I think Crowder&rsquo;s decision to record a private conversation and release excerpts of that conversation needlessly punched below the belt.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Conclusion</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">So I have sympathy for Crowder&rsquo;s concerns, and structurally, I actually agree that Daily Wire has a business model that will long term suck them into the big money liberal vortex (if it hasn&rsquo;t already). While many of the players and contributors have personal principles of conservatism (which I&rsquo;m very grateful for!), the fundamental ideology governing the business model is a right-leaning libertarianism and utilitarianism, which is ultimately a humanistic cancer in our society. It&rsquo;s great to have the libertarians as co-belligerents against bloated, overweening government, and on many policies, we can agree, since biblical conservatism really does envision a small, limited civil government and great freedom for individuals, families, and associations. But if we do not have a structural commitment to the biblical principles of liberty (freedom from the coercion of Big Tech, crony capitalism, etc.), it will not last long.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">*And for the same reason, I would urge Crowder to admit that the secret recording was below the belt, unethical, unkind, and apologize. If he really believes in conservative values, then that would prove it.*</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Otherwise, as it stands, it appears that Crowder has employed some of the same utilitarian worldview in the name of conservatism and calls his whole complaint into question, and that would explain why Republicans and conservatives in general can&rsquo;t have nice things.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">One last thought: some of you may wonder why it wouldn&rsquo;t be ethical to consider Daily Wire an enemy since they already appear to be so compromised on homosexuality and eugenics. Well, I would grant that someone might conclude that (although I don&rsquo;t, since folks like Walsh and Knowles seem to be holding a principled biblical line, albeit as Roman Catholics), but even if someone has concluded that they are enemies, I think good faith includes the honor of actually declaring war. Don&rsquo;t say you&rsquo;re still friends despite this disagreement and then stab your &ldquo;friend&rdquo; in the back publicly. That isn&rsquo;t good faith. If you&rsquo;ve concluded that your former friends are not friends anymore but actually enemies, then say so. Tell them directly. Then feel free to record every conversation you have. In this world there will be fights, and there will be wars, but we are Christians, and so we believe in just wars and clean fights.&nbsp;</span></p>]]></description>
   <author><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></author>
   <enclosure url="https://app.dropwave.io/episode/4d025fc7-a0e2-4f07-b02f-dfff977493ed/having-two-legs-big-tech-buying-big-con-crowder-the-daily-wire-and-the-ethics-of-tapping.mp3" length="807" type="audio/mp3"/>
   <guid isPermaLink="false"><![CDATA[4d025fc7-a0e2-4f07-b02f-dfff977493ed]]></guid>
   <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jan 2023 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
   <source url=""><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></source>
   <itunes:author><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></itunes:author>
   <itunes:image href="https://prod-assets-spc1.nyc3.digitaloceanspaces.com/20dde981-157e-4504-b38f-dd9d7b0e4c50/cover-art/ZdXVos6595FpTNoyp6qYqu16EQyUrG0zPvsBPzMA.png"/>
   <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
   <itunes:duration>807</itunes:duration>
   <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
  
  </item><item>
   <title><![CDATA[Having Two Legs: How to Be Happy [Pastor Toby’s Blog]]]></title>
   <link>https://app.dropwave.io/episode/8fc4dde1-22f3-408a-809b-42b92d42b462/having-two-legs-how-to-be-happy.mp3</link>
   <description><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">How to Be Happy</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Introduction</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Some Christians just can&rsquo;t seem to be happy. Sometimes there are real medical issues at work, chemical or hormonal imbalances in play, but sometimes it&rsquo;s mysterious. When there are no obvious medical issues, we should not relegate the spiritual to some other realm. The state of your heart before God is closely related to your happiness, your joy, your peace. How could it not be? The God of the Universe made you, and your greatest comfort and joy is in Him. As the Great Augustine said, &lsquo;Our hearts are restless until we find our rest in Him.&rsquo;&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">What Makes People Sad?</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&ldquo;A glad heart makes a cheerful face, but by sorrow of heart the spirit is crushed&rdquo; (Prov. 15:13). And what makes a heart sorrow? Sin. Hard providences like the loss of dear friends or death also cause grief, but when your heart is clean before God, the Spirit comforts and refreshes and the sting slowly subsides. But I&rsquo;m talking about the gnawing, aching darkness of unexplainable depression. The Bible says that one of the first things we should consider is whether we have unconfessed sin.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Psalm 32:1 says, &ldquo;Blessed is the one whose transgression is forgiven, whose sin is covered.&rdquo; But the word translated &ldquo;blessed,&rdquo; could just as easily be translated &ldquo;happy.&rdquo; Happy is everyone whose sin is forgiven and covered. Happy is the man against whom the Lord does not reckon his iniquity (Ps. 32:2). David knows this from experience, and he remembers the time before that: &ldquo;When I kept silent, my bones wasted away through my groaning all day long.&rdquo; When David refused to confess his sins, his bones ached, and every day was a dark downer.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Now when Christians get into these depression funks, when they have a backlog of bitterness, resentment, or other unconfessed sins, and everything goes dark, they often begin to question whether they are really Christians, whether they are really saved. And that is certainly a question that should be asked on occasion (2 Cor. 13:5). But in general when people have been walking with God and then find themselves drifting into a sad, dark place, this is actually not a sign that they aren&rsquo;t saved; rather it is a sign that they </span><em><span style="font-weight: 400;">are</span></em><span style="font-weight: 400;"> saved. David knows this, and he says so in the next verse in Psalm 32: &ldquo;For day and night your hand was heavy upon me; my strength was dried up as by the heat of summer&rdquo; (Ps. 32:4). Whose hand was heavy upon David? God&rsquo;s hand was heavy upon him. It was God who was making David feel so bad, so awful. And that means that God was with David. But God loves His blood-bought people so much that He refuses to let them be happy when they are clinging to their sin.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">In Hebrews 12 it says, quoting Proverbs, &ldquo;For the Lord disciplines the one He loves, and chastises every son whom He receives&rdquo; (Heb. 12:6). When you are disciplined, God is treating you like sons (Heb. 12:7). In fact, it says that if you are not disciplined, if you are not chastised when you sin, then that&rsquo;s when you should wonder if you are really a son (Heb. 12:8). God&rsquo;s fatherly discipline is not pleasant but painful for the moment, but later it yields the peaceful fruit of righteousness to those who have been trained by it (Heb. 12:11).&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">God disciplines his children and gives them temporary pain and sadness so that they will confess their sins and come back out into the light, back into the joy and fellowship, so that they will be happy. You cannot keep your sin and be happy at the same time. And we are the kind of stubborn creatures who cling to sins for a while, preferring them and our sadness, to the freedom and happiness that God offers us in Jesus.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">But the sadness is usually a proof that we really do belong to Him, and He is treating us as sons, not letting us get away with sin, not letting us be happy in our sin. A true sign of an old, dead heart, of reprobation, is someone who feels fine, who feels good even in his sin. I do not believe that they have true happiness or true joy, and even in those situations, there is still a prick of truth buried somewhere in their conscience. But there is such a thing as a hard heart and a seared conscience, and those are people that God has given over to their sin. They lie and do not remember. They steal and do not notice. They commit adultery and wipe their mouths and say, &lsquo;I have done nothing wrong&rsquo; (Prov. 30:20, cf. Rom. 1:24).</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">When David finally confessed his sins, God forgave him (Ps. 32:5), and that forgiveness was like a high rock above the surging waves of anxiety, fear, and sorrow (Ps. 32:6). The forgiveness of God is like a hiding place, a shelter, a warm home from the cold, a fortress of safety from every threat (Ps. 32:7). And David closes the Psalm summarizing the whole point: &ldquo;Many sorrows are to the wicked, but steadfast love surrounds those who trust the Lord&rdquo; (Ps. 32:10). And the implication is clear: those who are surrounded by the steadfast love of Lord are happy.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">So, are you struggling with recurring darkness, sorrow, lethargy, apathy? There may be other factors at work, but why not start with what the Bible says? Why not start with checking to see if you have a clean heart? Are you harboring anything? Are there any closets in your heart that you dare not open? And sins shoved into some corner, that you&rsquo;re hoping will just go away? Is God&rsquo;s hand heavy upon you because He wants you to be free? Is God disciplining you as a son because He loves you and does not want you to keep holding on to that old sin?</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Two Final Thoughts</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">First, sometimes Christians try to confess or start to confess their sin but they don&rsquo;t actually complete the task. So the pastor suggests confession as a solution to their sadness, and they say, &lsquo;I already tried that and it didn&rsquo;t work.&rsquo; But often the confession was thrown up to the ceiling in desperation, but it wasn&rsquo;t a thorough and obedient repentance. It&rsquo;s not enough to merely feel bad about sin. &ldquo;For godly sorrow produces a repentance that leads to salvation without regret, but worldly sorrow produces death&rdquo; (2 Cor. 7:10). So it&rsquo;s fully possible to feel bad about sin and really feel sorry, and for everything to only get worse. It&rsquo;s not enough to just feel bad; you have to confess your sin to the Lord and anyone you have sinned against and repent.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Repentance means turning, even turning around. Let&rsquo;s say you&rsquo;ve been angry with your wife or your husband for a long time. Maybe it was one thing they did or said years ago, or maybe it was a pattern of sins over a long time. And sometimes you think about your bitterness and you feel bad about it, and maybe you even confess that one moment of bitterness. But Hebrews says that bitterness is a root that springs up and defiles many (Heb. 12:15). In other words, you might have confessed one branch of that ugly prickle plant, but have you uprooted the whole knotted, oozing, and spikey thing? And in its place, have you planted flowers?&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Repentance means confessing, asking for forgiveness, and having put off that old rotting man, putting on the new living man. Have you confessed the whole thing, have you dug down as deep as you can go, and pulled the whole thing up by the roots, hating it all, kill it all, and put grace in its place? Or have you been like Bilbo the Hobbit with the ring, saying that you will leave it behind, but still mindlessly putting it back in your pocket? If you&rsquo;ve been struggling with bitterness toward your spouse for sometime, chances are good that they&rsquo;ve felt it, even if it&rsquo;s been under the surface. You need to confess it to them, and then you need to thank them for being your wife/your husband, tell them you love them, and tell them that you will be endeavoring to love, honor, and cherish them from now on, just like you promised in your wedding vows. The old habit may still pop up occasionally after that, but if you&rsquo;ve pulled out the beast by the roots, you can pull out the occasional little weed, and you&rsquo;ll be right back in the joy. But if all you ever do is pluck off the end of one gnarly branch, the whole spikey weed is still sitting there in your heart; so of course you&rsquo;re still not happy. You didn&rsquo;t do the whole job.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Lastly, a word about introspection. There&rsquo;s a particular temptation for some to spend an inordinate amount of time examining the soil of their hearts in search of weeds, and they struggle with bouts of anxiety and depression because they worry that they haven&rsquo;t really dealt with all of their sin, or maybe they haven&rsquo;t dealt with it fully or completely. First, I recommend the 30 second rule which is sort of like when you drop food and pick it up quickly. Except, it&rsquo;s not really like that at all. The only thing it has in common with that rule is the 30 seconds part. But what I mean is that if you&rsquo;re one of those introspective types, and you&rsquo;ve confessed some sin around 15 times but it&rsquo;s still gnawing at you and there&rsquo;s a little black rain cloud pouring on your heart, you should ask the Lord to name what the sin is that you have not yet confessed. And give it 30 seconds and no more. The Holy Spirit really does convict believers of sin, but the Holy Spirit is the Comforter. The Holy Spirit convicts believers of sin so that they can confess quicly, repent, and get back into the joy. The Holy Spirit gives us the peace of Christ. In other words, if you&rsquo;re sitting under that little black rain cloud for hours or days, that isn&rsquo;t the Holy Spirit. That&rsquo;s the Devil. That&rsquo;s Satan, the Accuser. God does not put His children on a spit to roast them over the fire of the Spirit. That&rsquo;s just not His way.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">But, one of you will say, but isn&rsquo;t His hand heavy upon His people sometimes because they won&rsquo;t confess their sins? Yes, but He does that for sins </span><em><span style="font-weight: 400;">they know about</span></em><span style="font-weight: 400;">. God&rsquo;s hand is heavy upon those who are intentionally keeping silent, who refuse to confess sins they know they should confess. He doesn&rsquo;t do that for vague feelings of guilt. The Spirit convicts us of concrete sins so that we can confess them immediately, get forgiven, and have peace and joy again quickly.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Frequently, introspection is a form of sadistic hubris and pride. Frequently, the introspectionist is obsessed with himself/herself, and you can tell because most of their sentences begin with: I, me, myself, I, I, I, my, my, me. But you aren&rsquo;t that important, and your self obsession with your feelings is often stealing from those whom God has called you to love and serve. There is also often a form of pride in refusing to believe and receive the forgiveness of God. Did you confess your sin? Then God has removed it as far as the East is from the West. Stop asking for forgiveness. He has buried at the bottom of the sea. He doesn&rsquo;t remember it anymore. Stop bringing it up. But when you climb on to the spit of your memory and insist on roasting for an afternoon or an evening or another week or month, you are arrogantly insisting to God that you know better than Him, that the blood of Jesus is not enough for you. Your sin is so bad and so important, that it requires some additional suffering that you are now providing for yourself. But that is of course ludicrous. You are not God; you are not Jesus. And you are terrible god, a terrible savior. And who do you think you are, telling God, &ldquo;no.&rdquo; He said that you are forgiven and clean. He told you to walk free with your head held high. He told you to shut up and smile because His grace is sufficient for you, because the blood of Jesus is enough. It is finished.&nbsp;&nbsp;</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Conclusion</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">So do it. Smile. Preach the gospel to your heart, to your soul. Believe in the cross and resurrection. Confess your sins (the real ones), and maybe confess your introspection or prideful self-obsession, receive the forgiveness of God, and then walk in obedience. Don&rsquo;t look down, don&rsquo;t look back. Look to Christ, look ahead, look up, and remember that Christ is all. Christ is God. We are not that important; we are not the saviors of the world. And therefore, we are free to just be ordinary people, ordinary people who confess their sins regularly and therefore have clean hearts. And that is how to be happy.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p><br /><br /><br /><br /><br /><br /><br /></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">&nbsp;</span></p>
<p><br /><br /></p>]]></description>
   <author><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></author>
   <enclosure url="https://app.dropwave.io/episode/8fc4dde1-22f3-408a-809b-42b92d42b462/having-two-legs-how-to-be-happy.mp3" length="836" type="audio/mp3"/>
   <guid isPermaLink="false"><![CDATA[8fc4dde1-22f3-408a-809b-42b92d42b462]]></guid>
   <pubDate>Mon, 16 Jan 2023 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
   <source url=""><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></source>
   <itunes:author><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></itunes:author>
   <itunes:image href="https://prod-assets-spc1.nyc3.digitaloceanspaces.com/20dde981-157e-4504-b38f-dd9d7b0e4c50/cover-art/wdSKzfd199QO6HwdUaYRK0tI4C6ca1WRD4vQ6dAU.png"/>
   <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
   <itunes:duration>836</itunes:duration>
   <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
  
  </item>
 </channel>
</rss>
