<?xml version="1.0"?>
<?xml-stylesheet href="/storage/feed-stylesheet.xsl" type="text/xsl"?>

<rss xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
 <channel>
  <title>FLF - The Comedian Next Door</title>
  <link>https://dropwave.io</link>
  <description><![CDATA[FIGHT LAUGH FEAST PRESENTS SHOWS PROCLAIMING THE LORDSHIP OF CHRIST OVER ALL OF LIFE.
]]></description>
  <language>en</language>
  <managingEditor><![CDATA[fightlaughfeast@gmail.com (FLF, LLC)]]></managingEditor>
  <webMaster><![CDATA[support@dropwave.io (DropWave Support)]]></webMaster>
  <pubDate>Tue, 25 Apr 2023 19:25:42 +0000</pubDate>
  <lastBuildDate>Tue, 25 Apr 2023 19:25:42 +0000</lastBuildDate>
  <image>
   <url>https://is4-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Podcasts113/v4/58/56/52/5856525c-2973-cf29-3db9-21faa8595391/mza_1144696925612154085.png/1200x1200bb.jpg</url>
   <link>https://dropwave.io</link>
   <title><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></title>
  </image>
  <itunes:author><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></itunes:author>
  <itunes:image href="https://is4-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Podcasts113/v4/58/56/52/5856525c-2973-cf29-3db9-21faa8595391/mza_1144696925612154085.png/1200x1200bb.jpg"/>
  <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
  <itunes:owner>
   <itunes:name><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></itunes:name>
   <itunes:email>fightlaughfeast@gmail.com</itunes:email>
  </itunes:owner>
  <itunes:category text="News"/>
  <item>
   <title><![CDATA[TCND: Part 1 Road Trip with The Comedian (Agreeable/Disagreeable Women) [The Comedian Next Door]]]></title>
   <link>https://app.dropwave.io/episode/85a5ed56-f3a9-40bc-b320-5c9f85d173d3/tcnd-road-trip-with-the-comedian-agreeabledisagreeable-women.mp3</link>
   <description><![CDATA[<p>The Comedian and the Peaches are in the car, taking a trip to southern Indiana.&nbsp; Come along for the ride!&nbsp; (Our GPS made the recorder glitch between the 13:00 and 14:00 minute mark... But it cleared up after that.) <br /><br />We'll kick it off with a riveting conversation about the benefits of being short--and the disorienting effect of new eye-glasses...&nbsp;&nbsp;<br /><br />Then, let's talk about the evolving role of a mother as her children grow in maturity. She has to be able to shift from "agreeableness" to a more "disagreeable" framework.&nbsp; What are the strengths and weaknesses of Agreeable/Disagreeable People?&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
<p>Typically women are more "agreeable," because they are equipped to deal with infants--who are very needy and dependent and can't be held to a higher standard until they've grown.&nbsp; &nbsp;It's easier to be the least mature person in a very mature system than to be the most mature person in a very immature system.&nbsp; &nbsp;Everyone wants to be the Baby of a very stable family--and no one wants to be the Manager of a whole bunch of babies!</p>
<p>Later:&nbsp; We have more to say about Sheila Wray Gregoire, who released a book this week called "She Deserves Better."&nbsp; &nbsp; Why are so many Evangelical MEN afraid to call out these Feminists?&nbsp; &nbsp;Well, short version: they are hesitant for the same reason many women/moms don't want to discipline their own kids.&nbsp; (It feels Too Authoritative.)</p>
<p>Books like "She Deserves Better" is creating perpetually immature women...girls who use their tears to get what they want. And, ironically, her whole strategy depends on men playing the role of Mommies who take care of these Baby Girls.&nbsp;<br /><br />Women have a big challenge in raising their children:&nbsp; constantly growing WITH them.&nbsp; "How do we know when it's time to comfort them and when it's time to challenge them?!"&nbsp; &nbsp;That's a very good question.&nbsp; And, just when we start to get a routine that seems to work for everyone, it's time for a growth spurt.&nbsp; When you try to sell a cookie-cutter message to EVERY girl/woman in the church, you are trying to sell a silver bullet formula that won't work for most girls/women.&nbsp;<br /><br />Finally:&nbsp; Being empowered means having responsibility. If you have power, you are capable of abusing it.&nbsp; But no one is warning these women about how to use their power, once it's given to them...&nbsp; &nbsp;Which is a recipe for disaster.<br /><br />-PITSTOP-<br /><br />You can reach out to the Comedian, John Branyan, by emailing <a href="mailto:nextdoor@johnbranyan.com">nextdoor@johnbranyan.com .</a></p>]]></description>
   <author><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></author>
   <enclosure url="https://app.dropwave.io/episode/85a5ed56-f3a9-40bc-b320-5c9f85d173d3/tcnd-road-trip-with-the-comedian-agreeabledisagreeable-women.mp3" length="2821" type="audio/mp3"/>
   <guid isPermaLink="false"><![CDATA[85a5ed56-f3a9-40bc-b320-5c9f85d173d3]]></guid>
   <pubDate>Mon, 24 Apr 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
   <source url=""><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></source>
   <itunes:author><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></itunes:author>
   <itunes:image href="https://assets-cdn2.dropwave.io/66903a54-b4b6-4a52-a303-eb0bd0b792e3/cover-art/obxsSs7zSTuWr3ZFLRWxryhYbCyvdrWYzXEN2soF.png"/>
   <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
   <itunes:duration>2821</itunes:duration>
   <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
  
  </item><item>
   <title><![CDATA[TCND: She Deserves Better (Nefarious Boobs and Swords) [The Comedian Next Door]]]></title>
   <link>https://app.dropwave.io/episode/d2f86f7b-7d22-4a0c-bd0a-69d2d3331f3b/tcnd-horror-she-deserves-better-nefarious-boobs-and-swords.mp3</link>
   <description><![CDATA[<p>Welcome, Neighbor!&nbsp; John went to see "Nefarious" at the theater, and it was quite the experience... These previews are NOT approved for all audiences.&nbsp; He shares his favorite quote from the movie, and admits he generally enjoyed watching Satan beat the Atheist.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The following is a much longer-than-intended discussion about the use of language, violence, and gratuitous sex in Rated R movies. (See: "Boobs and Swords") Also, on the complete opposite end of the spectrum, we reminisce about an old made-for-TV special that's near and dear to our hearts...&nbsp;</p>
<p>Later: let's talk about a book that's being promoted to Christian women, but let's pretend to censor the author's name.&nbsp; "Shasta McGwire" is about to release a book called "She Deserves Better." The premise is the church uses a double standard when teaching boys and girls about sex/modesty.&nbsp; (We've never heard that before, right?)&nbsp; It's not faaaaaaaaaair, Neighbor!</p>
<p>John doesn't want to call out the author by name, because he doesn't want to deal with their shrieking and finger-wagging.&nbsp; &nbsp;In other words, he doesn't love them enough to tolerate their tantrums in order to tell them something they need to hear. (That's probably what led to thousands of spoiled, insufferable women in the first place...their parents felt the same way when they were young.)&nbsp;</p>
<p>The obvious question, though, is: "She deserves better THAN WHAT?"</p>
<p>The Bible says we discipline children when we LOVE them. Only a fool despises wisdom and learning. So what's with all these "adult" Christian women, complaining that they're getting more discipline than their brothers? Even if it's true (and it's not), why are women demanding to be treated with Kid Gloves?<br /><br />There's nothing BETTER than holding someone to a very, very, very, very high standard. If you don't, they turn into whiney, self-sorrying Feminists.&nbsp; (Or self-pitying. Whichever you prefer.)<br /><br />Contact The Comedian Next Door by emailing <a href="mailto:nextdoor@johnbranyan.com">nextdoor@johnbranyan.com</a>.&nbsp; Also, time is running out to join us on vacation! Vacay with Comics is happening July 28th-30th. Details are here: <a href="http://johnbranyan.com/vacay-with-comics-2/">http://johnbranyan.com/vacay-with-comics-2/</a>&nbsp;</p>]]></description>
   <author><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></author>
   <enclosure url="https://app.dropwave.io/episode/d2f86f7b-7d22-4a0c-bd0a-69d2d3331f3b/tcnd-horror-she-deserves-better-nefarious-boobs-and-swords.mp3" length="2886" type="audio/mp3"/>
   <guid isPermaLink="false"><![CDATA[d2f86f7b-7d22-4a0c-bd0a-69d2d3331f3b]]></guid>
   <pubDate>Mon, 17 Apr 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
   <source url=""><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></source>
   <itunes:author><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></itunes:author>
   <itunes:image href="https://assets-cdn2.dropwave.io/66903a54-b4b6-4a52-a303-eb0bd0b792e3/cover-art/obxsSs7zSTuWr3ZFLRWxryhYbCyvdrWYzXEN2soF.png"/>
   <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
   <itunes:duration>2886</itunes:duration>
   <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
  
  </item>
 </channel>
</rss>
