<?xml version="1.0"?>
<?xml-stylesheet href="/storage/feed-stylesheet.xsl" type="text/xsl"?>

<rss xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
 <channel>
  <title>FLF - The Comedian Next Door</title>
  <link>https://dropwave.io</link>
  <description><![CDATA[FIGHT LAUGH FEAST PRESENTS SHOWS PROCLAIMING THE LORDSHIP OF CHRIST OVER ALL OF LIFE.
]]></description>
  <language>en</language>
  <managingEditor><![CDATA[fightlaughfeast@gmail.com (FLF, LLC)]]></managingEditor>
  <webMaster><![CDATA[support@dropwave.io (DropWave Support)]]></webMaster>
  <pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 13:26:12 +0000</pubDate>
  <lastBuildDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 13:26:12 +0000</lastBuildDate>
  <image>
   <url>https://is4-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Podcasts113/v4/58/56/52/5856525c-2973-cf29-3db9-21faa8595391/mza_1144696925612154085.png/1200x1200bb.jpg</url>
   <link>https://dropwave.io</link>
   <title><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></title>
  </image>
  <itunes:author><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></itunes:author>
  <itunes:image href="https://is4-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Podcasts113/v4/58/56/52/5856525c-2973-cf29-3db9-21faa8595391/mza_1144696925612154085.png/1200x1200bb.jpg"/>
  <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
  <itunes:owner>
   <itunes:name><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></itunes:name>
   <itunes:email>fightlaughfeast@gmail.com</itunes:email>
  </itunes:owner>
  <itunes:category text="News"/>
  <item>
   <title><![CDATA[TCND: Did Plants/Animals Die Before the Imago Dei Sinned? (Dopplar Effect) [The Comedian Next Door]]]></title>
   <link/>
   <description><![CDATA[<p>Here we are again, Neighbor... We're still causing a bit of a stir with our belief that it's difficult to talk about timelines when dealing with the creative behavior of a Timeless God.&nbsp;<br /><br />Is it unChristian to study theoretical physics and explore the impact of Einstein's Theory of Relativity on the biblical narrative?&nbsp; Should we have the exact same understanding of Scripture the Ancient's had--as if we don't own telescopes now?</p>
<p>If so--we are guilty as charged.<br /><br />But if you like to image what mass and gravity and velocity could have been doing at the moment God said "let there be light," you might actually LIKE this conversation...<br /><br />Ignore the part at the end where The Peaches says cooky things about Jesus reversing the curse and conquering death. Obviously, that has nothing to do with the Bible's teaching about death/sin, and women shouldn't be trying to understand this stuff.&nbsp; Email us if you'd like to set the whole family straight:&nbsp; <a href="mailto:Nextdoor@johnbranyan.com">Nextdoor@johnbranyan.com</a>&nbsp;<br /><br />Disclaimer:&nbsp; we believe the Bible is completely inerrant, and we affirm a literal, biblical interpretation of the Genesis story.&nbsp; :)&nbsp; &nbsp;Also--this is not a salvation issue.&nbsp;</p>]]></description>
   <author><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></author>
   <enclosure url="https://app.dropwave.io/episode/47d1fd51-6fcf-4898-ae50-d49d7d066868/tcnd-did-plantsanimals-die-before-the-imago-dei-sinned-dopplar-effect.mp3" length="2828" type="audio/mp3"/>
   <guid isPermaLink="false"><![CDATA[47d1fd51-6fcf-4898-ae50-d49d7d066868]]></guid>
   <pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
   <source url=""><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></source>
   <itunes:author><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></itunes:author>
   <itunes:image href="https://assets-cdn2.dropwave.io/66903a54-b4b6-4a52-a303-eb0bd0b792e3/cover-art/obxsSs7zSTuWr3ZFLRWxryhYbCyvdrWYzXEN2soF.png"/>
   <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
   <itunes:duration>2828</itunes:duration>
   <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
  
  </item><item>
   <title><![CDATA[TCND: More Creation Talk (Do the Dishes, Men!) [The Comedian Next Door]]]></title>
   <link/>
   <description><![CDATA[<p>Hi, Neighbor! We want to apologize for the quality of our last episode.&nbsp; It was actually a GREAT conversation, if you were able to decipher it.&nbsp;<br /><br />Today, let's talk a little more about creation!&nbsp; &nbsp;In essentials, unity. In opinions, liberty. And in everything, love.&nbsp;<br /><br />That's all well and good, isn't it?&nbsp; But WHAT ARE THE ESSENTIALS?&nbsp;<br /><br />Most Christians don't care (on the surface) how old the earth is... but we DO care about making sure our kids understand "the essentials."&nbsp; So, if we're being told we MUST read Genesis a particular way in order to raise Christian kids, that will pique our interest.&nbsp; &nbsp;Most mothers are willing to write "24-hours" into their Bibles, if that's what it takes.&nbsp;</p>
<p>People are concerned with what affects their DAILY LIFE.&nbsp; In general, they're not impacted by whether God used millions of years to prepare the earth for humans, except that they're being told their kids will leave the faith if they DON'T teach Young Earth Creationism.&nbsp;<br /><br />Later:&nbsp; A Good Man Will Do the Dishes!!!&nbsp; (Listen as we explain why Michael Foster is way more interesting than Ken Ham.)&nbsp;</p>
<p>There may be some Christians in reformed circles who are tired of talking about marriage, parenting, and other "basics." But we can't get tired of doing good! There are still many, many, many, many self-identified Christians who haven't learned how to LIVE like Christians, yet. Most of the moms in our home church are still sending their kids to public schools.&nbsp; &nbsp;Many are not even getting married and staying married. Many are still blaming their husbands (who fail to do the dishes) for their unhappiness.&nbsp;</p>
<p>When it comes to theology and growing in their walk with Christ--affirming that creation was accomplished in 24-hour days is not even a blip on the radar.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Contact the Comedian's family at <a href="mailto:nextdoor@johnbranyan.com">nextdoor@johnbranyan.com.&nbsp;</a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>]]></description>
   <author><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></author>
   <enclosure url="https://app.dropwave.io/episode/6085c568-6a7c-4517-8aca-4030ea1575e6/tcnd-more-creation-talk-do-the-dishes-men.mp3" length="2897" type="audio/mp3"/>
   <guid isPermaLink="false"><![CDATA[6085c568-6a7c-4517-8aca-4030ea1575e6]]></guid>
   <pubDate>Mon, 23 Oct 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
   <source url=""><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></source>
   <itunes:author><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></itunes:author>
   <itunes:image href="https://assets-cdn2.dropwave.io/66903a54-b4b6-4a52-a303-eb0bd0b792e3/cover-art/obxsSs7zSTuWr3ZFLRWxryhYbCyvdrWYzXEN2soF.png"/>
   <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
   <itunes:duration>2897</itunes:duration>
   <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
  
  </item>
 </channel>
</rss>
