<?xml version="1.0"?>
<?xml-stylesheet href="/storage/feed-stylesheet.xsl" type="text/xsl"?>

<rss xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
 <channel>
  <title>FLF - The Comedian Next Door</title>
  <link>https://dropwave.io</link>
  <description><![CDATA[FIGHT LAUGH FEAST PRESENTS SHOWS PROCLAIMING THE LORDSHIP OF CHRIST OVER ALL OF LIFE.
]]></description>
  <language>en</language>
  <managingEditor><![CDATA[fightlaughfeast@gmail.com (FLF, LLC)]]></managingEditor>
  <webMaster><![CDATA[support@dropwave.io (DropWave Support)]]></webMaster>
  <pubDate>Tue, 04 Apr 2023 07:25:45 +0000</pubDate>
  <lastBuildDate>Tue, 04 Apr 2023 07:25:45 +0000</lastBuildDate>
  <image>
   <url>https://is4-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Podcasts113/v4/58/56/52/5856525c-2973-cf29-3db9-21faa8595391/mza_1144696925612154085.png/1200x1200bb.jpg</url>
   <link>https://dropwave.io</link>
   <title><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></title>
  </image>
  <itunes:author><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></itunes:author>
  <itunes:image href="https://is4-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Podcasts113/v4/58/56/52/5856525c-2973-cf29-3db9-21faa8595391/mza_1144696925612154085.png/1200x1200bb.jpg"/>
  <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
  <itunes:owner>
   <itunes:name><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></itunes:name>
   <itunes:email>fightlaughfeast@gmail.com</itunes:email>
  </itunes:owner>
  <itunes:category text="News"/>
  <item>
   <title><![CDATA[TCND:  Meandering Kitchen Table Talk (Silly Injuries and Word People) [The Comedian Next Door]]]></title>
   <link>https://app.dropwave.io/episode/3a0628a4-653e-47e6-8b97-1eed5b5d0522/tcnd-meandering-kitchen-table-talk-silly-injuries-and-word-people.mp3</link>
   <description><![CDATA[<p>After fairly heavy conversations the last few weeks, we're just shooting the breeze at The Comedian's House...</p>
<p>Did you know the bathrooms are the most dangerous rooms in the house?</p>
<p>Comedians often hurt themselves in strange ways...&nbsp; (And we have several friends with strangely appropriate last names.)</p>
<p>Later: Listen to John's Noah Webster joke!&nbsp;</p>
<p>Then:&nbsp; Weigh in on a family scandal...Luke thinks our comedy work/business is the same as Poker Night! It's a fun hobby--not really work!!!!</p>
<p>What's the tangible outpur of a comedian's labor??? Are we just eating junk food and gambling over here???</p>
<p>Maybe comedian isn't a legitimate career choice.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Write to the Comedian Next Door by emailing <a href="mailto:nextdoor@johnbranyan.com">nextdoor@johnbranyan.com</a>.&nbsp; Watch the Starving Comics Show on the John Branyan YouTube channel. (It's a lot like a poker game.)&nbsp; &nbsp;Also, come on vacation with us in July! Visit johnbranyan.com for details about Vacay With Comics.&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>]]></description>
   <author><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></author>
   <enclosure url="https://app.dropwave.io/episode/3a0628a4-653e-47e6-8b97-1eed5b5d0522/tcnd-meandering-kitchen-table-talk-silly-injuries-and-word-people.mp3" length="2866" type="audio/mp3"/>
   <guid isPermaLink="false"><![CDATA[3a0628a4-653e-47e6-8b97-1eed5b5d0522]]></guid>
   <pubDate>Mon, 03 Apr 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
   <source url=""><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></source>
   <itunes:author><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></itunes:author>
   <itunes:image href="https://assets-cdn2.dropwave.io/66903a54-b4b6-4a52-a303-eb0bd0b792e3/cover-art/obxsSs7zSTuWr3ZFLRWxryhYbCyvdrWYzXEN2soF.png"/>
   <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
   <itunes:duration>2866</itunes:duration>
   <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
  
  </item><item>
   <title><![CDATA[TCND: If You Want to Be the Joke...  (DeMar Drama and Recycled Hair) [The Comedian Next Door]]]></title>
   <link>https://app.dropwave.io/episode/05b2ed73-02c8-4633-8a09-72e1cab08e21/tcnd-if-you-want-to-be-the-joke-demar-drama-and-recycled-hair.mp3</link>
   <description><![CDATA[<p>Welcome to the table, Neighbor Pkarghl!&nbsp; How do you feel about John twirking as part of his show?&nbsp;</p>
<p>No, don't answer that.</p>
<p>What's your earliest childhood memory?&nbsp; Here's one of Uncle David's!&nbsp; Please take our poll by emailing <a href="mailto:nextdoor@johnbranyan.com">nextdoor@johnbranyan.com</a>, but address the note TO JOHN, because The Peaches doesn't support this scientific endeavor.&nbsp; &nbsp;</p>
<p>If you want to email the Peaches, let the subject be regarding the weirdest thing you've ever heard of someone recycling.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Next: John shares the lesson he taught the youth group at Lighthouse.&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
<p>Later: We get down to business explaining why the more you try to take yourself seriously, the more of a punchline you become.&nbsp; It's Natural Law!</p>
<p>There are some folks in the Fight Laugh Feast group going on and on and on and on and on and on about Full Preterism (for weeks!!!).&nbsp; No matter how many times they are assured everyone agrees about the seriousness of heresy--they have made it their personal mission to be as loud and annoying as possible--all for the glory of Jesus.</p>
<p>This isn't a conversation about resurrection or baptism or meat sacrificed to idols.&nbsp; THIS is a conversation about the fact that prideful, self-important people ARE HILARIOUS, and we literally can't help laughing at their relentless babbling.&nbsp;<br /><br />Also:&nbsp; if you find yourself being proud of the fact that you have no friends--you might have taken a wrong turn somewhere.</p>
<p>Feel free to reach out to us and let us know if you still use the fly part of your undewear OR to warn us we're going to Hell. (Note:&nbsp; TO JOHN.)&nbsp; Time is running out to sign up for Vacay With Comics.&nbsp; Come laugh with us and our friends for a whole weekend in July! Details at johnbranyan.com&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>]]></description>
   <author><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></author>
   <enclosure url="https://app.dropwave.io/episode/05b2ed73-02c8-4633-8a09-72e1cab08e21/tcnd-if-you-want-to-be-the-joke-demar-drama-and-recycled-hair.mp3" length="2965" type="audio/mp3"/>
   <guid isPermaLink="false"><![CDATA[05b2ed73-02c8-4633-8a09-72e1cab08e21]]></guid>
   <pubDate>Mon, 27 Mar 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
   <source url=""><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></source>
   <itunes:author><![CDATA[FLF, LLC]]></itunes:author>
   <itunes:image href="https://assets-cdn2.dropwave.io/66903a54-b4b6-4a52-a303-eb0bd0b792e3/cover-art/obxsSs7zSTuWr3ZFLRWxryhYbCyvdrWYzXEN2soF.png"/>
   <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
   <itunes:duration>2965</itunes:duration>
   <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
  
  </item>
 </channel>
</rss>
